Oh, hello there. I am so glad you are here. This is the part of the show where we thank you, the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. It's a new month. I don't have a new list yet. But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver at this part of the show before this month is over. If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I sure hope you do, preaching fun.com is where you can go to hang out, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver right there. I'll see you in the next video. Bye for now.
There and who knows the life you save may be your own.
And now a show. Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to. Great. Let's go.
Jacob, I want you to know that the jokers of magic are making fun of this microphone on my face for the whole part.
Because you look like Britney Spears? Yeah.
I didn't. It's not the microphone that you just looked like Britney Spears.
I screamed social sitting over there in Las Vegas. It's Matt Donnelly sitting over in Pittsburgh, PA. It's Paul Mattingly. Also in Vegas. It's me. Jacob, the audio guy.
I love the microphone on your face, Matt. I think it's dapper backstreets back. All right. Yeah, it is. It's kind of cool.
I mean, it improved the audio quality of our show dramatically when I was traveling. So yeah, there you go. I'll take I'll take the jokes. Can't fight that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, I want to be very clear. I'm very willing to in exchange for improving the quality of this show. I am willing for you to be made fun of by your peers.
I said fine with that trade off. I packed it with my regular microphone road road rig microphones, you know, handheld microphones for right Africa Babel.
And I said, I packed this because that way I thought if I could drive and do that, we could do the podcast while actually driving and Mike Mills, our producer slash host said, what a terrible idea.
And why didn't Mike think this was a good idea, Matt?
Well, once we ended up driving through not one, but two blizzards.
Well, that would have been distracting. So trying to podcast would have been really, really difficult.
Honestly, I'm sad that we don't have just recordings of you guys trying to podcast through a blizzard.
No, we we hit a second blizzard and we were all upset because the first blizzard was very much talked about in the news is coming towards us. And then we hit a second blizzard in India.
And I was like, what? No, we had no idea. We had no idea we were going to hit a blizzard blizzard.
And then we we hit this gas station at like at like midnight, trying to fuel up and get some food. And we're just surrounded by snow coming down. It was, I guess, the tip of the lake. They kept saying so that the flakes are really big, chunky flakes, tip of the lake.
I was like, not not to borrow from my clown name, but chunky flakes, a lot of chunky flakes coming down. And then the clown, the guy in the gas, he was like, oh my God, no, we're getting at least 10 inches. And I just heard from Valparaiso.
They're getting, you know, 15 inches and the other reports. I mean, everywhere I go, it's like he was like, don't go anywhere.
And one, oh, we were at a gas station in the middle of some town that have hotels. So we were terrible advice for a gas station attendant to give anyone.
We were going somewhere. Yes. And then we were like kind of starting to panic about like, what do we do? And looking at the nearest hotels. And then I remembered, hey guys, the all the information we just got was from a cashier at midnight in a gas station.
So like all of the reports are coming from, you know, one point, even the cashier he was working with, she was like, can you chill out? And he's like, I'm just telling them. The other cashier called them down. Great.
And then she was like, that guy's a soft guy over there. You can ask him. And I was like, well, this is the kind of town we're in where we're actually at the coffee shop.
You know, the coffee stop where the guy who's salt in the roads is there. Yeah. And I said, oh, you know, the salt guy, she goes, he's my dad. And I was like, we are in a tiny, tiny town.
Oh boy.
But you made it out. We made it out. We lost an hour driving from Milwaukee to Wabash, Indiana. And then we got in, ended up getting in with the snow at like five o'clock in the morning with a nine a.m. lobby call.
So it was pretty great. It's pretty great. So we had two shows, Wabash, and then they put the man at two o'clock instead of four. But we did two shows in Wabash. We were a little delirious, but they were super fun. Great crowds came out and including the else Ross.
Hooray. Yeah. And Michael else Roth, always being a gentleman, brought me a Dr. Pepper cream zero for me to drive delicious. He knows is my favorite. He always brings him to scoop fest. He's he's he knows he knows his stuff.
But I got to sneak out and have a little bitey with with the else. Well, the hard part is always finding a hooker that's named Dr. Pepper cream zero.
I think he just tells how Matt happens to be in. I think he just pays extra for whoever to just say it. I don't think he can do the legal name change. I think so. I think so. Does anyone who's into commitment? It's Michael else from that is true.
That is true. So are you still in snowed in areas now or you're back? No, I'm back. I'm back in Vegas. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But you've been driving through crazy snow pack everywhere.
Well, yeah. And the good, the good news for me, I seem like I was making the big sacrifice. Everyone else was flying out of Fort Wayne. I drove the Sprinter van back to Cincinnati to drop off where we rented it from and flew out of Cincinnati.
And everyone's flights were messed up and delayed out of Fort Wayne and everything. Everything in Cincinnati is going off without a hitch. So I was like, yeah, would you drive three hours just to make sure your flights were totally normal? You would say yes.
Fine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Because I'm driving. Who decides to introduce letters to exit numbers?
You know, this has been at the top of my list to talk about for years. I'm glad we're finally getting to it as a secondary component of the exit. Right. So you go by 42 B, right? So you go by exit 41, then 40 to a 42 B 42.
See, don't you dare come driving out here and fucking Pittsburgh. You will lose it. It is everything is just blabbering. Blabbering. Blabbering. Oh, Pittsburgh is no, I mean, like it has to get so confused.
Riding with the Uber drivers in Pittsburgh is the worst. I just had, I had to stop paying attention, but it has to be a meeting. Right. And that means someone that maybe goes, whoa, whoa, whoa. Those exits are too close together to have their own numbers.
Well, I guess that's it. I guess that's it. The numbers are mile markers. Yeah, essentially. I mean, on the right on the interstates growing up, you'd have the mile markers and then you would have an exit and the exit would serve as a mile.
They're supposed to correspond pretty closely. Yes. Right. All right. So I guess the letters are just between the mile markers. But yeah, it seems like they've they've raged out of control.
Jacob, Jacob just said something that makes a lot of sense and I feel dumb for bringing it up.
But no, I think that's how it's supposed to be. I don't think that's how it is out here.
Well, it's definitely because they're just too close because we have exits. Like we have like on the freeway here, we have, you know, the Flamingo eggs and the Tropicana eggs that are not a mile apart from each other.
Right. The designs of all of it are just so it's just so bad. I drove I had to drive in for class last night and just two or three times.
It's like, God damn it. Well, Pittsburgh, the driving in Pittsburgh just isn't designed at all. No, it's not. And it's it's it's terrible road stacked on each other over the years.
And I just, you know, we keep discovering everything in our society is built as a massive Psy op to confuse and upset us and control our brains.
And I feel like the driving shit is a big component of that, too. Like they make these things. Now we're talking.
Jacob's making sense. Paul saying it's because of a Psy op. We're back in business. I'm telling you, it's all just like, I mean, of course, the interstates were built for.
Interstate trucking primarily, but now we all we have to use them to just get to our third and fourth jobs.
I don't know. It just seems fucking insane to me how much we have with the interstates initially built primarily for trucking.
Yes. Yes. Oh, I didn't know that. Yeah. Eisenhower was the president who did a lot of interstate stuff, right? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I like when you could point at a president and just casually list the thing that they did.
Here's just something that happened under this administration that was just, I don't know, I guess, a net positive.
I guess. I don't know. Sure. At the very least, it's something that got accomplished.
But also the crazy fucking thing with my commute. Now, I've gotten to where I'm really leaving very early because I know how insane the commute can be.
But it's approximately, I think, as the crow flies, as you'd say, about 12 miles from my house to where I'm going. Good shape.
And I couldn't fly 12 miles if you paid. And it takes me no less than 45 minutes.
Yeah. Ever. Really? That's the that's the quickest ever. That's just the amount of time that that trip takes.
Because you got and I'm so I got so spoiled in Vegas, too, because it's all on a grid out here.
It's do do do do do do. This used to be a horsey trail. This guy owns a part of this. This is where you cannot be.
This is a demilitarized zone. Do do do do. It's just fucking bananas. The loopy doop floop driving shit on the horse.
One hundred fifty years ago. Does that how you were going to get to work today?
Yeah. Oh, well, there's the easiest way for the nag to get through without breaking its leg.
That's my wife. I keep asking you not to call her that. That'll work. That'll work for a Porsche in about 100 years.
That's perfect. No problem. Yeah. Perfect for a German engineered piece of machinery.
Horse rhymes with horse. I'm sure it'll be fine. But anyway, yeah, so I've been busy with improv this week.
I had a free class on Saturday that I co-taught with my friend Sarah. We had a couple of ladies come out.
We're going to be working with them on a project, too, which is cool. They got to see it.
Big shout out to Malia for coming out to the class, too. And it was awesome to have her there and a couple other scoops.
Alex and Anna showed up, which is awesome. Just great to see scoops coming through at my little events.
I don't know. The algorithm is not promoting the stuff I'm promoting.
I thank every scoop for retweeting and putting out as much info on that class as we could.
We still had nine people. I promoted the show. I mean, I got promoted. I didn't pay for anything.
You're having a crazy winter, aren't you? That's part of it, too. Yeah. Yes. Yeah.
Ultimately, it was we had nine people show up in two degree weather. So that's pretty good. Right.
That's also possible that everybody knew about it. It's also possible that the algorithm just did its job and everybody in Pittsburgh knew about that class.
Nine people were in. It's possible. It's quite possible. It's cold as fuck. It's cold as fuck out here and just insane.
And every time like and then I was going to teach my new level one, which had to get postponed, I was doing that yesterday.
So last night, again, I'm heading out early. My class starts at six thirty. I'm in the car around five.
I open up the garage door and it's fucking snowing again. I was just like, what the hell?
It just doesn't stop. But we've got a solid, you know, almost 10 to 12 inches for Pittsburgh, parking and weather with the famous fall.
Yeah, he's got a solid 12 inches and it's just not moving.
It's not going anywhere. It's just there. I've already had to dig out my mailbox. I had to dig out a place for my fucking.
Did you get your mailbox? I had to dig out the mailbox because the mail people were like, please dig a path so we can get to your mailbox.
I'd love to deliver your mail, but we can't. Yeah. So I had to dig, dig a big old path to get them.
Yeah, that big high of seven on Saturday. Scoop and overgrow. Yeah, it's cold as fuck out here.
And then I dug a place to put my trash can so that it wouldn't be out on the street exactly, you know, and the plowing is crazy.
So it's where I'm digging out is like 14 inches.
No, I mean, my buddy, my oldest friends, Pat said a picture of him and his kids standing on the Navisink River in Red Bank, New Jersey.
Oh shit. That river never froze over the entire time that I lived in my entire lifetime.
I've never heard of that river being frozen. It was, it was nuts.
This is when Matt goes into his no such thing as global warming because the river froze spiel now.
That's right. Exactly. The people don't understand. Like it's young guys.
It goes both ways. It gets real cold. We've been asked to have an emergency Vegas parking and weather.
Okay, here we go. Oh shit. No one does it better than ICS from Ryan.
Is it me or is there a recent increase in people who insist on backing into parking spaces?
Why is this? What does it mean for our society as a whole?
I need an emergency Vegas parking and weather. This is a great point.
I have noticed this too. And I asked, but I just like Jacob had a very logical answer for my exit thing.
There is a logical answer as to why there's an increase in this happening. Great.
Because I've noticed this too. I want to know the same thing. Quality of reverse cameras.
You're right. All these cars put much better ways where they show you the lane that you're turning in
and everybody would rather park pulling out of their spot that way than backing up.
It's annoying. Ready Rich has the best take on this is that you shouldn't be mad that people do it.
You should be mad that people are bad at it. That's right.
Because that's it. It's like what happens is that it takes so much longer if you're waiting to park
and you're behind someone and they have to do this giant production to get the car back in.
So just pulling in the goddamn space. I'd like to, I'm a backer inner.
I've been a backer inner for decades unapologetically, especially with the truck.
If I'm driving a pickup truck, it's just so much easier to back in and then pull out nose first.
But when people are bad at it, it's terrible. And if there are a line of cars behind me in the parking lot,
then I do the gentlemanly thing and I go nose in just to do it a little faster.
So I don't have to pull forward and then back in. Yeah, I'm a consummate pull through guy.
So I go all the way to the other side backing in, but I'm going through and then I'm ready to go.
That's only dangerous for like two split seconds. Yeah. What do you mean dangerous?
If someone else is someone else wants to pull into the regular spot that you're pulling forward.
You don't understand how I do my pull throughs. I park in BFE.
There is not another car around me, my friend. This is the thing that drives the nearest abandoned lot.
Seriously. And goes fucking crazy over my parking.
She's like, you always zig when I think you're going to say automatically I go.
I go so far away. She's like the other night it was it was balls cold again.
The wind was blowing. We had to go to Lowe's.
This was right before the fucking crazy storm hit and we went to go find a terracotta pot.
Just in case we needed an emergency heater type thing.
We could pack because we had plenty of candles and we just needed a terracotta pot to use as an emergency heater.
We absolutely lost power and everything went to shit. That was your backup plan. Hey, man, it works.
It fucking works. I love this. I love that. That's your backup plan.
So we went to go get a terracotta pot. It was freezing cold backstage at Madison, Wisconsin.
And Mike noticed that the dressing rooms had old light bulbs, not LEDs, but old style light bulbs.
It was like, yeah, close the doors, leave the lights on.
And we went and did a sound check and we came back to the toastiest dressing rooms.
We basically easy. We easy baked ovened our dressing rooms in Madison.
They are. They are hot. This is how you fucking do it.
And yeah, so these are the hacks. But yeah, I parked over by the garden section and pretty close to the front.
There was nobody else there. And we had to walk all the way in.
She's like, what the fuck you doing, Mattingly? You're killing me. This is crazy.
She's like, just shivering and shaking the whole way. I'm cold, too. It's cold as fuck.
But then we got the thing and we're heading out the door and I'm like, can we go back over to the door we came in on?
She's like, no, we have to go out this exit, which is even farther away from where you fucking parked.
And I'm like, I didn't know. I thought we could go out the front again.
She's like, no, we can't. Why did you do this? This is insane.
That's really she. She does not like my parking. But I don't sound like this.
She does. But my parking could not be could not be safer in so much as there's no one there.
No, I don't like people combat park when it, when the spaces are diagonal, you don't back into spots when they're diagonal.
That's right. No, you don't. You do not back. That's that's how they're designed.
And so you don't have to back yet to the douches and still do it's buddies literally doing that right now.
Listen to me, douches. Stop it. Hear you. Hear you, douches. That's like almost doing a donut to get into that shit.
Right. Stupid. That's making a you. What a load of people do that in the Caesars parking garage all the time.
Sure has the angled parking spots, but they will get into the wrong lane.
You know, they'll be they'll be going up the down lane and now they have to back into the spot just because they can't get into it.
That's a double douche. It's not too negative. Don't make a positive. That's a double douche.
That stays double douche. It's two squared. It doesn't make a positive.
I don't know. When I see them doing it, I give them the stink eye.
They know what they did. They know what they did. We've got snow lined up on the streets everywhere still.
And the small as the roads already are, it makes some lanes like even more super tight.
So it's a little dodgeball out there. We should note that it's a it's a Patreon bonus month.
So thank you for everybody. Yeah, thank you. Thanks, everyone.
We're pretty fun dot com. We broke our bonus level.
And for that, we are going we owe you a bonus episode.
Now, we were going to give you a bonus episode anyway, because it's the Super Bowl.
And we always do our Super Bowl prep for people who don't love football, where we have Mitzi, our odds maker.
We have a lot of people who love football. We have a lot of people who love football.
No, don't do that! No, don't do that! Oh, Vulcan rings are notoriously razor sharp on penises.
But not on fingers, strangely enough.
I know. I know. It's weird.
Oh no.
Well, congratulations Starfleet.
SJ had some weird travel this week.
Oh yeah?
She's been in Canada for the last, I don't know, week and a half or so.
Doing shows with the Spice wannabe show.
Oh great, that's back up and cooking, huh?
SJ, just stay there.
Oh yeah, no, they've got a lot of road gigs.
SJ, just stay there. You're better off.
Well, that's...
Just hang out there.
Well, that's just it. That's just it, Matt.
On Monday, she had a gig back here in Las Vegas.
Oh.
And so she flew down, did her gig here, was in town for about 15 hours?
Yeah.
And then 4.30 this morning, back to the airport, back to Canada to do a show tonight.
Holy shit.
And she's back in Canada until, I think, Saturday.
How's she doing this? It's insane.
Oh, air travel, Paul.
No, like those things that pass over you in the sky.
Oh boy. I'm talking about the physical toll. My God, that's gotta be awful.
Oh no, she's hurting. She is hurting.
Yeah, we did that show together with Sarah Sarash. She was talking about this travel schedule.
And I said, you know, these are the kind of things like in our 20s, like we've been loved.
Absolutely.
We did it in our 20s.
I got to do this gig here and they got to fly.
You can fly right back here and finish out this gig.
Yeah.
And when you're older, you're like...
Yeah, now that SJ is in her late 20s, she hates it.
It is different in your late 20s. It's true.
Yeah, it's very different in your late 20s.
Speaking of Sarah Sarash, I guess, I don't know.
Do you trigger warn for the only curse word we really have in the English language?
The only one that's left?
Yeah, she has...
Yeah, go for it.
She has a song...
A cunt trigger warning.
She has a song out called Serving Cunt.
And if you look closely, you can see me dancing as an Elvis impersonator on Fremont Street with her.
There it is.
It's very fun. It's directed by my wife, my very talented wife, who may or may not be in the room with me right now.
And...
Hooray!
She did an amazing job. It was super fun.
And gave me my backup plan for if anything goes south as I got stopped multiple times for pictures just walking in my car, dressed like Elvis on Fremont Street.
There you go.
I now know what's going to happen, you know, when my #MeToo scandal hits.
So...
Right.
We'll be right there.
You got a solid $30 a day coming to you there.
Remember? Remember when people listened to The Will of the People? Wasn't that fun back in the day?
Did they?
Those were the days.
I don't even know anymore. I don't even know if The Will of the People were ever listened to.
I don't know what the fuck's going on.
At the time it didn't seem like it was, but now it seems like it really was.
God damn.
Shit is fucking crazy right now.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck. Shit's crazy.
Somebody wrote us the other day on Pod Therapy.
Actually, as this comes out, that show might not even be released yet, so I might be crossing timelines here.
But they were saying, you know, we commented on Pod Therapy when the most recent presidential election happened.
And just said, you know, basically, let's all stay calm and react to things as they happen.
And then, you know, a lot of things have happened since then.
And continue to.
And so they wrote in and they said, you know, hey, you guys, you said react to things as they're happening.
And now a lot of things are happening. And now what?
And we were like, yeah.
Whenever you think about that, that's what we think, too. We agree.
That's, yep, that's just it.
I have a lot of friends in Minneapolis from the improv community back in the day.
Sure.
I'm so grateful that we got to go out there, that you brought me along for that festival just recently, because I got to get a taste of that place.
And the people who were working at huge at the time got to take me on a quick little tour.
We went around, they showed me the George Floyd Memorial and everything.
So I was in that whole zone, right? Like it was chill.
It was totally chill.
No, Minneapolis is a great city.
And there's a lot of pride in it.
And so like what I'm seeing in my timeline is like I am actually like really proud of my Minneapolis friends.
I feel like I feel like I feel like I feel like they chose the wrong city to mess with in a lot of ways.
It really seems like that.
I proud is a good word.
It's they're doing a really good job.
I feel bad. This is just arbitrarily heaped on them because someone was mad.
They didn't win the state in an election.
Oh, no, I'm not mad about that at all.
I am I am thoroughly not bothered by the arbitrariness heaping on Minneapolis.
The shit that just that seems fine blows my mind.
The stuff that just making me so I don't know, not hopeless,
but I'm very curious as to where we go from here in a lot of ways,
it seems to me that no one is exempt from this shit no matter what side of the aisle.
It's getting you know where we're going from this.
We're going we're going to full on anarchy colonies.
Mad Max style.
I think you might be right, Jacob, because we go.
It's just going to be city states.
It's going to be old school city state.
There's no one each other.
Athens and Sparta.
There is no one for me.
There is no one at the federal level I would trust in any respect.
So how do you take directions like there's no one to give us a voice.
There's no one to unify and say, hey, maybe this is our next move or maybe we should try and improve this next.
You know, there's no there's no steps that are being lined out.
There's no actionable plan to be taken as I simply do not trust anyone.
I nominate you, Paul. Paul, you should take us to take us to the promised land.
No, no.
All right. No, Jacob.
Will you just going to go around the horn here?
No, I don't.
I don't know that I don't.
I'll go to the rest of the Zoom technical school port.
Will you take us to the promised land?
Take us to the promised land.
It's not supposed to be any one person.
That's why we have a group of government.
Oh, you're right, Paul.
You're right, Matt.
I see what you were doing wrong.
Zoom chat, Zoom chat.
This group of people.
Will you take us to the promised land?
You know, one person, it's a group of people.
I would love to have a community lead us into whatever's next.
For a fee.
There's a Patreon level for that chaotic clumsy.
Who the fuck knows what's going on?
Anyway, I'm just as she just texted me.
She is at the hotel in Canada.
Oh, good. She made it back.
They didn't take her passport.
Well, we were a little, uh, leaving Canada.
Cause she's there on a, on like a work visa thing.
You know, it's all legit and everything.
And, uh, she was like leaving and then coming back in less than a day
later during the, during my work visa.
That was the only thing that she was a little itchy about going back yet.
Of course.
But I like it all.
She has the paperwork for everything and it was all just legit.
Paul.
It is nice.
That is the nice thing about doing this in your late twenties versus your early
twenties is, uh, you're, you're prepared and you're just doing it all legit
this time.
Whereas when we did it in our early twenties, we were just doing like
tourist visas and be like, no, we're not working while we're here.
I still remember bringing a suitcase of Mr.
Piffle's, uh, customs of being like, it's just for friends.
Um, going to show it off to some pals.
If we had our merge confiscated, um, multiple times by Canadian, uh,
officials sell t-shirts and Mr.
Piffle's dolls.
What do you, what do they, they hold it for you to come back?
Is that how that works?
Pick it back up on your way out.
Yeah.
That's not so bad.
They sell it at the duty free shops.
I was going to say, I doubt they just, I doubt they just hold onto it for you
now anymore.
I don't think anybody's doing us any favors at the borders these days.
I think our goodwill ship has sailed back through and everybody's wearing
the dog who knows shirt.
Um, Paul, I'll just say, uh, I was, I did Penn Sunday school yesterday.
Um, and again, this will probably come out before that.
So we're jumping on podcasts in multiple directions here.
Okay.
Um, but Penn, uh, always brings up, it's a quote attributed to Gandhi,
but people are suspicious of whether it is, but that it is a first, they ignore
you.
Then they'd laugh at you.
Then they fight you and then you win.
And the, the quote was about fight you stage.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, there is reason to be hopeful.
Look, Lawrence O'Donnell talks about all time.
Protests always work.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, and I, I know I brought up on presenting school, the counter example,
you know, that I don't like is there was anti-abortion protests my whole life.
And I thought there's no way they're going to take away freedom of choice from,
from women.
It's, that's a, it's, it's, it's really bigoted towards one gender.
Uh, that's not, that's not the way laws are supposed to work, but, um, it did,
it worked.
So, uh, January, you're absolutely right.
J six definitely kind of worked.
Yeah, it worked.
So, uh, you know, we were at that, we were at the fight and jail phase of,
of the protest movement.
So, yeah, I'm just, my hope is that we can survive the fighting,
the fighting stage.
I agree with you.
I think the, I think the, the, the old way is, is dying.
And this, and these are the death throes.
Yes, there is some of that too, for sure.
I just hope we can, we can survive it.
I hope we're good at the end of it.
And a lot of people who are staying on the sidelines are no longer staying on
the, like it is, it is, it is galvanizing what is happening.
That is true.
Yeah.
Well, I've certainly, I've certainly seen, you know, plenty within the, uh,
podosphere coming forth and letting our voices be heard.
And I don't want us to be out of that conversation anyway.
I want everybody to know which side we're on, at least which side I'm on for
sure.
And, uh, I want everybody to know that they're not alone out there.
We see it.
We feel it.
We hear it.
It's fucking horrible.
And, uh, I like, I guess, like Matt said, um, we're coming together.
We're getting out there.
We're getting our voices heard and we're going to get through it somehow.
I think so.
We don't have any choice.
We don't have any choice, but to get through it.
I mean, I don't think we'll ever do things that are better for the
environment.
There's certain things I've think the ship has sailed on, but I think for
protecting our own freedom and stuff, I think we're going to, we're going to
get better at it.
Hopefully, hopefully.
Yeah.
The river will freeze over a few more times and somebody will go, Hey,
wait a minute.
Well, I mean, it's all fucking connected, right?
Like I, I truly believe we're going to have to dismantle these, uh,
goddamn data centers and, um, uh, holding cells.
We're going to have to dismantle all that.
We're going to actually physically have to get in there and break apart some
structures.
I'm following, uh, there's a new giant data center being built in, uh, rural
Louisiana, not too terribly far away from my mom's house.
And, uh, so I've been following this and it's, it's, uh, you know, huge.
It's, uh, I, I don't even know how many multiple acres.
Yeah.
Like acres and acres of warehouse being built and it's the new meta like AI
center.
Uh, and it's being built in a town of like, I don't know, a few thousand
people.
Uh, and everybody there is just like scared and weirdly in the dark about
everything that's happening.
Cause it's going to, it's going to take all their water supply.
It's going to fuck up their water.
Electricity is going to be a thing.
Yeah. The fact that they can just arbitrarily decide, well, now
electricity costs five times what it used to, because we need more of it
for this.
I guess.
So Will Smith can eat spaghetti in a more convincing way.
What the fuck, man?
You know what?
I was off of it until you said that.
Now I'm kind of back.
Now you're back on.
I do like being more convincing.
If I watch unbelievable spaghetti eating, it ruins my day.
Noodles.
Yeah.
Oh, we've got to do something to get through this uncanny Valley.
I'll tell you what else we're going to do to get through it.
And that's listen to the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Bob Evans flavored toothpaste.
That's from Florida man scoop in 2024, Bob Evans flavored toothpaste.
Well, how do y'all and welcome on into my barn shaped restaurant.
Bob Evans, you know me for my delicious biscuits and gravy, my fresh country
raised eggs and my oh so succulent bacon.
Well, now the flavor of Bob Evans is delivered right to your mouth on a
toothpaste holding device, hopefully a brush.
But here's the thing.
We've decided to forego our classic country cuisine and you're getting the
direct flavor of Bob Evans.
That's right.
Me.
This toothpaste tastes like me.
My scientists have worked day and night to make this toothpaste.
Tastes like me, like you're eating a piece of me.
Bob Evans, the real man behind the restaurant.
It doesn't taste like your delicious breakfast items.
It tastes like my delicious breakfast items if you like huevos el Bob Evans.
What's huevos del Bob Evans taste like?
Well, open that mouth, let me dip them in.
You can be the judge when you actually slide some of that paste on.
See how close we came.
Speaking of close we came, I did say dip them in.
Anything for my teeth.
So let's do it.
Oh, here's the thing about Bob Evans paste.
It's good for any cavity if you know what I'm saying.
Our scientists didn't stop with just flavor.
They've also worked on lubrication.
It's the slickest fucking brush you've ever had in your life.
Soylent gravy.
Soylent gravy is Bob Evans.
That's right.
Get her hay scoops at checkout.
That was so upsetting.
It'll drip right off you like come on a gold tooth.
I don't think that's a metaphor.
I think you just put like.
That's essentially what's going to happen.
That's a simile, not a metaphor.
I don't think.
Hey, I'm just a plain old barn bar and restaurant tour.
That's the difference.
I'm not a dentist degree.
What's the dentist doing?
He's right here doing the dip.
I want to do a Matt was right segment.
Beast games continues to be the craziest fucking bat shit thing on television anywhere.
I'm on episode three with my kids are watching it.
Oh my God.
I see that survivor.
I just can't watch it.
It scares me to see it.
OK, so last year, this is a spoiler.
Never mind.
I'll wait to the whole thing.
It's crazy though.
Like last year we talked.
We talked about these games because Matt started watching Beast games with his kids when it came out.
Because Matt's kids like every other child on the planet watches Mr. Beast on YouTube.
Uh huh.
And so watch that.
I watched it because I love really bizarre reality TV game shows like the competition reality TV thing is like a weird spot that I like to dig into in these things.
I'll say this is truly like the weirdest one.
It is.
This year is much more competition based and less psychological torture based so far that I've been watching.
So that part I like it is still so funny where he sets up things to have like this twist.
And when people don't become absolute assholes, it's so clear he's so disappointed like he's so upset that people are.
I am on episode four.
Yeah, I'm one episode ahead of you.
Yeah.
And I'm going to tell you that he has noticed that too and changes some of his tactics going forward to get them to do it.
And he wants people to be themselves.
The niceness might not continue as it is in the earlier episodes.
No, it doesn't go.
It does not go to psychological torture, though.
I mean, it definitely doesn't do that.
But they kind of laugh about it.
The first season, there was so much crying.
Yes.
And so much like it was just awful.
Yeah, I can't.
I can't do it.
It makes me upset to see in the clips.
Like I said, I just get something to come up in a scroll and I'm like, oh, this looks awful.
Yeah, I know it's tough, but it is it is really like super.
I watched this one, this other reality show competition game out of Korea because they make some fucking weird ones over there.
And this is the idea of it and the execution of it, both are so much bigger and stranger because of it, because they're doing these things on such a large scale.
I mean, when they when they filmed it in Vegas, they were in Allegiant Stadium.
They go out to these places out just in the open areas and build these giant scale things.
And it is weird the amount of effort that goes into something that is so stupid.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I say that as a podcast.
But we have it on the effort and we're right.
We're in check. We're in check.
We got it. We got it.
We're fine.
I don't know. I keep watching it and I'm like every time I go every time it says TVPG, it's the beginning of it.
I noticed that and I think of your kids and I go like, yeah, because kids are because kids are watching this and I've been trying to watch it through the lens of a young person watching it, which is impossible for me to do.
It is it bothers me on it doesn't bother me, but it like it it it makes me uncomfortable on a different level. Yes.
Well, on a more positive media note, new show, new show note, I will shout out Mystery Science Theater and Rift Racks are combining again.
Rift Racks is basically re taking up the mantle of Mystery Science Theater 3000 and they are going to produce four new episodes utilizing Kevin and Mike and.
Oh my God, Bill from the OG Rift Racks crew as, you know, reprising their roles as Tom Sarvone Crowe and him and yeah, it's going to be really cool to see them back in the saddle instead of the whole new crew, which nothing against the new crew.
For the most part, there were one or two times that whoever was voicing Crowe on a couple of this last season.
I was like, shut up. They're just screaming. They were just screaming like that is not the fucking voice.
But yeah, it's already up to 1.6 million on Kickstarter. It's amazing brand new thing.
And they've still got 45 days to go something like that. Wow. But it's a wonderful thing to see them back at it.
And this is the Rift Racks fans coming through big time for them because I've backed several of their kickstarters to a back the mystery science theater crew too.
But I am far more in the camp of what Rift Racks has been doing than the last because that in more than the than the MS the last MSC three K failed because people were just kind of like that because that last season was just not great.
And it's because they really jacking around with who they had voicing Crowe.
They had a couple of people who really knew how to do it.
But then if you're watching a movie and someone's in there shut fucking up, I can't.
I love the things that bother you about about movies.
Paul, it's I watched that mystery science theater 3000 season and there was a single time that the robots voices even occurred to the most recent one.
The most recent season.
I don't know if you saw this most recent season because the most recent one you because you would go, oh shit, I can't unhear this.
It's awful.
It's just a screeching Banshee.
And and it just ruins any of it.
So they had good performers that first reboot.
They were fine.
I was like, this is great.
You know, let's go.
But now I'm really excited because it's the old bots with the old voices.
It's you know, you don't want weird sounding Muppets.
It's the same shit.
People are on the Kermit thing, too.
You know, there's something to it.
There's really something to it.
And you know what the frog always said, it's not easy being blue.
Hey, invent some new robots.
They invented some new robots.
Throw them in there.
That's fine.
But also, just don't be screechy screechy ain't going to just goddamn screechy ain't funny.
It's not not Dustin Diamond is he's no longer with us.
Yeah, he's no longer.
And so, I mean, just just bringing it up is it's truly in bad taste.
So everybody who is doing screech impressions on Mystery Science Theater 3000 episodes, just stop it exactly.
Well, they've stopped it because they didn't get funded in the last one.
But anyway, Mary Jo Peel is going to be back as Miss Forrester and that's going to be funny.
Pearl Forrester.
So that's going to be funny, too.
They got the proper antagonist with them.
I think it's going to be quite good.
I'm looking forward to the new four episode mini season thing.
I went ahead and backed it on the Kickstarter.
And of course, got to get my physical media on.
So I ordered the four DVDs and VHS tapes.
Yeah, the VHS tapes are going up, dude.
The money on those.
It's crazy.
It's true.
I don't doubt it.
They're really expensive now comparatively, especially like horror.
I think it's dumb, but I don't doubt it.
I know it's dumb, but there is a huge market for it.
But anyway, just want to say shout out to the Riff Tracks guys.
I listen to them every night pretty much.
Matt, have you dipped a toe yet on the old to be?
Did you take in any of the Riff Tracks films yet to try and use them as sort of your lullabies?
I have not used them as lullabies or check them out.
I should.
You really should.
They got some really great stuff in there right now.
Yeah, I'm about to do another two week stint on the old Sun Princess, so maybe I can crack it then.
Well, I'll just put this out there as my number one recommendation for anyone who wants to see if they like this kind of shit.
Go on to be look up Riff Tracks and then watch Samurai Cop.
The Samurai Cop episode of Riff Tracks is one of the funniest things I've seen in so many times.
I still laugh my ass off even just thinking about it.
It is a super cheese.
Oh, B movie action thing.
It's crazy.
I it's great.
You know, if you if you grew up like us when that was the thing like, you know, aping commando and all those kind of things.
But Samurai Cop, God damn it.
The movie is so crazy on its own.
And then there had a commentary just blows it out of the water.
So check it out if you get a chance.
It's also amazing.
Like how many movies have they covered?
They are.
I think they they're cracking around 500, maybe more.
It's just amazing.
Like how many like because it's not like there's a certain aesthetic because there's a lot of like just bad bad.
Yes.
And it's it's it's it's a very fine needle of thread.
You wouldn't think, but it really is.
And there's some of them that are better than others by far.
I mean, it's basically it feels like what their show basically is, is it seems like if if Penn's old movie night had morphed into a podcast.
I mean, that's that's what you know, Mystery Science Theater was always that.
But there there has to be a certain level of watchability to the movie.
That's like it can't just be absolute trash, unwatchable and again has to have decent audio and all that kind of thing.
Because otherwise it just, you know, you can't sit there for two hours and watch it.
And there's been a couple of of them that are really pushing the line because they are digging pretty deep in the catalog.
But yeah, man.
Oh, God, this hammer.
I cop will fucking.
Well, I mean, we we learned that lesson, too, with some of the episodes of what was the Michael Landon Angel show?
Oh, yes.
Highway to heaven, highway to heaven, highway to heaven.
Not all gems, not all.
Some of those were just so bad you can't make fun of them.
Right.
This thing's like I love the movie night at Penn's house.
It was like one of my favorite things.
And then when I was younger and I had a house full of guys, that's what we do.
We would just flip to find the worst movies on HBO and make fun of them.
It was an activity.
I loved it.
I miss it.
I was like, I'm basically hoping like my kids are now getting funny enough that like if I can get them on board, I have to figure out a way to like get them into the idea of making fun of a movie while we watch.
It out loud to make use of the lab.
But I feel like I can recreate it with my with my boys right now.
Show him some mystery science theater.
Rift Tracks has some some question like Samurai Cop would not be suitable for your youngins.
It's violent and there's boobies and shit circles and circles.
You wanted me to show them Terrifier 3.
I mean, I do still want you to show them Terrifier 3 on Christmas.
I would give you I might I would I might actually give you money for that.
If you show them Terrifier 3 on Christmas.
It's the first 15 minutes.
They lose their fucking minds.
All right.
Tell you what.
If Matt loses Jock vs. Nerd today, he's showing his kids Terrifier 3.
On Christmas.
On the hunt for balls on the hunt for balls.
We have a Winter Olympics themed scooper from Freehold Scoop today.
The categories are curling, biathlon, luge and bobsled.
I'm up first.
Oh, let's see.
I'll try curling for 400.
This is how much the stones that the players slide down the ice weigh in pounds within five.
This is the first one.
This is the first.
How much does the Rockway is the first question?
But Jacob, they're called stones.
And you know, in Europe, when you say, oh, I lost 30 stone or more, you know, or lost five stone over the summer vacation because I stopped eating gummy bears or whatever.
So maybe I believe that's 20 pounds.
You think you think one stone is 20 pounds?
That's what I was about to say.
I don't know.
I think that's what it is.
Uh, fine, Paul.
20 pounds.
That's my logic.
All right, let's try it.
Forty two.
Oh, the answer.
That's much heavier than that.
That's heavier than 20.
That's two.
Not within five at all.
I think it's well, I don't know what I thought is one.
I was going to ask you.
Is one stone 20 pounds?
That's what I thought.
Did I say somebody weighs however many stones?
Oh, it's 14 pounds.
Oh, one stone is 14 pounds?
Yes.
Sorry.
Paul, you're up.
Okay.
Biathlon.
Let's go.
For 14, for 400.
Biathlon combines cross-country skiing and this other sport.
Target shooting.
I'm sorry.
It's rifle shooting, Paul.
You're not shooting targets.
It's rifles.
Matt, you're up.
Curling for 800.
Curlers use these household devices to melt the ice causing the stones to go further and curl less.
Brooms.
Or brushes.
Chim-chiminy, chim-chiminy, chim-chim-chiri.
Jeff Loomis, not in my house.
It's me.
I'll try bobsled, 400.
An Olympic bobsled team consists of either two athletes or this many.
I believe it's four.
I believe two or four.
Nice.
Don't they have single person bobsleds or are they called something different?
That's skeleton.
Oh, that's right.
Skeleton is one where you lie down and go feet first.
Skeleton.
And then you die.
What's the one where you go head first?
Is that the luge?
That's skeleton.
Head first is skeleton, feet first is luge.
Oh, maybe that's the first question on luge.
Paul, you're up.
I will take biathlon for eight.
Biathletes shoot at targets from two positions, standing in this lower position.
Fucking.
That's why they're biathletes.
They have to show that they're biathletes.
One of them is fucking a lady and the other is fucking a dude.
Band kick.
Standing in this lower position.
Kneeling.
One leg up, kneeling.
Prone.
Like the--
Oh, so we were talking about sexual positions.
Like the shrimp.
Doggy.
Prone shrimp.
Is prone kneeling?
I don't know.
No, prone is laying down flat.
Oh, OK.
Elbows.
Butt up, elbows out.
I'll show you.
Gotcha.
Yes.
Oh, that's what it is.
I'll teach you some proning.
Matt, you're up.
I'll do curling for 1,200.
All right.
Daily doubles.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
It's happening.
The target scoring area of the ring is called this.
The same thing you might call your residence.
Buckhouse?
[LAUGHTER]
Domicile?
Don't go to the tickle house.
[LAUGHTER]
Who's tickling who?
Is it just the house or the--
I think it's home base, like in tag.
Oh.
Home base?
No, I think it's just home.
I think it's just home.
Did they send it home?
I think that's what that's from.
I'll go with home.
All right.
The house.
Oh, it's the house.
Holy shit.
The house.
We were closer.
Nobody listens to Jacob.
I would have been closer to Buckhouse.
Yep, you would have.
It's me.
I'll try-- fuck curling.
I'll try biathlon for 1,200.
You two are both in Vegas.
You should know the house always wins.
Athletes must hit targets at this distance in meters
during Olympic competition within five meters.
14 pounds, Jacob.
14 pounds, final answer.
It's English money.
I feel like it's--
I want to say it's like 25.
But it might be 50.
I don't know.
I got to pass.
Paul.
I'll go 50.
All right.
It is 50.
Look at me.
Back on the board.
You know you're biathlon.
I'm a biathlete.
Sure.
Paul, you're up.
I'll do it for 2,000.
Let's go.
Daily double.
Look at this.
Here we go.
Norway's old inner bjrnsrun holds the record for most
Olympic biathlon medals with this many, within three.
Oh, for every--
For every--
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
--offended by Paul's accent earlier,
think about how the Norwegians feel, OK?
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
That's it.
So those things only come around so often.
Four years.
Four years, I think.
No, no.
Matt, every so often.
Can you win multiple medals?
Like swimming?
Yeah.
In biathlon?
I mean, I think you just win for the biathlon that--
I'll go--
--year, right?
I'll go with five.
OK.
Let's see.
13?
Jesus, fuck me.
What?
So you were-- you were doing the right math.
You just did not get close to what--
What the shit?
--Norway's early inner bjrnsun said.
Well, he just had-- he had multiple events to place in.
I didn't realize it was a multiple event.
I mean, you're assuming he.
I'm not assuming anything.
Only?
Only--
I don't know.
--the dude's name.
Sure.
I think.
All right.
Great.
Double down, same points.
[LAUGHTER]
Is only a man.
Double or nothing.
Matt, you're up.
I got a curling for 2,000.
The main two types of shots a curler throws are draws
and this other type designed to remove the opponent's stones.
Dickhead moves.
Destration.
Boppers.
Boppers is a great answer.
If it's not called boppers, I missed it.
It should be boppers.
I'm going to go with knockouts.
Ooh.
Good guess.
Takeouts.
Oh, so close.
So close.
You were so close.
You should have thought Chinese food.
I should have thought Chinese food.
I'm getting Chinese food later tonight.
I can't fucking wait.
I'll go bobsled for 800.
The athlete who steers the bobsled from the front position
is called this.
Captain Suicide.
Edward.
His name is Edward.
It's something about they have like a leash, right?
It's like it's a couple of little strings.
Pull things.
Yeah.
A little pulley string.
So it's probably something like the leashman or the stringman.
The leashman.
I saw those guys.
They played prim.
The quartet.
The leashman.
I saw it when Chuck Connors was still on it.
You did not see Chuck Connors in the leashman.
The leashman.
Everybody says they saw Chuck Connors in the leashman.
Nobody saw Chuck Connors in the leashman.
It's like the steerer or the wheel man.
The steerer.
There you go.
Wheel man.
He's using ropes.
He's like the ropester or something.
No, they call him the wheel man ironically, Paul.
Oh.
Because he drives to the event.
Well, he uses his feet probably too.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't think they use their feet.
Yeah, it's on a thing.
Yeah, I don't know.
I pass.
Paul.
Okay.
Here we go.
They use their feet.
Final answer.
Ropesman.
Show me ropesman.
Pilot or driver.
Well, well, well.
Aren't we creative, Mr. Bob Sled?
Or should I call you Robert Sled?
Paul, you're up.
Fuck.
I'll do luge for 2,000.
Oh, let's do it.
I got to get back on the board.
Germany has dominated Olympic luge, winning approximately this fraction of all gold medals in the sports history, within 10%.
73%, Jacob.
That is dominant for sure.
Let's see.
I'm sorry.
It's 60%.
You're off by 3%.
So close, Mattingly.
So close.
Horse shoes and hand grenades, Mattingly.
Matt and Natalie.
Well, now that I've leapt into second place.
By the way, we've got five questions left.
Quick score check.
I am currently winning with zero.
You're not uncatchable, Donnelly.
Matt has a negative 2,400.
Paul has a negative 4,000.
I would like to just say at this point in the show that the three of us really know our winter Olympic sports.
Got that winter Olympic fever.
That's right.
I think it's the flu.
Matt, you're up.
Let's go.
I'll go luge for 1,200.
Okay.
Luge runs are timed to this tiny fraction of a second where races are often decided.
My penis.
It does come in second.
I would guess thousands.
Oh, good.
A thousandth of a second.
That is a tiny fraction of a second.
You're on thousand.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's hundreds.
Missed it by one order of magnitude.
A bridge too far.
Gift of the Magi.
Last places within my grasp, Matt and Lee.
Mine too.
This is the maximum weight limit in pounds for a four-person bobsled, including crew, within 100 pounds.
Well, each of the people weigh 120 pounds.
Yes.
So that's 520 pounds.
Right.
Plus some of them have been snacking.
So let's put it at 550 just for the people.
About 550.
550.
Maybe.
Let's be generous.
They're athletes.
They're hefty.
Muscle weighs more than fat.
Let's say 600 just for the four individuals.
Okay.
The thing itself is very lightweight, I think.
The sled.
I would imagine the sled, the chassis, is all fiberglassy, right?
It's something, yeah.
So, I don't know.
30 pounds for the chassis.
Okay.
Then you've got to have the structure and the thing to hold it together.
That's where the real weight comes in.
Wait, the chassis isn't the thing holding it together?
No, I'd say the legs and the thing would be the, that's another 200.
So, let's just make it 250 for the whole kit and caboodle.
So, 250 plus 600.
So, 850.
That would be my guess.
Okay.
I pass.
Paul, you're up.
All right.
So, 850 I think would be a safe bet.
Maximum weight, I'm going to guess, is 1,000.
Let's try 1,000.
1389 pounds.
I underestimated.
You underestimated.
Paul, you're up.
You've got Luge and bobsled left.
Bobsledding down on the farm.
For 2,000.
Jamaica famously competed in this year's Winter Olympics, inspiring the film Cool Runnings.
Oh, Cool Runnings happened when I was still in high school.
Which had to have been '92 or '93.
Okay.
John Candy was alive.
Right, but when was that Winter Olympics?
Okay, now I've got to count it down.
So, 6, 2, 18, 14, 10, 6, 2, 98, 94, 90.
It had to have been '90.
1990.
Motherfucking shit.
I needed to go one more.
One more.
A bridge not far enough.
Wait, I guessed 1990 and it wasn't even, I was off by two years somewhere.
Where'd I lose two years?
Man, I suck at math.
Matt, you lose for 400 or 800.
No matter what you do, it doesn't matter.
I'll do a luge for 800, please.
I think I got one bobsled question right, but then I clearly lost that money somewhere.
Luge sleds have no brakes, so athletes slow down using these parts of their body.
What parts of their body do they use to slow the sleds down?
I think it's the hands, isn't it?
The scrotums.
Whoa, Bob Evans.
Just like a beaver tail.
Just dragging it down.
Beaver tail.
Jesus, you need to get that thing checked out.
If you're scrotum, it's beaver tail.
I mean, it's got to be hands or feet, right?
It has to be one or the other.
I'm done guessing at this fucking game.
Is it their knees?
Or their own heads?
The luge, are they on their stomach or on their back?
No, they're on their back.
Skeleton is head first.
Okay, so they're sitting.
Luge's feet first.
Okay.
Chaotic.
They use their opponent's stones.
They throw up parachutes.
I'll say hands.
Let's try hands.
Feet or toes.
Damn it.
I've been really good at narrowing it down to 50/50 on this one.
And I've gone the wrong way every time.
You have been really good at at least saying the correct answers somewhere in your discussion every time.
I have good math.
I am closing out the category and the game luge for 400.
If I get this question right, one of us will be in positive points.
Well, I'm not counting the day.
Unlike Bob's letters who sit upright.
Yes.
Luge upright.
Oh, news.
Athletes race in this body position.
They're on their backs.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Jacob, that puts you in positive points.
I have 400 points and I will.
What just happened is I won the game with 400 points.
Matt is in second place, though, with negative 4,400 points.
And Paul is in third place with negative 7,200 points.
Winter Olympics.
Catch the fever, everybody.
Catch the fever.
Get pumped.
J.J. just popped into the chat.
I'm trying to get J.J. on earlier, but she had a very important doctor's appointment.
Oh, sorry, J.J.
Good to see you, though.
Can you unmute yourself, J.J.?
No, she can't.
No, the answer is absolutely not.
No.
Oh, well.
No, the answer is genuinely she can't unmute herself.
Hey.
Did I do it?
Yeah.
You did it.
You guys, I just had my Botox and filler redone.
You can do it.
Revenge Med Spa.
Revenge?
Revenge Med Spa?
I mean, you sound so happy about this, but you look so apathetic.
Oh, my God.
Right here.
It worked, dude.
It worked.
It weirdly feels good.
I feel like it's some sort of weird face massage for weird people like me.
I was like, "Do the needles."
But yeah.
J.J., as someone who is open about their cosmetic work, can you tell the story about what happened
to you at the Las Vegas airport, please?
Fuck, man.
This is such bullshit.
I was so mad.
So I get off the plane, right, and I'm like, "I have 20 bucks.
I'm just going to put it in a machine and see what happens."
Sorry, the Botox doesn't work yet, so my face is all over the lot.
So I sit down with my backpack, and I've got my Magic Castle hat on.
I put my 20 bucks in, and it goes to 60.
And I'm like, "Whoo."
And the lady comes around the corner.
She puts her hands on her hips and goes, "Hello, little one."
And I'm like, "What the fuck?"
And I was like, "Are you talking to me?"
And she's like, "Yes."
She goes, "So you're trying to gamble?"
And I was like, "Yes."
And I was like, "I'm 36 years old."
And she's like, "We're going to have to see some ID."
Oh, my God.
So I got out my passport.
She opens it, and she goes, "Oh, God."
Yeah.
So, but that means that this shit works.
I guess.
Yep.
The hands on hips little one is so degrading.
Hello, little one.
I get to go like that.
Do you think this is an affectation of you dealing on Disney
so long that you are just de-aging
because the Disney magic is just continually de-aging you?
I'll tell you what.
I've gone places where people are like, "She's a vampire."
Matt was at the Crazy Castle in Savannah, Illinois,
where people that tour it try to get me to stand in front of a mirror,
and then they go, "She does have a reflection."
It's crazy.
But no, Disney, I literally asked him.
I was like, "Listen, I don't want a lot of shit."
I was like, "Disney cheeks.
I need Disney cheeks."
Okay.
There she is.
Disney cheeks on point.
Oh, Lord.
We're at the end of the episode, so we have to save your topic.
You have to come back on next week and do the other thing we want to do.
Oh, deal.
Because if people want to hear about some porch pirate shit
and Jesse going full Nancy Drew, I got you.
All right.
Yeah.
Of course you did.
Of course you fucking tracked down a porch pirate.
I did the police's job for them, and that is a story for another time.
Yeah.
JJ, you're on a ship next week?
I got on the ship the 5th, but I have really good Wi-Fi on Disney.
Okay.
I'll let you know, because I'm doing it from the ship, too.
So we'll both check in from our ships, and we can do your porch pirate story.
Yes.
I've got photos and video, too.
I documented the whole thing.
Wear your life preservers.
Congratulations, and make sure you have an adult hold your hand
when you go on the ship, okay?
Careful there, little one.
Okay.
Oh, you trying to get on the ship?
Oh, look at you trying to get on the ship.
It is a big, pretty ship, isn't it?
Where's your little guardian?
I work here, cunt.
I am the oldest person in the entertainment department on this ship.
Like, by 10 years.
Holy crap.
Oh, yeah.
The kids are on the ships.
The kids take the ship jobs.
That's true.
Some of them are, like, 18.
Like, I saw Maleficent came out of the elevator,
and they have to stay in character, even in the crew area.
So I was backstage, and she's like, "Move out of my way, peasant."
And they were like, "She's 18 years old."
I was like, "Well, fuck."
What do you mean they have to stay?
We're going to talk more about this next time you're on.
They stay backstage in character?
What?
No, no.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
My Loki, Maleficent, Cruella ship.
This is why we can't have you pop out at the end of episodes, JJ.
You're a powder keg of craziness.
We need you to give you a proper episode slot.
Disney characters on the cruise ships have to stay in characters backstage.
That's incredible.
Yes, until they get to the wig room.
Yep.
The wig room.
What happens in the wig room?
It stays in the wig room.
They just break down.
It's like, "I was mean to so many people.
I was just such a jerk."
I killed a real puppy out there.
I had the same character.
The puppy came up to my head.
They handed me a puppy.
I'm Cruella.
What would Cruella do if somebody handed her a puppy?
Make a handbag on the deck in the moment.
Dude, the Cruella 2, the amazing thing on Destiny is the people that are Loki, Cruella,
and Maleficent, there's not multiple cast.
It's just them.
So they know everything that's been said.
They are awesome.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
There's actually a Cruella improv show, and it's awesome.
It took me until just now to realize that you were saying Loki, L-O-K-I, and not Loki,
L-O-W-K-E-Y.
I was like, man, JJ is saying Loki about a lot of things.
It's Loki, Cruella, and Maleficent.
I was like, okay.
I guess they're Loki about it.
Loki giving Mickey a mini.
All right.
All the Disney life.
I'll send you the Zoom links next week, JJ.
Yes, yes.
My face won't be nearly as mobile, but I'll have fun.
Oh, shit.
All right.
We'll see you then.
See you, JJ.
Love you, JJ.
Bye.
All right.
Amazing.
I want to thank Smitty Scoop for her scoop pretty.
I want to thank Pinch Up for creating this podcast.
It wasn't Smitty.
Who was it?
It was...
Oh.
It was Freehold Scoop.
Oh, thanks, Freehold Scoop.
I always think Freehold Scoop and Smitty Scoop are the same person.
No.
But they're not.
Not at all.
Oh, no.
I don't think they are.
They have two different names.
Because Smitty is the Middletown Scoop.
Their questionnaires fuck us both in the same way, but yeah.
Yeah.
Well, I apologize.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I had positive 400 points.
I apologize to Freehold Scoop, but I kind of don't, because that really buried me.
That really hurt me.
That one did kick you right in the face.
That was my worst scooperty in a very long time.
It was.
I think that was our worst collective scooperty in a very long time as well.
Yeah.
When you start losing that hard, you just got to swing for the fences.
I know.
You just got to fucking go for it.
You just got to say fuck it.
Here we go.
Good money after bad.
Yeah.
Just say, "There we go.
Here we go.
Let's see."
Oh, by the way, if you want to send us one of those, if you want to send us a scooperty
or any kind of jock versus nerd, heyscoops.com.
Go over there.
You can send us a scooperty, any kind of jock versus nerd.
Also send us some scoop mail, do all those things over there at heyscoops.com.
All right.
It's a new month.
We haven't organized our Patreon thank yous yet, but we will get everybody thanked throughout
the month here.
We want to thank everyone for supporting us.
A huge thank you to all of you for getting us over the hump onto our bonus episode spot.
Let's see if we can maintain it for February.
Absolutely.
Right.
We appreciate all the new scoops coming in and contributing.
Please keep it up.
We want to keep bringing you bonus episodes every month if we can.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
All right.
Well, thanks for, thanks for putting us in your ear holes week after week.
And if you want to support us as a patron, get access to some of those bonus episodes
and other other cool rewards, head on over to preaching fun.com.
Or if you're also excited about scoop fest, Norway, head over to farts in a bag.biz that
along with preaching fun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little
as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon supporters, so please, if you think this show is worth
more than $0, preaching fun.com, farts in a bag.biz.
Those are two of the ways you can support us.
They're kind of the main ways you can support us.
Another way you can support us is you can tell people about us.
Spread the word, be part of the obelisk scheme.
We need more listeners.
We want more listeners.
We demand more listeners, but we will not stoop to doing a pyramid scheme.
No.
That is unethical and we will not do it.
Gross.
Awful.
We tell those two friends and then they each tell two friends and all that stuff.
That's a pyramid scheme.
We are an obelisk scheme.
One person.
You'll find one person that's going to really dig this show, vertical growth all the way
to the top.
Build the obelisk.
Tell that one person who you think is going to really dig this weird shit that we're doing
over here and they will then be part of it as well, then they'll tell a friend and they
will build the obelisk.
If everyone listening right now would simply tell one person and get one new person listening,
we could nearly double our listenership.
Almost.
Praise yourselves, everyone.
Paul's doing Kentucky math.
Again.
Hey, is there a store where people can go to buy our merch, Jacob?
Oh, no, no, no.
We've gotten rid of that store.
Oh, okay.
The store.
We used to have a store.
It was a whole thing.
It had a jingle and everything.
Oh, yeah.
No, I'm kidding!
Store jingle, store a big store song, we've got a store, brr, brr, brr.
It's store jingle, of course, HeyScoops.com/shop.
Go there now.
Do it.
All right.
Thanks, folks, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Mike Neal sent in the chat.
He started a couple of obelisks.
That's a fine way to do it.
Just as long as you can.
It's a fine way to do it.