oh hello there i am so glad you are here this is my favorite part of the show this is the part of
the show where we get to thank you the ice cream truck drivers who are the ice cream truck drivers
why those are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
right now i'd like to thank bearded scoop chasing the dragon scoop christine elsesser christy
salinas coach rat and bastard darren cunningham and darth scooper if you want to be an ice cream
truck driver just like these fine folks and i hope you do preachingfun.com preachingfun.com
is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows life you save
may be your own otherwise i'll see you at the cone there it is because you're dead you died
you want to go to an ice cream social yeah i'd love to great let's
go
like uh sunglasses for like my larger head okay and i got the polarized and it comes with a swatch
that says polarization test you can put them on and see like a secret word in a little swatch
and the word was israel
it's time for matt and maddie's ice cream social sitting over there it's matt donnelly sitting
over there it's paul maddie over here it's jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun very
polarized
polarizing sunglasses very polarizing polarizing extremely polarizing sunglasses i'm not even sure
if that's a real story or just a dad joke uh it's a real story up until the israel part
it just said their brand name in a little swatch but i laughed at polarization test
really hard yeah oh that's so good that's really funny um uh so i was making burgers for my kids
last night using okay using the smash
that jacob sent me a link for uh last time we brought up making burgers i was uh can't smashing
can't smashing some burgers for my kids and my youngest likes himself a pretzel bun so i get like
a fancy i get like nice pretzel buns from the uh from from a supermarket and then youngest has
excellent taste so then i get like a nice like kind of like a brioche style bun for my other
kid who doesn't like pretzel buns he normally just takes a regular hamburger regular just
usually gets a regular hamburger and then he gets a regular hamburger and then he gets a regular hamburger
bun but he's the only one eating it so i'll buy like a roll you know and um and he's eating it and
i said uh you don't you don't like the fancy bun do you and he goes dad i'm an american
there it is i want no fucking brioche bun
ah
mm-hmm
my i demand that my bread have a clown on it
wonder has to be in the title it has to be just the most bleached i need it yeah i need to be
so preserved yes like mold cannot grow on it no i want my hamburger bun to have been made in 1987
ah i wanted to have been sitting that's when they were still good oh they were good preserved
under salt
they were so good then it's like those mcdonald's buns with that exact same weird white spot on the
bottom of all of them oh classic classic consistency out are you out get out of my
house i don't know how many decades it's been since i had a mcdonald's hamburger clearly it's
been a minute yeah uh and uh jacob i know you you've long not been a fan of the southwest general
seating procedure
we've documented no i i have not been and it seems like i might be finally getting my way
you might be but in the meantime you know as someone i don't mind it i i don't i like it i
i love it a lot even though they started even though they started charging for bags it's still
cheaper to check bags on southwest than any other airline and so i still yep fly southwest because
it's still like 35 bucks and i just had a long conversation uh last week about uh airlines
because we were talking about like airline uh credit cards
and for her band and for for all of her gigs and everything and all the travel that she does
yeah and and we we ended up uh because we've been using southwest and we were like let's look at
these other airlines let's look at the other cards and everything and nope southwest that's
just where we that's where we stayed man i'm telling you you've got the major hub there in
vegas and that was what i got weaned on having to go out to jersey i had to not fly southwest from
here
there was no southwest from here to jersey no there's not it was out very disturbing
baltimore i think i went on united i went united both ways and i was just like oh i don't like this
i do not care for this i do not care for this united stuff at all i am uh getting online in
chicago to fly back home uh here from after doing my corporate gig uh-huh and uh it is um it is
tight quarters in uh
oh uh oh i'm blanking on o'hare and i i'm blanking because i should uh side note i drove like hell to
the wrong airport uh i went to oh that's the worst and the only thing that the only thing that was
good was that you know i had rented a car but i since i do have checked bags what i like to do
is like to pull up the curbside rush up the curbside check-in oh i like this move yes check
my bags then return my car rental car and i'm not lugging all of my bags through the airport
uh yes taking my carry-on
because there's a secret that most airports don't want you to know and that's that they can't tow your
car instantly they can threaten it they can threaten to find it they can yell about it a lot
they can do that they can't tow it instantly so they were like trying to check my bags at at midway
and the woman is making a very confused face and i'm panicking because as she takes longer i'm
looking to see making sure i'm not getting eyed for a fine with my rental car and uh and and she
goes uh you i don't know what's going on i've never gotten this message before i brought this
guy over he doesn't get the message before i think you have to go inside and my brain went
no i don't i have to go to a different airport my brain is like wait and so i was like somehow
did i book a ticket home from a different airport and then i realized i landed at a different
airport and didn't realize it i had just been to chicago three weeks ago for chicago magic lounge
and so my brain was just confusing the two airports and i so i luckily uh uh left with a
lot of time so i arrived at the proper airport with very little time so i was still rushing
but i wasn't going to miss my flight or anything i was i was like oh god but i i drove like hell
between those two airports anyhow so i'm there i'm in southwest and it is tight at o'hare it is
like you know because southwest makes you line up they usually make you line up along along the thing
the line they have here is like a very stunted little little uh they don't have the uh the
square footage no they don't in the airport there so you gotta like basically they've got the square
footage at midway but not at o'hare and there's a young man well coiffed man from india i believe
with his tall very tall sister or girlfriend i don't know yep and he is either way they were
making out he is he is beaming
uncomfortable anger already like he is holding his bags and he is like elbows out and we're in
tight quarters and you got to do the thing we're like hey what number are you i'm this number sure
yeah yeah this is what i'm okay with and jacob hates and i'm trying to figure out you know where
to stand or whatever and um you know it's within increments of five it's within increments of five
uh and i honestly i do have my own pet peeves with it where like some people kind of go
like if if i'm seven and they're nine and they're in front of me and i go i'm seven they go they'll
some as a southwest person will confidently go like yeah like meaning like you don't have to
get in front of me we're both in the same vicinity and i kind of go like close enough and i kind of
get like no that's the whole fucking point is numbers that's that's some bullshit is lower
than nine that's some bullshit ass so this guy has got his elbows out and i'm saying i'm a seven
i'm saying it you know and uh i'm saying it out loud and i get a couple of people give me him and
his sister wife are not communicating and he is like stewing i can feel him stewing from his back
you know someone's so angry oh it's the worst doing right goodness and so finally some guy
comes up like a little late to the party and is like excuse me a1 a1 a1 excuse me a1 yeah yeah and
i was like oh this guy's coming through like lipitor through a vein here and uh uh he is uh
there and the guy goes no no no no no no and he goes yes i'm a1 and he goes no we're all a1
which confused us all i was like i was like we i am spartacus i today we are all a1 no buddy
matt never got off the plane i don't know who paul's been talking to this entire time we live
here um and so uh uh i was laughing he goes no i've done this before i know how this works i'm a1
excuse me i'm definitely up there and he shouts like no like he starts like to open his arms and
clear everyone back like no one move kind of body language oh that's i feel so bad for this guy
that's just the worst because he's having a terrible day and he's like and so the guy with
a1 is like waving like anyone from south was like get get over here please get get over here
whatever and he says the the indian guy says no no no you announced that uh it is open seating
oh boy and the and the flight attendant's like no yeah when you get on the plane it is open
seating goes no you announced open seating so it is now open seating meaning that like
no no no like whatever you want is wherever you want to go no son like no no no you announced
open seating so now anarchy you know what this means
i was like listen he's like our podcast is a similar our podcast is a similar rule about dibs
so i understand what you're saying yeah dibs has been called is what you were saying you're saying
yeah once once anyone with south us utters open seating the numbers on our on our tickets become
useless they're right out out the window disqualified nope don't even look at them
again they're not worth the paper that they were printed on the open seating
motherfuckers so i take this opportunity to turn a person with a nine and i'm actually with someone
with a four and a three who don't want to go past this angry person so we're all we're all like our
little why we're all why not it's like little clutter space together right behind him so i
decided to announce and interpret what is happening i was like this guy thinks because
the words open seating were uttered in any capacity our tickets don't matter now
oh boy
i make a point of nothing else matters you gotta get up super early or stay up super late
yeah and you and you get on that app and you wait for the moment that thing flips over
and you hit your button to get your good seat availability i'm telling you right now uh mr a1
and myself we are you know we both fly southwest enough uh that when you you get a list they check
in for you you're gonna get your a well an a1 is is that's a 50% chance you're gonna get your a1
50 ticket
also a1 is i know because like they make sure that like pen gets it uh whenever he flies because he
can get that one seat that has the he's six seven so there's that one seat you have more more like
room yeah but that's an extra expense yes and it's and it's yeah and oftentimes it's a privilege
like it's oftentimes like it's like a anyone traveling often is a1 is like someone who travels
like every day like it's just a it's just a huge right right thing or whatever but i uh but yeah i
was laughing so angry and he continued to be a show they they got the front row with the extra
seats so they could feel like they were in first class you know that's all i think it's all they
were anxious about was getting that first row which means you have to put all your shit behind
you which i hate so i never sit in that row i fucking hate that right um and then uh guys i
tell you something i was i was haphazardly stick with me as a good person so i says i already checked
bags i would say if it's a full flight i will gate check my one carry-on bag and only have my book
bag oh okay and so i get on the plane but i put my book bag up in the carry-on which they is it's
that's not okay they frown upon that right yeah but here's the thing i do the same thing i do the
same thing though and i'm ready and i'm ready exactly so i put it up there and i go if they
call me i'll break my book back down if they don't call me i bet the person who's got this
center middle seat is going to have their bags they're gonna be pissed they have to put their
shit all the way behind them and i will i'm going to put my book back down and i'm going to put my
offer that row so i waited till the whole thing was on the person was like can i sit in the middle
seat like i'm fucked uh i said yes and not only that here and i took my book bag out put it at my
feet and then i put their carry-on into the space and they'd carry on right above their head
not all heroes wear capes guys not a champion of the flight not all heroes wear capes but this one
carried a book bag i was waiting for tears is maybe strong but a thank you uh whatever
give a shit that i did a good thing for they didn't care at all oh wow what do you know i mean
they still they still gave you the the the thank you hand jay during the flight right i mean that
person is an american
i was like did you realize what i just did for you like do you understand yeah
they did not you owe me you i said that's it
open seating and then i hit a music cue and everybody had to switch seats until the music
stopped did the guy end up getting on the plane where he was was he was he not stopped what they
didn't put him back anywhere no they let him on and he was just i mean he got up like probably
like seven times to get something out of one bag or another and then they were yeah
he was having a terrible day i see these people in airports and on flights where i'm just like
i like you were being horrible to everyone around you and i hate you so
much are these that being said yeah i recognize that you are having just the worst day that a
human being can have and i'm sorry for you do you think it was because he didn't want to fly
do you think it was he was a nervous flyer and you know these people they they can't handle
the loss of control that flying is and so i mean i think i think it factors a lot you know i think
we have we have uh folks here who work in the airline business but i i've including myself i
think i'm much more anxious on a plane and i get much more fucking pissed about little shit that
sure but i find as someone who is with you often uh both in and out of airports
uh yeah yeah no matt you're definitely much more anxious flying
i can just you don't have to wonder buddy hey i just are i said nothing to that woman that shook
my seat i didn't say you're not a hero sir i just said you're more anxious uh right and so i tell
myself you're not going to care about this in like 20 minutes right like that's what i tell
myself when when i start to get future matt does not give a shit about this shit about this um so
that's the trick uh but it is it is yeah i think i think everyone gets fucking pissed about going
on planes um no it's not it's not a fun experience for anyone so uh speaking of good deeds guys well
well i'm patting my own back here okay uh other arm so
there was uh uh an attack on verizon either a cyber attack on verizon or just a big fucking
fuck up at verizon but all right all verizon went down like two days ago uh-huh oh shit i was giving
like uh like crappy service like across the country and uh at the same time there's an apple
update that night before on my phone and then okay i got up my phone was not working and then i was
like oh shit maybe the update messed something up or maybe whatever right and then all of a sudden
people and they had their phones down too man going around without cell service for more than
24 hours is crazy like i know it's so dumb but i was like man the world would fall apart if this
happened for like four days oh yeah we'll fall apart matt yeah we'll we'll fall apart because
paul is looking forward to it the amount of time to just hop to my car is like all gps it from the
car and all of a sudden i was just going like shit no i'm out
i have to figure out incorrect i have to figure out where i'm going wow um
and so uh uh but i'm getting this thing on my phone that's a sim card failure
and okay and i got it gordon knows what i'm talking about and um yeah and everyone else
i'm talking about who has verizon phones didn't get that message right oh but i went into a verizon
store and i was like oh my god i'm gonna be like oh my god i'm gonna be like oh my god i'm gonna be
like hey uh i have my phone says sim card failure and they literally there's three of them and they
all went yeah i know the network is down and it's down like across the country or whatever and i
said oh but mine said sim card failure he goes they're all saying different different things
the different people if you look or whatever so they were like ignore all the other things it's
the network yeah the network is just wreaking havoc yeah now i'm against people in chat saying
they have verizon and nothing went wrong with them
well good for fucking you okay
if you google the news stories say verizon outage you will see uh news stories on it
uh i'm looking at it right now uh the weird thing is it doesn't seem like verizon has
said still what what caused it they have not said what caused it i'm thinking i ran but i don't know
but why not guess you think you ran too much i think i ran too hard and messed up my phone
yeah yeah well i'll tell you i said
no so i said i said i said i said oh i i go oh so you've been dealing with this all day and they go
right yeah and i and i go oh that can't be fun they go one woman literally pointed us and said
it's your fault and you're not doing anything i was like really the retail person working
for verizon storefront is in charge of the network they're like i like to sell your phone
and keep this entire network going across the world wow now now matt it sounds like you made a bit of
a some an assumption there yeah when this retail store employee just told you this story you then
assumed that they did not indeed control the verizon network oh my god i'm a fool i didn't
even ask you buddy it's it's right there but do you yeah right i could i could but do you i could
have just said that and then it'd be like as a matter of fact you caught me on the undercover
boss day yeah i'm tom verizon i run this thing i'm tom
verizon i decided to get a little taste of that old 1475 an hour see how see how that treats me
see it take a little taste of how the other half lives watch this and then he takes off his glasses
and shakes down his long hair and he's a beautiful girl the whole time amazing i'll tell you who else
was a beautiful girl the entire time you didn't even realize it and that is the following sponsor
there's more to the story but today's show is brought to you by
the bearded liberal truck driving school school for the bearded liberal truck driver trucker
trucker the bearded liberal trucker driving school one of the most polarizing characters
some people don't like when we do this character and i love that character um yeah but uh yeah so
that's from 2022 sex guy jimmy d scoop and that's the bearded liberal trucker driving school all
right you pansy sons of bitches strap on your rainbow hats and let's get going
all right get in the goddamn truck and follow me to truck driving school you're gonna learn how to
parallel park this son of a bitch that's right you're gonna be able to aim this thing slide it
right in getting right in between the marxist ideology and union theology you're gonna just
zip it right in there tight as a tight as a cord yeah you're gonna love it yeah you're gonna be able
to maneuver on the highways and byways of this great country better than a woman's right to vote
i'm sorry i do we learn how to drive trucks while we're here at all i was hoping to learn
how to drive a truck eventually mr yambi pamby boy oh boy you sure like to mouth off a lot you
know you might want to think about taking some meditation classes fucking shit no i was just i i
thought that was a good idea i thought that was a good idea i thought that was a good idea
i thought this was a truck driving school and so i was just here oh it most assuredly is it most
assuredly is but uh i can't help but notice you got some pretty fancy shoes on there
they're uh they're nikes you have any ideas where those were made and by which infant's hands
boy oh boy uh no no i i don't i i just bought the shoes uh pay less i think hey uh
let me ask you a quick question what's your favorite war
i'm sorry wrong answer there is no war but class war get the fucking truck
so i leave the verizon store with no service
uh-huh decide to wait out the the outage and i um i go next door to the smith's and i get cupcakes
and i bring um all the workers oh that was very sweet oh i say sorry and then they fixed your
phone for you that's really nice they're like here you go here you go sir let me turn your phone
well i wake up the next day i do a little research at night you know research i asked
chat gpt how to fix my phone and uh that's it you're fucked buddy and then i go on youtube
uh and watch some videos
uh and then i go on youtube uh and watch some videos and then i go on youtube uh and watch some
oh you did do some research and i'm trying to do all this shit to my phone did you figure it out
pretty quick youtube's like hey everybody's screwed no no i meant that like uh like like
oh so oh sorry i skipped a step so basically i started i started talking to all my other verizon
friends and they got their bars back and i didn't by the end of the night oh ah okay so at midnight
you know everything's closed but at midnight i'm realizing that like everyone else i'm the only one
still with no service on my phone have you tried turning it off and turning it on again right i did
put it in rice i shoved it in rice um i tried to uh rub its thigh and whisper in its ear
to turn it on and um tear and it's tear duct
and then it tells you like you can take out your sim card thing have you ever taken out
the sim card of your own phone it's a pain it's scary you gotta get like a little paper clippy
thing and you gotta like push real hard like harder than you would on like a delicate object
and then like it goes and then it comes out and i laughed because i was following the directions
on the youtube thing but of course you're playing pausing playing pausing and it says do not blow
into the empty slot like a nintendo and i was like oh that's exactly what i did i had too late
you need to put that before you need to tell me i did that immediately that's a go have you guys
seen all the videos where people pour molten uh glue into their phone holes and pull it out
as a cleaning method yeah oh no i've seen those i don't know that that's advisable i don't think so
i i haven't done it um i don't i've seen the videos i haven't been tried to replicate i don't
think you'll go i don't think you'll go to the apple store and they'd be like have you done
molten glue at home i don't think that's ever gonna be i think it would fuck you up i think
you could maybe do slime maybe no i'm do not i'm not putting any goo in my phone yeah they use the
hot glue
yeah i don't know yeah like if i get a little fuzz in the in the charging port of my phone i get a
little q-tip and just pop the pop the fuzz out you get wait you pop out fuzz with a q-tip with more
fuzz that seems ridiculous fight fuzz with fuzz fight fuzz with fuzz well you know now that i'm
saying no now that you're saying it as an old-time video game collector you know we when i'd buy all
those used copies they got and and movies too they got stickers all over them of course the best way
that sticker residue off is with another adhesive sticker there you go so there you go fight fuzz
with fuzz fight fuzz with fuzz uh mike nielsen matt have you gotten the $20 account the the
account credit uh i haven't gotten that i probably show up on your next bill uh you're you're owed
well i think you have to get it i think you have to call them and oh we say hey motherfucker you
better get on according to the new york post there is a call for this to be done automatically now
imagine it's like a $20 account credit which is being slammed for being inadequate do you feel
like $20 is adequate or inadequate for your pain and suffering like i mean so a day without cell
service is worth more than $20 oh yeah definitely more than 1 30th of your bill well i think i think
it's a breach of their contract and i think it probably isn't given all the legalese that i'm
sure it's not but at the same time i think that but i'll go to the prices store and tell them that
but in certain cases it's a life or death situation i think i think they could really
become uh here not heroes they could make some good positive news if they waive the monthly fee
for everybody yeah i think i mean that if they said scooper nova girl matt wants to know how
much the cupcakes were did were you even with the $20 credit are you still in hot to uh verizon here
i got $60 cupcakes each whoa basically i got the
nicest cupcakes i've ever seen with jules and ramsay's corner cupcakes um no i got you know
seven bucks yeah okay nice cupcakes so even with the 20 you're coming you're coming out a little
ahead even even with the cupcakes on the 20 you're coming out a little ahead i'm probably not gonna
go for the $20 credit i'm just gonna let you know right now you're not those are things where you
value your time at zero i don't value my time are you kidding me
to just call them up and say hey give me $20 they go yeah there's the word there's the word what do
i do paul right just just call them just it's so easy the word just makes it so easy oh boy i won't
be on the phone for an hour on hold with all the other schlubs trying to get a $20 fucking refund
okay maybe you don't do it today but no way no way they're gonna let people stay on on hold for
an hour for their $20 thing that's fucking great oh so you just click a link there you go i'm sure
you can do it you should absolutely do it i just got $20 back from my uh oil change i'd spent but
i spent 20 minutes doing it but that's worth it to me that's a dollar an hour for me you're really
distracted by this $20 this is not where this story is going i'll tell you why because this
is the $20 that's what this is to me you're speaking in terms of action figures that's a
craving the hunter are you crazy you don't want to crave in the hunter are you insane
are you insane not really i don't want to crave it though well you don't want to crave in the
hunter you're not a spider-man fanatic he killed spider-man you know how hard that is to do
this guy figured it out people have done it yeah i think he's the only one call the cops
that's a crime that is murder he ended up dying over it
oh he didn't actually kill spider-man that's the twist
look this is all adding up to is on the day there was a software update on the day there
was some kind of weird cyber attack or not that took down a lot of verizon's network
yes by total coincidence on the same day my sim card crapped out
just a total do you think it couldn't have been coincidence it was some kind i think it was
no or the update what do you think jacob what do you think i i tend to i i do tend to lean
towards paul's way of thinking on these uh with the electronic stuff is is uh if if one thing
happens i i don't i don't think it's usually coincidence i think it's usually somehow
by something yeah maybe not in the way that maybe not in the way that we're thinking about but like
i have an older phone i
have a 12 right okay so i think what's the 17 is out now i think
did someone give your phone a comic book with boobs in it because that's the ultimate corruption
circles on circles circles in circles
i i showed i showed my sim card the entertainment landscape in las vegas and it just gave up and
crapped out it went like yikes you made me
you made it research the boring company was like corruption corruption
corruption joe lombardo corruption corruption file corrupted
well joe lombardo is the uh nevada governor so somehow yeah somehow somehow he's the nevada
fucking governor boy we got out of that i wasn't telling you i was telling the people listening i'm
telling you i got out of there by the skin of my teeth before i started dude compared to some other
look i don't like joe lombardo and i'm not voting for him ever right but i mean compared to what other
states have for politicians i guess you're right i count my blessings he's an old school
intelligence scumbag not a just a blatant youtube lying scumbag right um suppose
yeah yeah like there are some things that he says when he's like yeah i was just over there
and that that i walked over here i'm like oh he he just said something that was demonstrably true
okay that's okay
okay okay
yeah laurie in the chat like hello indiana over here could be a lot worse
i count my blessings with lombard you know hey you throw a dart at the old us of a you're gonna
find some horrible shit right now i'll tell you who disagrees with paul about that completely
and that is matt's son who is an american that's right also the following sponsor this show and
this friend of mine who is an american who is an american who is an american who is an american
was not supposed to carry over two commercial breaks but um uh this show is brought to you
by sales ship sale sale yep that's sales ship sale sale from night scoops in 2021
sows not sorry sows ship sale sale you get it right i get it okay
hey i'm so i sell ship sales
and today i'm having a sale on my ship sales
would you like to save when you buy a ship sale from sal
today's the day of the sale so set sail for savings with sal ship sales
sailing takes me to sales where i can buy sales for my ship oh yeah that's right i'm sal with the
pipes
saling it's a discount that you'll apply at the register me her open open seating open seating
wherever you sit on the boat it's yours no you don't understand i'm gonna sit here this is where
i'm sitting now no you don't understand i own this boat now i'm sitting on it no no it's a sale for
ships oh my god enter hay scoops at checkout losing everything boy that did not go well
oh boy stop my ship sales buyer beware
i realized uh this week i was having a conversation with a friend of mine this week
and i realized that there is something that happens to me uh with some regularity that i
don't think happens to other people uh i think in most cases ever in their lives happy beginnings
happy beginnings
okay happy beginnings just because is it just hold on just because because i'm just gonna push
through it i went back into verizon the next day because the only one who didn't have a phone
working i said is there such thing as an e-sim card they said yes they sat there took a half
hour to repair my phone and i said how much do i owe you they said you gave me cupcakes yesterday
don't worry about it and so i whatever they're gonna charge me that's the whole fucking story
i was trying to get to and that's why i don't give a shit about the 12 credit okay go ahead
that's a win right no i'm sorry we're out of time matt that story carried us all over all three uh
parts of the show here uh sorry everybody uh we're actually out of time we can't do any more
episodes we used all of our time for all future episodes on that story the whole so i'll see you
later everybody uh i can't even play the outro music i'm sorry i would but uh what happens
everybody turn off your podcast listening devices constrained by our pretend constraints
what is your uh what what's going on jacob what happens to you that doesn't happen to other people
i uh get accused uh probably weekly of giving someone a false name
whoa oh my name is so common yeah jacob smith i get accused almost weekly of giving a false
name to people i have never been accused of that so people go like no no no what's your real name
yes like in what environments like if i have to give a name for anything
like a valet yeah like a valet parking starbucks anything anything like that if i have to give a
name and uh it's like going up for a reservation uh party of two for alan smithy please and they're
like what yeah well it does read it reads pretend i mean i'm not convinced it's your name you
shouldn't wait we just learned this lesson so we get to put it in action right away is it your real
name
all right
breaking news
breaking news who could say yeah like like i'll drop a car off at the valet and then they'll be
like oh we need uh we need a last name for the ticket smith and they will just stand there and
look at me and not move their pen at all to write my name down yeah no no we like we've heard it
all dickhead what's your name yeah and they will like i'll get like i'll often get like an eye roll
or or anything and i'll be like i it's common because a lot of us are named smith i don't know
what to tell you okay jacob so now you need to take on like a bob dylan jack frost type vibe here
you need okay you need you need a day-to-day events like that where you're getting reservations
or uh valets you need a pseudonym or a nom de plume if you will that will somehow at least
ring less false than jacob smith
okay okay sir antoine no no a lot of people know they're knights a lot of people don't go don't go
you know putting a hat on the hat here don't don't make this into too flowery all right no no i've
been jacob smith my whole life i'm going flowery let's go to the chat here actually just the first
name what what does jacob look like you see a guy who looks like jacob approaching give give us some
latter-day scoop is already saying hire him
i like that are you getting a gary and a peter alex alex okay so far i think hiram twatberger is
winning but let's see hiram twatberger oh sebastian thank you canadian scoop i do like
saying my name is sebastian george jetson you should go by paul mattingly that's a good one
i mean name mattingly solid choice oh any cheek is right you should go by murray
murray oh of course that's what i should do what's your name murray murray murray here's my
second suggestion your last name should be a name really known in town
so it should either be like win or green spun or whatever you want to you want to really try
just wink and nod it like yeah i'm gonna park your car it's like sure no problem murray win
and they gotta go like wait is he a fucking win-win is he who knows and you gotta put everyone on
their toes you gotta make sure murray riviera yeah yeah yeah i don't know if newton's strong
enough for wayne newton so i think you have to go straight wayne newton oh yeah the third the third
you have to go wayne newton junior yeah no who are the who are the ones who used to own
the palms and all that oh oh oh the uh the maloof's that's it oh murray maloof
that is that will get you that might get you some stuff that might i'll get a license plate
that just says third maloof third loof third loof
maloof three
murray maloof holy shit maloof is great nobody's gonna bat an eye at murray maloof in las vegas
i won't get a single look with murray maloof and in the early 90s
comedy
movie of this of course you end up uh being uh kidnapped and thrown in the trunk because
oh murray maloof that's it and there's a hilarious stream of hijinks that gets me out of it how hard
is it to get a player's card with murray maloof on it from hard you need a fucking id i think i
think for me impossible how hard is it to get an id that says murray maloof
if only we do anyone they could put together an id for me with pictures they already have of me
murray circus circus
murray circus
i was thinking about uh just goodwin my name is uh jacob goodwin you know murray goodwin
i used to get accused of i used to get accused of dying my beard when i had a red beard
uh-huh now i do dye my beard and no one brings it up um yeah but uh
um but uh like how do you react because i used to really like i used the first time the first
few times it happened i was really like what the what do you what are you talking to me about
like does it really throw you i am always ready for it now okay i'm i'm ready for it so i literally
i i just i see the interaction coming uh if it's like i we valet we live in vegas we valet our cars
more than than people in a lot of other places do so i keep going back to valets that's why we're
just we're around valets a lot and uh so like i'll see the i'll see it's like oh this is a this
is a valet that i don't know in a place that i may be a regular at or whatever and uh i'll see it's
the kind of eye roll or the kind of look and i'll just in in an effort to keep it moving
i'm ready to just keep the keep the process going like no no write it down it's smith i
promise that's the real name let's go really okay do you have your license handy are you
ready to like fling your license at them or something i'm not i'm not that no i'm not that
far um all right how about candy venom candy venom as your new hip street name and then see
test yourself see
keep your same energy where you're like i know i know write it down like you know that's it
candy write it down yeah i know it's common you you're you have like eight candy venoms in the
lot right now i get it all right it's it's calm it's it's it's common for a reason a lot of us
are named candy venom i don't know what to tell you candy was the most popular name when i was
born a boy uh in nevada every boy was named candy for a week it was the candy crush uh
game was all the rage oh sure everybody was uh and then venom of course america's number one
favorite spider-man villain that's why he is uh matt sun's favorite villain
american oh man american america so i want you guys to think about uh just just be aware of it
keeping the back of your mind over the next few weeks uh i want i want reports of things that
happen to you that you don't think happen to you that you don't think happen to you that you don't
other people that's a good one oh i've already preferably mundane this is a good scoop mail thing
too that is a good one because i have already just oh yeah yeah you're not talking to me you're
talking to our listeners yeah i'm talking to you buddy yeah but like you already know all stuff
about each other uh like i uh our neighbor uh chris who we all know is chris lash he just moved
into my neighborhood oh nice and i haven't talked to him yet i want to keep i forget came to tell
him like hey you and i are first and last name people we are always introduced as first and last
people talk about us um i think chris lash and sj are friends from before chris moved to vegas oh
wow yeah i think sj i think chris is the one i think sj and chris did a gig together uh like
shortly before he moved out to vegas and then he moved here and just blew up yeah uh yeah he's he
works like crazy here in town oh yeah he's we should say chris lash is a wonderful musician
here in vegas yes not who we should probably talk about in the future but i think chris lash is a
wonderful musician yeah i think chris lash is a wonderful musician yeah i think chris lash is a
wonderful musician yeah well i tell you what and this is very early they literally just had like
one meeting but you know for fun for one of the quiz shows they decided to do a version of weekend
at bernie's the musical where they did like a 10 minute version of the musical and now it was so
fun to work on they they want to actually work on weekend at bernie's the musical oh good so they've
only had one meeting but i can't wait it's casey uh sarah and chris and so uh it's going i just had
a fucking realization last night this is just a personal thing it doesn't help our our podcast at
all but i just had a personal realization last night that made me so happy and that is uh casey
wilson and i are on the same schedule at absent these days oh nice and that means that the next
time they do a a quiz show it'll be on one of my off nights and i'll be able to go go play oh very
nice i was i really just thought about this last night i was so happy to realize that well i guess
sarah has to ross's show i got to do the show with your wife that's right yeah i heard about it
i heard it went well i saw a little bit of video from it it was super i heard your set uh went very
well it did it went very well i was so happy after doing like three corporates in a row that i was
oh my best just just letting loose uh it was really really funny um it was super fun i also
had like awesome people hop up uh so you know for straightish jacket escape uh i had a a gay guy and
raise their hands for who are the straightest guys in the room.
And they came up, and they were just hysterical.
You know, like, when audience members try to be funny,
and they aren't, it sucks.
If they're funny, it's not.
Great.
I laid out, and they just, she just took over.
At one point.
Smooth sailing.
You know, I come up, I got the shackles stuck between my legs.
And a guy in the back just goes, oh, balls.
Like that, like that.
And I was like, that's funny, right?
Like, this is funny.
And I go, and I let her go, I would tip my cap to you, sir.
But obviously, you know, and I just show that my hands are stuck between my legs.
And the girl just walks over and just doffs an invisible cap over my head.
Just tips my cap for me.
Hilarious.
Well done.
I was like, this is great.
Is this a burlesque performer that you know?
No.
I just, I just, I met her that night.
Oh, that's great.
Shay was her name.
Yeah, yeah, she was great.
Who was it?
Nice.
Shay.
Yeah.
Okay.
She's named after a stadium.
Oh, you should give that as your name.
I was going to say, I should have asked if that was her real name.
She gave me a fucking valet name.
She gave me a fucking fake valet name.
Yes, I'm Shay Stadium of the Connecticut Stadiums.
You know, we have all that stadium money.
We have all that stadium money.
How much stadium money do you have?
But, yeah.
Do we have two knitting scoops?
We do.
We have two knitting.
This is good.
I love it.
It's a higher compliment than when we're told that people, people like to, people tell me
like straight confidently.
Like, I fall asleep to you all the time.
And I don't know how to take that as a compliment.
You should take it as a compliment.
I said that, I said that to Joel Hodgson.
He did not take it as a compliment on Twitter.
But that's because he couldn't hear the nuance and love in my voice.
That's right.
I live by those movies.
But knowing, I think knowing that people knit to us is maybe, that is the highest compliment, I think.
It's a pretty high compliment.
I can see multiple knitters.
It is very relaxing.
David Sorensen, what do you do with your hands, buddy?
Get to knitting.
Go.
Come on.
Let's go.
There he goes.
He's doing it.
Mattingly, what are you doing with your hands?
Losing at Jock vs. Nerd.
Boo!
You want to do a little Jock vs. Nerd action?
Oh, am I?
Fuck.
Fuck yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Excellent.
Hunt, hunt, hunt for balls.
Balls.
On the hunt for balls.
Oh!
All right.
Real quick.
Two things.
First of all.
Okay.
It's colder than a witch's tit out here in fucking Pittsburgh.
It's so...
Paul Mattingly's favorite saying, everybody drink.
But you love your governor, so lucky you.
We do have a pretty good governor.
It's so cold out here.
Uh, that's why I'm literally wearing a jacket because we have heater on in the house.
It's just, it's cold.
It's so, so cold.
It's been bitterly cold for days and the, the cold is just seeping into the bones of the
home at this point.
Uh-huh.
Uh, and then also.
We have stopped, we have stopped the show.
Paul is cold.
I don't know if you saw, but the final reveal has been made.
Uh, the Pokemon.
On the Masked Singer?
The Pokemon crossover with Lego.
The first three sets have been revealed.
Oh.
Did you see?
Pokemon Lego?
Yes.
There's new Pokemon Lego?
I have not seen, no.
So, Mega Bloks, which is the company owned by Mattel, which is one of their rivals, they
had the license for a while and they were making Pokemon Legos.
So now the Pokemon company is working in tandem with Lego.
Can you, uh, put a guess out there as to what the biggest set of the, it's Charizard, uh,
Venusaur, and Blastoise in a big diorama.
What is your price tag you think might be on that?
Uh, three piece, big display set.
Oh, I thought you were going to have us guess what they were, but you named the characters
because I was all ready to guess.
Um, there's two other sets.
I can have you guess.
Okay.
Well, I wouldn't have been able to name any of the characters anyway.
Well, what do you think?
I was going to guess either Riachu, Pinky Rat, Foxfire, or Hermie.
Uh.
I'm reading them off my phone.
No.
Um, okay.
Pikachu, of course.
Riachu is an evolution of Pikachu.
You could make a Riachu out of that Pikachu.
Yeah.
Riachu is an evolution of Pikachu.
Okay.
Price tag for all three of them is a Lego build.
It's a, it's a, it's a one piece.
It's the three big bads from the original game in a, in a large display base.
Big.
It's big, big.
And like, it's pretty big.
So a lot of pieces.
It's big.
It's a big, it's a big set.
What is your, what is your price tag guess for this big Pokemon Lego set?
$20.
I mean, it's going to be 20 bucks.
All right.
Good guess.
I'm seeing $350.
I'm seeing $495 in the scoop here.
$1,000 is guessed by Andy.
$4.95.
I think it'd be more than that.
Dave Sorensen is.
Is it limited?
Is it?
Are they only making blank amounts?
No, it's not limited.
No.
Okay.
Oh, that is a great hat, Yarn and Sticks.
That is a great hat you just made.
That is a nice looking hat.
That's really cool.
I would pay.
How much is it?
I just, two birds for no reason.
I would, I would, I would pay three.
Oh, the whole house.
The whole hat is middle fingers.
Because it's all birds.
It's a bunch of hat middle fingers.
See, it fools you.
Oh.
That's a nice cozy hat to wear to a protest in Minnesota right now.
Yeah.
That's exactly it.
Okay.
So, I'm going to guess that I would, I would do five Yarn and Sticks hats for that Pikachu.
I mean, that's good.
Oh, easily.
Good trade.
I don't know what the little sets are going for.
Now, the big set is actually priced to move at $650.
God damn it.
I know.
And this is the thing, right?
Like, Pokemon is very much a kid-oriented brand, or it was for a time.
And Lego also, kid-oriented brand for a time.
But this is a, this is a specific product based at adult collectors.
Yeah.
And so, you could, they even asked in like an AMA, and people were like, is this a Lego
set for kids?
And they're like, nope.
This is for adults.
Okay.
So, they, you know, they acknowledged it at least.
Adult collectors.
Yeah.
No, no yucking anyone's yum.
No, you know, kink shaming, no whatever.
But like, if you bring a possible lover back to your house, and they're going to touch
the thing, you go, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That was $650.
Like, I feel like, I feel like the date is over.
No, I think the date might be over if that's the reaction.
If you don't care that they touch your $650 Charizard, I think that makes you cool.
who oh that was like because i have a lego i have a lego batmobile on my bar at the at the house
yeah yeah and uh and you're always going
but like a friend we were having we had people over one day and uh one of our friends was over
and they had one of their kids or they had their their son here with them and uh their son was you
know of course uh super polite kid great kid uh young kid goes can i can i play with the batmobile
on the bar of course yeah take it down hand it to him put on the floor walk away i just got like
some little moving parts and stuff on it and i come back over there a few minutes later and the
kiddo and his dad are both there and the dad is holding the batmobile and he goes he was he was
twisting a thing in here and now it won't work to twist it anymore i think he i think he might
have broken it uh so sorry
i was like oh i freaked the fuck out i was like no no i'm not i'm very happy that your kid is
playing with the batmobile and i don't care if it's it's a lego like it come here kid you broke
my toy you broke my fucking please please do not think that i'm doing the no no no thing on you
keep playing with it i don't care it's fine it's fine it's fine here's a bill you can pay an
installment i'll send you a venmo request don't worry about it don't worry about it don't worry
about it not a big deal i mean they're canceled uh you can't get the new ones anymore but i think
they still have some on ebay uh you know it's big money but you know you can you can you're
gonna be out like 1200 something like that yeah well that is the other thing too is matt you you
make the point you know of of someone's sees that in a possible partner's yeah yeah a social
situation and what's their reaction but you have to also know that lego
as an investment have appreciated at a rate greater than even gold and that is true
the evaluation of lego is greater even than gold in the last what else is the last like 15
this is at least the 20th time paul has told us this no no maybe maybe twice i've told you that
let's do a little jock versus nerd we've got a jock versus nerd today
from uh oh shit i can't see it uh from raisenberg yeah and it's all about 2025 this is a uh a
scooperty in in look back oh god to the year 2025 i just want to know i'll be taking free
at the cars i want you to know that every time sarah and i take a call from a financial planner
i always say you have lego in the portfolio and if they say no i fucking hang up the phone every
time hang right up and he's and i tell you right up i reiterate i say no physical lego i want
you to buy sets and vault them for me please because that's where the fucking money is i don't
care about their stock i want to be able to resell animal crossing lego sets in 25 years
for 10 times their purchase price thank you
the categories are sports movies and tv music culture matt you're up first what you want i'll
200 please this team won the wnba championship for the third time in four years that would be
our own las vegas aces the las vegas aces of course take that lombardo i don't know what that means
stay down i think he's happy about it honestly oh yeah good point seems like it's something to
be happy about uh paul i'll try movies and tv please for 200 on february 16th nbc aired a three
hour live broadcast to celebrate this show
50th anniversary oh
oh uh snl i was like what are you doing yes i'm sorry it's saturday night live saturday night live
i was i was trying to remember i was like uh did they do a special on good morning america or some
shit um the simpsons yeah well i'll try a culture for 200 this numeric pair was the dictionaries dot
was dictionary.com
word of the year really
i guess that's a word of the year it's got to be yeah word of the year yeah six seven i guess
that's the word of the year man it is strange times for 69 jokes don't even get kids to raise
an eyebrow anymore no no not a bit no i mean it's all over the internet who can a 69 joke
that's just innuendo you go online it's right there ain't no jokes anymore i mean it's not
no jokes no like back in our day it was like when you started to think about it it was like
oh my god the possibilities but if you're eight years old now you've seen every iteration possible
you're just if you if you somebody mentioned 69 too you're just thinking of the last porno that
you watched were they 69 exactly exactly exactly you're up uh sorry i was just picturing my kids
watching porn um circles and circles circles and circles uh they're just they're just doing
illustrator and just drawing um
photoshop away from them if we could actually just draw something that we would get off on
like that'd be pretty that'd be pretty great you can't you can't do that no oh no no sorry you guys
don't have that superpower that's why paul's christmas book is so sticky every every woman
i draw just looks at me like i'm ugly and i lower my self-esteem
i'll take sports 400 please
this man won the third annual las vegas grand pricks winning the race for the second time
third annual uh
this is this is nevada's own joe lombardo uh uh this is uh max for stopping
that's right max verstoppen
paul
max for speeding up uh movies and tv please for 400 this canadian sports romance television series
is the surprise hit of the 2025 holiday season oh oh canadian sports romance television series
is in quotes by the way yeah heated rivalry oh i was about to say i was about to say hot on the ice
but i knew that wasn't it it wasn't hot on the ice
on the ice i was uh hot ice equals water i see hot i see hot broke back goons
broke back goons holy shit broke back goon and oh that has a double meaning that has a double meaning
sorry i just drew something i found very alluring
no yeah sure you gotta take care of that i have to tend to this raging boner that i just induced
with a camera i have to tend to this raging boner that i just induced with a camera i have to tend to
cartoon i made i'll do movies and tv for 600 this movie took home five oscars including best picture
at the 2025 academy awards oh man fuck i'm laughing i know it's like we just don't give a shit about
the oscars anymore fuck i have no idea not even a little bit of an idea i will pass matt man i'm
mad i even listen like a showbiz podcast uh
when they go over this stuff i know i'll know it when i hear it i work in show business i work in
show business i know show business i know oscar i'm murray maloof i should know this i probably
produced it fuck i'm here to kidnap you oh damn it uh pass i i'm gonna kick myself to pass paul
five oscars this thing won including
best picture
well what even came out last year i i don't know man i just go i only see movies with my
that my kids want to see and it's just citizen kane over and over again titanic reboots is leon
i don't even like it wasn't avatar 3 i mean oh i know it now but i can't remember the name
do you i'm trying to think of
any prestige type movies no it wasn't it wasn't that's a different movie it's about magic oh was
it it's the stripper the russian stripper stripping russian mafia movie oh i don't even know what that
is me either pass let's see what it is what is it matt i'm trying to remember the name of it but i
know the i know the first name of the actor anora that's it yeah anora anora ignora ignora is what i
did to that movie i did matt um how the fuck does i didn't even know that movie existed here's the
thing not only that when an oscar it's about a stripper who gets wrapped up with the russian mob
it checks all of my boxes and i still haven't watched it i still haven't like an oscar winning
movie about a russian stripper and the mob it checks it checks all of your boxes or it rushes
all of your boxes it ukraines all of his boxes you crane your neck to see an ignora it two knuckles
all of my boxes oh two knuckle oh the country of two knuckle matt you're up
sorry i heard your lego sculpture in two knuckle we'd be aggressively pet sculptures
that's where balky's cousins are from he's from two knuckle i am from two knuckle sports for six
hundred please this basketball star was named time magazine's 2025 athlete of the year tiger
tiger woods y'all brani james uh brani james dio james brani james oh brani james and ronnie
james dio of course both ronnie james dio both are as good at playing basketball
stay down ronnie james dio he will not good at basketball he will stay down he is dead as
dillinger i am debating you know uh it could be luca it could be uh-huh she lived on the second
floor yeah second floor luca she lived upstairs from you it should be alexander but will time like
do you mean like time doesn't like this is a true sports magazine was it kobe sga right they go kobe
did they go like if they went to any
if they went to any card collection uh convention that it's still kobe uh yeah kobe still rules
at kobe's the hot card collectible now huh yeah always hotter than jordan i'm gonna go
with jake elders alexander no wait black mom no wait no wait okay what it's caitlyn clark
there it is ah aja wilson of the las vegas aces oh wow
well good that's actually well deserved she's a three-time mvp i actually apologies to aja for
not knowing that i actually forgot i actually forgot to ask i want to i wanted a jersey of
hers for christmas and i should have asked for it oh yeah yeah you don't get what you don't ask for
matt that's true it's true that's true i just looked online yeah it's 650 dollars
that is pricey you get at least one lego set for that paul almost uh movies and tv closing it out
this movie generated the highest domestic gross of any film released in 2025 taking in 423 million
nine hundred forty nine thousand one hundred ninety five dollars what was the big wiener
anora no i guess it's gotta been uh
the oz movie right wicked for good wait careful careful with your subtitles wicked for good is
the is the new one
yeah as the other one still was still going on in 2025 was that both
no i think the other one was released in 24 i think the first i think the first
oz movie was 24 yeah i'll pass because i really don't know for sure so oh that shit that goes to
me um i i thought it was the new avatar movie you might be right yeah yeah uh i think that's
avatar last year or was that just it came out in december did it okay yeah fire i'll guess that one
avatar 3 no we're all wrong it's a minecraft movie oh we all forgot about the chicken jockey
fiasco yeah fiasco yeah whenever chicken jockey showed up on the screen everybody would lose
their shit and trash the theater yeah that sounds like a wonderful uh artistic event
i mean fiasco it sounds it sounds a bit like rocky horror picture show so i can't i don't
hate it right oh it's me i'll do uh sports for 800 this player won the 2020 2025 heisman trophy
if this is paul uh name any active college football player i would still not be able to do
it i would not be able to do it i have cut football out of my brain and this is college
football i know
and that's an even less thing yeah uh he just won the heisman he plays for indiana
uh he's probably gonna play for the raiders next year
uh do i have to give his first name can i just give his last name no i'll give you points for
his last name all right mendoza mendoza yeah fernando mendoza forgot fernando i forgot fernando
that's the enemy
look we should all get to know that name he's going to be playing here so we need yeah he's
gonna be in the silver and black next year
matt you're up i need to make up some points here yeah oh yeah score check well we're all
pretty close paul's got 600 i've got 200 matt has zero uh there's still two daily doubles
seven questions anybody's game well you know me and culture let's do culture true how can
there be any answers in 2025 there was no culture in 2025
this power couple announced their engagement with the tagline your english teacher and your
gym teacher are getting married uh this is uh travis kelsey and paula abdul ah yes um travis
kelsey and taylor swift that's right i did not know that i didn't hear that quote paul it was
dumb then it's dumb now yep i agree for 200 all right daily double
you
give paul some distance performer was spotify's most streamed artist of 2025 dethroning taylor
swift oh youtuber cg5
who beat taylor swift for streams oh my this is where we find out that the weekend
just snuck in there and had so many streaming listens that we just didn't know about
i mean no that wouldn't no i would think maybe charlie xcx but that was 2024 when she was rocking
up on it and i don't think she ever dethroned taylor swift there are two two two prominent
guesses in the chat since it's a daily double and you have to guess oh some people are saying
sarah carpenter because of the popularity of stranger things and other people are showing
uh bad bunny oh it's bad that's my guess it's bad my guess is bad bunny yeah he's he's big big big
bad yeah yeah you going bad bunny i am let's see it is bad bunny yeah well done doc uh yeah i was
like i i bet that the whole uh super bowl controversy really uh got him a lot of a lot
of listeners yeah apparently he's really really good so oh no he's fantastic of course might have
also exposed some some some racism in this nation uh what what what what are you talking about
look let's just eat regular hamburger buns and talk about it wait would you say this nation you
mean this one this nation wherein my own citizenship might be in jeopardy what are you talking about
i'm just gonna ignore matt and whatever craziness he's talking about and just move on to culture
for 600 god damn it andy byron and kristin cabot are best known for the role they played in this
2025 event
andy byron shit i don't know pass matt andy byron and kristin cabot cabot i said cabot but i don't
know c-a-b-o-t this is culture played in this yes event uh new year's eve i know that's i'm like
uh the west virginia
state house elections pass paul a pass let's see coldplay kiss cam couple oh yes
infamous infamous coldplay kiss cam couple matt infamous um culture 800 please let's see
after thieves stole 102 million dollars in jewels from the louvre in paris
france it was reported the password for the museum surveillance system was blank damn it i knew
all the factors that laid out in the question and then then i knew i knew it was jules the amount in
the louvre but i think that's it matt the password no it was password no the jewels well it might be
password it's either password or louvre i think ah that's it
that's it is the password
um or or password it's one of the other i'll pass you can take home all the money oh no i don't want
to try guess i don't know i think it's the louvre but i'm not 100 now now you got me guessing
i think it was louvre it was sticky going lou it was sticky cheese if the eye was a one
and the keys and the cheese were three let's see
i heard it was the louvre
i gave you i told matt i told matt it was the louvre
paul you got music for four six or eight hundred one of them's a daily double and that one could
fuck you up well i guess i might as well go out big with 800 please music for 800 in may 2025 the
song wasted love performed by jj and written by him along with tedora spirit and thomas turner
won the eurovision song contest for which country oh that's uh
oh shoot who won the eurovision i don't pass i don't know oh that passes to me there was
a uh large amount of conversation this year about eurovision at work uh with all of the
europeans and everybody that i was there really there was a ton of conversation about this event
oh i didn't listen to any of it i also did not follow the story at all um
is my final answer pass good austria that's right i didn't remember that austrian went yodeling
that's right that's me i got music for 400 or 600 matt has 400 i have 200 paul has 2000 so i'm
probably not going to catch paul uh let's see i'll try to try to get some points on matt here and get
second place music for 600 name any of the eight artists that were nominated for best new artist at
the 2025 grammy awards
shit
is my answer to that question ice spice uh i don't think that's even this year
um
um yeah i don't know pass matt i don't know paul pass
chaperone was this year oh motherfucker benson boone sabrina carpenter oh this is all i i would
have thought that several of those well that's because the grammys are behind the fucking time
i was gonna say sabrina carpenter's been around for a minute yeah that's dochi's been around for
a minute i feel better about not getting this question right now i'm not gonna get this question
right now yeah i recognize at least most of the teddy swims yeah he oh no we're back from our
technical problem uh oh yeah none of his guests on that one oh our matt closing out the category
end the game that paul is definitely winning and matt is gonna probably get second place it's a
daily double we'll have to get this so i get third place so there's stakes here oh that's true yeah
we got stakes this song began 2025 at number one on the billboard hot 100 and fun fact it is the
number one song on the day i am writing this scoopity 12 10 25 that's not a helpful hint at
all well it means it was number one for either a long time or twice billboard hot 100 oh i know it
is this a sabrina carpenter song i don't think so i think this is a song that comes around
in december oh oh oh uh uh uh amy winehouse is no uh
amy winehouse is they try to make me go to rehab and i say merry christmas
i could go to rehab i gotta wrap presents and no no no um pariah carries all i want for christmas
all i want for christmas is you matt that's right and that is the game
ball wins with 2 000 points matt's insane with 800 i'm in third with 200 that's from rum raisenberg
and that was 2025 in retrospective that's a great scoopity good job nicely done rum raisenberg
uh how much we don't remember but uh you know like you know maybe i'm i'm a little embarrassed
that i've never heard of the best picture winner that's yeah i hadn't heard of it either
although i'm not as embarrassed as they should be well 2020 was famous
this is why i listen to my showbiz podcast is that like it was famously hampered by the
this is still the echoes of the writer's strike uh or the actor's right so they couldn't get
enough stuff into production so movie theaters were pissed about how little product was coming
to the pipeline in 2025 it was a bad year for tv too um it's just like everything was so delayed
from all the strikes great year for keeler though that pluribus is just taking off he's doing great
hey i see paul chambered up there i don't think he's paul a full proper shout out
but i had a i had a uh a corporate gig in south bend and he basically lives he lives in south
bend not basically he lives in south bend um but he basically stepped up as my advanced man
he he oh wow he helped get stuff to to the venue that need to be he was there at the venue before
i got there he introduced himself to the person running the venue and like he had me all set i
like walked in and everything was like set up for me because paul did everything and it was really
great it was it was awesome and just oh awesome further proof that just our podcast audiences are
amazing
so there you go yeah we have the best listeners he'd been in the turn with his son before so that
was very nice to see him again yeah speaking of our listeners that uh scoopery was from a listener
if you want to make a scoopery or any kind of other jock versus nerd that we do on this show
hey scoops.com is where you can go head over to hey scoops.com you can also send us some scoop
mail from that page do all the things over there at hey scoops.com do it now please and i want to
thank the following people who support us over on our patreon page let's do it i would like to find
these people all uh bought lego back when you just buy a pair of socks for lego and now i can't
believe how much it's worth today um that's aaron boyd aaron abe sloan adam goff adam ribzik
yep you nailed it and then uh adam stickney alex morehead anarcho scupo andrea anderson
uh andrew langmead andrew also chuck andy hayworth angela chan and smith anton jernberg
aramis that's it aramis czar barry rowe bart vonk bj joyer and ben gal thank you so much
these people have a sim card corruption error ben sherman big load of scoop big sexy butters
bill newton black people escape bo campbell bobby becerra brendan light brendan allen
brian emra brian galuta brian lehman brian richard brian t wolf brian gregston brian
traves bull scoop callie ghost carmen perry carolyn albert and carson lomas and the following scoops
are americans and that's why they like their bread white that's caven o'hara chaotic clumsy
charles eaton charles ullman uh charlie thompson chris depero chris ellis chris hoffsetter chris
jackson chris roberts chris the micro scoop christine phillips christopher hayworth christopher
linda i think cj magnata coffee bean scoop cory owens corianna chimora court myers crocodile scoop
and daniel loser thank you so much that's it jacob that's a little dex feel a little shy over here are
we sure we have a lot of people it does uh i was about to say we we have uh new list stuff going on
we have new stuff going on from patreon uh i am looking into it this list feels light oh oh yeah
bud yeah it's like yeah no i was i was looking at it yesterday
and and yeah yeah but yeah we're gonna figure all this out we'll get there if you're new if you or
if you haven't been around for an episode or two uh annie is no longer with us our our uh long she's
alive she's alive she's alive yeah yeah she's with us capital u she's not with us lowercase
uh yeah yeah no but she's she's been with us with us for years and years we love annie
uh but she has moved on and uh yeah so we are figuring out new lists and all of that stuff
on our own now
with uh slaking fools help as well so yeah uh yeah so we'll we'll keep yeah we're gonna get it
all figured out and yeah it'll all be there if you it'll all get put together if you want to be
part of the exclusive technical error thank you list uh for this month then you want to get over
to preachingfun.com it's like the tier that fits your budget today come visit
or if you like matt donnelly you're buying eight different types of hamburger buns to feed his
family go to farts in a bag dot biz
that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preachingfun.com it does take you over to our
patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air we
are dependent on our patreon subscribers so please if you think this show is worth more than zero
dollars preachingfun.com farts in a bag dot biz that's where you can go i'm just still it's just
rattling around in my head like how many different types of hamburger buns does matt that's what i
do it really throws people for a loop right where i go uh i'm making barbecue burgers uh what kind
of bun do you want what kind how do you take your bun how do you take your bun i think yeah how do
you take my bun it's gonna be just is there preparation to the bun do you do you offer
grilling or toasting i try to i toast i toast the bun on the grill yeah that's jay donnelly has a
great many amenities i was gonna grill the bun i've grilled the buns in the past but i realize
like i'm like i don't want to get my kids in the habit of having extra butter and cholesterol on
their already cheesy burger so do you steam the bun is enough what are you talking don't get him
having delicious food you don't want to ruin their palates is that it you want to keep them american
he don't want to shovel butter and salt into their mouth uh all the time which does make
him less american it does it does but to quote jeff goldblum butter finds a way butter does find a
way all right thanks for us everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
yes
you soon
you
I'm
young donnelly it is blatantly egotistically i'm
trying to compete with like in and out and like other other fast have you have you bested those
other fast food places thus far i want them to say i'm gonna say hey why don't i make burgers
tonight i want the kids to go oh awesome you know like that's the instead of why don't we go out for
burgers that's it i'm trying to go like or we go in and out is the other thing that can pop up right
so that's what i don't want well so far you've got him to say i demand pretzel or don't serve me that
french shit so you're halfway there
i'm gonna do a basically a bun flight uh next time we'll just do
here are sir's choices for the evening
please make your selection and i will go back to the kitchen
this one is awfully yeasty
yeah yeah yeah
these buns here don't don't
jump right into this yeasty mess
this is real yeasty this one's real yeasty careful careful hill too much yeast
this is this now this one is this one is whole grain over here this one you don't want to jump
straight to whole grain either this is from an artisanal sourdough starter that began in 1874
you believe that which is almost as old as your mom you are tasting revolutionary bread basically
Bye.