Oh hello there, I am so glad you're here. I want to take this opportunity to thank the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers. It's a new month, we don't have a new list just yet, but we will thank each and every Ice Cream Truck Driver.
Before the show starts, this part of the show right here, on a future show, not this show, this show we're already recording now, and I don't have the list yet.
But thank you to all you Ice Cream Truck Drivers out there, those are the folks that deliver that fucking Ice Cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
If you would like to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and I sure hope you do, because that Ice Cream needs a driving.
Head over to PreachingFun.com, PreachingFun.com is where you can sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
I just feel like you say-
Here's the show!
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Hey, let's go!
That's better.
Hey, if you want to join the Scoop Fantasy Football League, Jacob and I are playing.
Just go over to Scoop Fantasy Football League group on Facebook, and ask to be invited into the group, and Matt Daugherty will take care of you.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social, sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly, sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Daugherty, and in Las Vegas too, let's check out the audio guys, we're PreachingFun.
Preaching for the fun.
I'm not anywhere until August 20th to 24th, I'll be in the Magic Castle.
Nice.
And then, then someone went to like give me a weekend at a Magic Club, and I looked at September, October, November, December, and I was like, I can come in January.
Oh, you're booked.
I am booked.
That's wonderful.
Yes, it is good, it is good, no complaints, no complaints.
Now, you're home for a little bit then, for like a week or two.
Yes.
And are the boys still out of school right now?
Right, as the last week, they start school August 11th.
Okay, so you're finally putting your boys in school.
Yeah, the homeschooling thing turned out to be, you know, it's for some people.
Yeah, yeah, no, I get you.
But it turns out if I'm on a cruise ship, you know, virtual learning from me on a cruise ship is not really the best way to...
Oh, can you imagine any of us just homeschooling in general? Just homeschooling anyone's children.
Look, we went through the pandemic, so every parent has a taste of what they'd be like as a homeschooling teacher, no matter what.
And part of it was a little, I mean, as it was daunting for all of us, it was exciting at some point.
Like at one point we were like on our own for a couple of weeks while the schools figured out what they were doing.
We were like diving in at home trying to figure out ways to like do cool stuff, like anything our kids were curious about.
Turns out there's a YouTube documentary on something or the other.
That's true.
Whatever. And so we did for a little while have like we're going to watch an educational documentary a day.
We did work on their stuff.
The strange thing was that in the panic of, and maybe other parents relate, in the panic of schools getting their shit together,
originally they just put together work packets for the parents to do at home.
Right, I remember that.
And then they switched to giving everyone a computer and doing virtual classrooms with the teachers in the classrooms.
And the virtual classrooms with a kindergartner and a first grader were useless.
Yeah.
And the work packet stuff was awesome.
Like I actually liked when they were just handing us different work packets to do at home.
Yeah, you could teach from that, sure.
Like it was really great.
And so I basically remember like a month into like the virtual classrooms and watching my kids just like, you know,
when like kids are so bored, they're like crying with boredom, like they're just like aching with boredom.
Like I was just like.
I see that happen automatically every now and then too.
On this show, on this show.
I'm not immune.
I was like, I wish we were just working on the packet stuff.
But I guess for people who actually had to like work work and not just cry and hope that entertainment wasn't over as a thing.
Those people were more and more grateful for the virtual classrooms.
That's probably true.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you guys up on the descendants?
You guys up on all the zombies movies on all the Disney on the Disney Channel?
I am not.
The descendants are doing zombies right now.
There's two franchises in the Disney world.
One is called Descendants and one is called Zombies.
Zombies is like the B franchise.
Descendants.
Like last year, I went to the kids Halloween parade and I was like, why is everybody wearing dressed as I was like, is everyone dressed like Deadpool?
And turns out no, no, they're all dressed as this character Red from Descendants.
Yeah.
And his thing, my my oldest kid didn't get in either one of them.
My youngest got into the zombies thing.
But then Kimmy Gatewood, Apple sister.
Yes.
Got hired to direct the latest Descendants movie.
Oh, wow.
And then all of the Disney, right?
So then all of a sudden there's these concerts with all the people from zombies and descendants doing live concerts across the nation.
And so Kimmy got everybody backstage passes.
So all the Apple, all the Apple children went to the concert and then went backstage and met everyone who's in Descendants and Zombies.
And the side effect of that is that it is way into it now.
All my kids listen to in the car like everywhere, it's like we're driving Arizona and back and driving them all to, you know, their soccer and drums and also their stuff for kids houses.
I am just listening constantly to Disney music and it is driving me insane.
Who is Red a descendant of?
Because they're all descendant from like famous heroes and villains of Disney.
Yes. And it's hysterical because in the show, they'll be like, and my dad, you know, you know, Maui or whatever, they go.
And everybody acts shocked when they find out a kid is related.
Like basically the show is just a parallel of like like a Beverly Hills Grammar School where like everybody just finds out that their parents work in show business one place or the other.
So every single character is a child of a major Disney character and they all have a wink to what there is.
And so Red is the child of the queen of hearts.
Ah, so OK, a bad person.
Most of them are. It's mostly the children of villains.
Yeah. But are they good children?
Yes, they go through their own adventures where they figure out whether they're going to be good or evil.
So it's runaways. That's cool.
Yeah, yeah. But Disney owns Marvel now.
So that's totally fine.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I mean, I'm fine with it.
I will not have you disparage the originality of them where they're rehashing all of them.
I don't know if Brian is writing credit on descendants.
He may that be great.
Who are the runaways children of of all kinds of Marvel villains?
Yeah. Yeah, but they're like mid-tier villains that you don't necessarily know that much about.
But I like that your point is that it is even more unoriginal feeling than it was already feeling.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, Matt. It's already not that good.
They're like we have two options.
We can either pretend to zap them and make them go back in time to children or we can say that they're children of the property we already own.
Yes. Cooper Nova girl in the chat.
Marvel, baby, is that making your dreams come true?
I never watch runaways. I never watch runaways either. I read it.
I can't speak to the quality. Oh, no, I can't speak to the quality of the show.
I'm not pleased. He's up motherfuckers.
Take a moment to puff on that pipe, you intellectual.
I've not heard the best things about the film adaptation.
I prefer to see it happen in the eye of my mind.
No, honestly. Yeah. No, no. I mean, it's a graphic novel.
I don't have those kinds of abilities, Jacob. I can't just read books. I need picture books.
Come on. Yeah, I read it.
But the thing is like it's it's Disney, right?
So they have like these crazy, you know, music and, you know, everything's a musical and that kind of stuff.
And it's all really well produced music.
Like some of them are catchy, which the snag is that it's all sung through the throats of very precocious children.
So like it's all like these really super like it could be like rap or R&B or like all these things that like a very popular music.
And then it's just like tiny children singing it.
And you're like, it's so weird. Yeah, it's kids bop.
And it really kind of makes me I'm like, is this a good thing or a bad thing?
Do you guys listen to kids bop? Did you go through a kids bop phase when I was younger now?
No, I mean, with the kid with your kids.
No, this is the part of like the things like I like I said, like my kids were born just after Frozen was popular.
And I was like so glad to not be you miss that listening to that on repeat.
And, you know, Moana didn't catch on as as feverishly as as that.
No. And then my kids got into like real music.
So they always used to switch from basically real music to like just YouTube, YouTubers, YouTube music, where they just sing about video games.
And some of that was pretty good. And some of that's just strange to me.
But they go back and forth. Is Hill still in his Gigi Allen phase?
Because I know he was way into that.
Wait, who was the drummer that you had to like wear raincoats and stuff to perform with him because he was so disgusting?
Well, Keith Moon, because he was always crazy with Ginger Baker. He was dangerous. Oh, I don't know. No, I don't know.
I don't know. No, never.
Anyway, anyway, whatever he did, he did all kinds of gross stuff on stage to, you know, he'll use it in the car used to fall asleep to Iron Man.
That was the way to get him to fall asleep was that he would just chill to Iron Man and the Sabbath Iron Man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, you know, and then we went and saw MJ the musical over the summer.
And so Michael Jackson music was dominating our household, which obviously gives me mixed emotions as a parent.
But the music is catchy, but the music is well made.
And so now I'm stuck in Disney produced weird music land.
Would you prefer the Disney or Michael Jackson?
Well, I would let me say I would not have liked someone getting a backstage pass for my children to meet Michael Jackson.
So let's just say let's start there. Oh, interesting, interesting. OK, OK.
We're different people. All right.
No, my only my only hope for the coming out of this phase is that my my my oldest is still in school of rock.
And so he is learning different rock songs on drums and he has a concert coming up.
I'm hoping that that music will take over the car soon.
That's what I'm hoping probably will. There you go.
Yeah, probably. What's his favorite music to play?
Like a favorite song to play or anything. Yeah.
I mean, like he plays like like Red Hot Chili Peppers, Weezer, trying to think what else they go through over there.
Yeah, he plays it. He plays a bunch of different stuff to destroy my sweater.
No. Weezer, man. Yeah.
I would love it if your son just started singing Weezer randomly all the time around me.
It would be so confusing, but so delightful.
When they first dropped, I had a class that I had to go to.
But at the record store down in Louisville, they were putting on a show in Louisville.
Yeah, like three dollars right when the Blue Album first hit.
And I was like, oh, I really wanted to go, but I didn't really know much about them.
And I had like, like I said, I had some other little responsibility.
But boy, if I could go back in time, I would tell me to go see Weezer for three dollars.
Yeah. So one thing we didn't get into last episode.
But I was debating whether to share it or not. But it was a low point for me.
I was when I was hosting Magic Live. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I basically we finished one of our shows and I said I'm going to have to go to the bathroom,
but I'm going to go downstairs because I don't want to hear what people think of the show in the bathroom across from the venue.
Oh, no. OK. Buddy, you're already overthinking this.
And also, like, take a walk, like get away, like go. OK, there you go.
I'm like, I'm going to go to the bathroom. What's the rule?
Just get out of the magic blocks. What? I don't know.
Oh, my my rule was always next county, next county.
Yeah. You couldn't say anything about the show or about the venue or the personnel until you got to the next county over.
Yeah. If you're on the road, that's a good that's a good rule.
Right. There is like some there is like some universally acknowledged like five blocks, ten blocks, something like that.
Even then, that always scares me because I because I go into a restaurant.
I'll go. I'm the guy that goes into the restaurant like 20 miles away and goes like, holy shit, that venue was terrible.
And then I hear from the next table over like, oh, you were at that venue. I do the tickets for that. Exactly.
Yeah. Well, I thought they wanted to hear the reactions to the show and reactions to people hearing me pee as well.
So I'm fighting it. I'm fighting a UTI and I'm just it's just a lot like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Did someone bring a bean filled horse cock into this bathroom?
All I hear is plops and drops. Good God.
You know, you should drink some cranberry juice.
Yeah, man. Clear that shit up. That's disgusting.
Look, everyone's leaving the chat. Everyone's.
That did it. That did it.
Matt is beans.
So I I go downstairs and I finish peeing in the toilet.
This is after the show is done.
After this one. Yeah, I saw one more to go. So I'm like, oh, I'm on a break. OK.
And a guy just goes like, oh, you should say now they can get into the magic circle.
There you have a closing joke for your show. OK, I go.
Oh, I go. What is that?
It's like I'm already. So so to catch people up, I was hosting a show that the show was having any mixed reactions.
Some people love it. Some people hated it. And I was not necessarily like a good fit, I thought, for the show.
So I just felt awkward hosting it. And so right.
But it was a big magic convention and it was a big deal to be asked.
And so I am just trying to process those feelings.
But I'm but I'm five of six shows and I'm just like I just want part of me just wants to be over already.
Right. Yeah. And so to catch people up from the last one, you said the show was more out there than you were really expecting it to be.
And probably more out there than maybe anybody was really expecting it to be.
I spent a lot of it to be out there, but it was they all had kind of like a chill and cerebral vibe to it.
That's what I wasn't expecting. It was tough coming out to try to be the funny, funny comedian.
Nobody wanted a wacky host in between these rights. Right.
And that's all I'm good for, guys. Yeah.
And again, like I don't even want to blame circumstances. I thought I also was doing just an OK job myself, like just personally.
I just thought I could have been doing a better job than I was doing. Right.
And so it was a bit of an uphill battle, though, from the start.
Yeah. And so I literally like have no patience. I go like I go. What?
And he goes, no, you say you have a joke for the end of the show.
You say, now you get the magic circle. And I go, I don't understand that joke.
That's not a joke. I just looked at him point blank as I don't understand that joke.
Simply not a joke. And he goes, the last guy was doing a very comedic version of a Cups and Balls routine.
And so and he goes to get into the Magic Circle in England.
It's the big organization in England. Right. You have to audition with the Cups and Balls.
You can't get into the Magic Circle unless you can do Cups and Balls.
OK, I consider myself somewhat in the magic world. Blah, blah, blah.
Whatever. Yes. I've never heard that before in my life.
That is fucking baseball. Right. No, this guy's on to it.
Here's how you deliver it, Matt. Fine. All right.
That last routine was awesome. Now you can get into the Magic Circle in England,
because as we all know, get into the Magic Circle in England.
You have to present the Cup and Balls trick. Good night.
That's a perfect topper. It's kind of like my closer joke. Yeah.
That was my last joke, everyone. That's my closer.
So he said, OK, I'll use that joke like that. Yeah.
So I felt bad of being addicted to this socially awkward person.
It's a magic convention. I should have more empathy.
Everybody there is socially awkward.
Should you, Matt? You're too close to the flame right now.
You don't remember how magicians need to be ostracized.
But this is just... Natalie, he's got a point.
This is just the prelude. This is not the story.
I do love, in this prelude, I do love when civilians catch you in your blank face.
Matt will go into that moment where he just can't talk to you for a minute.
Just give him a minute now. And then when people go up and talk to him,
it makes me laugh every time.
Because my comedy entertainer self is the shell I've put over this bitter asshole
who growing up without comedy was an angry, bullied jerk.
So it was only through comedy that I found a way to be palatable in this universe.
And so sometimes I go back to that kid that just wants your lunch money if you talk to me.
And I have to walk away. I have to recalibrate.
Oh, man.
I just need a second.
I need a second. I know who I am right now. And you won't like me.
I'm aware. It's not that I'm unaware. I am aware. That's why I'm taking this walk.
Yeah, yeah. But a closing joke.
Behind him is some guy. He's like aggressively drying his hands with paper towels.
And he's wearing like a drippy t-shirt. He does not look like a magic attendee.
He's not well put together.
What's that? What do you mean a drippy t-shirt?
Like he's he is like a skinny person and he's wearing like a large t-shirt that is like hanging off of him.
It's like he's very much draped and not wearing the shirt.
And he's a Vegas local. So he looks a little messy.
His outfit is not bespoke.
No.
And he says, he says, you know, as funny as most people don't even know where the suits of the cards come from.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, my goodness sakes alive.
You're right. That is funny.
That's it. That's it. Boy, that right there. That's a joke.
Finish it out like that. That's my closer.
One last funny thing, folks.
A lot of people don't even know where the suits of the cards come from.
And so I ignore him.
Now you can join the magic circle.
You ignored him. Good for you.
And I try to walk out and he stays over my shoulder.
Oh, he's following you, telling you the story of the of the suit.
And he goes one more time, it's because most people don't know where the suits of the cards come from.
Now, I will tell you, in this moment, my brain is going through multiple things and I I literally go like, oh, I literally go in my mind.
Oh, no. Is there religious connotations to the suits of the cards?
Because that's the way this guy is aping me. I was like, this is not right.
He's not trying to fun fact me.
No, he's trying to set you up for a Bible. He is giving you what?
Circa nineteen ninety four piff the magic dragon routines.
He's about to bust out Christian card magic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. The three silks are the father, son and the Holy Ghost.
Look at this glass of filthy water. You would never drink this glass of filthy water.
But you bring in the Holy Spirit with the cross cleaned up.
And notice, I'm still not going to drink, still not drinking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's still horribly poisonous.
It's just clear now. So again, I'm in a mood and I don't want to be.
Yeah. So I stopped dead in my tracks and turned to him and I go, go ahead.
Hit me. I go ahead and he recoils an offense that I've said, go ahead.
Because I basically I don't want to say I'm curious as I'm not.
Right. Yeah. It's like, you know exactly how curious you are.
You and Google could provide me the same information right now.
And I want to talk to one of you.
You and Google can both provide me the same information that I don't care about.
He goes, oh, well, I didn't realize, you know, you're going to be so sour about it.
I don't know if we have to get into it or whatever.
We're in the fucking bathroom, man. And I go, well, then we don't.
And so he huffs ahead of me and turns right out of the bathroom.
All right. Yeah. So I go left.
And for people who've been to Scoop Fest or in the Orleans before,
knows that this bathroom is right outside the Keno station.
When you walk into the Orleans, it's the Keno thing.
I know what you're talking about now.
So it turns out my man is just a Keno player.
So even though he went right, he just circles back
and just weaves back through the chairs towards me
and is mouthing off about me out loud as he parades through the Keno chairs.
I was just going to tell this guy about the different suits of the cards
and where they come from. He doesn't want to hear about it, though.
I don't know what his problem is.
I was going to tell him about the hearts of the diamonds, the spades of the clubs.
And people don't know about the frogs. That was the fifth suit for a while.
But I was going to tell him all about that stuff. He didn't want to hear it, though.
I guess I'm going to play Keno. Bingo. Shit. Wrong game.
See, I'm throwing off my game now. I mean, you're 90 percent.
Yes, Jacob. Yes, it's exactly what's happening.
And I don't know why I stopped. I don't know why I should just kept walking.
Oh, buddy. Oh, but I stop and go like, what is your problem, man?
Yes, my problem. What is your problem? You're the one being a jerk. I go.
Oh, because you're being nice. Is that what it is?
I'm a jerk while you're being a very nice person.
You just want to tell me your fun facts.
Tell me your fun facts. You know, man, I don't need to do that, whatever, man.
And he goes, he goes, no, you can go off, you go off, do your thing, man.
He goes, I'll see you at the throne.
Ah, it was religious. And so I go, what? Oh, I go, what?
And he goes, nothing, man. I go, no, what did you just say?
What was the statement you just made? And he goes, no, nothing.
I go, no, you said something about a throne. What did you just say?
And he said, I'll see you at the throne.
It means that when we are done with the life that the Lord gave us,
we meet at the throne to figure out how we spent our lives.
You and I specifically meet at the throne?
Nothing better than a heartfelt evangelical moment
from a degenerate gambling piece of shit in Las Vegas.
That's what I said. I go, oh, that's you being nice.
And he goes, yeah. I go, really? And then I step right into space.
And I go, so when you and your friends part ways,
you guys go see you at the throne and you high five and you walk away.
Everyone just says see you at the throne when they get in their car and drive away.
Everyone just saying see you at the throne all the time.
I go, are you just being a condescending dickhead? Yeah.
He's saying see you when you die is what he's saying. That's what he's saying.
I'll see you when you're dead, fucker. I'll see you when you're on your way to hell.
I'll see you from heaven. Yep.
I'll be in the throne sitting on daddy Jesus's fat lap.
Leon thought that the throne was a gay bathroom thing.
Leon, it would have been better.
A gay bathroom thing would have been a great surprise here.
Yes, correct. I would have actually been much happier if he was like,
I'll see you when you take a shit. Like, that's right.
I'll follow you. I'm going to follow you to the bathroom.
Everyone's got to go sometime and just when you least expect it.
Elvis was the king.
I saw you eating that protein bar earlier. Yeah, it's good coming in.
It's rough coming out.
And I was like, there's a little voice, a voice, a sane voice in my head.
It was like, why are you still here? What are you writing?
What are we doing?
And then one of my friends was like, if you get kicked out of the Orleans.
For arguing with a crazy Christ.
If you get 86 from the Orleans for this, Matt, I am going to be angry with you.
I was like, it would be the only thing people were talking about in Magic Live
is that the host of the show got kicked out for fighting a crackhead religious person.
And then, and then the scoop fest is at the Orleans, so I can't get banned from the Orleans.
I can't get 86 from the Orleans.
And so I did walk away, finally.
No, Dan Lazlo, Dan Lazlo in the chat says scoop fest live from the Orleans parking lot.
When they 86 you can't be in the parking lot either.
Yeah, it's got to be from like the Chevron. Yeah, across the street.
In view of the Orleans, scoop fest 2025.
We really have to pull our weight with fucking.
McMillan's. Yeah, McMillan's. Oh, yeah.
We'd have to be like, please, McMillan's, please.
The alcohol free Irish bar.
You know who else is as successful as an alcohol free Irish bar?
That's the following sponsor.
The show is brought to you by.
Customs scrotal implants.
That's right from scoop of Henny or scoop of Henley.
Sorry, scoop of Henley in 2022.
That's custom scrotal implants.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, children of all ages.
Welcome to custom scrotal implants.
The only amusement park dedicated to fake balls.
That's right. Yes, come on in.
Come on in.
We've got nothing but food rides and shows dedicated to false testicles.
Yep. We have the ball buster.
Our number one roller coaster in the nation.
An 800 foot drop with no seats.
So you rattle your taint right against the floor of the car.
Ow, you're going to need some of our famous fake balls after that.
We also have Jimmy yum yums.
Big old buckets of balls that serves nothing but prairie oysters.
That's right. Go to Jimmy yum yums and get yourself a big old.
Prairie oysters with our patented ball free sauce.
That's right.
It's ball free because there's no balls in it.
Or are there? We don't know.
We don't even know what Jimmy yum yums is selling.
Honestly, I brought this guy in.
He told me he had prairie oysters.
I took him at his word.
It's on you and Jimmy yum yum to sort it out.
And don't miss the cavalcade of stars performing in testes one,
two, three on our big commemorative stage in the Hall of Presidents.
That's right.
We talk about all the presidents testicular problems from FDR's
folded boys that he couldn't ever access because he was constantly
sitting down to Abe Lincoln's Ring of Ding Dingers that swung like
the Liberty Bell itself.
All the presidents testes coming out swinging.
That's right.
That's what it's called.
Come out swinging.
The show is called coming out swinging.
And then the finale, which everyone loves, Gravity Wins.
That's the finale song.
Gravity wins.
And it's nothing but saggers.
But guess what, everybody?
That's what this ballpark is all about.
This ballpark is dedicated to fake balls.
So when Gravity does finally defeat your testicular sack,
you can come here and get what we're really famous for,
which is ball replacement surgery.
Get your fakeies in there.
As someone who got ball replacement surgery,
I can't tell you how fun it is, honestly.
I have my fake tiny balls and I put a bell around my scrotum.
And now whenever I play with myself,
people think I'm collecting money for the Salvation Army.
And you might be.
There's no way to tell.
When I got my ball replacement surgery,
I had them replace it with those clicky clacky things that are on
desks in people's offices, you know?
Where like the one ball flies in and it hits the other balls and
then the one ball flies off the other way.
That's what I got them to replace mine with.
It's great.
When I walk along, I just go click clack, click clack.
All kinds of wild, wacky ball replacement stuff.
You can get those kinds that you put on your truck.
You can get truck nuts put on yourself.
Why the fuck not?
Who cares anymore?
Just go nuts.
Go nuts.
It's our company slogan.
That's our slogan.
Go nuts.
Oh, man, I want to scoop baby.
Just turning it out of his seat and he's got a real gamer chair, man.
He's got a real comfortable gamer chair.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, look, there we go.
There they are.
What are you holding?
Oh, proper sack.
He's dangling his fake balls.
Yes.
I couldn't remember.
I need to get Jacob to the internet.
If you wouldn't mind.
All right.
Is there a name for when dogs get neutered?
They have fake balls that you can implant on your dog so they don't feel so emasculated?
All right.
Are they called like nudicles or something like that?
Or, or nexticles or fake stickles?
There's some.
Is it?
Nutri, neuter calls.
That's it.
Neuter calls.
That's when they get neutered, neutered calls.
That's the new name of this podcast is neuter calls, neuter calls.
They're called these nuts.
You're right.
Newticles.
Yeah.
All right.
Newticles.
That was the one I was searching for.
But I was like, it can't just be newticles.
But I guess it is newticles.
I guess it is.
All right.
Yeah, that's all.
What was the story you wanted to get into before we got on air?
Oh, well.
So for those of you who may not know, America is in steep decline and it's being helped
along by a bunch of Gestapo bastards called ICE.
And unfortunately, you guys know how many times I've lamented the options that we have
here in beautiful Allison Park PA for eating.
That's right.
At least 12.
Right.
So one of the places that Anne and I have frequented over the years has been a Mexican
restaurant, Emiliano's.
And they have a couple of locations around this area and it is one of our favorite spots
to go to.
We've been like probably 40 times, I would imagine.
Yeah, we go there fairly frequently as far as stuff goes.
Their owner was in Florida, I believe it was Florida, was away.
She was overseeing her son's graduation and gets an emergency phone call that there's
an ICE raid at the restaurant and comes back to people missing.
There's video of they just ransacked the restaurant.
Like there are ceiling tiles all fucked up.
They started a small fire in the kitchen.
There's just shit all over the floors.
It's insane.
It looks like somebody came in and robbed the place, which essentially they did.
And it just feels so deeply wrong and illegal that I'm just beside myself thinking that
these are government authorized agents acting supposedly in the name of the people of Pennsylvania.
It's just fucking sick.
And it's so frustrating that anyone who's in this country that wasn't born here is considered
a criminal at this point, even if they have paperwork and stuff.
Even if they're trying to get things done properly.
And there's a naivete, I guess, an ignorance of basically how much we rely on illegal immigrants
in this country.
We have been relying on people who have snuck into this country for many, many facets of
our economy for a very long time.
For generations.
And the majority of them are not criminals besides that one aspect we just discussed
of sneaking in here.
And yeah, it's just not...
But even that, the criminality behind that, and we've discussed this before, asylum seekers,
which until the person who runs the government didn't understand the difference between asylum
and insane asylum got into power because that's what he honestly thought.
That was his insane thing.
He thought asylum seekers were people who were from insane asylums.
He doesn't understand what the term asylum means.
Anyway, that's a whole nother kettle of fish, but it's just so fucking crazy.
And illegal or not, quote unquote, illegal or not, this is fish in a barrel type shit.
There is no actual seeking down these drug runners or sexual predators.
This is where the Democrats have fucked it all up too.
Of course we don't want drugs or more drugs or violent criminals or any of that in our
country.
Oh, yeah.
I don't want violent criminals in our country.
Nobody does.
Nobody wants that.
But you want is a way for the government to step up and figure out who is those people.
And you don't do that by ripping families apart that have been here for decades.
No.
Multiple generation families that have been here for decades.
Yeah, if your first line of attack is the Home Depot parking lot and Mexican restaurants,
you ain't going after shit.
That's just the stupidest fucking thing.
And my only hope is that we get this turned around somehow and that there are any legitimate
courts left to fix this.
Well, you know who stepped up to help this situation?
Who is helping?
We need a hero.
We do.
Dean Kane.
Right.
Superman has stepped in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The 90s Superman has announced that he is joining ICE.
Yep.
As if the show "Mashes of Illusion" on the CW couldn't get any grosser.
Well, he's outdone himself for the Superman curse.
He's clearly the worst example of the Superman curse.
Yeah.
What is the Superman curse?
It's notoriously that the people who have portrayed Superman have had very rough ways
to go of it in their later life.
Yeah.
Who was it?
The first guy...
Christopher Reeve was fine.
George Reeves.
Yeah, yeah.
No, he didn't.
Nothing happened to him.
He was fine.
Yeah, you're right.
That's a fellow with some good old horse sense right there.
No, they're all...
They all have tragic things, but this is the worst.
This is clearly the worst.
This is fucked up.
Christopher Reeve just hoofing it through life.
But it is like...
This is like...
I don't understand the way ICE is operating to go like, "Oh, yeah.
I got to get in on that.
I got to get in.
I got to be a part of that."
Well, he's following the playbook from...
Oh shit, what's his name?
The action star, the Aikido guy...
It's Steven Seagal.
It's Steven Seagal to the next level.
Yes.
Yeah, he's following...
Because remember when Steven Seagal was doing the cop reality show?
Yeah.
They made him like an honorary sheriff in town.
He was like roughing people up on TV and everything, and they were like, "Shit, this is getting
too much."
Bounty hunting and all that kind of shit, and then he moved to Russia.
What a fucking joke.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Jurassic scoop.
He's starting from Superman to Homelander.
There it is.
It's not a far leap.
It's not a far leap if you're not careful.
Homelander's at least funny though.
Dean Cain is not funny.
I haven't listened to the dollop in a while, but the dollop they did on Steven Seagal is
outrageous and amazing.
It is worth-
I can't imagine.
It is worth it.
If you have a podcast or a video or whatever that you're like, "I want Jacob Smith to
watch this," just start off by telling me about Steven Seagal.
If you just start your whole thing by telling me some ridiculous thing that Steven Seagal
did in 1996, I am in for your entire show.
Before he hit at all, before he was famous at all, he had three different wives in three
different countries before he even-
Yeah.
He was already a fucking-
Motherfuckers got shit going down.
Yeah.
That guy was just a disgusting narcissist from the jump and-
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But he's hilarious to me.
That crazy karate bullshit stuff where he's sitting in a chair and people come up to him.
He's like, "Whoa, whoa."
Yeah.
He says he's an Aikido master.
He's a something all right.
I mean, Dean Cain thing, we talked about this before in the pod, which is if you're an actor,
these actors keep making themselves prominent in these different movements and stuff like
that.
Right.
And it's because all you want, your dream is to be told what to do.
That's what your job is as an actor.
When you dream of being an actor, you dream of being handed something and being like, "Become
this," and then having a director direct you to do stuff or whatever.
And so yes, it seems like Dean Cain having, hosting 13 episodes a year of Master's Illusion,
not enough for him.
And so he needs something to do.
He needs to be told.
Well, I mean, it does speak to the travails of Hollywood right now.
It's hard to find work.
So you know.
It's especially hard to find work if you're Dean Cain.
Oh, for fucking sure.
For fucking sure.
Yeah.
When you've burned every bridge you've ever encountered.
Right.
A lot of...
Yeah.
Nobody's knocking on Dean Cain's door.
There's a lot of people who swing their politics the other way because they're blaming Hollywood
for their misfortune.
Of course.
They're saying they're ostracized before they're ostracized and then they double down on politics
so they can claim that they're victims of something instead of just, "It's really fucking
hard to maintain a career.
It's really hard to be an actor for a very long time.
It's really hard to be in more than one hit thing."
It's just hard.
I consider myself extremely fortunate and basically an outlier to have made as much money
professionally performing as I did for as long as I did.
That's just ridiculous and I'm grateful for that time, very grateful for that time.
I'm hoping maybe it swings back again one of these days or something, but this is such
a wonderful outlet.
I'm so grateful for this, having this opportunity too.
But yeah, it's incredibly hard and if you can't just straight up say, "Well, due to
some circumstances that are in my control and some circumstances out of my control,
I just don't have the same career that's happening."
By the way, you can outrun Dean Cain.
That guy is a little long in the tooth.
He's older than you think.
Yeah, no.
He's an old guy.
Oh, yeah.
Him joining ICE is helping no one.
That's not...
No.
Let's also be clear.
Well, ICE is helping no one.
Well, that's the ultimate thing that really just broke my heart today is that Emiliano's
has set up a GoFundMe page to try and help the families that are being...
Legal defense.
Yep, legal defense, and to help rebuild their trash restaurant.
Jesus Christ.
Right.
It's fucking insane.
But they're already over 40 grand in 24 hours.
And that's just like...
But that's exactly the point is these people are in the communities.
They are functioning in the communities.
Absolutely.
They are loved in their communities.
They make their communities better.
We have to find a way to honestly assess what's happening with these families on an individual
level and how they impact their community, and we have to find a way on a governmental
level to give credit where credit is due.
The Statue of Liberty tells us who we want coming to the country, and nobody fucking
is down anymore.
I bet you that preamble's been eliminated on the government website.
I bet you can't find it on the website.
It very well may have been rubbed out at Ellis Island, for all I fucking know.
They may have sandblasted that shit.
Statue of Liberty's on Liberty Island, not Ellis Island.
No, but yeah, you know what I'm saying.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
But isn't that on Ellis Island, too?
They're all gone, Jacob.
All the islands are gone.
No, no, no.
By the way, that was the most ready Rich I've ever felt doing a podcast.
That's fine.
Just getting it correct on one quick little thing.
Yeah.
Very happy with that.
That's fine.
Isn't that saying on Ellis Island, too?
It might be.
I have to find out if this comment is true or not.
Jurassic Excuse says they rubbed one out on Ellis Island, and I've got to know if that's
true.
Hold on.
I'm checking the records.
I've got to know.
That was like a bad class trip.
What are we talking about, Jurassic Scoop?
Where are you?
Show yourself.
I think Jurassic Scoop just masturbated at Ellis Island.
Yeah.
Jurassic Scoop is saying they were at a fair in Wisconsin having some fried cheese.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm just curious.
I'm just curious what would motivate someone to rub one out at Ellis Island.
That's all I know.
I'm just curious.
Hot immigrants.
It was just a bad joke.
He's saying it's a bad joke.
Sexy immigrants.
Yeah.
I mean, inside my balls is the whole of mastering to be free.
For that joke.
That's just how it goes.
You better rub one out right now.
Have the courage to man up and be the bit.
Not on Twitch.
Don't do it on Twitch.
So anyway, just if you happen to be around the Pennsylvania area and you're seeing Emilianos,
go and frequent them.
Give them some business.
Give them some money.
Give them some love.
Yeah.
Just, yeah, fuck this shit.
This is fucking gross.
The poem, The New Colossus, which is the poem that you're referring to, Paul, that gave
me your, you're tired, you're weak, all that stuff.
That is on the, it is inside the pedestal of the Statue of Liberty.
Right.
According to the U.S. National Park Service.
Okay.
So that is on Liberty Island.
That's on Liberty Island, not Ellis Island.
Got it.
Ellis Island is where the immigrants would come and do the processing and whatnot.
Right.
Where you change your names.
That's right.
I have the copy of my great-grandfather, my dad's grandfather.
I have the copy of the Ellis Island form that he filled out when he entered the country.
Wow.
Yeah.
You can apparently request these through Ellis Island.
It has a picture of the ship that he came in on and the information they took down from
him when he entered at Ellis Island.
And he landed on Smith for a last name, huh?
That's right.
All right.
Creative guy.
Yeah.
I got my creativity from him.
Well, you know what?
I bet back in the day, Smith was probably, Smith was probably a good name to go with
because you're just like, oh yeah, I'm a Smith, I can do anything.
I can do it.
I'm ready for work.
Everybody knows how to spell it.
Yeah.
And it just means, oh yeah, I'll be a blacksmith, I'll be a candle-smith, I'll be a rake-smith,
I'll be a lawn-smith, whatever.
You need me to rub one out?
Did you just say a rake-smith?
A rake-smith.
Rake, R-A-K-E.
Rake-smith.
Goodness sakes.
You need me to rub one out?
I'm a jack-smith.
Jack-a-vault.
Smith.
You know, it exists.
It's totally real.
I've got this very emotionally needy ferret that needs attention.
It needs medication on the hour every hour.
My fur baby has the sniffles.
Latter-day scoop.
I think just look at it as more of the social engagement that you'll be gaining from it
and, you know, don't worry about, I don't know, what is your objective?
What are you hoping to get out of it?
Well, it's something that I chose because, one, it was cheap.
Okay.
Something I could afford.
Two, it's sort of in my wheelhouse, but not something I'm great at, that's for sure.
I'm looking at it as, because everything I know is self-taught, and I went to college
previously doing multimedia, which included animation and graphics and all of it, and
it was just not a good time.
So, even if I learn nothing, it's not much of an investment put into it.
All right.
So, at the very least, I'll learn something, hopefully.
Again, me personally, I would put the emphasis on the social aspect, the fact that you can
meet some like-minded folks who might be in the same industry, and, you know, I think
that's the best that you can hope for.
Don't put this on yourself.
But you might meet someone who you can truly collaborate with, and, you know, I was fortunate
enough to have Matt drop into my lap out there in Vegas.
Hey, guys, I'm Donnelly.
I wish Matt would drop into my lap.
Yeah, don't we all.
Don't we all.
There's a price.
But that absolutely changed the trajectory.
Preachingfun.com.
Matt will drop into your lap for a price.
Totally changed my trajectory and helped me in a myriad of ways to keep me more creative
and the opportunities that have come my way because of my association with him.
So, you know, I think that's key, at least that's been my experience is that it really
it's all about networking and getting those those social webs designed.
Paul's bringing up something actually pretty significant, which is that you actually might
find someone in there that you want to collaborate with.
In other words, like that's that would be interesting.
All the things that hold you back, you might find someone is like is better at it, right?
Like so like if you're not an organized person, you might have someone who's organized but
not funny, right?
Or organized but not a good writer.
Right.
And so like you want to figure out like you basically want to find someone with different
superpowers, right?
And so that might happen through this class.
I think these are all good ideas.
I do think that you shouldn't ignore the idea of that is presented in such classic films
like old school and the Rodney Dangerfield film.
Yeah, school.
I think you should emulate these people.
I'll search out the showers.
How should be your heroes?
The raging party zone.
I think you should endeavor to have your classmates call you old blue.
I think you should just go with the full bit.
Old school, old school.
That was one of the characters in old school.
That's my boy blue.
Because in Australia, blue is slang for someone with ginger hair.
Oh really?
Ow.
Yeah, it is.
Because you have red hair.
What the fuck?
It is.
Like I didn't understand it as a kid and one time.
I don't understand it as an adult.
And went to the butchers.
I'm like five years old.
And the butcher says, oh, good day, blue.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
Well, I was five.
I wasn't thinking what the fuck.
I was thinking, this guy has been mean to me.
What the fuck did you just say to me, motherfucker?
Yeah.
So as we're leaving, I'm like, see your sausage face.
And my mom's like, how dare you.
I'm like, I'm just giving it back to this guy.
He gave me the business.
I'm giving him the business.
It's up there with, hey, buddy.
Nice hat.
Yeah, it is.
See your sausage face.
I see a joke about two kids hanging out with the wrong kind of kids.
And they've been learning how to curse words and stuff like that.
And they just think it's exciting.
And wake up in the morning.
And mom goes, what do you guys want for breakfast?
And the kid goes, I'll take some fucking eggs.
And mom just backhands them across the room.
You don't speak like that in my household.
And what about you, little Jimmy?
What do you want?
And he goes, well, I sure as fuck don't want some fucking eggs.
Yeah, so I think that's what you need to aim for.
OK.
Backhand the kids.
Yeah, yeah.
Is blue a derogatory term for gingers in Australia?
Or is it just a term?
No, no.
Sausage faces, though, yeah.
Derogatory is, for me to say, a term for gingers in Australia is ranger.
Ranger?
Spell that.
Ranger, yeah.
I'm assuming it's got to do with orangutans or something.
Because they have orange hair.
I haven't searched the etymology of the word.
That sounds right.
I think you do.
Yet.
No, you just hear that when you run, right?
Get out of there.
Right, yeah, yeah.
He just hears that word and wants a banana.
Well, thank you.
Well, thank you, Wayne.
Good luck in school.
Keep us updated.
Yeah, no, thank you for the advice.
Yeah, yeah.
Good luck, buddy.
Let us know how it goes.
Form a frat, an awesome party frat headed by just the oldest people on campus.
I should make it clear that this is a one night a week, three hours a week course as
well.
Then it's going to be easier to have the frat house.
They'll never expect that the group at least expects zeta, zeta, zeta to form.
Thanks, Wayne.
Thanks, guys.
Let's see, we had Captain James T. Scoop in the chat.
Wait.
You had a story to tell us.
Yeah, yeah.
Go for it.
Yeah, you.
Yeah.
Where are you, Captain James T. Scoop?
Let me find you here.
There you are.
All right.
So you said you had a story to tell us about the -- you had two stories to tell us.
Which one's better?
Well, actually, well, they're the same story.
I just didn't know it.
Even better.
Just in case my first job --
Ha, ha.
She got you, Jacob.
She pitched two stories in the same one.
I know.
Yeah.
Perfect, perfect.
I will stay there.
Okay.
So, thank you for answering my last email.
That was about my grandfather passing.
I appreciated that advice.
That was really cool.
So, I mean, he'd already been dead for two weeks, so it wasn't, like, super helpful.
No.
I'm just kidding.
That's our brand.
We don't want to be too helpful.
Two weeks?
That's pretty good turnaround for a Scoop Mail.
That's better for us than it is for Scoop.
Actually, you're welcome.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, thank you.
Better relation never.
But at the end of that, I mentioned something about a return missionary dating application.
Yes.
And Matt seemed, like, kind of grossed out by it, right?
Like, oh, that's weird.
I think this is, like, actually an application for will you date me when I get back from
my mission.
Well, Matt was absolutely correct.
And I sat and thought about it, and I was like, well, that is, like, fucking creepy.
Like, that's not funny.
That's weird.
And, like...
That's what I'm here for.
I know.
It just got me thinking.
Matt Donnelly, not funny, but weird.
That's right.
Now you can join the Magic Circle.
It just got me thinking.
It just got me thinking about these things that, you know, you do growing up, probably
in any religion, but growing up Mormon, that don't seem weird, that are weird to outsiders.
Yep.
So I've got a story for you.
July 24th is a state holiday in Utah.
It's called Pioneer Day, and it's the day that we all celebrate, you know, Brigham Young
and the early church saints, as we called them, arriving in Utah, right?
So, something else that we do for the youth in the church, when I say youth, this is between
ages 14 and 18.
You do something called Trek.
You do it during the summer.
Paul.
I didn't mind.
It's not what you think.
Yeah.
It'd be a lot cooler if it was, though.
Yeah, it would be, yeah.
So, I had my Trek experience.
I grew up a military brat.
We were living in Virginia in the time.
Y'all are from the East Coast.
You know how crazy humid it gets in the summer.
It's, like, disgustingly hot.
So, the summer before my senior year of high school, I went with my youth group from church.
We went up to the Marriott Ranch in July, you know, to celebrate Pioneer Day, even though
we weren't living in Utah.
We all had to dress up in Pioneer clothes.
Oh, that's great.
I'm already happy with this.
Slower, slower.
Were there buckles on your shoes?
Tell me there were buckles on your shoes.
My regular, I think I had regular shoes on.
I don't remember that.
Damn it.
But, yeah, I'm right.
So, this was, like, a three-day trip.
We were not allowed to bring anything that the pioneers would not have had.
Syphilis.
So, that's not just, like, phones and, you know, MP3 players or whatever at the time.
I mean, that's, like, toothpaste.
Yeah.
Toothpaste.
That's a lot.
No.
Come on.
Disgusting.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm serious.
It's a bunch of 14 to 18-year-old teenagers in Pioneer clothes pushing hand carts on the
Marriott Ranch for three days with no deodorant or toothbrushes.
I was going to say, it's like, these guys are going through hormonal changes and puberty
and everything else, and they already feel horrible about themselves.
How can we make them feel even less attractive to each other?
We must.
Did you see Latter-day Scoop posted an image in the chat there?
Does that match your experience, James T. Scoop?
They're pulling some kind of wagon and mud.
Let me see.
Oh, it's people, like, strapped up to a wagon and pulling it themselves instead of horses.
Yeah.
Also, I've got bad news.
That's pretty much what they were doing, huh?
I've got bad news for you, James T. Scoop.
So, Brigham Young arrived in Salt Lake City or the Salt Lake Valley in 1847.
Toothpaste was invented in 1824.
They already had toothpaste by then.
They were just fucking with you and didn't want you to brush your teeth.
They were lying to you the whole time.
Couldn't you technically bring, like, golden glasses and a couple of tablets and be like,
"Hey, I just read on here that every modern thing is cool.
It's all good.
We can just bring whatever the fuck we want."
I should have, right?
I should have.
No, I've got some invisible tablets here that say tooth brushing is fine.
Become a new prophet.
Kudos to the rich.
I mean, I'm a woman though, so they wouldn't have listened to me.
Kudos to the rich kid that was like, "I'm bringing a horse.
We're bringing a goddamn horse.
We're taking care of the horse the whole time."
So, is there a start point and destination?
What exactly is the...
Yes.
Yeah.
So, there's a place that you start and a place where you end.
And so, we get there.
They go through our bags, make sure we don't have anything we're not supposed to have.
No toothpaste.
My toothpaste.
We're dividing into families.
You can keep the whiskey.
The whiskey existed then.
Go ahead, here you go.
That's right.
Right?
Yeah.
I should.
Yeah, right.
They divide us into families and we're all paired with a married couple that we have
to call Ma and Pa.
Gross.
Boo.
Is there a way for Matt, Paul, and I to become one of the people that they call Paul?
Yeah, yeah.
Can I apply to be a camp counselor at this thing?
No.
I would bring my own fishbone record with that Hey Ma and Pa song.
Hey Ma and Pa, what the hell is wrong with y'all?
I promise I'll show up with the dirtiest mouth and the stinkiest armpits to apply.
Oh, God damn it.
Does that help?
God.
Yeah, totally.
That'll get you in for sure.
Well, you want a side tangent, but for girls camp, the LDS girls camp, they always want
priesthood holder volunteers.
You don't have to have a girl going to the camp to volunteer.
Just throwing that out there.
Super creepy.
Of course not.
Oh, he's creepy about that.
Why doesn't anyone care about young women?
But he's got priesthood, so we're good.
I like that Chuck E. Cheese literally has better security.
Chuck E. Cheese literally has better, more guidelines about who can touch the children
in their establishment.
I could be way off base here, guys, but I feel like there could be a correlation between
these organized religious practices and the fuckery that's going on at the top levels
of our government right now.
I might be missing a beat here somewhere.
No, no.
Our president has very shiny teeth.
He's got some toothpaste.
You think those are his real teeth?
Fuck off.
And do I think he brushed them himself?
No.
Oh, no way.
No way.
Certainly not the bottom row.
I think he just brushes the top teeth and just ignores everything else.
That's weirdly horrible.
Okay.
If I found out that was true, I feel like that would be the thing that I thought was
the worst thing about Donald Trump.
I got news for you.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll try to speed this up.
I'll just mention a few of the most egregious things that happened.
Please.
All right.
Okay.
So for the three days.
So we start on this handcart trip.
For lunch that day, we got a cutie, one of those little cutie oranges, and that was it.
Jesus.
I was so hungry.
I ate the peel.
Oh, God.
I was so hungry.
And then for dinner, we got a little 10 cup of broth and a roll.
And then to sleep in, we got a tarp for the whole family, and we could choose to either
sleep on top of the tarp or underneath it if it was going to rain.
Those were our options.
And this was your real family, or these were the people that you were just instructed to
call ma and pa?
Oh, he was instructed to call ma and pa.
Oh, and I was called the big sister.
I got nominated to be the big sister, and there was a big brother.
So you are getting under a tarp with a fake mom and dad and family.
Yeah.
Well, after having a cup full of broth.
And a cutie.
And a cutie, Matt.
I have to tell you, I think the pioneers were better at it than this.
I just want to say that I don't think -- this sounds like someone who didn't understand
history.
I don't know that they were that much better at it.
How was this broth contained?
Was this in a sealed canister?
Was it like a soup canister?
What was that?
How was the broth contained?
Oh, well, no, they made it over the fire.
Like they heated it up in like a pot and then ladled it into the cups.
Okay.
All right.
Gotcha.
So we had to walk along with our little cup and then we had a ladle of broth.
What was it made of?
It was just like teardrop broth.
It was probably just bouillon cubes, to tell you the truth.
Right, right, right.
Like salty flavored chicken water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Good news, though.
The orange peel actually has more vitamin C and fiber than the inner fruit.
So you did yourself a favor by eating the cutie peel.
Well done.
You won.
You won the game.
You won the survival game.
Yeah, yeah.
I knew that all along.
I was just testing you guys.
Yeah.
I wanted to see.
That's the kind of instincts we need a big sister to have.
Yeah, exactly.
You know, I'm bringing I am in real life a big sister, so I'm just bringing that experience
everywhere I go, you know, bringing that knowledge.
Yeah.
But a couple other things.
So one time it was supposed to be a lesson on faith.
We had to be blindfolded and they would tell us where to go with the cart and guide us,
you know, with their voices, but the worst one.
And even at the time, like and I was, you know, I mean, I'm 17, fully in it, fully believing.
But even at the time, I was so upset at this.
They have something called the woman's pool.
And there was a stretch of time, you know, but there was a time.
It's a wagon.
It's a wagon washing fundraiser.
That would have been a lot better.
It would have been a lot more fun.
I'll tell you that.
But it was supposed to commemorate this time that we're like the men went away to do something
and the women spent some time with the hand cards on their own.
And so we were supposed to like it was like in their honor kind of a thing.
Right. So the boys were not permitted to help.
They had to stand on the edges.
They waited till we got to the steepest, hardest part of the trail.
Well, it wasn't even a trail, but of our area.
And that the boys were allowed to do was like fan us with like their hats and stuff.
And us girls, the women in the women's pool, we had to push the cards up this huge hill all by ourselves while singing hymns.
And at the end of it, we had like a testimony meeting, you know, where everybody can talk about how amazing and wonderful it was.
The boys got up and they were like, it was so hard to watch you struggle.
It was just so difficult.
And I can't imagine how those husbands must have felt leaving their wives.
I just wanted to help you guys.
And I'm like, you little bitches.
No, you didn't.
You're just glad you didn't have to do the hardest part of the whole thing.
Do these little Mormon boys think that the Mormon pioneers had just watched and fanned their wives with hats while their wives did all the work?
Well, I don't know, man.
I don't know.
But they just kept going off about how like it was so hard for them to watch us struggle so much.
And I'm like, I'm sure it was.
No, they're the victims in this.
Do you understand?
It's good to be a lily white Mormon boy.
Is there any way that they could have stepped in?
Was that a possibility that they could step in and just help or they were forbidden?
No, they weren't allowed to.
What do you think would happen if somebody did?
Oh, you know, I mean...
It'd be at least as bad as drinking coffee.
Oh, you think that bad, huh?
I think that bad, yeah.
Wow, holy shit.
I mean, I think somebody would have intervened and told them to stop and that they hadn't.
I would have stepped in.
I would have just been like, man, let's help push this wagon.
Also, I would have never done any of that stupid shit.
Maybe. I don't know.
I got roped into some dumb shit when I was young, young.
But I think I...
And we started a podcast.
It took me to like 20 to really free myself from this shit.
And even then I was still kind of fucked with it.
It's hard.
I mean, yeah, I started questioning, you know, mid-20s, but then just that fear of like...
Right.
I don't want to go to hell, you know?
Yeah.
But, you know, it ended up okay.
We got to kill a chicken and learn square dancing.
And then I got my period at the end of it.
So, you know.
See? Pushing that cart uphill.
There's a plan for everything.
Thank you, Captain James D. Scoop.
Amazing. Thank you for sharing.
I killed the chicken because I was the big sister.
The big brother had to kill the chicken.
I was allowed to de-feather it, but I could not behead it because that was a boy's job.
But anyway, that's my story.
Awesome.
Yeah.
All right, Captain James D. Scoop.
We'll see you at the throne.
See you at the throne.
Thanks for letting me share, guys.
Oh, yeah.
Also, you look good as a wrangah.
Now we've got...
Thank you.
Now we've got you in more Australian slang.
Perfect.
I'll say it.
I think the Mormons got a couple things wrong.
I know I don't want to ruffle too many...
All right.
I don't want to ruffle too many recently plucked chicken feathers, but I think they got a few things wrong.
Well, we'll see you at the throne.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Chuck vs. Mike.
I'm chicken feathers.
Okay.
So I want to scoop, baby.
I want to scoop, baby.
Just put in the chat.
Is that going to be a thing?
The throne thing?
And I was just thinking, like, we've got I need help salt pork as our greetings.
Yeah.
How about as our farewell?
See you at the cone.
That's our new check you later.
Huh?
See you at the cone.
Approve.
We're going to workshop that.
I think it's good.
Turn the pages in.
So all right.
Yeah.
Well, let's just hear from the...
All right.
Love it.
We'll see how it catches on.
See you at the cone.
I like it.
To every Orleans employee you encounter at Scootfest, please end every conversation with I'll see you at the cone.
See you at the cone.
I think people are down.
All right.
Thank you for this drink.
See you at the cone.
All right.
I'm running.
Joe, you could use it.
You got to just come out to a Scoop event.
Come on out, man.
And hopefully there'll be some more Scoop events around the country next year.
That'd be a great goal.
I'm running into a time conflict here.
So let's do the...
Oh, shit.
Oh, let's go.
We got a Scooper today from Diamond Scoop.
The categories are Oakland, Los Angeles, Las Vegas, and Raiders.
Paul, you're up first.
What do you want?
I will go ahead and try Las Vegas for 200.
Las Vegas for 200?
Everything you think of when you think of Las Vegas, including the Strip and the home
stadium of the Las Vegas Raiders, is not actually in the city of Las Vegas.
What is the name of the unincorporated town these attractions reside in?
It is known as Paradise, Nevada.
Paradise, Nevada is correct.
Yeah.
Me, I'll try Raiders for 200.
Every year there are stupid rumors that the Raiders will trade QB Derrick Carr.
Oh, this is an older Scooperty from before the Raiders traded Derrick Carr.
This is a very old Scooperty.
Derrick Carr has already played for the Saints and retired.
Yep.
Maybe they'll stop now that the Raiders traded for this player who is an All-Pro, a Pro Bowler,
and Carr's former teammate at Fresno State.
That was shit.
Adams.
Yeah.
Devontae Adams.
Come on.
There it is.
Devontae Adams.
Nice.
Man.
Matt, you're up.
I got to test my vintage Raiders knowledge here.
I know, right?
Raiders for 400.
By the way, we could use more Scooperties.
Head over to HayScoops.com.
Just a reminder.
The Raiders are one of the more mobile teams having played home games in LA, Oakland, Las
Vegas, and even San Francisco for their opening season while Oakland Coliseum was being built.
What year did the Raiders move to LA within five?
1985.
Wow.
That's right.
That neighborhood.
'82 for sure.
You got it.
Safe.
Well done.
Paul.
Vegas, please.
Vegas.
During the last weekend of April 2022, Las Vegas will hold this event with people coming
from all over the world to attend the festivities.
Oh my God.
Was this ScoopFest?
It might have been.
I'm going to go ScoopFest.
Taylor Swift.
Let's try ScoopFest.
It was ScoopFest.
The NFL Draft does not count.
Oh, that was the year that we had ScoopFest during the NFL Draft.
That's right.
It's me.
I'll try Oakland for 200.
This former Oakland resident is known for his comedy and political podcasts and his
very sexy salt and pepper hair and beard.
He currently resides in Austin, Texas.
I believe that would be the one and only Justin Robert Young.
Yeah.
Jury if you're nasty.
Matt.
Raiders 600.
Daily Double.
All of it, Jacob.
I want it all.
Raiders legendary owner Al Davis is known for his catchphrase, "Just win, baby," and
suing the NFL so he could move to LA.
Al got his start with the Raiders in 1963 in this position.
Doggy.
Doggy position.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, it's a Daily Double, so I have to come up with something.
Was she the water boy?
Was she the guy that brought the waters?
What's it called?
When you collect the uniforms and stuff.
Like the equipment manager?
Equipment manager.
Equipment manager is my guess.
Head coach.
He would write the head coach.
Excuse me.
Jesus.
The equipment manager for the entire team.
The head coach.
Equipment, personnel, all of it.
Yeah.
Paul.
Las Vegas, please.
The other Daily Double.
Not digging it down.
Look at you fellas.
Vegas is becoming quite the sports town, it sure is, with the Golden Knights making the
Stanley Cup finals in their first year and the Raiders making the playoffs in their second
season in town.
What other major team is rumored to be moving to Las Vegas?
The A's.
Let's see.
It is the Oakland A's.
Maybe they'll room with the Raiders again.
They are still rumored.
I'm actually draining my pool right now because we're going to build a stadium right by backyard.
Can you believe all that dirt moving around, bullshit they're doing for nothing?
Yes.
Yes, I can.
They can afford it.
Yeah, they can.
I'm Las Vegas for 800.
No, they can't.
In the year 2281 of the Fallout universe, after the Great War wiped out most of humanity,
Hoover Dam is the site of much turmoil, as depicted in Fallout New Vegas, two factions
fight in the second battle of Hoover Dam.
Name one of the factions.
Damn.
Damn, son.
I don't have a single idea.
I have to pass the mat.
Oh, well as a Fallout player, I pass.
Yeah, but you don't want to reveal the secrets.
Yeah.
Paul.
Vault-Tec would be my guess, but I don't have a guess because I don't know.
I'll pass.
All right.
NCR, that's the New California Republic, and/or Caesar's Legion, or just The Legion.
Hey, Leann Casab, don't type the answers into the chat during the scooper, you jerk.
Oh, no.
No, Leann's just too used to us playing our night games.
He's playing with me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Leann.
I can't see the chat.
I'm sharing the screen, so I'm not getting the answers.
All right, Matt, you're up.
Los Angeles, 200.
All right.
LA is the home to a ridiculous number of sports teams, including the surrounding suburbs.
How many professional teams from the big four leagues currently call LA home, plus or minus one?
Let's see, we've got the Kings in hockey, Lakers, Clippers, and then we've got the Chargers.
There's a WNBA team there, I'm sure.
Yeah, but they don't call that part of the big four.
Really?
Big four is basketball, football, basketball, and hockey.
Seven.
Baseball.
Let's see.
Eight.
Wow.
There you go.
Chargers, Angels, Dodgers, Lakers, Clippers, Kings, and Ducks.
Ducks is what I was missing.
What's two more if you include MLS?
Ah, you didn't have the Anaheim Ducks.
No, the Ducks.
But you got it within one.
Wow.
Paul, you're up.
I'll close out Raiders.
What the hell?
I don't know anything about this.
This head coach led the Raiders to their first Super Bowl win, has the second highest win
percentage, and revolutionized sports video games by insisting the series with his name
on it was the most realistically.
He tragically died in 2021.
That is John Madden.
John Madden, of course, the coach.
It's me.
I'll try.
It's a me.
Oakland for 400.
The Oakland Coliseum was the shared home of the Raiders and the A's for many years.
In its later years, it was known for the dugouts flooding with sewage.
What year was the Coliseum built within 10 years?
Within 10 years?
Let's try 1980.
1966?
Holy shit.
They don't build what they used to.
They don't.
I saw a lot of games in there.
It didn't seem that old.
Matt.
Let's do Oakland for 600.
San Francisco Oakland Bay Bridge opened November 12, 1936.
True.
Six months before the Golden Gate Bridge at a cost of $78 million.
The estimate to replace the Eastern span in 2013 was $250 million.
With overruns, how much did it actually cost within a billion?
Pass.
Passes to me, Paul.
Matt and I both have zero.
I'll take a swing at it.
I'll say it was supposed to be $250 million.
I'll say $2.5 billion.
Good guess.
$6.4 billion.
What the shit?
I'll say it.
That's too much.
That's a lot more than I expected.
Yeah, it is.
Paul.
That's worse than the sphere.
Los Angeles, please.
Which is impressive.
And 2028, L.A. will tie London and Paris for hosting the most Olympic games.
Name one of the two previous years L.A. hosted the Olympics.
'84.
'84, I think that's right.
'84 and '32, that is correct.
Yeah.
Me, I'll do L.A. for 800.
In 2022, Will Smith slapped the shit out of Chris Rock during the Oscars,
held at this theater named after an American company specializing in audio noise reduction,
audio encoding, compression, spatial audio, and HDR imaging.
Oh, sorry, that question is directed at me.
That's right.
I was just reading the question and waiting on one of you guys to answer it.
I believe that is the Dolby Theater.
Got to be.
It is the Dolby Theater.
I was like, why aren't you all talking?
The Thomas Dolby Theater.
Matt, you got it, Oakland or L.A.?
If I get both of these questions, I can get in second place.
And right now, I'm just in second place.
No, I'm in third.
I'm in second place, yeah.
Get 200 points behind me for second place.
Oakland for 800 to seal a tie for second place.
Let's do it.
According to a random list I found online,
the ATAT from Star Wars was inspired by the huge four-legged cranes on the port of Oakland.
It also says the port is top five in North America.
What does @@ stand for or what's the largest port in North America?
Geez.
Matt, there are two very simple questions here.
You can answer either of them.
Artificial testicle, artificial testicle, because it's two balls.
Sure, you got that one dead on.
Yeah.
Go for your bonus.
I thought the largest port in North America was the port of San Francisco, but I might be wrong.
But I have to guess here because we're at the end of the time here.
I'll go with the port of San Francisco.
All right, let's try it.
All-terrain armored transport or port of Los Angeles?
Port of LA.
You're just a little north, just a little north.
I got all-terrain, but I couldn't put my finger on armored transport completely.
Paul closing out the category and the game, Los Angeles for 600.
LA is the home of many conventions and trade shows.
This trade show covers the video game industry and at one time was the largest gaming expo of the year.
E3, which no longer exists.
E3 or Electronic Entertainment Expo, that's absolutely right.
It's gone.
And with that correct answer, Paul just submitted his win with 3,000 points.
I'm in second place with 200 points.
Matt is in a close third with a negative 800 points.
Port of Los Angeles.
Port of Los Angeles for the loss.
Thank you, Diamond Scoop.
If you want to send us a scooperty, heyscoops.com.
Head over there right on the home page.
Make us a scooperty, make us a Price is Right, Jack vs. Nerd.
Make us an obelisk, Jack vs. Nerd.
And buy some tickets to Scoop Fest all right there at heyscoops.com.
We opened up a couple of more whiskey barbecue tickets for Scoop Fest.
So there are a couple of them there on the website to purchase.
Head on over there, get you some whiskey barbecue tickets, get you some Scoop Fest tickets.
Come join us here in beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada at the end of September.
My brother's coming.
My brother's going to be at the thing.
Oh, that's fantastic.
So come and meet my brother.
Yeah, yeah.
And we're going to do it at the Orleans.
Call the Orleans, use our discount code.
Stay at the Orleans with us.
I actually see Akshay Mysore up there.
I believe he was the first winner of the American Accent contest at Scoop Fest.
Yes, I believe he was.
Akshay, good to see you, buddy.
Yeah, thanks for popping on, pal.
I love seeing Akshay.
Shout out to Wayne and Captain James T. Scoop for joining us here today.
Thank you so much.
If you want to join us for a live broadcast, you should be a member of our Patreon.
Join us at any level and you'll get invites to our Zoom link.
And you can do that at PreachingFun.com.
Oh, right.
I forgot I had to hit a button.
Or if you, like Dead Lazlo in the chat, wonders aloud if Matt Donnelly will still be allowed
in the Orleans in September, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
See you at the gym.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can help
keep this show on the air.
If you think this show is worth more than $0, we would certainly appreciate you visiting
PreachingFun.com and/or fartsinabag.biz.
You don't really have to go to both, but it couldn't hurt.
All right.
Couldn't hurt.
Well, thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you at the Cone.
We'll see you soon.
It's just a nice friendly thing that my friends and I say to each other.
Anytime we're just leaving the room, we go, "Hey, we'll see you at the Cone."
What are your favorite songs to play on drums, Keeler?
Oh, no one else by Weezer, because that's one of my favorites.
All right.
Solid choice.
Let's go.
We're PreachingFun.
Come together on the drums.
Boom-ba-boom.
That's the drum solo.
solo and come together. See ya!