(upbeat music)
(laughing)
- This is the part of the show where we thank you,
the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
I'll tell you what, guys, I am going through these lists.
I am so close.
I'm really close to being able to thank each and every one
of you by name this month.
And by the next episode, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna thank each and every Ice Cream Truck Driver
by name this month at this part of the episode.
Don't you worry.
All you Ice Cream Truck Drivers out there,
who are the Ice Cream Truck Drivers, you may be asking?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
- These are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream
straight to your fucking ear holes.
If you wanna be an Ice Cream Truck Driver,
and I sure hope you do, preachingfun.com is where you can go.
Preachingfun.com, head over there,
sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
- Ooh, a show.
- Hey, Johnny, do you wanna go to an ice cream social?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Great, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- Are we on Twitch, Jacob?
- We are on Twitch.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello, Twitch.
(laughs)
- Ann advised me to raise my computers.
(upbeat music)
- All the problems are solved.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social.
Sitting over there in Las Vegas, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting over there with a nice raised computer,
it's Paul Mattingly.
I'm Jacob the Audio Guy, we're preachingfun.
- You know why to go chin gut first to the audience, Paul?
- I mean, I can do whatever is gonna sell the tickets.
Whatever's gonna put butts in seats.
I know some people are here for the chin gut.
I'll tell ya, now I just have to find
a more permanent solution.
'Cause right now, the computer is balanced
on a big stack of DVD holder bags.
- Oh no.
- Bags?
Bags.
- What do you mean bags?
- Bags.
- So these are what I got.
- What's a DVD holder bag?
- This is a DVD holder bag.
So it opens up--
- Oh, like a CD wallet, a big CD wallet bag thing.
- Sort of.
But it holds DVDs.
- Yeah, you know, I see what you mean.
I'm trying to describe it for the audience
who can't see your crazy thing
that you have your computer balanced on.
- It holds whole DVD.
I've got a stack of five of these in another bag.
And then on top of that, I have precariously rested
a box of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
little figure people from Fisher Price on top of that.
- You don't have books? - In another box.
I do have books, but I feel like,
you know what's funny, Matt?
You know what's funny?
That was my first thought.
First of all, right next to me is where I keep my stack of--
- So incredulous.
- I keep my stack of improv books right here next to me.
- Yes. - Okay?
- Right.
- I just happen to take all my improv books--
- Should I use these books?
No.
- No, I took them all, they're in my backpack.
I took them all to class for my first class on Monday
to show everybody what books to check out
if they're interested in looking up more improv stuff.
So I don't have, but here's the other thing.
Here's the other thing.
Nice, stack of wires.
I do have a box of wires.
- It's a box.
Just don't worry about what's in the box.
- It's a box of wires.
- It's the box that matters.
- Well, I've got a box of wires right down here
that'll work.
- Matt just shifted his camera so that we could see
a clear box filled with some electronic doohickeys
that he has just sitting in his office.
- It's all my audio equipment for any kind of podcasting.
- Yeah, I've got--
- It's an excellent box to set a laptop on.
If Matt needed a box to set a laptop on,
I'd be like, "Matt, use that box right there."
I didn't notice what was in it.
- I'll have to do that.
Unfortunately, the space here is limited.
I'll figure it out, but I do need a box.
- Call me crazy, I'm a box-not-bags guy
when it comes to putting valuable equipment on a--
- But I'm also a bags-not-books guy
because for whatever reason, my brain goes to,
oh, but what if I need that book?
- I'll send you some of my magic books
that I've never cracked.
(laughing)
- Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I have, do you have sentimental books
that you keep in your home?
- Yes. - Oh, yeah.
- I have several sentimental books that I keep in my home
that I can't imagine ever reading,
but they were given to me by like family members--
- Oh, that you never read? - Or something like that.
- Oh, yeah, I have something I never read.
- Oh, no, I don't have any--
- My uncle was an automotive expert.
- Oh. - He would go to court
and testify for, I'm really not exactly sure,
so I'm telling you kind of what I understand.
- Was he the one behind unsafe at any speed?
- Wasn't that Ralph Nader?
- Yeah, it was Ralph Nader.
- Okay, no, that was Ralph Nader's fault.
- You're related to Ralph Nader?
Holy shit, Jacob Nader?
- I did have an aunt, or I guess I do,
who worked for Ralph Nader.
- She used to be like his chief of staff or something.
- It's all coming together, what a tangled web we weave.
- We have technical scoop port in the chat here,
and there's technical scoop port for a living.
I'm wondering, do you ever have to address
what people are putting their computers on top of
as a technical scoop port person?
- Yeah, it's getting a nod. - He says yes.
- He's nodding, he's just nodding with,
all the time, he says in the chat, all the time.
- So like, I put it on-- - So people's computers
just fall off of things all the time.
I've put on a series of delightful pillows,
and now I'm having difficulty operating my computer.
- I had my computer-- - Oh, have you ever had
the thing where they-- - Perfectly balanced.
- Stacked the laptop up on pillows and everything,
and then the pillows clog up the fans,
and the laptop overheats?
- Right, yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's happened to me.
- I had 'em-- - Just blocking up the fans.
- I had it stacked up on a bunch of bananas,
and the bananas went south of cheese,
and then my laptop got infested with fruit flies, so.
(laughing)
- So you have a record.
- Paul, say that sentence again.
- Well, I-- - For the--
- I stacked my, no, I didn't really.
I was playing, I was playing.
I would not stack my computer on well-stacked bananas,
let them go to rot, and then let the computer--
- Bullshit, bullshit, you would not do that.
- I wouldn't do that.
No, no, no, if you came into this basement,
I will tell you what you would not find.
Any food or decayable items outside of laundry detergent
and a bottle or two of diet soda, that's it.
There is nothing-- - What about small rodents?
What about squirrels?
- No, everything else in this basement is plastique, baby.
Plastique.
Plastic or pressed wood, that's all that lives in this basement.
- I'll give you some pressed wood.
(laughing)
- All my shelves are fucking pressed wood.
- When all the kids left my birthday party,
I took all the leftover balloon animals,
put them in one pile, and I put my computer right on top
with the old balloon animal.
(laughing)
- Let it heat up. - Really propped it up well.
(spitting)
- Paul.
- No, I have books about auto accidents and stuff.
My uncle used to go testify about auto accidents
and tire marks on highways and that kind of thing.
He was one of those types of expert witnesses.
- It'd be like, well, Your Honor--
- Books about that kind of stuff.
I'm like, I'm not gonna read these books,
but they're cool.
They're never gonna come around.
- Clearly the victim in this crime
was a worthless piece of shit
because there were no tire marks
in front of where he was struck by the vehicle.
(laughing)
- He was clearly not even in an automobile, Your Honor.
Clearly denoting him as one of the poors.
- One of the poors.
One of the worthless piece of shit poors.
- One of the poors who the law does not apply to.
One of the poors.
- All right, Matt, what did you wanna know?
- Well, I'm just saying,
Jacob's uncle was trying to get him paid.
You know, you get paid to testify in court
when you're an expert.
- Oh, yeah, no, he was a paid expert witness.
- Making that money, making that dollar.
- He worked for LSU and he was a paid expert
in those types of cases.
- Now, he wasn't working for the big, big auto people, was he?
- No, no, no, no.
He was a university professor at LSU.
- Oh, so he was standing up for the middleman.
- He was an independent expert.
He would come in and testify for like,
yeah, just testify to the facts of an auto accident.
- Leon piping up in the chat
that he has to pay quite a bit for his expert witnesses,
so he would know.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
So, Paul, I'm gonna tell you a story
that's gonna make you too messent, buddy.
- I've got a feeling about what it is.
Go ahead, tell me.
- I was going to mail some things out yesterday
to the UPS store nearby my house.
I was, it's actually totally random.
Someone reached out and said,
"Hey, this is a crazy question,
"but I guess this is what Facebook is for.
"I think I went to one of your comedy shows in the '90s
"and I bought one of your shirts
"that said possible side effects but said free sex."
- Yeah.
- And I--
- Oh, yeah, yeah, the one that says two different things
depending on where you are.
- Yeah, if you look at our store,
the one with the salt pork shirt is based on.
- Yeah, we modeled it after that.
- And, apologies to Mike Nilsen for using UPS.
They're closer, buddy.
FedEx is all the way up on Stephanie.
And--
(laughs)
Anyways--
- That's Brooke's company.
- This is a side note, but yeah, yeah.
So they reached out and I was like,
I go, "Oh my gosh," and I was like,
"I don't know where those shirts are."
And I go, "You know what?
"I have a box of old shit in my garage.
"I bet I have one in there."
And I looked into my box and I found my last
free sex possible side effects shirt and I thought,
"Well, it's sitting in a box for me.
"This person wants it."
- Right.
- So like wear or hang up.
So I went to the UPS store to mail this person the shirt.
- That's very kind of you.
- So a part of you decided that you didn't need
to hold onto that for the future Matt Donnelly Museum.
- Yes.
- Go ahead and just give that away.
- Yeah, yeah.
Matt at 47 looking back at the T-shirt he made
when he was in his 20s is a fine length of time
to remember that time.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Ever since I showed Paul my rig,
slowly my laptop's been sliding into my lap.
- Oh, and yet my DVD bags remain solidly steadfast.
How strange.
- All right, time in scoops.
Team bag, team box, team books.
Let's go.
- Paul was right.
Paul was right.
(laughing)
- Get more bananas, Leafy Screamer.
- But I wouldn't have done it unless I showed you my thing
and I put everything out of my arrangement.
- It's a poor craftsman blames his tools, Matt.
- I'm so happy right now.
I was so close.
I ran out of time.
I was so close to adjusting my monitor set up
in my office here before we started today.
And I'm so glad I didn't be falling over right now.
(laughing)
So I, right next door to the UPS store
is the comic book store.
- Oh yeah.
- And I was like, man, Paul got me
that absolute Batman trade.
- You hit it exactly the right day, serendipity.
- Totally, I didn't realize it.
I walked into the complex with the day it came out.
- The day of volume two.
Oh really?
Yeah, the day of absolute volume two, absolute Batman.
Yeah, oh crazy.
I walked in and then he was like, hey, what are you here for?
I was like, oh, I was curious if you had absolute Batman.
He goes, oh, that's right, that came out today.
And I go, I didn't realize it.
I literally just happened to be mailing something next door.
And he's like, oh yeah, no, it's a great book.
Are you enjoying it?
And I wanted to be like, look, we can do small talk,
but I am not one of you, is what I really wanted to say.
- Right, right.
- But I can't say it.
- Jump in.
- You wanna like stop him and explain to him?
Be like, no, no, I really didn't know it was coming out today.
- Jump in both feet.
- This is great.
- I was like, oh man, I don't, I was like,
my kids come here 'cause they're in the system.
I was like, maybe 'cause my kids come here
'cause children buy comic books.
And--
- And so do well-educated men and women
and people of indeterminate gender
or whatever they want to be.
- He plowed right ahead.
He was like, you closeted nerd.
And he just dove right in.
- Yeah, good for him.
He knew what to do.
- He saw you, he knew you.
- Yeah.
- One of us.
- Okay.
- And I said, it's really my podcast partner
who turned me on to this, the bond.
He goes, oh, what's your podcast?
- I gave him a chip that last time.
- Well, Paul, so did I.
- And?
- I'm just saying, I went in.
- You chipped him again.
- I chipped him again.
- Awesome.
- Get to message, Paul.
- I am.
- I was like, so I bought an absolute Batman.
He said there are two other books in the series
that aren't included in the trades.
Art Gam and some other adventure.
And I bought those.
- Wow, look at you.
You're even deeper than me right now.
- Oh, he even upsold you.
- He upsold me.
'Cause here's what happened.
I flew on Frontier and that's a hellscape
that humans don't deserve.
Among it being the Maury Pulvich show airlines,
Jerry Springer Airlines.
- It's also no Wi-Fi.
While you sit on those uncomfortable lawn chairs,
it's no Wi-Fi.
And my absolute Batman got me through a flight
and I was like, oh, I need to just have this handy
for my next travel.
And so I bought the thing.
So I bought, I put my name in the system
and I chipped the guy
and he said he wanted to check out our podcast.
- Fantastic, dude. - All right.
I am so proud of you on so many levels.
- I'm glad you brought this up though.
'Cause you always do Wi-Fi on the planes.
- I do.
- Paul, do you do Wi-Fi when you fly or no?
- Not usually, no.
- I don't either.
I kind of enjoy the few hours where I'm disconnected.
I read a book or watch a movie or something.
- Yeah, I go into airplane mode
and I turn on something I've downloaded.
I usually just listen to podcasts when I'm flying.
- Like I'm aware that you can get Wi-Fi on planes.
I just don't really think to do it.
- I'll turn on my podcast and fall asleep is what I do.
That's-- - Fair.
- That's kind of the whole thing.
- And then you have to rewind your podcast
and find where you left off?
- No, it's usually just podcasts.
I've decided these are just my sleep podcasts
for this round, yeah. - Okay.
- 'Cause I travel with just my phone.
So I'm an ogre and don't know how to download
an episode of television to my phone.
So I usually just try to see if the Wi-Fi is strong enough.
- Oh, right, right, right.
- So I know like different airlines
have different strengths of Wi-Fi.
Netflix is generally pretty agreeable
with even the weakest Wi-Fi.
- Well, Netflix is also the app that works best
for downloading stuff too.
- Okay, well now I know.
- Netflix has the best download technology on their app.
So they are the best in airplane mode.
- That's what I have to start doing.
So I'm jealous-- - But now like HBO
and some of those others have caught up a little bit
with the app technology.
- When I see them download, I'm so jealous
of people who have downloaded full shows
or movies to watch on the plane.
- Oh yeah.
- You're ahead of the curve,
busting out the graphic novel, dude.
You're ahead of the curve having to trade paperback
'cause people can be, but plus I'm telling you like,
you're on the right track.
You cannot go wrong with that absolute Batman book
because Scott Snyder, who did the whole "Court of Owls" series
and a bunch of other Batman stuff that I love,
a lot of his work, he's done some of the best Batman
of the last 15 years.
But this series, it is selling so well.
Like numbers keep going up per issue.
I believe they're on issue 18
and the orders are higher than when they started,
which is crazy for any book.
- Oh, right, right, right.
So it's increasing in popularity and stuff.
- Yes, people are buying it, more people.
So comic books or comic shops are ordering more copies.
So it is just, it is growing, growing, growing
in a way that is not normal 'cause it's that popular.
So you're looking, what you're reading right now in 10 years
will probably be the DCU film adaptation.
- That's what seems like it's headed for sure.
- Oh, gotcha.
Let me ask you something, Paul.
- Simply because it's so popular, yes.
- These different kind of Batman properties,
like back in the day, there'd be like the detective Batman
and now there's this, all the different things.
Is that, that's just different writers
or different creators all under the same corporate umbrella
or is it different people that are going to them
to do this or are these part,
I guess what I'm asking is like,
is the author of this current Batman series
that y'all are talking about here,
is that somebody who's been working
with the Batman comic group, whatever they are,
for some time, there you go.
Has he been working with DC
or have they been working with DC for some time
or is this like a new person that has come in
to push things in a different direction?
- No, Scott Snyder's done Batman forever as far as--
- Oh, this is Sny, oh, okay.
I didn't realize this was Scott Snyder.
- Comic book time. - I know that name.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so he's been at it for a while
and this is a new re-imagining reboot of the character.
A very interesting take, which I love.
So it lets everything become kind of fresh and new.
And everything's under this absolute umbrella.
So I don't know if you recall,
it's crazy to me that it was 20 years ago
when the Marvel Ultimates started, but it did.
So Ultimates is what basically inspired the MCU.
So-- - The movies.
- The films that you see are essentially based off
the Ultimates in a lot of ways.
So "Ultimate Spider-Man" was probably the strongest,
followed very closely by "The Ultimates,"
which was "The Avengers."
- Got it.
- So those were the two books
that I followed really closely.
But every little while, you've gotta do a reset.
And currently, DC is eating Marvel's lunch
as far as the success they're having with "The Absolute Line,"
which allows for these characters to be set
in a new timeline, new era, new stuff,
and not say, we're not throwing out the baby
with the bathwater.
You still have all the other classics up.
And there are still ongoing series based more closely
on classic interpretations of the characters.
This is not the only "Batman" book right now.
This is not even the main "Batman" book.
The main "Batman" book, I believe, I wanna say,
is it Zdarsky who's got it right now?
No, Zdarsky doesn't have it right now.
- Okay, let me ask you this.
So whoever's writing the main "Batman" book
and then Snyder writing this one,
are those people working together in any way?
They are not having to-- - Are they having discussions?
Are they like coordinating, storyboarding,
anything like that? - Not currently, no.
- They're completely separate, and they're--
- The only way that those-- - I'm more curious
about the business aspect of how these things work.
Is it like the, you mentioned the MCU in film.
Is it like that where you have kind of the whole thing
storyboarded out? - Now this is the thing.
- And then you're trying to, hold on, hold on,
you're trying to work within that storyboard.
Or is it several different artists working independently
but kind of keeping an eye on each other?
- Within the Absolute Universe,
they are just now starting to do crossovers
within the Absolute Universe.
So Absolute Wonder Woman has met Absolute Batman.
So that's starting, those characters are starting
to interact within the Absolute Universe.
- How did it go?
- I don't know, I didn't read it yet.
- Oh, straight to anal, straight to anal.
- I'm still waiting for my Absolute Wonder Woman volume two
also, but yes, Jacob, that's kind of been a weird thing.
- They both discovered they were tops
and then it got awkward.
- It's been a weird thing with all the,
you know, the crossovers that these comic book companies
have become addicted to.
So when you do something like Civil War or Secret Wars
or KO is the big crossover event that's happening
right now in DC, so a lot of the mainline books
do have to communicate with each other
'cause their main characters are interacting with each other,
but a lot of times that will throw a monkey wrench
into what other creators are working on
in their individual books and it'll either completely
fuck up the story in some way
and maybe they'll have to rejigger everything
or they'll just be like, well, here's two issues
that don't have anything to do with the continuity
we're trying to project, but this fits in
with the ongoing overarching storyline
that's happening in the universe.
- Like, Paul, you brought up that like the,
Marvel just launched a thing called Secret Wars
'cause they thought war and secret
were exciting words for kids.
- Yes, that was the thing that they did back in the '80s,
yeah.
- And that's why I think DC just launched a new series
called La Boo Boo Mr. Beast, so.
- Wow, that's gonna fly off the fucking shelves.
- Yeah, it sold out.
- That's the way to do it.
I just saw there was a George Lucas La Boo Boo
limited edition.
- How big's the goiter on it?
- Look at it, it doesn't not look like him.
But he's wearing like--
- I'll tell you who else doesn't not look like George Lucas
and that is the following sponsor.
- Today's show, Madden Manley's Ice Cream Social
is brought to you by these fine makers
and providers of products.
A single photograph of US President Martin Van Buren.
That's right, today being sold to you
could be a single photograph of US President
Martin Van Buren and that's from Belgian Tripple Scoop
in 2025.
- Hello, I'm a single photograph of Martin Van Buren.
I'm speaking to you through the magic of picture magic.
This photograph talks, that's why it's so expensive.
That's the only way we can keep the company afloat.
I cost 18 million dollars and after I'm sold, that's it.
We're shutting the doors on the storefront.
We're closed for business but we'll stay open
until someone buys me the talking picture
of Martin Van Buren.
That's all, that's it.
However--
- I'm sorry, was that a prerecorded message
or can you have conversations with people?
- Oh, I can talk to people.
- Bah!
- Yeah, welcome to the shop.
That's why I'm so expensive, I'm 18 million dollars.
Here's the thing--
- Are you conscious?
- Yeah, very much so and to the point
where I've been giving advice to my business partners,
I've been telling them this is a stupid business plan
just to sell one picture of Martin Van Buren,
talking or not, conscious or not.
18 million dollars, that's great but what are you doing?
Your overhead's gotta be out of control
for the rental of this space so I've decided
that we're going into furniture as well as my picture.
So you can buy the Martin Van Buren while you're here,
you can shop and buy one of my beautiful Martin Van Buren's
suitable to put me on top of someday.
- Does the bureau also speak?
- I'm afraid not, unless you put me in it,
you can do that, you can stick my picture inside
and I'll be like (mumbles) haunted or something,
I don't know who, it's not really haunted though,
I'm just a talking picture, it's different from a haunting.
- That's a good question, are you a talking picture
or do you have the consciousness of Martin Van Buren?
- Not at all, I'm just a picture that has consciousness.
- Oh, you just look like Martin Van Buren.
- Well, I'm just a picture of Martin Van Buren,
I look like a two dimensional image of you.
- Do you know which president Martin Van Buren was?
- No, I don't even know who I am, I don't know what I am.
I'm a picture thing.
- Are you also selling a red and white wine blend
from France?
- Yes, you are, okay good, I was worried someone else
was trying to profit from your name
and selling Martin Van Bordeaux.
- No, Martin Van Bordeaux's are being,
you can buy the Martin Van Bureau's
that's so angry. - I actually stacked my laptop
on top of some Martin Van Bureaux.
(laughing)
- Just bottles?
- Just bottles, it's very sturdy.
- Well, I also told the guys, hey, what do the kids love?
They love the vape, huh?
Yeah, so we got you hooked up G, we got that sticky icky,
if you know what I'm saying.
So come on in and try some of Martin Van Blazen's.
420, what up G?
- Now, you're not selling containers
of just your piss, are you?
- Martin Van Juren, of course.
- Okay, all right, let me make sure
this line is very diverse.
- But it's not just containers of my piss,
it's in custom shoes made for skateboarders.
They're Martin's Vans Juren.
(laughing)
- All right, let's go for the check out.
- The soggy step.
(laughing)
- Martin Van's Juren.
- Dead last low, a bird sanctuary, Martin Van Buren.
Yeah, I like that, that's good.
Oh, I had a kitty cat named Martin Van Puren.
That was like Katy Perry, that's Kitty Perry.
Good one, Leon.
We, if my brain had been in a more punny place,
we could have rocked that a little bit longer.
I was, I was, I'm still pulling on the old--
- Oh boy, that's a shame.
- I'm pulling on the old motor.
Ah boy, you son of a bitch, you son of a bitch.
- Too bad, too bad for the rest of us.
(laughing)
- This is that he had his laptop on a book of puns
so he couldn't access it.
- That's right, he needed that book.
He needed that book. - Never stack,
never stack on books.
You might need that book.
(laughing)
- I had to listen to my own fucking advice, I'm stupid.
- Matt, are your boys trying to buy up
all the Mr. Beast jerky and whatnots?
- You know, they're surprisingly not
as like uber-focused like that.
So like for a second, my youngest was into Prime drinks,
and then-- - Okay.
- But then he's like, after a while he's like,
these don't taste good, I'm gonna stop buying them.
- Oh, for God's sake, they're the worst shit ever.
- Those Paul boys are the devil.
- Now, Mr. Beast does pride himself
on doing ethical chocolate,
which actually is like a huge thing
that we don't like to talk about
'cause who wants to start taking pride in their chocolate?
- Oh yeah, I thought that was only in Vegas.
- Well, I'm in Vegas, I don't know if it is anywhere else.
- Ethel M. Chocolate?
(laughing)
Isn't that a Vegas company?
- It is a Vegas company, yes.
- Okay.
Oh, ethical chocolate.
- Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Ethel cool chocolate.
- So he does--
- She should call ethical chocolate.
- So the kids will buy some Feastable bars,
but I'm okay with that since he is trying
to actually set a precedent of you pay a little more
for your chocolate, but it's ethical.
- Does he pay the cacao harvesters $2 instead of one a day?
- That's right, that's right.
- What a saint.
- Yeah.
- Hey, my question, the only thing that I care about
as far as your kids are concerned,
did you show them the He-Man trailer?
- I brought up at dinner and we have not had a chance.
So last time I had a corporate gig,
I wasn't home.
Tonight I'm home with the boys
and I'm gonna try to show them the He-Man trailer.
I did bring it up.
They showed very little interest in watching it,
just so you know.
- Oh, of course, 'cause they don't know from He-Man.
- That's right, but we are gonna watch it tonight.
And I'll report to you either privately or publicly
about it.
(laughing)
- Well, it's gotta be public, that's what it's all about.
We're gonna hear it on the pod.
- Fair enough, fair enough.
- Speaking of public things that people are gonna hear
on the pod, this is technically Scoop Mail,
but I wanna do it now.
Lauren Shreve sent us an email
and Lauren is setting up an LLC for HR Consulting.
- Okay.
- Needs a name for the business.
Lauren is asking us to help name the business.
- All right.
- HR Consulting business. - HR Consulting,
what's it about?
- Oh, HR Consulting.
- HR Consulting. - Not like HR stands for,
it stands for human resources.
- HR does stand for something, Paul.
- I know.
- I thought it, well, it stands for a puff and stuff.
- It's Lauren is setting up an HR puff and stuff, LLC.
- Okay.
- Don't discuss Israel, LLC.
- That would be.
(laughing)
- This is not about Israel, LLC.
- HR is the enemy, LLC.
- Fight the real enemy, LLC.
- Yeah.
- There's still. - Oh, okay.
- There's still such thing as the C word, LLC.
(laughing)
- Why didn't you just tell me to my face,
I would have reacted better, LLC.
(laughing)
- We're watching you, LLC.
- Let's see, 'cause you don't wanna do something corny
like Olive Branch or like Peacemaking or Peacemaker,
that'd be good, Peacemaker.
- Peacemaker.
- How about like, humane recognition?
- No.
- For HR.
- How about workforce alchemy?
- Synergy, the show.
- Yeah.
Two plus two equals five?
- Resourcing humanely.
- Well, we're getting some suggestions here in the chat.
- Coca-Cola, LLC, try that one, that's good.
- Lemur Kramer is the Martin Vroomen resources, that's good.
Leon Kasab's got hitting some dingers, LLC.
That's a good one, scooper nova girl,
this could have been an email, LLC, I like that.
- This could have been an email, LLC, it's really funny.
- That's pretty good.
Chris Angel has a Chimera.
Why is your union rep here, LLC?
I like that.
HR Us, from Lemur Kramer, I like that one.
HR Mart, Lemur Kramer is just cranking them out.
- How about Ipatch HR, you like the VR, Ipatch HR.
- Ipatch HR?
- Yeah, 'cause Ipatch, like I patch it up,
I'm making it better, right?
There's Ipatch Pirate, and then HR with the Pirate R.
I'll just go ahead and declare me the winner on this, I won.
(group clapping)
- Oh, my dogs are in here and they are so mad
that they're not getting fed right now.
- Here's the question, so like sometimes you want,
like you have a regular business name,
but like what you put on the checks is funny, right?
- Sure.
- So like, my wife has like 11 jobs
with the same company,
but they all have the different LLCs.
And every time I get the stuff for the taxes,
I'm like, what is the company called?
And so like, no one calls it these companies,
but it's just a funny thing.
- Some of the names are wild, yeah.
- Yeah, like for this, I get paid from Penn Sunday School
from preaching to the choir, LLC.
So it depends, do you just want a funny name for the LLC
for someone to cut the check to?
Or is this like, I'm gonna get a website
and market my services, I need a real name.
- This is gonna be that.
- It's gonna be the funny check thing.
- When do you think it's gonna be?
- No, I think it's gonna be the second.
I think it's gonna be the name that she wants people
to be able to see and do business with her.
- How about Bat Shit Crossom?
- What do you think, like free beer?
- Free beer and chicken.
- Just name it after old improv teams.
- How about you call it a bear in the woods, LLC?
- Oh, I like uncomfortable conversations.
- Slang for shit.
(laughing)
- We need to talk, LLC is good too.
Yeah, something like hard conversations
might really be on the right path.
'Cause that's all anybody wants
an HR consulting firm for, right?
- Exit strategy.
- Golden parachute.
(laughing)
- Final interview.
Exit interview, exit interview, LLC.
- Exit interview.
(laughing)
- You could do which exit interview?
- It could be a New Jersey based HR firm.
- Which exit interview?
Exit only interview.
- Trim the fat LLC.
(laughing)
- One of us doesn't have a job LLC from elsewhere.
- There you go.
- That's exactly the conversations that HR--
- Oh, Fudging the Whale, Higher Expectations, H-I-R-E.
Higher Expectations.
- Oh, I like that.
- That's pretty good.
- I don't like that.
- Higher Expectations is pretty great.
- Yeah.
- What I think you have to do is take your,
the name of your first pet and the street you grew up on,
and that's how you name a company.
As far as I know, that's a--
- That's right, that's right.
- How about Employee Time of the Month?
(laughing)
- How about Anonymous Post-It Note, LLC?
- Anonymous Post-It Note.
Whistleblowers Anonymous.
(laughing)
Whistleblowers Friend.
- Yeah.
- Whistleblowers Exposed, LLC.
(laughing)
- Whistleblowers Exposed, Whistleblowers Handled.
- Oh, no.
- Well, I think you got one out of that pile, Lauren.
You're welcome.
- Just one more, just for left field, just the hawk.
Just, I don't know, it sounds pretty,
just sounds pretty boss.
- Prep that resume.
- Don't worry, we've hired the hawk.
And then--
- Hawk HR.
- Yeah.
That'll get you hired by a lot of dude, dude,
dude bro companies.
- Yeah.
- Typhus.
- We can teach people how to--
- Quit, quiet quitting, LLC.
Diversity Terminator, LLC.
(laughing)
Diversity Terminator is ridiculous.
- Yeah, I work for a company
who hired the Diversity Terminator.
- You're right.
- Part time.
- Yeah.
- Fucking shit.
- Part time.
- But at least they're helping out ICE.
- I swear to God, every day I go in there,
I work a little bit less.
- Yeah.
- Just like, fuck this company forever.
(laughing)
Fuck this company forever.
- That'll show ematically.
- No, I got 'em, I got 'em right there.
Even though I sweat my fucking balls off
and move millions of dollars of merchandise
every goddamn week, I got 'em.
(laughing)
Oh fuck that company.
- I can't quit you, LLC.
(laughing)
- I can't quit you without two weeks notice, LLC.
- If I can make you quit, this company doesn't have
to pay unemployment benefits, LLC.
(laughing)
- If working here's right, I don't wanna be wrong, LLC.
- What pension, LLC?
- What pension, indeed, indeed.
- Well that's a joke I was doing my shows now,
where I get someone up on stage and say,
"What do you do for work?"
And they go, "I'm retired."
And I go, "Oh my God, Gen Z, close your ears.
"Close your ears."
(laughing)
- Right, yeah, 'cause it'll never happen.
- It'll never happen.
- That's a really good one.
- That's a good one.
- It'll never happen, it'll never happen for you.
- How about silence plebes?
(laughing)
- Oh, oh, I like that.
- LLC.
- Gen Z, close your ears.
- Failing upwards, LLC, that's a good one, Leon.
The Oompa HR Loompas from Bossy.
(laughing)
Yeah, @will LLC from Lemur Kramer, yep, yep.
Oh, @will HR LLC is really good.
- What's the, it's a 10-9, is that the form, right?
- 10-99?
- Or is that, what's the independent contractor form?
- 10-99.
- Yeah, 10-99, yeah.
(laughing)
- I don't know, it's just, you're an independent contractor.
- Yeah.
- LLC.
- Here today, 10-99 tomorrow, LLC.
- That's it.
- You know what else has a really good name
for their business?
That's the following sponsor.
- Today's show is brought to you by,
we did a single photograph.
Yes to Prop 69.
That's from Open Bayou 2021.
Vote yes to Prop 69.
- Well, hey there, hard going, everybody.
I'm here from the Open Bayou out here in Louisiana.
We looking to pass us the Prop 69, huh?
- Yeah, you know that Prop 69, what it's gonna do,
it's gonna free up all the gators living in that swamp.
Go ahead and say yes to freeing up the gators.
Then walk across all the way to Beale Street.
We're gonna open up Beale to the gators.
We're just gonna give it to the gators.
We took it from them, we're giving it back.
Beale for the gators.
That's what Prop 69 is all about.
Say yes to gators walking up and down Beale Street.
Sliding into jazz holes,
listening to the fine music that gets played
up and down the boardwalk.
- Where do you think Beale Street is?
- I don't know.
Where is it?
- What city do you think Beale Street is in?
- Memphis is where Beale Street is.
- Okay, so this is why we gotta pass this Prop.
So we let all the gators in New Orleans
do a parade you see all the way down to Memphis town, huh?
- We're doing a second line to Memphis share, come on!
- Oh, when the streets get filled with gators,
oh, when the streets get filled with gators,
they're gonna walk all the way down to Memphis.
Oh, when the streets get filled with gators.
- Yee-hoo!
Who wants to come on down to Bourbon Street
and try some barbecue today?
- No, no, no, see, share,
we going all the way down to Memphis, hon.
We had enough of your...
- Hey, cowpokes, welcome to Bourbon Street.
We got dry rub, we got wet barbecue.
This my kind of place, now I tell you what.
Hon, please don't be turning me into a pouch bag
or some kind of shoe.
I'm a friendly gator, don't you see?
- A pouch bag?
(laughing)
- Don't you go making me a pouch bag?
- Don't make me a pouch bag perfect
for putting a computer on top of you for balance.
(laughing)
- I found my thrill as a gator on Beale.
- I just sit there, I was like,
he does not know where Beale Street is.
- Of course I don't know where Beale Street is.
- Yes, no, but nobody else brought up Beale Street, Paul.
- Isn't that that cop show?
- Nope, Beale Street Blues.
- Oh, Beale Street Blues.
- Now y'all go on out there and be careful.
This here, Memphis, we don't want nobody,
we don't want nobody getting hurt out there now.
(laughing)
Memphis P.D.-- - Right here in Memphis.
- Memphis P.D. out there on Beale Street
ain't never gonna be the same.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna go listen to some Dr. John
playing down here in Memphis.
(laughing)
Come on, Dr. John, where you at?
- Oh yeah, the gators are coming.
- I just got a voicemail.
- Oh shit. - Oh.
- My glasses are ready.
- Where from? - Oh.
- Pearl Vision.
- From the Pearl Vision?
- Yeah.
They take-- - What you stripped?
- They take, oh, I'm actually not as bad as,
oh, did I talk about that?
I talked about that I was gonna go to the eye doctor.
Did I talk about going to the eye doctor?
- I think we were gonna talk about going there
and we talked about having reading glasses around the house.
- Yeah, yeah, so I have reading glasses around the house
and I went there and I was like so afraid
that they were gonna be like, did you drive here?
- Here's these Coke bottles, you blindy.
- But they gave me five vision tests.
I did like a round of different tests,
the test for different things on the eye.
- Uh-huh.
- And they said I have a very basic prescription,
nothing too crazy.
- That fits, clock that.
- Basic bitch.
(laughing)
- Here's your basic bitch glasses, you basic bitch.
Once you go have your chicken salad for lunch,
you fucking basic bitch, get out of here.
Here's your glasses.
- Are you nearsighted, farsighted, or both?
- Both.
I need tough, I got progressives, right,
so I can do the far from the top and tiny at the bottom.
- Let's just pour some milk in your fucking eyes,
get you some lactic acid, you basic bitch.
(laughing)
- You fucking cereal eating basic bitch.
So--
- Milk is a basic acid, right?
Or is that Beale Street?
- Beale Street.
- That's Beale Street.
- I'm trying not to give you, oh shit, oh fuck, real quick.
To derail everything.
- That's fine.
- Corrections time.
- I'm not passionate about talking about my glasses,
but that's--
- Corrections time.
And made me put in a correction.
Last episode I claimed that the interstate
was designed specifically for truckers.
- Uh-huh.
- It was in fact specifically designed
for the military industrial complex
to be able to transport military vehicles more efficiently.
First and foremost.
The trucking thing was a secondary benefit.
- Oh, a side effect was helping the trucking industry.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- And destroying the train.
- And destroying the train bearing monopolies.
And yeah, well I mean we have far less children
with one leg in this country thanks to that.
That's true.
More dead ones, but far less maimed kids.
- Oh man.
- But dead whole kids.
- Oh yeah, dead and intact for the most part.
Dead in the car, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean well, I guess how do you judge intact?
It's still belted in, does that count?
- Yes. - I guess, yeah.
- It depends. - Blood on the freeway.
- If it's a really tender chicken,
you can like pull the leg out.
I don't know, it depends, it depends.
- It's done.
- Oh, you just jarred another thing from me, Matt.
- Let's do it, let's keep going.
We're on fire.
- Guess what I did this week?
- Yes.
- What?
- I made chicken and dumplings.
- Yeah.
- Out of a can?
You made chicken and dumplings?
- Nope, nope.
I'm learning, I'm learning.
- Okay.
- This was--
- Did you use a cooking pot?
- Yes.
This was a six or a seven, I would say.
Six, seven.
- Six, seven.
- I did not hit it out of the park like I'd hoped,
but I'm going to change up my recipe.
- Your first attempt.
- First attempt, yes, yeah.
I'm pretty happy.
- Myra wants to know, did you use a Dutch oven?
- No, just a big pot.
No vegetables are added in my--
- I just farted directly in Anne's face.
I didn't hold her under the covers.
- No vegetables are added in my--
- But Paul says chicken and dumplings.
He means chicken and dumplings.
- Yeah, that's it.
No vegetables, no, no, no.
There are plenty of people who do celery and carrots
and onions and shit. - Peas.
- Peas, peas is a common one, yeah.
- Peas, get the fuck out of here.
- Yeah, throw some peas in there.
You don't even taste them.
- Disgusting.
No, no, no.
So we bought a bunch of--
- It's like a football ball in your soup.
- Yeah, it's delightful.
We had a bunch of chicken from Costco, which was--
- You're making a gesture with your hands
like you're holding a shotgun.
What did you buy a chicken in?
What form of chicken-- - It was in a sack.
It was in a sack.
It was de-boned rotisserie chicken in a sack.
- Paul would show you the sack,
but it's currently holding up his laptop.
- Wait, that sounds, wait, who sells de-boned,
how does one get de-boned chicken in a sack?
- At Costco. - Really?
I didn't even eat the chicken.
- Yeah, it's like shredded chicken in a bag.
- I didn't really get it de-boned.
- Jacob knows exactly what I'm talking about.
- I do.
- Just because I don't doesn't mean I'm accusatory.
I can learn too.
You're learning, I'm learning.
- You son of a bitch.
- I bought sack chicken from the Costco.
- You come on down to Beale Street,
we all settle this man to man.
- We're gonna settle this up right here.
Who's eating who's chicken?
Dr. John?
- That person speaking, Aaron Burr.
- Aaron Burr.
We had this chicken and it was gonna go,
it was gonna go south in about a week.
So I needed to put some pedal to the metal.
- It's gonna go south of mustard.
- I went online and I watched several how-to videos
on YouTube until I watched, until I saw stuff
that the end result was consistent with visually
what I recalled from my grandmother eating.
So I was like, okay, that's the one I'm going with.
So it was very simple.
I put in an egg, flour, egg, little bit of chicken broth,
that's it, mushed it up into a dough.
- For the dumplings.
Mushed it up into a dough, added flour as needed,
rolled it out half the end.
- Oh, I was gonna ask you if you rolled it out
or if you did like the dumpling ball.
- No, I rolled it out, we do the flats.
- I'm very impressed.
- I went to a comic book shop and Paul is rolling
out his own dough.
It is a new day, it's a shiny new day here.
- We're getting old, we're getting old,
we're running out of things to do on the planet.
- I've been sober for a day and a half.
- Holy shit.
- It's a weird world, it's a weird crazy world.
- It's a weird world.
- This is a very weird time.
- I haven't been sober for a day and a half.
(laughing)
- Getting carried away.
- Cut up the dumplings, had a whole lot of dumplings,
it was really great.
The two things that probably came up short
were the chicken and the stock.
So I got just box stock, right?
- Gotcha.
- In the future.
- Oh yeah, you gotta season up.
You can do the box stock, but you gotta season up
the box stock a little bit.
- I seasoned it up, but I didn't season it up enough.
But I think in the future, the trick is just straight up,
make your own stock, boil bone-in chicken
until it falls off the bone of a couple of pieces,
clear out the bones, chunk up the chicken,
take out the chicken, and you've got the stock.
Maybe add a bouillon, I saw another recipe.
- No, no, keep the bones going.
Take the chicken off the bones and then keep the bones
there, let 'em really-- - And keep 'em really going.
You can even break 'em, break the bones up.
- Get the marrow out for a little while.
Yeah, or add a little bouillon.
I saw another recipe, added cream of chicken soup.
- Eisenhower used the bones of children
that died making trains.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's how my grandma used to make chicken and dumplings,
and it's honestly the best way.
- Train baby gravy is the primary way--
- Train baby gravy!
- Is the primary way to eat chicken and dumplings,
but I didn't have the things available to me at hand.
- I still say that's James Taylor's best song.
(laughing)
And I walked into my mother's house
I could smell it on the stove
The train baby gravy
Just like she made from home
It was supple, soft, and slippery
And it slid right in my mouth
Fresh from the tracks at the railroad crossin'
A baby went down south
All the way to Beale Street
Woo hoo, all the way to Beale Street
Woo hoo, look out, here come them getters
It ain't closed
Lookin' for that baby
That baby train gravy, train baby gravy
Here comes the great strollin' parlor band
From Beale Street
- This is another thing, Matt,
that I'm afraid the elites have stolen from us.
Besides our future and our hope,
they've also stole the ability.
They've stole the ability to really make fun jokes
about eating babies, because now it's just a stark reality.
(laughing)
There was a time when dead baby jokes
ruled the playground for kids.
Nowadays, it's just like, whoa, who are you trying to be?
Elon Musk?
Yeah, oh boy.
Anyway.
- How do you fit 10,000 dead babies into a phone booth?
You give 'em to the elites, they'll figure it out.
- That's how you do it.
You figure it out real fuckin' quick.
- Oh, I also have a piece of side note business
popped into my head.
- Okay, okay.
- We had one of our scoops right on Patreon.
I don't get the Angry Goose joke.
Someone explain it to me.
And I just thought I should maybe also explain it on air.
'Cause we're making it in reference to Fisto
from Masters of the Universe.
And I didn't know this until, I guess,
you can hear early episodes of us learning this, basically.
But in the actual sex act of fisting,
you don't actually make a fist.
You don't just punch someone's butthole.
(laughing)
- I mean, unless they've asked for that.
- I'm just saying, there might be people out there
making mistakes.
- Making mistakes or just granting wishes.
- Yeah.
- Sure, sure.
Featured on a bug, maybe.
- Put the Paul Mattingly biography.
(laughing)
- Making mistakes and granting wishes.
- Yeah, making mistakes and granting wishes.
The Paul Mattingly story.
- A lid for every pot, a fist for every cornhole.
- Now, Paul, your camera went out.
Is it 'cause your computer fell off the bags?
- It's because I'm wiping my nose
because it's two degrees in my goddamn basement.
My nose is running from the fucking cold.
I thought I'd spare our listening audience
and viewing audience, me digging for nose goblins.
- Now, Bossy and Cham is a good point.
He's saying, "Fisting 101" by Matt Donnelly.
Yeah, don't let me be the only source on this, okay?
Please.
I'm not doing--
- Do your own research.
- I'm not doing a sarcastic Joe Rogan
where I give some lunatic a platform for four hours
and then say, "Do your own research" at the end.
I mean, I really want you to not let me be the only source
that you get this from.
Is that some kind of high women joke?
- I don't want you to punch people in the assholes
and I don't want you to use me as your only fisting source.
- That's right.
But you actually form your fisters into a point
as if you're like pinching up--
- Well, if you see many of the sex toys
that are sold as fisty, they are that same thing.
They are like somebody's getting ready to--
- You make a cone, a cone of fingers.
- It's basically prekermit.
- Prekermit, yeah, yeah.
- So if someone says prekermit, my butthole,
we're talking about the same thing.
(laughing)
- You know, you can still get pregnant from prekermit.
I heard that was a myth.
- No, it's not a myth, buddy.
- Oh, I heard it's a myth.
(laughing)
- That's how, look, Paul's only nine months apart
from his brother, believe me, you can get pregnant
from prekermit. - You can get pregnant
from prekermit, for fucking sure.
10 and a half months, that's right.
- I thought it was eight and a half.
- 10 and a half, razor close.
(laughing)
- So yeah, angry goose is referring to the actual shape
you make when one fists another person.
- Right.
- I just wanna make sure that we're all caught up.
And-- - It's pump at hand.
- And-- - Inside joke explained.
- And it's been a while since you've explained--
- That's a literal inside joke.
- That the best way that we express gratitude on the show
is by saying, fuck you in the face,
you dick and tit farmers, of which I am the farmer.
And so that's when you get a thank you email
from me for signing up for Patreon.
That's what that means on the bottom.
- We have a wonderful comment here in the chat
from Chris Angel has a chimera.
As an old queer man, we used to tell a joke
back in the '90s, how can you tell if a guy is gay?
Ask him to make a fist.
- Oh, that's great. (laughing)
- I like that a lot.
- That's great, that's a guy, I had a friend
who was a lesbian who was like,
listen, girls like to say they're bisexual.
And she goes, I just look at their fingernails
and be like, no you're not.
(laughing)
- All good talk.
- That's a big tell.
That's a big tell for sure.
- Right there.
So yeah, yeah.
All right, what do we have?
We got some Scoop Mail, Jacob?
- Now let's do a little jock versus nerd.
- Oh that's it, we already did Scoop Mail.
We snuck it in.
- That's right, yeah, we snuck in.
- Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
- That angry goose don't speak anywhere.
(upbeat rock music)
Time for jock versus nerd
- The exclusion of angry geese.
Hello, fabulous face fuckers.
I wrote this scooperty on Black Friday,
which made me think about a gift
everyone must have received at least once in their lives,
a quote of the day desk calendar.
You know the kind where there are about 365 pages
and you rip them out and each page you have a new quote
and you keep on tearing a sheet off every day,
starting on January 1st until about mid February
when you throw it away when nobody is looking.
Here is a scooperty with some famous quotes of people
in the areas you three enjoy.
And this is from Psych Scoop.
The categories are comedians, magicians,
comic books, and sports figures.
I'm up first, I'll try magicians 200.
- Filthy magicians.
- On the subject of pattern,
this magician said generally magicians
don't know what to say so they say stupid
and redundant crap like here, I am holding a red ball.
I mean, it sounds a lot like Penn.
I'm gonna say Penn Jillette.
Tell her.
- Well, you were halfway there.
- I was kind of close.
- You were very close.
- Well, actually, that is the thing.
I end up talking to magicians about the whole,
once you're not doing the sarcastic teller talks thing.
But he is one of our greatest living magic minds
and I always say that one of the things
that makes him such a great magic mind,
both Penn and Teller are,
we've talked about this, not sentimental.
If they don't wax poetic or get into things being too,
whatever, and emotions in any kind of way.
So Teller is remarkably practical at magic advice.
And that's an example of right there.
He's very much about just do this, this sucks,
this makes people go, wow, this is deceptive, this isn't.
He's very clear and bare bones about his magic advice,
which is really awesome.
- Yeah, nice.
Matt, you're up.
- Magicians, 400 please.
- This magician said there is nothing worse
than good magic at the wrong time.
(laughing)
- That's a really funny quote.
- I don't know who said this.
- Copperfield. - But I like that a lot.
And I really want to know the context of it.
- Dude, he's on his way out, huh?
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
You don't think they're gonna push him?
- Who knows?
- I guess there are no consequences for anything anymore.
I don't fucking know.
- Well, also, if he's the only one
who suffers consequences for this,
that'd be really weird too.
Because basically they were like--
- It'd just be him and Bill Gates,
so the only two that have gotten anything,
any kind of blowback.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh no, I think several of them got blowback.
Oh, blowback.
- No, but (laughing)
yikes.
- This magician said there is nothing worse
than good magic at the wrong time.
- I'll just say this on this,
just to put the finer point of what I'm getting at,
which is that I think he's too much
of a non-current celebrity
to get too much shit for what's happening.
I don't think-- - Outside of Vegas,
he's not really-- - Outside of Vegas,
I don't think-- - Oh, yes.
- People think of as a nostalgic name
that recalls to their childhood.
It is not like bringing up someone
who's operating right now and thriving right now.
- Did he ever bring back the Statue of Liberty though?
I mean, we never-- - Oh, it's all he does.
It's like, we're like, stop, put it away, David.
It's the Statue of Liberty here, Statue of Liberty there.
Can you just please order?
We're waiting.
I'm gonna fly across the Grand Canyon
With my leg crossed
Indian style crisscross applesauce
- I'll also say, I don't see too many magicians saying no
to getting in his private jet
and going to his island right now,
so it seems like there's really no ramifications happening.
- Wait, who's Private Island?
- David has his own private island.
- Copperfields.
- Of course he does.
- But that's the whole point.
That's why they're, like, that's actually why
they were mostly connected,
and not mostly connected through his--
- Oh, they were island friends.
- Yes.
- I suppose, ugh.
- Like two people with Jeeps
doing the weird finger wave at each other?
- Two people with Jeeps.
Yeah, they'd go over to each other's island,
give each other a rubber duck every month.
- No, no, no, it was just a weird finger wave.
They did a weird finger wave with each other.
- Anyhow, pass.
- Paul.
Mattingly.
Paul Mattingly.
- Pen.
- All right.
David Roth.
- David Lee Roth?
- David Lee Roth.
- Amazing.
- Yeah.
- Hey, you know what, there's nothing worse
than good magic in the wrong time, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
- Panama!
- Diamond Dave.
(laughing)
- Bozey, bozey, bozey, bozey, bozey, bozey.
- Don't bring out magic in the good times.
- Wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah, wah.
- Toe time to jump!
Paul, you're up.
- Get me a coffee and a glazed donut to go.
- I'll go with comic books for 200.
- This comic book figure is known for saying Excelsior.
- That is none other than Stan "The Man" Lee.
I am wearing an Excelsior badge on my shirt right now.
I have it on my coat.
I have a little--
- That's something that people care about.
- They do.
- I'm doing sports figures for 200.
Winn questioned about his work at the news conference.
This sports figure responded, we talk about practice?
- Oh, you're gonna know that.
- Practice?
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- We talk about practice?
- You know that.
- Coach Mora, baby, Coach Jim Mora.
Alan Iverson.
- Oh, that's the wrong thing.
Playoffs, I'm thinking playoffs, god damn it.
- Oh no.
- Playoffs, not practice.
- Oh, you went the wrong way.
- I went to the wrong press conference.
- In your defense, Jacob,
people mix up Jim Mora and Alan Iverson all the time.
(laughing)
- Constantly, all the time.
That won't even be the last time on this show
where it happens.
- Oh boy, oh boy, give me Comedians for 600.
- Let's try it.
This gone too soon comedian said this
after encountering Jacob's favorite waterfowl.
I find a duck's opinion of me is very much influenced
by whether or not I have bread.
- Oh, shit, I know who this is, I'm picturing it in my mind.
It is not Steven Wright.
- No, you got to go outside and trim--
- Mitch Hensburg.
- There you go.
- Yeah.
- Paul.
- I'll do comic books for 800, I'm gonna shoot the moon.
- This superhero said there's always a way
when the odds are impossible, do the impossible.
- Oh.
- Captain Planet.
- No, this is tricky.
- The power is yours.
- The odds are impossible, do the impossible.
It sounds like Superman, but it could be a lot,
it could be Captain America 2, that's a pass.
- Oh, that passes to me.
That is Howard the Duck.
- It definitely sounds like cast or soups.
- Sure, pass. - It's one of those pass,
ultra goody goodies. - Matt.
- That would be Fisto.
Pass.
Superman.
- It's me, I'll try comic books for 400.
- I fell asleep.
- This shield bearing comic book hero said
I'm loyal to nothing, General, except the dream.
- There you go.
- That is Spider-Man.
- Spider-Man, Spider-Man has a web shield.
- I'm loyal to nothing except the dream.
- He does have a web shield.
- That is the crow from the Sandman.
- That is Brandon Lee's The Crow.
- James O'Barr's The Crow.
- Eric Draven. - Captain America.
- Eric Draven.
- Matt.
- I'll do comedians for 800.
- This late comedian said cocaine is God's way
of saying you make too much money.
- Oh God, shoot.
I know that quote, it's a very good quote.
- It is.
- Somebody just leapt into my head.
I have a guess, but I'm not sure if I'm right or not.
- Well. - I'm gonna pass.
- Oh shit. - Paul.
- See, now I'm second guessing myself.
- Who are you thinking?
- Well, talk us through it, baby, talk us through it.
- My first thought was Carlin.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- And then-- - That's my first thought
as well. - And my second thought
was Bill Hicks.
- Okay.
- And then my third thought was Mark Maron.
- Oh, wow.
I think, yeah, Mark Maron and Carlin.
- Any one of those.
- I think you're both forgetting about Pryor.
- Oh. - Oh.
- Yep. - I'll pass
to let you take that shot, bruh.
- No, no, no, I'm passing as well
'cause I'm right there with you.
- Oh my God, it was Robin Williams.
Of all the cocaine addles.
- I was gonna say, so it was Richard Pryor's.
(laughing)
- Oh, oh, shots fucking fired.
- Stay down, Robin Williams.
Too good, too long.
Paid everybody for every joke you ever told.
Oop, oop, oop.
- On blast.
Robin Williams on blast.
- Paul, you're up.
- I will do comic books for 600, please.
- This superhero said when there seems to be no chance,
that's when it counts.
- Oh, piss.
- Piss man. - Piss man.
- Piss man.
- Martin Van Buren is piss man.
- Seems to be no chance.
- When there seems to be no chance, that's when it counts.
- See, this is also a very goody two-shoezy.
This could be like Green Lantern
or there's another big--
- No, no, Paul, this was a motivational speech
given by Lex Luthor in the big Doom house
that would fly around and the super friends
would have to chase them around.
- It could be Batman.
I'll have to pass.
- That passes to me.
I happen to know this one.
It is the Left Wonder Twin.
The Left Wonder Twin.
I don't know, pass.
Matt.
- I have no idea.
- Spider-Man.
- His is, there's great--
- I just walked through a comic book.
I walk into one comic book shop
and suddenly the pressure's on to answer these questions.
- Tested.
- Oh yeah, no, that one did come out today.
You're absolutely right, sir,
to be here on the day that that one came out
that you just came in and asked about.
- I swear it's a coincidence.
- It's not, you're a nerd, you're one of us.
- Well and the thing is they also probably had 40 copies.
- They did have a lot of copies.
- It sounded like fucking hotcakes.
- I don't think they had 40, but they had a lot of copies.
- It's my turn and I just accidentally clicked on a question.
I don't know which one I clicked on.
This hot-headed coach said when my time on Earth is gone
and my activities here are past,
I want them to bury me upside down
and my critics can kiss my ass.
- That's your boy from UNLV, or not UNLV.
- May, is that Bobby Knight?
- Is it Bobby Knight or Tarkanian?
- It's Beale Street.
- Beale Street.
- Is it Bobby Knight or is it Tarkanian?
- No, I don't think it's Tark.
- I don't think Tark's a kiss my ass guy.
- It's Bobby Knight.
- Tark is the, my friend here
is gonna break your legs later.
- Yikes.
- Yeah, I'll say Bobby Knight.
Fuck yeah, it's Bobby Knight.
- It's Bobby Knight.
- Which one was that?
That was sports figures for 600 maybe?
- Yep, score check, Jacob.
- Let's see, Matt and I are both tied at 600.
Paul has negative 200.
And I think there's still two daily doubles left
out of the six questions that are left.
So anyone's game.
Matt, you're up.
You got comedians, magicians, and sports figures.
We've burned all the comic books.
- I'll do sports figures for 400, please.
- Let's try it.
This baseballer said they don't think it be like it is,
but it do.
Although many falsely attribute this quote to other players.
- Oh man.
- They don't think it'd be like it is, but it do.
- Is this Reggie Jackson?
Or is this-- - Yogi Berra.
- That says this is like Yogi Berra.
- It's not, there's no irony in it.
So it's not, people falsely quote Yogi for a lot of things,
but there's usually an ironic twist.
- Okay, yeah.
This either Daryl Strawberry.
- I'm gonna be Pancho.
- Joe Pesci, Bill Cosby.
I'll pass.
- Paul.
- Was it Pancho Ponce de Leon?
- No.
- Satchel Paige.
- Is that your guess?
- Yeah, I'll go with Satchel Paige.
- Your guess is Satchel Paige.
Great.
It's Oscar Gamble.
- Everyone knows Oscar Gamble.
We were just talking about Oscar Gamble,
the very well-known baseball player.
- Well, I just Oscar Gamble several points and lost.
- You did, you did.
Satchel Paige, that is a deep baseball poll, sir.
Paul, you're up.
- Not deep enough.
I'll go with magicians for 800 to get back on the board.
- This magician born in the 1800s said
the personality must be bigger than the prop.
- Gotta be Houdini.
- Who?
- Houdini.
- Harry Blackstone, sir.
(laughing)
- Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
- My turn.
I'll just try magicians for 600
just because Houdini hasn't been an answer yet.
- Shit.
- Daily double.
- Oh, boo, boo you.
There is no official record.
- This person whose name is Houdini
says Houdini things. - Anyone who believes
in magic is a fool. - My name is Houdini.
- But people attribute the quote to him anyway.
- I'm Houdini.
My name is Mr. Houdini.
Said this Houdini.
- Harry Houdini.
Houdini.
- Boo on you.
Fuck you.
(laughing)
Fuck you, fuck you Houdini.
- That worked out so well.
Matt, you're up.
- Comedians 400.
- Daily double.
- The hits keep coming.
- This humorist first said in 1923,
I don't drink water.
Fish, fucking it.
- Oh man.
I am up to date on my 1923 humorists.
That's for sure.
- Oh, you don't know this one?
- That's gotta be the cowboy.
It's the cowboy guy.
- Will Rogers.
- Will Rogers?
- It's gotta be Will Rogers.
(coughing)
- Yeah, Matt, it's gotta be Will Rogers.
- I think this would be Harry Blackstone Jr.
- That's it.
- Is it W.C. Fields?
- Ooh.
Ooh, that's a good guess.
- Oh, I'll go with Fields.
- All right.
W.C. Motherfucking Fields is correct.
- Water closet Fields himself.
- My favorite quote is, again, maybe mis-tributed.
I mean, you can find it attributed to different people,
but it's, if you wanna make people laugh,
dress a guy up like an old lady
and push him down the stairs.
If you wanna make a comedian laugh,
push an old lady down the stairs.
(laughing)
My favorite Fields quote.
- Paul, you have negative 1,400.
Matt and I are both tied at 1,200.
- Let's get on the board with sports figures for 800, please.
- All righty.
This prominent pugilist, poetically proclaimed,
it's just a job.
Grass grows, birds fly, waves pound the sand,
I beat people up.
- Okay.
- I think Matt will agree with me,
there is only one person that this could possibly be.
- I mean, Foreman?
- That's what I would've guessed.
- Foreman?
Like, it's not poetic enough to be Ali.
- Okay.
- And it's too cogent to be Tyson.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, I don't think it's Tyson.
I think it's Ali.
- Well, I'm going with Foreman.
- Okay.
Muhammad Ali.
- Ah, hell!
(laughing)
Hell and damnation!
- I gave you the best hint I could think of giving you, Paul.
(laughing)
- Well, it wasn't good enough.
- For the win, I am closing out the category
and the game, Comedians for 200.
This sassy French guard said,
"I fart in your general direction."
- No, it has to be the character's name.
- Or the person who put in the character's name.
French guard, French castle, the number two, yeah.
- It's French guard number one
from Monty Python's Quest for the Holy Grail.
- That's right.
- Oh, you wanted the, oh, you did want the actor.
John, please. - Yes.
- Oh, sorry.
- With that psychological destruction of Jacob, I win.
(laughing)
- Ah, man, got it, 1,200 points.
I've got 1,000.
Paul's got negative 2,200, and that's from Psych Scoop.
Thank you, Psych Scoop.
- That was a good one.
- Oh yeah, all the others were the comedian names, wasn't it?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - That's right.
- I was half joking when I said it, and I feel bad, so.
- Don't feel bad.
What do you feel bad about?
- I felt like I accidentally coached you
into giving the wrong answer on that one,
and I didn't mean to, I was being a joke, joking to Kev.
- Oh, no, no, no, I gave the answer I wanted to give.
I do enjoy, though, that you feel bad
about a jock versus nerd result, though.
- Especially, it was 1,200 versus 1,000 points,
real squeaker.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yes. (laughing)
- A nail-biter to the end.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Thank you, Bossy.
Bossy thinks I should get the points.
Yeah, yeah, I agree, Bossy.
- He's his own judge, Bossy.
He gave himself the negative.
We can't, we can do it all we want.
He's in control of the points.
- No, no, no, I would like to continue under protest.
(laughing)
- I would like to continue with protest over my right hand,
as my left hand, and I would like to get the points.
- Fuck you.
- Ouch!
- Oh, I want to thank Penn Jillette for being in this podcast.
- Thanks, Penn.
How is Penn?
We got a health check on Penn?
- He's doing good, he's doing good.
He is really staying strict to doctor's orders,
which surprises no one.
So he's moving around very little.
He just announced this week on Penn Sunday School
that they will attempt to do, basically,
some kind of theatrical presentation of Penn
to resume shows starting February 12th.
Penn will be, he doesn't want to go on a wheelchair
'cause it's too, like, weird.
- Oh, no, no, he's gotta do the Axl Rose.
- That's it, they're gonna do the--
- He's gotta do The Throne.
- The Throne, they're gonna do a--
- Yeah, Axl Rose, Ozzy, yeah, you gotta do The Throne.
- And so, that'll be happening there.
And so, yeah, that's that.
- Those will either be the best Penn and Teller shows ever
or the worst Penn and Teller shows ever.
- Right, right.
- Those will not be mediocre Penn and Teller shows.
Those are gonna be ones that you're gonna wanna go see.
- Yeah.
- If you are a Penn and Teller fan,
those are the shows that you wanna go check out
because that's gonna be limited edition.
- I just wanna hear, like, three jokes that happen
from, like, a lack of being able to figure out something,
you know, like, seeing how many dominoes it pushes.
- Yeah. - Oh, right.
- That's what I wanna see, so, yeah, it's gonna be fun.
- Oh, yeah, no, it's gonna have some things.
- Speaking of Penn,
I wanna thank him for creating this podcast.
- Thanks, Penn.
- I wanna thank all the people who join us here on Zoom.
If you wanna join us on a Zoom call,
or if you want access to a myriad of other prizes
that we offer at different tiers,
head on over to preachingfun.com
and select the tier that fits your budget today.
Come visit preachingfun.com
It's better than hanging with your mom at a deep end
- Or if you get all of your advice
on fisting from Matt Donnelly,
go to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts
Fartsinabag.biz
- That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with Preaching Fun
takes you over to our preachingfun.com.
- Roll it down, Jacob, start over, start over.
Take it from the top.
- Fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com
takes you over to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon.
So if you think this show is worth more than $0,
preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz.
Head over there now.
- I just read a great one from Unbanned Scoop.
He invites you all to select a tier
that is above your budget, YOLO.
- Oh, YOLO indeed, Unbanned Scoop.
- Let's do it.
- I don't, no, I do not take that advice.
- Come on, come on, Matt, YOLO.
- We love you all sexually.
- And we'll see you soon.
- It's YOLO, not FICO, fuck it, let's go.
- YOLO, not FICO.
(upbeat music)
- YOLO, not FICO, fuck it, let's go.
That's a great shirt.
(upbeat music)
YOLO resources, LLC.
YOLO, angry goose.
(upbeat music)
Farts in the DVD bag.
We're preaching fun.
See ya.