oh hello there i am so glad to see you i want to thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you
so much richard dunn roy stansberry sarah boyle sax guy jimmy d scoop and slurpy ka motherfucker
if you are what i can't talk today if you want be ice cream truck driver i be you want to be
an ice cream truck driver head over to preaching fun.com preaching fun.com is where you can go to
sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save may be your own
buckle up i can't talk for the podcast hey johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social
yeah i'd love to great let's go we are here in the middle of snowmageddon part two
i'm broadcasting
from the frozen tundra where none can pass the white walkers are on their way the wall is falling
it's all ice dragons from here on out forget it
well it's time for matt madley's ice cream social sitting over there it's matt donnelly
sitting over there it's paul madley over here and check out the audio guy i'm a little chilly too
yeah wait y'all 60 degrees over there yeah i think it's closer to 70 but i do have a space
heater going right over here next to me
my feet are a little chilly crazy out here we got so much snow yesterday it just did not stop
12 consecutive hours of snowfall it's time for pittsburgh yeah parking and weather with the
famous fall yeah yeah yeah so uh it's thick thick and rich up in this motherfucker
we've had to dig passageways for the dogs to go out to poo and pee like you know like
there's a big mound of snow
up on one side of our porch that yeah ted keeps playing king of the mountain on it so it's really
cute and very funny they love it the corgs love it they got those double coats they don't give a
shit they're out there farting around in snow and then they come running right back as soon as they
get a little bit inconvenient so well i'm just gonna come back inside now but they're they're
ridiculous um yeah they're they're spoiled we're very fortunate we did not lose power at all during
all this so we didn't really get any kind of ice per se uh you know we didn't get any kind of ice
per se uh you know we didn't get any kind of ice per se uh you know we didn't get any kind of ice
we're still digging out we had generous lovely neighbors come by at the height of the storm
yesterday and one guy on his atv with a snow plow on the front plowed most of our driveway and
another neighbor came and snow blowed the rest of the driveway and then it got another six inches on
top of that where they'd cleared so we had to shovel again and i've got to shovel again today
you called them back you called them i did not call them back over they did they did more than
they needed uh where are you guys we uh we got guys hello hello no they they did great so it's uh
gonna take a little while to dig out i was supposed to have my first new class this evening
for a new semester at uh skit but we put everything on delay because everybody is
buried in snow and it's still pretty difficult to get around lots of schools are closed for
the next couple of days the temperature is only going to go down from here so
yeah sexy temperature the tough part is going to be as there's a little bit of snow melt during
the day then this temperature goes way below freezing and yeah ice ice ice baby so we'll see
we'll see how it goes i don't go back to work till wednesday thank goodness or until thursday
wednesday night thursday morning um so yeah i got a little bit of time and had to go in today
but she's got that snow mode and she said once she got onto the main roads it wasn't terrible but
you know still not great yeah uh unless you're a corgi unless you're a corgi then it's then life
is pretty fucking good right yeah they're loving it jacob i wasn't paying attention who'd you thank
the ice cream truck driver at the top of the show uh not uh not technical scoop port you did not
you're not no no he's on the next show he's on the next show that's why i laughed at myself
before we started the show because he was saying he hadn't been thanked yet i was like i got him
he's queued up for today too bad for him we're doing a double show today so he's gonna hear
about himself on two episodes well we'll thank technical scoop port twice how about that that's it
holy shit a large black cat just walked past my back door and it just scared the shit out of me
you don't have a black cat no i don't own any cats it should scare the shit out of you
large animal he's coming for your coming for your puppies oh oh it just turned into a human
it just turned into a human oh shit
just turned to a goth looking human well we also found out he's leaving we have a we have a fire
hydrant in our front yard and during because we had about three days of real heads up on this
major storm coming through and so and doing her due diligence looking up different factoids and
whatnot about preparation etc turns out we are responsible for keeping that fire hydrant
under control so we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything
we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going
to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do
anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're
not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be
able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything we're not going to be able to do anything
funny enough it's not really covered it's kind of clear that leads me to believe that that water
line has some it's a big kind of heat it's a big metal fire hydrant right yes but it also i think
it has must have some kind of heat source in that water line to keep that all warm you don't think
it's moving though i guess that's it it's just flowing everyone knows that hot water puts out
fire faster than cold water science it's just science it's just a big metal fire plug like
that thing's gonna hold heat longer than stuff around it well nick newman is giving me the wave
off uh that there is no heat under that that uh fire hydrant what are you gonna listen you're
gonna listen to a fireman i guess i'm listening to a firefighter i don't know why nick gets all
fucking crap around here i said it wasn't fucking he didn't listen to me
he's a firefighter fireman shows up makes some chili it says it's not heated you go well i guess
it's not heated i very quickly changed my opinion on the on the information of experts jacob
something something i think more of us could learn i just was gonna say it's 2026 are you
really gonna listen to a fireman tell you what how a fire hydrant works right what a dumbass
you listening to the experts you want to do your own research why don't you vote
you
yeah uh get a glass of warm milk uh warm raw milk and uh spit at the house that puts it out
did i talk did i talk about this i was at i had lunch when i was in uh when i was in uh burbank
with my friend uh eli and uh his wife erica and she's a doctor yeah and uh she says all the time
now she goes we're gonna you know we we think your child has you know blank and we're gonna
and our plan to take care of them is to do blank blank blank blank blank blank blank blank blank
and they go hold on hold on and they type whatever she's saying into like chat gbt oh they don't even
already have an opinion i was already cringing because i thought the parent would already have
an opinion but they have to look no they're not that informed oh that's even worse yeah they
question they they go hold on before i tell you to proceed i have to look this up and figure out
what this chat gbt tells me about what you just told me and whether or not i approve great of the
doctor's plans this is why no one should be using chat gbt no one should be using
any of this ai garbage it is a detriment to all of us uh absolutely i use it all the time
but uh you shouldn't i don't use it to i am chat gpt i don't use it to question experts i don't
use but you're feeding the beast baby you're feeding the beast just be careful i just tell
chat gbt every day that paul mattingly loves you tell him whatever i want to get paul's i want to
get paul's name into that chat gpt brain chat gpt can come to my house
we'll have a real nice talk come to my house i fed that beast a long time ago uh i remember when it
first happened i don't think i've told the story on air but i think it's been long enough i can
the statute of limitations has run out yeah so i when it first came around it was fascinating and
and and and and so i put every approved script of pen and teller fool us into chat gpt yeah
and uh figure
maybe it can help me write more scripts because one of the biggest challenges being a writer on
that show was writing 80 versions of we'll be right back with more magic after this sure right
write 80 versions of that every year try to put some cute jokes in it that kind of stuff
yeah so i put it in there and then one season
uh all of a sudden like the producers start experimenting with chat gpt to see if it was
like worth doing and all of a sudden i got like this note that was like hey
chat gpt stuff it's it's pretty good and i know i gave it all of our scripts like whatever but i
didn't make that argument and then they were like uh we we'd switched from a 14 episode
season to a 20 episode season yes right which means that i uh but you had longer to shoot it
so that was fine but i got paid it was about money it was about whether i sure how much
more am i getting my episode rate is there a flat rate like what's happening
uh with it and they were dragging their heels uh i was the executive producer was not getting back
to me and then they kept making jokes about chat gpt and replacing me with chat gpt
so all of a sudden it was like three weeks before the season started yeah and i wrote a very uh uh
formal note they hadn't hired paul back yet um and i wrote a
very formal note being like hey if you don't want to fly paul back out uh i'd happily switch
from being a writer to warm-up comic for this upcoming season ah
um because clearly you got you guys don't know what's getting back to my contract i'm hearing
jokes about replacing with chat gpt just make me the warm-up comic and let's call it a day
and i wrote it to
the one executive producer wasn't getting back to me i wrote to both executive producers and
the showrunner good good this seems like a reasonable response
because i was just getting pissed yeah i got the angriest voicemail i've ever gotten from
the executive producer
he cursed me the fuck out like read me the riot act like i know exactly what you're talking about
where he's coming from
because obviously when i did work the two other producers called the that executive producer who's
in charge of signing the contracts and said what the fuck's going on with that right and so
uh that was an awkward it was awkward backstage a couple times throughout that season it was
a little frosty in the green room a few times uh that particular season of
with that producer with his chat gpt for halloween that year matt felt like it was pointed a little
bit at him uh yeah no i mean look you know yeah it is what it is uh i said that like my current
opinion with uh ai and chat gpt is like we thought we were creating like this god of all knowledge
right that we could consult and what we created
was like a
really eager fresh out of college assistant that's like who's just like wants to just supply you with
everything sometimes they're right sometimes they're wrong but like they got your back
right right they're just like uh here maybe maybe you want all this you're like uh maybe two of
those things but thank you actually you said this but that's not even true what you wrote here i
don't think you researched that properly this is just wrong this is entirely wrong yeah yeah so
now that's how i look at that's how i look at chat gpt is is like it's a it's a really really
wonderful thing to do and i think it's a really really really wonderful thing to do and i think
wants the gig it's really going places but right now it's just fresh out of college and it's yeah
and it's trying too hard boy do i like using it to uh to sort information i like putting a lot
of information into it doing like make me a table that shows me all of that yeah yeah it works really
well for that that's it for like clerical and like clinical things it's good you know for knowledge
and like advice it's terrible oh and for like clinical things it's good you know for knowledge
advice forget it and for humor it's abominable yeah right but for sexy dating chat go ahead
let's go they'll tell you exactly what you want to hear
i'll tell you exactly who loves a good sexy twitch chat not twitch chat chat gpt chat on twitch
and that's the following sponsor today's show mad madley's
ice cream social no no i'm getting a boner stop absolutely i can help you that boner if you want
oh that's would you like me to list seven things you can do with your boner seven things you can
do with your boner today's show is brought to you by oh new sentient tampons hungry for blood
hungry for action new sentient tampons from goof scoop in 2023
hello it is that time of the month i know because i looked at your calendar
hey i am count absorbo i am here to fill your vaginal cavity and suck up your blood
yes count absorbo's guarantee is no leaks a dry panty every time
you never have to fret when count absorbo he sees the wet i will take it away slurp slurp slurp
away it goes into my hungry maw i count absorbo promise that
no blood shall go wasted please run to your local supermarket or big box retailer
and pick up a package of count absorbo's insertopons they are fresh and ready to be used
in your vaginal cavity
insert upon what i insist upon you insert upon you insert upon you insert upon you insert upon you
better hate scoops to check out uh why are they called insertopons
it's it's a trademark account absorbo's trademark way of saying tampon is insert upon
yeah i like it yeah yeah they should be called oh you're saying why aren't they called insert upon
i think uh the man i don't know i honestly think that all of the world has kept everyone in the
dark about everything for as long as they can everybody just tries to obfuscate and and confuse
everything
constantly
constantly something wrong this week why like something's bothering you
why are condoms constantly being placed on bananas in health class use a fucking dildo
use a fucking penis what the fuck i don't know this is everything's weird everything's a fucking
game everything's a fucking shell game i don't know
how you doing buddy it's all bullshit i'm fine i'm covered in fucking snow is what i am
i don't mind it though uh we got we went out to a fancy dinner on friday night which was lovely
oh that's nice matt and malia how much you got out you got a little fancy dinner before the snow hit
how much of what how much of what you ordered was cut in half and put in a plate of molten cheese
oh my god have you been seeing the videos of the thing have you seen the videos it's exactly what
i said and they're all just like they eat the first one and then they go for the second one
and the whole plate comes up and they're all just like they eat the first one and then they go for
because it's fucking glued to it it's hilarious congealed it's hilarious oh my god we just chat
gpt'd count absorbo oh my god that is outrageous who did that is that laurie my god laurie that's
great oh no that's really good oh that's gonna be at uh scoop fest i mean that i'm saving that
as count absorbo for uh john versus third uh can you save that for a sticker art
please uh that is wonderful my god that's great laurie holy shit that's exactly what i was thinking
in my head he likes he's like let's make a sticker out of it i don't well yeah well i mean we're not
making stickers anymore but you also just ranted against using chat gpt and now you're blown away
by chat i am i know i hate it well but you know and it's terrible because i know we don't use
chat gpt to make our stickers we don't use chat gp we have artists to make all our stuff
stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from whoever
makes our stuff we don't have any of that stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other
art that's clearly stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other art that's clearly
stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other
art that's clearly stealing from other art that's clearly stealing from other art that makes garbage pill
that makes garbage pill
that makes garbage pill kids oh there's also that does look a
kids oh there's also that does look a
kids oh there's also that does look a little bit like specifically
little bit like specifically
little bit like specifically however it should serve as inspiration
however it should serve as inspiration
however it should serve as inspiration for the jack versus nerd costume ball
for the jack versus nerd costume ball
for the jack versus nerd costume ball so there you go yes no i do want people
so there you go yes no i do want people
so there you go yes no i do want people to come as count absorbo for jack versus
to come as count absorbo for jack versus
to come as count absorbo for jack versus pull burger is out of hand
pull burger is out of hand
pull burger is out of hand it's so dumb so anyway yeah we went and
it's so dumb so anyway yeah we went and
it's so dumb so anyway yeah we went and had uh fancy dinner at the little winery
had uh fancy dinner at the little winery
had uh fancy dinner at the little winery down the road which was lovely um and we
down the road which was lovely um and we
down the road which was lovely um and we also had uh
also had uh
also had uh my friend scott and sarah came with us
my friend scott and sarah came with us
my friend scott and sarah came with us too so that was awesome and it was just
too so that was awesome and it was just
too so that was awesome and it was just kind of one of those nice little things
kind of one of those nice little things and was still on vacation
and was still on vacation
and was still on vacation and this was a thing i had planned for a
and this was a thing i had planned for a
and this was a thing i had planned for a long time the
long time the
long time the six of us to go have dinner together but
six of us to go have dinner together but
six of us to go have dinner together but anne's schedule
anne's schedule
anne's schedule we'd made plans with uh matt and malia a
we'd made plans with uh matt and malia a
we'd made plans with uh matt and malia a couple times and anne had to bail
couple times and anne had to bail
couple times and anne had to bail because she got pulled into work so i
because she got pulled into work so i
because she got pulled into work so i was like
was like
was like hands off work so i didn't invite
hands off work so i didn't invite
hands off work so i didn't invite anybody until thursday
anybody until thursday
anybody until thursday this is like it last minute's the
this is like it last minute's the
this is like it last minute's the way to go with all this kind of stuff
way to go with all this kind of stuff
way to go with all this kind of stuff and we did it social butterfly it
and we did it social butterfly it
and we did it social butterfly it worked it worked out it worked out
worked it worked out it worked out
worked it worked out it worked out great and then i ran back home to get
great and then i ran back home to get
great and then i ran back home to get back on the uh
back on the uh
back on the uh the
the
the zoom and we had a real fun scoop zoom
zoom and we had a real fun scoop zoom
zoom and we had a real fun scoop zoom well no one wins the scoop hey no no no
well no one wins the scoop hey no no no
well no one wins the scoop hey no no no um
um
um uh scooper star mc scoop slot general
uh scooper star mc scoop slot general
uh scooper star mc scoop slot general scooper starby scoop slot he won a bunch
scooper starby scoop slot he won a bunch
scooper starby scoop slot he won a bunch uh and uh
uh and uh
uh and uh scoop shooter was tearing it up too uh
scoop shooter was tearing it up too uh
scoop shooter was tearing it up too uh galactic president scooper starby scoop
galactic president scooper starby scoop
galactic president scooper starby scoop slot thank you richard yes that's that's
slot thank you richard yes that's that's and uh richard uh did really well too
and uh richard uh did really well too
and uh richard uh did really well too slurpee kai came through pretty hardcore
slurpee kai came through pretty hardcore
slurpee kai came through pretty hardcore uh yeah we had a bunch of great we had
uh yeah we had a bunch of great we had
uh yeah we had a bunch of great we had the cavitas buttholes that was a great
the cavitas buttholes that was a great
the cavitas buttholes that was a great one leon yeah uh i won one or two but um
one leon yeah uh i won one or two but um
one leon yeah uh i won one or two but um yeah it was this is a really fun night
yeah it was this is a really fun night
yeah it was this is a really fun night we played one weird game this murder
aim for I'm trying to aim for different nights of the week so that different people can play
here and there weapons drawn that was the game and did not make any sense um yeah but thirsty
won that one I don't know he didn't know how he won it but props to him for tearing it up so yeah
it was fun so we've had we had a good week off and then we kind of buckled down for snowmageddon
coming in here and here we are unfortunately Ann had to go back to work today which sucks but I've
got a few more days to still kind of just literally chill out and I am well so so cold
I am uh I'm looking for uh there we go I see Matt Daugherty in chat here he sent us a breakdown of
our scoop fantasy football league uh here in review here oh good it's coming down to the wire
I forgot oh no it's done it's all over it's all over yeah it's all over uh but uh let's see uh
here's a wrap up of the
2025 scoop fantasy football league in okay the upper league Jake Harrington team 185 lumberjacks
took the championship over Mike Brosberg the manimal yeah uh Otto Eisenberg sweat house
employees uh took third place over Matt Daugherty savory Matty D being relegated down to the lower
league is Matthew Burdick Matt Matthew welcome to the lower league buddy I've been down here the
whole time uh
welcome we have free lemonade and I think you're gonna really like it here it's pretty cozy do not
drink the lemonade it's not it has gone bad I will absolutely be here waiting for you when you get
down here so no worries there uh and so is uh Troy Soto uh Troy Sato I don't say no how do Troy how
do I have we ever said your last name correctly I don't know I say Sato Troy Sato yeah he's been
well he's been obviously running helping run this league for the very beginning so
yeah he's welcome to lower league buddy uh and the lower league Jacob Smith Matt what's that team
Hasselbeck Matt Hassel back that ass up uh you won the championship in the lower league Jacob
oh did I yes you did oh that's interesting this is the first I'm hearing of it uh you beat Paul
Clayton whose team arsonist gets all the TDs uh he he you beat him
but you'll both be moving up to the upper league next season buddy
Jacob Smith everybody Jacob yeah no I'm in trouble next year I'm in trouble next year
um also I guess I have to play next year I I guess after winning I'm I'm obligated to play
another year I joined uh uh 12 magicians in another league and I won that league
and just want you to know how much worse magicians are than scoops at fantasy football just so I'm
sure
that that tracks that definitely tracks uh yeah so uh Paul Clayton let's see in third place game
Dave Peterson whose team Tyreek of alcohol beat Justin uh Jelinek from the fighting squirrels
uh so yeah and that's it so if you want to join our league next year this year we were better we
had like a Facebook group and the Facebook chat was a good place to interact and bust balls so
we yeah good some fun trash talk we stepped it up this year uh uh for that was the only thing I was
missing in the other years was there was no consolidated place for me to uh make fun of
myself uh but this place was very it was very comforting this year I told SJ she was like did
you win your fantasy football league I said well my my because she was asking about the the big one
that I play every year yeah I said oh I got I got third place in that one but I won the uh the scoops
one and she looked at me she was like you
you played a fantasy football league with the listeners to your podcast and then you you won
that's that's that's precisely what happened
she goes did you organize this league I said I did not I did not yeah yeah yeah thankfully I
at least did not put the thing together I just played at least the illusion of of arbitrary uh
yeah yeah we had 22 uh 22
people 22 people 22 teams we've room for 24 so if you want to get in touch with Matt Daugherty
or Troy next year as we headed it we'll announce it as we head into it but they always we all pay
to get in the league and then they give a big chunk of change right back to us as a donation
for our our podcast which is very generous of them and they're wonderful thank you guys oh wait that
means I won money for this too yeah I forgot about that technically yeah yeah so I took money from
the scoops as well
insult to injury over here I uh if you uh if you look over on the chat
Leon has posted one of the winning t-shirts from the t-fury battle uh which is no ai that was my
illustration of a duck and then uh people put cavernous butthole under it and you can order
that through t-fury
great I think the cavernous butthole ducks would be a great
uh team to add to the football fantasy football league for next year
my team name this year was I say horse you say beans so maybe next year I'll change it
go with cavernous butthole cavernous butthole the cavernous buttholes yeah the fighting cavernous
buttholes yeah so I I was uh 18th out of 22 players which is pretty good hey look at you
holding your own pretty good pretty good you're a regular Kansas City chief over here 22 you're a
regular Dallas Cowboy I'm in the lower league right so those those they're automatically above
me oh they're all just all okay yeah they're automatically above me who's even in the Super
Bowl has it happened already do we know it did happen Paul breaking news because this airs
Thursday who won uh the Patriots with a decisive victory over backup quarterback Stitham
won 10 to 7 so they're coming into a Super Bowl with a lot of heat that's it
a lot of heat 10 to 7 did you did you watch that game at all I did because I'm on tour with Eric
Dillman who's in New England there oh sure sure and we were snowed in right which I haven't got
that story yet but we we we were we were uh I I'm uh I am in the snowed in hotel uh in Bloomington
Indiana and so we trudged through the snow to the upstairs bar uh here in town and it was packed
because it's a snow day sure uh and we watched what should have been an awesome day watching
football and instead was one of the most boring actually one of the most poorly kicked games I've
ever seen was it one of those games where it was all field goals no it was all missed field goals
oh no and all botched punts like right and so that changed the outcome of the whole thing huh
yeah it was it was it got snowy and super windy like the game started and it was a clear beautiful
sunny day in Denver oh and then like a blizzard rolled in like third quarter it was clear and
fine by the fourth quarter you couldn't see your hand in front of your face well that was crazy
that was the weirdest thing on uh Thursday I guess it was out here Thursday was like spring it was
weird we were like what the fuck is going on it was sunshine beautiful still snow on the ground
but just gorgeous and then turned on a dime weather-wise yeah and then well then and the
Rams in Seattle played probably the best game I don't think the Super Bowl is going to be better
than that game no I don't think so I think that was it that was a really good game came down to
really like crazy weird mistakes and yeah like it was a real battle
yeah it was fun that was a great game uh Gelato Steve in the chat I haven't seen Gelato Steve in a
minute he says go Pats yeah I mean it is uh it's it's going to be it's it's funny that like both
teams will be an underdog story if the Patriots win it'll be crazy for a team that had four wins
last year to take a second year quarterback and win this early would be bananas right and Sam
Darnold has literally been shipped off by two teams and if he wins as the Seattle quarterback
it'll be a crazy story for him to win if Sam Darnold wins as the Seattle quarterback
the Jets should have to go to the SEC
because if he wins as the Seattle quarterback that means the Jets are so much worse as an
organization than we ever even thought they were actually no I'm reconsidering we don't want them
in the SEC I was just gonna say I think every Jet fan I know would take that deal yeah I think
every different I'm thinking about what LSU is doing I'm thinking about what LSU is doing I'm
thinking about what LSU is doing I'm thinking about what LSU is doing right now LSU is definitely
running its team better than uh the New York Jets I would Vinnie Grasso's a huge Jets fan I was like
I bet he'd be like yeah yeah let's do that for them let's do that for a few years let's see how
we can handle the Tennessee volunteers for a while go down there I'll tell you who else can
handle a bunch of volunteers and that's the following sponsor today's show Matt and Manley's
ice cream social is brought to you by Dan
Ackroyd's acronym Emporium that's right Dan Ackroyd's acronym Emporium hello there my friends
how are you doing how's it going it's me Dan Ackroyd star of many films stage and screen SNL
alum and purveyor of the paranormal that's right I look into ghosts and ghost research I love to
look up strange stuff and put vodka inside skull shaped receptacles that's my life that's what I do
but my sidekick Dan Ackroyd is Dan Ackroyd's acronym Emporium that's right Dan Ackroyd's acronym Emporium
is a new one and very intriguing I've decided to start coming up with acronyms Ackroyd's acronyms
yes you go ahead and give me any kind of organization and I will acronym the shit out
of that I will make up an acronym for your organization sir what organization are you with
oh we uh I I run a a factory that that makes silverware for for tables all right we're gonna
do spoons spoons s-p-o-o-n-s and that of course stands for silverwares put on ornate
shaped
I think you missed it in oh s-p-o-o-n-s silverware put on ornate new
new shaped that's it
silverware put on ornate new shapes there you go that's a classic Ackroyd acronym give me another one
what's another place of business what are you doing what are you selling what are you making
oh I work at FedEx you work at FedEx all right let's come up with uh let's call it uh shipped
shipped will be the acronym uh that stands for shit I put I in
shit has
has it put
shit has it put
it fucked it up by the second letter hey look Ackroyd's acronyms aren't perfect
shit shit has input uh express delivery
there we go
huh what do you what else you got uh I work at Ikea Ikea perfect let's go with tuba terrible
underwater breathing apparatus
oh spelling is not the kid's forte I I misspelled weather I went with the wrong spelling of weather
in one of my little uh advertisements for the class I'm teaching on Saturday night uh out out
in Toronto you went with the the h yeah I went with the wrong one the one that describes how the
the uh atmosphere is doing rather than you know oh oh you went the other way no I went the wrong
way yeah so I still can't even get it right when you're correcting me I don't even know I just I
that's that's a that's an Achilles heel uh for me that one but also it's a blind spot I think in the
future it will be an advantage for me to have my spelling errors uh riddled throughout my writings
as it will be indicative of my non-chat GPT infused work so people go oh yeah there's
Mattingly trying to spell again he clearly wrote this without any fucking help obviously from him
is obviously him with his no no ability to spell yeah uh you guys want to do a little scoop mail
yes a little scoop mail I would love it
let's see uh oh we're starting off with uh with a heavy one today we're starting off with one from
the OG Scoop uh he's in the chat with us as well but he wrote this a while ago hey guys I wanted
to reach out and just say thanks uh to you guys and all the Scoop community in early October I
lost my brother at the young age of 56 sadly he had suffered from mental illness and addiction
for most of his life and was homeless when he passed uh he was in my town uh living in section
eight housing for the past few years but
drifted to Florida and ultimately ultimately to Las Vegas in August coincidentally he was in
Vegas during Scoop Fest because of ICS and the Scoops I consider Vegas a treasure at home away
from home and the fact that he passed in that area near Scoop family gave me some peace in all
of the sorrow and issues that arose concerning his arrangements I just wanted to remind you uh
that you guys and the Scoops have brought me laughter joy and friendship and it doesn't go
unnoticed thanks again for all the love and support love you all even you you know who you are
that's Andy the OG Scoop Andy uh so sorry pal yeah man yeah that's tough and then the whole
scenario that you brought up that seems really tough I don't know how I would deal with uh yeah
with it with a situation like that that's really and I know there was an issue uh I know Andy had
uh had you know just all of the the the stuff that goes along with that you know
transporting the remains back and doing doing all of that stuff right uh you know it it
makes a lot of it makes a lot of work and uh it sucks yeah yeah it's it's incredibly difficult
you have to almost delay your grief and put on your professional hat yeah I remember Anne having
to go through a lot of that shit when her father passed and she really had to kind of postpone her
feelings for a while to get everything else lined up properly um it's hard it's incredibly hard to
be responsible I can't imagine being in Las Vegas and being like my brother is unhoused somewhere
around here that's a really weird thing to deal with it's a hard thing to have to deal with yeah
I don't think there was crossover I don't I don't think Andy was in town while his brother was here
because Andy didn't make the the most recent Scoop Fest but his brother was in town during
the most recent Scoop Fest gotcha yeah yep no it sucks but the uh the the Scoop community
of course is always fantastic and uh and that's uh you know part of what OG was was trying to say
that is something that's always worth compliment rescinded nope oh never mind never mind I tried
I tried everybody you heard me you heard me try shit rejected I will not take it we got one here
from poutine scoop hello fuckers what was your first clue that you guys liked music as a kid
I don't mean uh bus dumping bands while on the island music but the first time you knew for me
it was Alanis Morissette I didn't get you uh
I didn't get you you ought to know oh that must be what that's supposed to be autocorrect uh had a
field day with this email sorry uh I didn't get you ought to know as a teenager but when hand in
my pocket came out as a single I had to get my first cd and radio what was it for you poutine
scoop poutine scoop I know that my first cd that I bought when cds come out came out was uh
razor's edge the classic acdc album razor's edge and I stand by that purchase I stand by that
I you know I've always been embarrassed about my musical tastes and uh I've always been
self-conscious about that even like I shared a room with my brother Rob and when we did homework
together I would default to his taste in music uh he he played the music in the room that we did
homework too uh like I I was still buying just like springsteen and billy joel stuff
I was gonna say having watched that springsteen documentary I think you're uh I think your
embarrassment is justified fully justified the movie the movie you said doc right but the movie
the movie's bad but the documentary is good um oh I haven't seen the documentary uh it's on hulu but
uh he was playing like dylan he was playing old school rem he
right
he was playing like cool stuff and then I was always just aping whatever my brother older
brothers were into so yeah I I would say I my first cd purchase I literally was like what's
the greatest selling cd at the time was pig fight pig fight dark side of the moon oh all right
um I would actually probably say it was when when uh post island time
I think like uh when steve and I uh did reduce and I moved to san diego as our as our as our less
interesting and less fruitful sequel uh we had a roommate mikey there and he got me into all
kinds of cool bands I really got into tom waits at that time uh yeah it was just a bunch of cool
bands came out of that and that really kind of shaped the way I listen to music I swear to god
that I don't think I like I'm curious how I listened to music before I took acid once once I
took acid I heard music differently the rest of my life huh and I can you describe that well yeah
I don't I was just a melody person I was into whatever the catch was you weren't listening to
lyrics and then all of a sudden I took acid no I still to this day I'm still not a good lyric
person but I love arrangements instrumentation like how far where's the
bass of the mix like versus like where's the drums like where the keyboard and I get fascinated
by arrangements and sounds and quality of sounds and and types of sounds and and I like all of that
stuff in music now and that did not happen until I took lsd okay and I don't know matt I didn't even
do that often you know I mean like I can count on my hand how many times I've done it but it just
changed the way I heard music forever I think you really need to much how I listen to music
I think you need to spend some time with nine inch nails the fragile I think that
album will uh I bet I would go back and really appreciate it I think you would because that
that's a double album and it is just layers and layers and layers a lot of shit yeah I mean I
definitely listen to music in a very similar way I definitely listen to it uh I'm listening to like
the structure of it I'm I'm listening to like interesting uh side melodies and harmonies and
all uh and yeah I'm bad about listening to lyrics as well yeah I remember like like going to
Beyonce's album and like hearing she puts hints of her other songs in other songs and she's like
following those threads and stuff and the patterns and yeah I like all that stuff now
uh but I'm still self-conscious you remember years ago when 50 shades closed I was an uber
driver for two weeks oh yeah and the thought of putting on my own music when someone else got into
a car stranger was like good lord like that was the most stressful thing to me was what to have
on the speakers when someone entered my vehicle yeah my brother and I were very lucky
as kids for a little while while we were going to St. Mark's uh mom and dad couldn't pick us up
after school we had a babysitter for a couple months and she would come and get us and she was
a cool college student and she was jamming to the Violent Films she had that oh solid car the whole
time um and that first Violent Films album it was fresh it was brand new then and John and I
listened to that a lot that was her jam and so we both got to that John even more than me
like he's seen them in concert a couple more times than I have he's a big Violent Films head
and then we just got into you know a little more alternative stuff you know he went Depeche Mode
Tom Waits I went um they might be Giants and Body Count so you know we both had our things
uh we listened to all kind of crazy shit but that's the thing both of us very diverse musical
tastes does there was a great time and there was a great time and there was a great time and there
like I'm on uh I'm on a tour right now and we're sharing a Sprinter van yeah and we were doing a
late night drive and all of a sudden it was like we should put on some music and I was like I'm in
I'm in the front seat you know and I was like you have you have control you couldn't do it I was
like and I literally was like what is everybody like like I was like I'm not gonna lead the
charge I will not lead the charge on this I will not do it I was too scared I yeah I was like I
don't think this whole place is gonna jam out to the Avett brothers I don't think that's gonna happen
you never know
just gotta go for it Southside Johnny baby I say the other fails the other part of of John and I's
music and I think I don't know if this applies to you or Jacob Jacob probably you but we were
in a region coming up through college and whatnot that got a lot of bands tons of bands come through
Ohio and Louisville they just there's just a touring circuit through there with venues that
are older venues that can house you know three hundred to a thousand people for level bands
coming up
and at that time you could go see a concert for 15 20 bucks you know yeah so got to see all kind
of shit coming up in college I don't I don't guess that's really an option for a lot of college
students today I don't know I got to see this is a weird random one I got to see Vanilla Ice on one
of his first concerts that he did when he switched over to like thrash metal oh yeah when he first
came out of rap
oh right yes like Vanilla Ice or Ice Ice Baby would it might have even still been on the charts
when he was doing this and he was doing like scream thrash metal versions of all of his rap
songs crazy it was crazy it was at a place called the Bait Shack in Louisiana and yeah it was like
this is insane I remember going up to Ohio with John uh one time we went to see Alanis Morissette
right before she blew up uh we saw her on her Jagged Little Pill tour right before everything
really got huge like I said we probably saw her for 20 bucks and uh Tyler uh what's his name
the Foo Fighters drummer was with her at that point oh um that was one of his early gigs the
guy who just passed away sadly yeah yeah Tyler Hawkins thank you Hawkins that's it all I could
think of was Horton thank you uh Scoop Chat so yeah and it was just uh you know it was just a lot of
you know yeah it's cool and I also got to see Gwar at that same spot I saw Gwar twice in the same
weekend I saw him in Louisville and then saw him again in Cincinnati oh by the way Gwar's uh cover
of Pink Pony Club is so good right it's just spectacular it's just if you haven't seen Gwar
cover uh Pony Club then do yourself a favor pour one out for odorous also there was a really good
there was a really good rock uh radio station in my hometown growing up so I could I could pull
that up and they they always had really good songs they played some really good songs and
they played some fucking bangers on there and uh yeah it was like I don't know what the number was
it's like 106 or something like that uh but yeah that was that was probably the most that was most
of my music growing up because like we had cassette tapes and all but like I wasn't going
out and buying them I didn't have we didn't have cassette tape money not all that I was just
looking at my library to see like what what what are my top like what not
not my top my most recent uh ones I F1 soundtrack I really liked it uh great uh Springsteen Arctic
Monkeys Jesse Wells Brandi Carlile Jesse Wells that's good Jesse Wells is killing it yeah um
uh Noah Cyrus uh Irish band called Seal another Irish band called the High Stool Prophets that
was obviously inspired from Scoop Fest uh yeah yeah more Irish music in my life
two skinny J's Lena Hall uh Imagine Dragons Avett Brothers Brandi Carlile again what we got
Postal Service yeah what's the skinny with uh Pine of Plain they uh they still out and about
they're there's now they're going out two out of three at a time and rotating between the three
of them because this cruise ship uh changed their policies about hosting trios because of the amount
of cabin space it takes
up oh for fuck's sake yeah well there's only one solution one of they have to pair up somebody has
to pair up right yeah yeah yeah there's only one solution they have to become one of those things
like they have to attach each other's mouths to their assholes become one of those things
so they can go on tour together the only thing that they can do hey guys it's Matt Vian and Phil
start fucking quick
uh let's see what have I listened to lately oh yesterday I was listening to uh victory lap uh
Nipsey Hussle album oh I forget what triggered Nipsey Hussle in my head but boy was that album
fucking great uh gone too soon oh and then and then randomly uh boy talk about two sides of a
different coin here uh randomly last night I was listening to one more from the road which is a live
Lynyrd Skynyrd uh concert from the 70s wow so that's my two most recent is Nipsey Hussle and
Lynyrd Skynyrd wow so I guess nobody living I suppose now that I'm thinking about it as well
nobody living nobody living oh let's see we got one here from hey scoop get off my lawn hey guys
exciting news for Christmas my wife bought us tickets for Matt's show in Lexington next week
oh hell yeah that I don't think it's next week anymore right it happened it means I saw you it
means you came and we hung out yes I kept talking about it and she had to pretend it would be awful
to see Matt for a third time just so I wouldn't think that she didn't want to go or just so I
would think she didn't want to go
uh boy is she right now the real question is will you do Battle of Dreams again I'm convinced and
possibly wrong about how the trick works so I'll be watching carefully the last time you did it you
kept my wife's dream and put it away for later still waiting to know why see you soon Matt and
here's an obelisk I did a while back for you guys enjoy hey Scoop get off my lawn uh quickly before
you get to that game uh yes no Battle of Dreams was cut from this show uh that was a fooler's run
and the jokers uh they did not want it in the show um uh I don't do that trick as often as I used to
just because I haven't ever been performing in an environment where I have I tried to do it on
cruise ships and what happened was I found that the staff would not get all the papers out to
everybody but they would get out to like 20 or 30 people and it made it feel more exclusive than
exclusive uh with people in the audience there people were upset that they didn't get to do it
yeah and it's also part of the prover that anybody can do it that's it anybody can participate yeah
so sometimes people don't even have the papers like what the hell do I care yeah I actually want
to change the so right now Penn and Teller are doing it in their show and they have made it much
more sophisticated is it going well and it's going very well and Penn has really made it his own and
he invented the trick and performed the trick saw the latest version of Penn and Tellers and said I'm
not going to do it anymore you guys are doing such a better job with oh wow I did and so he said I'm
going to stop performing it um are they back at it you should have you should have started by saying
that you should have started by being like I'm not doing it in my show anymore because Penn and
Teller are doing it so well well so hondro and I have decided not to for now I didn't really like
that we were all doing it and like we would also all three of us would kind of like talk about
different things we've learned from different versions of doing it
anything that part was awesome you know to feel like I'm included in the group with hondro and Penn
and uh I actually want to change the trick for myself now uh because of doing crowd work off
people's dreams uh versus like I basically I'm trying to like figure out a trick that could
I could cut into more social media friendly things right uh and put it earlier in the show not make
it like a finale piece
uh I'm thinking about asking people for fun facts about them or someone in their family
as a go-to ask instead of asking people to come up with a crazy dream
I think I want to get like hardcore some kind of fun fact about oh yeah fun fact about somebody
that you're there with that's a that's a fun that's a fun ask yeah and I think that and so
uh but right now I'm doing the Joker's tour so there's no room for new material I pitched it
right I said no and um uh uh I pitched it
I said not funny enough so we moved on and I have a bunch of cruise work coming up and then lately
I've been doing more corporates I don't think it's the kind of trick I want to do for corporates yeah
right I want to like put it in a live environment first to feel what it really is before I figure
out what the corporate version is um so I'm trying to figure out when the hell I can add
new to my show but the first time the first opportunity I get I'm adding that to to the
to the routine oh yeah um because it was finishing with a physical production of the dream uh right uh
because it was finishing with a physical production of the dream uh because it was finishing with a physical production of the dream uh
when I was touring and uh especially for my show a production is a big deal uh because I'm a one-man
operation uh and I think I have a fun thing for that I think I have a fun way to finish the trick
out so uh we'll see and you got that um and you got that prop that I sent you for your new finale
spot too Jacob sent me I ran across a sale it was a sale on like Facebook Marketplace yes for like a
giant fire cage like a disappearing so you go inside set yourself on fire and disappear right
yeah the best thing about Las Vegas is people selling magic props on Facebook Marketplace
well I I gave away uh uh my levitation uh rig all right on Facebook Marketplace
and and and we're interacting and the person who did it is actually a performer here in town
she showed up right so we're interacting
and all of a sudden a woman pulls up in a truck and I was like oh I didn't know the person I was
interacting with was a woman and then it's that thing of like oh God we're meeting over Facebook
Marketplace how do I not be creepy but then the thought of that makes me automatically creepy
right plus you were saying all of this out loud you were thinking out loud oh God a girl
and I just dropped my pants down to my ankles
and I I basically was like hi wife wife wife my wife your wife my wife my wife wife my wife my kids I
have wife and kids we are not this is not weird um but we ended up becoming uh we actually ended
up becoming Instagram friends and now I'm gonna see the rig in action uh I think uh in April oh
yes um which would be great because I never put it into my show but uh yeah so and now it'll
be in Jim Kramer's show yeah yeah but Lexington so a bunch of scoops came out to Lexington and
obviously obviously like not keeping that fresh in my mind that we did a turnout here but yes oh
yeah scoop John B Mike wins Nicholas Newman his lovely wife uh so many scoops came out I was
giving out the chips Paul you'd be proud of me I was giving I am I'm very proud of you for giving
out chips and the Criss Angel has a question stickers that Harry the grillogician made for
me thank you and of course we huddled around because as you know everyone's entitled to free
high fives and to watch the video on my phone of the sex doll experience sex doll eyes explosion
hilarious it's the new best part about seeing us in person I'm sure it was the hit of all of it
it was I mean it delivers that's all I'm gonna say
it's pretty intense huh I've gotta pull that up and save it on my phone just for when people ask
for that reason actually send it to me send me the text of it I'll save it I'll send you I'll
send you all three videos because you have to watch the first two before the oh right you got
to see this yes the awkward setup for the build up yeah yeah I have it all on uh on Messenger
somewhere but I don't have it on my phone hilarious oh let's do a little jock verse
nerd is the thing I'm gonna do when I find the button
versus nerd action oh am I yeah I'm on the hunt for balls
on the hunt for balls oh we got an obelisk jock versus nerd today from hey scoop get off my lawn
we have double downs we have super steals where you steal the other people's points you have
regular steals where you just steal the control of the game and we have uh 50 50. that's the other
one yeah yeah we have 50 50s uh just like the old millionaire game and yeah uh let's see the
question is the $200 question is States and it's going to me first nobody's doing anything yet
let's see what this question is which state was founded first
Jersey Kentucky Louisiana Nevada Nevada's out we know it's not in Nevada yeah it was one of the
last yeah I mean it's got to be Jersey right I'll say Jersey yeah Jersey one of the original 13.
yeah uh oh it's still me right uh sports if somebody's gonna steal yell at me uh no the Pelicans
team has Origins dating back to 1887 what state are they in Kentucky New Jersey Nevada and Louisiana
I mean I think the answer to this is Louisiana yeah I'm just gonna say Louisiana is the answer
to this question it's Louisiana it's Louisiana Pelicans there is a minor league baseball team
I think it's South Carolina that's the that's the Pelicans as well
uh let's see Capitals Capitals Paul you love Capitals you ought to steal this question uh no I
really don't you can go ahead and crash which state has the largest capital city by area spell this
capital Nevada Louisiana New Jersey or Kentucky largest capital city by area oh that's a good
question all right Nevada is Carson City it ain't that big you know what
I would bet Louisiana I mean I would bet Kentucky I would bet Kentucky
what's the capital of Kentucky is it Louisville Jefferson Jefferson Jefferson I mean Baton Rouge
is pretty big Baton Rouge Baton Rouge I don't think it's Jersey I don't think it's isn't
Jersey Jersey City Trenton Trenton is the capital oh well in that case I really I think it's even
less Jersey now Trenton I'm gonna say Louisiana I think it's Baton Rouge Trenton is French for the
stick interesting holy Nevada Nevada Carson City Carson City yeah sorry Nick I meant Frankfurt not
Jefferson I'm confused Jefferson Jefferson County I don't know it's like God run uh uh uh
they got run uh uh Zoom Twitch and Zoom and yeah Twitch and Zoom because otherwise we have to just
be corrected over emails preserve it for life it's fine I'm I'm fine to be yeah yeah uh question for
$800 question comics Paul the the uh it switches over to you Paul for comics okay great oh it's
always naturally switches turns when I I missed it oh right now I got it wrong so I lost control
that's how games work I understand moving that's right that's right what state has the most comic
book stores 103 is the estimate Kentucky New Jersey Louisiana or Nevada oh
which state has the most comic book stores Kentucky Louisiana New Jersey Nevada
I'll go Kentucky let's try it I'm sorry it's New Jersey it was between New Jersey that's pretty great
oh and it switches over to Matt just in time for magic the thousand dollar question yes
how is Penn and Tuller's bullet catch trick performed ah is it a mirrors
AI search which state has the most magic shops Nevada Louisiana Kentucky or New Jersey well
now what do you consider magic uh are we talking like stage magic are we talking like
voodoo voodoo dolls and Louisiana got it all beat oh oh I thought you were going to talk about the
uh the card shops the the magic cards oh no no no no those are specialty though and it's rare to have
just a card shop those are always like multiple games shops most of the time what I know the one
in Kentucky just closed so Kentucky is right out it's gotta be well I don't know when he wrote this
it's an obelisk Matt that's true that's true uh it is a few weeks old there was a magic shop that's
only open for an hour a week it was also a clock repair shop and I went for an hour a week you would
just be yeah yeah and the line was out the door with people holding the clocks because there's
like one that was a much bigger need than selling magic stuff I still I bought a chop cup and a
couple other little magic things from there that's cool that's cool but he died so it's gone oh oh no
lazy ran out of time did he I'll go with Jersey again let's try it Nevada oh Nevada makes sense
is this one of those that like Penn and Teller's uh merch booth counts as a magic shop on AI or
something no but I can I can name three uh here in town and that's that's a lot three is more than
most towns have yeah most towns don't have back to me just in time for audio video 1200 question
anybody stealing nope according to AI search which state has the most audio video stores
oh like best buys and Nevada Kentucky New Jersey Louisiana
all right I'm taking Louisiana out people in Louisiana don't have money it ain't about money
it's about did you get that base in your car did you want the jams yeah man I understand what you're
saying they ain't got no money I bet it's Jersey I bet it's Jersey too I'm going Jersey it's Jersey
yeah they got their electronics in Jersey we're known for our malls and the amount of malls we
have so there's gotta be oh there you go in every mall yeah of course oh let's see I've got gambling
$1400 question gambling which state has the second highest revenue from gambling Louisiana Nevada
Kentucky New Jersey Jersey again I don't know Louisiana's got all the casinos oh Louisiana's
got a bunch of riverboat casinos too yeah she's got Atlantic City yeah they've got Atlantic City
oh yeah I mean they've got casinos in New Orleans and they're a bunch of riverboat ones yeah I don't
understand I like this play Jacob I like where you're going yeah yeah I mean it is like there's
more in Louisiana than you think yeah that's what I think Kentucky I feel like is out well
yeah we have to go to Indiana how much money is just better the Kentucky Derby alone
oh sure yeah I guess damn it horse racing yeah I mean that's gotta be the Kentucky Derby in the
middle I think are still the two biggest uh gambling events like single single day gambling events
um huh even the chat split on this all over this is this is a crazy one this is this head scratcher
uh I'll try ah I'm going to I'm going Atlantic City I'm going Jersey it is Jersey yes Jersey pride eat it
$1600 question it stays in my wheelhouse drugs I will steal oh oh I think Paul said it first Paul
stealing I'm stealing drugs has the most drug related deaths New Jersey Nevada Louisiana or
Kentucky I'll go with Kentucky let's try it it's Kentucky yeah I I honestly feel like all three of
us would have gotten that right no you know what's crazy like honestly the last time I was back in
Kentucky this was probably 10 years ago plus now uh driving in my hometown of Richmond uh-huh the
areas that were just normal everyday little side streets were absolutely ramshackle crack house
yeah death row looking just oh no it's horrible it's awful I think meth has just really been bad
ripped through that state it's it's meth it's a lack of money it's lack of good jobs it's lack
of people uh feeling like they have uh somewhere to go and and like a a finish line in life to try
to get to it's awful I hate all of it yeah uh really speaking of really good things you know
alcohol would have helped those problems is less immigrants god damn you're so
good oh boy this country is so crazy uh Matt you stealing the alcohol questions yeah I'm stealing
it you want you stealing it are you super stealing it I'm gonna steal just because of this I gotta
say because you're gonna super steal for me and I have to be able to super steal back which state
has the most alcohol related crimes slash deaths Kentucky Louisiana Nevada New Jersey oh this is a
tough one because obviously that's gotta be Louisiana right Nevada New Jersey is a huge
population but Nevada man do people get drunk
and run people over here that's just uh yeah we were it's our state task we just had an article
touting that we actually did not hit 400 vehicular deaths in Las Vegas this year the first time I saw
that the first time since 2021 we finally this is what we're celebrating all right no one was on the
road since the first time since horse and buggies yeah but Jersey's so huge yeah Jersey's big
Louisiana I mean yeah I mean that's not that's not it's not a sober state nope nope alcohol related
crimes but it's not per capita and ah all right I'm gonna go Kentucky's got a lot of bourbon I'm
gonna go with uh uh Richard and Chad sub 400 sub 400. I'm gonna go Jersey just because of the
population Jersey it's Louisiana oh good job Louisiana whoa all right guys getting with it
uh Paul is getting happiness no he's not I'm stealing if it was I guess Louisiana the second
oh yeah uh this state is ranked fourth in the U.S uh in happiness in recent studies fourth the fourth
happiest so fourth happiest overall I guess probably Nevada because there's nobody living
there comparatively yeah like Nevada's population is pretty low right oh no we have a lot of self
esteem down here in Nevada we do uh I feel like Louisiana is not happy I feel like it's filled
with not happy people especially right now they're all snowed in and iced in
uh shout out to my mom's neighbors who uh took my mom and my and my sister-in-law and my niece
in when all their power was out generators they have a generator so my my family stayed with them
that's very well that's very sweet and neighborly oh certainly certainly uh I would expect nothing
less from these neighbors they're wonderful people uh it's got okay I'll say I don't know Nevada I'm
not happy with this question at all oh wait no I wanted 50 50. I'm 50 50 in
oh that got rid of Nevada that got rid of Nevada and Kentucky Louisiana or New Jersey it's got to
be New Jersey then I'll go see New Jersey oh yeah living in the shadow of New York and Philly just
so unhappy super steal Paul is super stealing
category birth over 80 percent of people born in this state never leave it for residency New Jersey
Louisiana Nevada Kentucky wow 50 50 me there dick all right my name is Jacob that got rid of New
Jersey and Nevada I was gonna say people get the hell out of Jersey I'll tell you that much yeah uh
I'm gonna go with Kentucky these these were the two that I would have questioned is Louisiana and
Kentucky gotta be it is Kentucky I wouldn't have been surprised by Louisiana super stealing for
the game I didn't think this through money is the category the estimated net worth of all residents
in this state is 7.7.
9 trillion dollars the estimated net worth of all residents in this state is 7.79 trillion dollars
Kentucky Louisiana Nevada New Jersey ah 50 50 me there dick that got rid of Louisiana and Nevada
yeah which I feel like we're the two easy ones to get rid of it was I felt the same way the word
residents and and uh that got rid of Nevada
and Louisiana as I've discussed in this show ain't got no money so once again I mean Kentucky
Louisiana needs to have a Patreon going state of Louisiana I'll tell you that just just the horse
Farms alone in Kentucky might be worth trillions of dollars but uh you know New Jersey like I said
it's it's it's it's uh community got that old money you drove me past all those Mansions yeah
yeah and it's and it's it's right near New York and it's right near Philly yeah they got that money
they got that money giving it up giving it up for New Jersey all right let's see it it's Jersey oh my
God he got it all he got it all and that is the game oh yeah Atlantic City Paul and I are tied
with zero points a piece and Matt eked out the win with with sixteen thousand eight hundred points
Springsteen and Bon Jovi live there you know what I mean like it's got to be way up there there's some
there's some money there uh thank you who created that that's hey Scoop get off my lawn thank you so
much get off my lawn if you want to send us an obelisk or any kind of Jock versus nerd or any
kind of uh scoop mail head over to hey scoops.com hey scoops.com right there on the home page you
can send us a Jock versus nerd you can send us some scoop mail do all those things right over there
at hey scoops.com do it now all right uh I want to thank all the people who uh listen to our show
week in and week out we really appreciate it um if you want to help us out uh in a way that doesn't
involve uh cash or money uh can you recommend us to a friend of yours could you pick one person
and one person only check out a couple episodes of our podcast it's called the obelisk scheme because
a pyramid scheme is unethical that's not what we're about so recommend us to one and one person only
and see if they can dig our show uh and that really helps keep this podcast going uh all
these years as we enter your as we approach year 13 12. we'll never know oh oh who can say well we
started we'll never know we started in 14. no one knows no one knows uh and uh uh I'm also gonna
thank some of the people supporters over on our Patreon page these people uh selected a tier that
entitles them to uh an on-air thank you
and all of these people uh have both a high net worth and very low uh drug death uh percentage
in their households oh good job Peter McDougall Phil Rendley Phil Tomlinson Phil Guyton uh Phil
Guyton by the way he's him and Andy made me go back and watch the season finale of land man when
I wrote it off they're on my list I'm not happy with it Rachel Forrester radioactive scoop Ralph
Barrett Randy Norris
the following people have decided that they are going to conjoin with a couple other folks
in a human centipede style so that they can perform Irish music on a cruise ship Salt Lake
Scoop, Sanja Petrovic, Scoop Bucky, Scoop Knack Paddywhack, Scoop Lindsey, Scoop Nick, Scoop Nurse, Scoop of Henley, Scoop Skywalker, Scoop Hall's Drag Race, Scoop Mids, Scoopaluga, Scoopy Geek, Scoopy Ramones, Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess, Scoopy Bartfast, Scott Muldering, Scott Robin, Scott Schofield, Sean Kellner, and Seanathan P.
And the following Scoops all went into a record store in Asbury Park and asked for the most popular album, and that's how they got their CDs of Southside Johnny.
That's Sir Scoopy McScooperson III, Smells Funny, Smitty Scoop, Sola Scoop, Soundman Scoop, Stab and Dash Scoop, Stacy Coleman, Stacy Westerlin, Stephen Clively, Stephen Landon, Stephen Biggs, Stephen Marinelli, Stuart Wilson, Sugar Russ Socio, Take It Evie Podcast, Teddy Mueller, Tess Miller, Tess Sterling, That Thing in the Attic, The Bad Humor Man,
and of course, The Bad Humor Man.
And of course, The Didgeridoo. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. If you want to be thanked on air, and you love this podcast, you want to keep it going, you can support us over at patreon.com slash hey, Scoops.
What?
That's really tough. Why don't you just type in preachingfun.com?
Or if you enjoy writing down your dreams and then throwing them at magicians, go to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts, fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz. That along with preachingfun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon supporters.
So please, if you...
If you think this show is worth more than $0, preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those are the places you can go.
Head on over there right now.
Yeah.
It's pretty good.
Do it.
Yeah. And thanks, everybody, for all the...
All Scoops, we will stop by our Zoom today.
All the people who joined us on Twitch, we appreciate you.
For everyone listening out there, we love you.
Stay safe out there, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Bye.