Oh hello there, I'm so glad you're here, it's time to thank the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers, this is a bank show so I don't have a list,
but thank you to each and every Ice Cream Truck Driver out there, we sure do love ya,
and we're glad that you're bringing this fucking Ice Cream straight to people's fucking ear
holes.
If you wanna be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, head over to PreachingFun.com, PreachingFun.com
is where you can go to sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows, the life
you save may be your own.
Now here's the show.
Hey Johnny, do you wanna go to an Ice Cream Social?
I do.
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go!
It's a bank show, it's the day after the bucket show, here we are, home at it and still in
town.
We're in town, it's time for Matt Madley's Ice Cream Social, sitting over there, it's
Paul Madley, sitting over there, it's Matt Donnelly, sitting over here, it's Shakeup
the Audio Guy.
Can I get you to 8.8?
We're PreachingFun.
Maybe.
No, this is Stopgap.
Yeah, this is churn, stopgap.
Churn, stopgap.
Stopgap, churn, you make me wanna stop my truck and fuck you.
Stopgap churn.
Oh, I knew it was roomy.
I don't know what to talk about first, whether we had a good bucket show or not, or that
Paul gave my children porn, I don't know which one we should dive into first.
I would say let's start with the bucket show and let's billboard Paul giving your children
porn.
Fine.
I'll take it, I'm no prude.
I feel like that was shots fired at my direction.
Oh yeah, there were, there were definitely shots fired.
Now I'm gonna talk about it, now we're gonna talk about it.
Okay.
Now it's out there.
Why'd you give Matt's kids, Paul?
So I got to go to visit Ralph's, which is my favorite comic book shop in the world and
got to talk to my buddy.
He's doing good.
Don't miss Ralph out at Alternate Reality Comics.
It is the hot spot for the comic bookage out there in Vegas.
And I got Keeler, Keeler is very into comic books right now.
I got him some books last time, got him some Fantastic Fours, and he's got a couple of old
Guardians of the Galaxy.
So we were looking for maybe get some more of those Guardians of the Galaxies, that kind
of thing.
Ralph did not have those.
Fucking Ralph.
No, they're a little harder to come by.
But he did have a copy of Infinity Gauntlet, the trade.
So I grabbed that.
Okay, Ralph.
Because that's a key thing that Keeler needs to check out because like, and I, you know,
it's been a minute since I reread that story, but Mephisto plays a role in that.
And that's the new--
From He-Man?
No.
This is not, by the way, where the story's going.
Paul's just doing a recap of all the comics that Keeler bought.
It's not Fisting Porn that he gave you?
And then I bought him--
If he gave your son Fisting Porn.
What was the other one?
You haven't gotten the latest issue of The Angry Goose?
I got him--
The pissed off Goose.
The All-Star Superman.
You're waiting for the trades to come out?
You don't want to get it?
Those spoilers, please.
Angry Goose game is hot shit.
No, I got him the All-Star Superman new mini trade.
And that's the pornography?
No.
Oh, okay.
Then I went to the 50 cent bin because I love to raid me some old comics because you can
find some gold.
I found a--
Early 2000--
Savage Dragon number one, Minty Fresh, a bunch of stuff like that.
I got him some Rob, Batman, and Robin.
You're just going to do Rinner Corridor to this bank episode twice, one where Paul tells
his version first and one where I tell my version first.
Right.
Yeah.
It's going to be great.
And then the audience can decide which one they want to listen to first.
And then I see there's a copy of Powers.
Okay.
Here you go.
One of my all-time favorite books.
Powers.
Brian Michael Bendis.
Kyle Austin.
Brian Michael A. von Ohming, whose artwork I love and follow through a bunch of different
books.
So--
Do they have any particular styles to their artwork?
It's very angular.
Okay.
So I think Batman Beyond.
Right now I'm thinking of the movie Heavy Metal.
That's what I'm picturing right now.
More Batman Beyond.
Okay.
You know Batman Beyond?
You familiar with that?
Kind of very, very angular.
It's almost Bruce Timm.
Oh, Bruce Timm.
Sure.
It's very Bruce Timmian.
Great.
Michael A. von Ohming stuff.
Anyway, I pick up that book and I'm like, oh, great, Powers.
And it's a newer issue, newer in that it probably came out 10 years ago.
And you were like, Matt's children need to be introduced to Powers.
I was like, Powers is such a good book.
This is the guy who invented the Miles Morales Spider-Man, which my kids love.
Yes.
That's the Spider-Verse Miles Morales.
Okay.
Brian Michael Bendis did Ultimate Spider-Man back in the day, reinvigorated the character
in whole huge ways.
And he is a juggernaut of--
I still haven't seen that second movie.
--comic stuff.
The first one was so good.
I just never got around to seeing the second one.
And he's deep with that movie, too.
He was big in-- I think he had a--
It's one of the only movies where the multiverse really just is the plot and works.
You're like, oh, this is just a really well-earned use of multiverse.
Oh, did you not see the Dr. Strange?
What was that?
Which one was that?
It was the Dr. Strange.
Yeah, I saw all of them.
Yeah, yeah.
First, I saw Dr. Strange.
And then I saw Dr. Strange from Google.
Yeah, that was good.
And then finally came back, Dr. Strange, like, guys, seriously, though, you won't believe
it.
Dr. Strange.
Lots of places.
Dr. Strange and the Net Full of Jello.
So I get it.
And I've got a couple other books.
And then we're heading out.
That's Paul's brothers, by the way.
Paul's brothers in the house, by the way.
Oh, yes, honks here.
Yeah.
And so I bought these books for Keeler.
And then I'm handing them over.
And then I'm like, oh, wait a minute.
Sometimes--
No, we got in the car.
Comic book's in hand.
Everything's purchased.
Matt has had enough.
Paul turns to me and goes, oh, there might be boobies in one of those comics.
I hope that's OK.
OK.
Are the kids with you?
What am I going to do?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Turn around, yank it out of his hand, go back into the comic book store.
If I knew it was to the 50 cent bin, maybe it would have been more of an option than
I thought.
But I was like, well, there's no turning back now.
We live here now.
This is the multipurpose that we currently live in.
I'm not upset that he did it.
I'm upset at the sequence of events.
But I sequenced it out of my head in the wrong way, too, because I just didn't remember.
I was like, oh, yeah, there's some-- but it's very like circle with another circle on it.
It's very like happy face eyeball.
Paul, some of the great graphics of the boob.
My son has to understand that the main character in the very first page is at a strip club.
And I have to let him take in that plot point and just figure out how he's living his life.
Look, my kids are being raised in Las Vegas.
They pass little darlings billboards all the time.
That's right.
There was a moment at the Bucket Show last night where I think Jonathan stopped the show
just to make sure that everyone knew that those two kids in the front row were your
kids.
Yes.
It was like, everybody, I need you to know something, there are two children up here.
They're Matt's children.
They're fine.
Jonathan made some real hay about them in the front row.
It was like, why do you bring these children to this R-rated show?
At one point he went to duct tape Hilliard's eyes.
Oh, good.
Well, it was funny.
The last Bucket Show-- and we'll get back to-- there's no way to go back to it.
Basically, I was just like, the sequence of events is before you hand my child the thing,
think is there boobies in it.
The second thing is then ask me before you purchase so that I can get cool dad points.
Right.
You're right.
Instead, Paul just put me in a position to just be an impotent fuddy duddy.
Right.
There's no way I was going to stop.
And I won.
I won completely because then we pulled up to another-- we pulled up to another comic
shop.
Paul, what did you win?
I'll tell you what I won.
We pulled up to another comic shop and we're getting ready to hop out of the car.
And I was like-- I was kind of half apologizing.
I may have overstepped there.
I didn't really recall that there are boobs, possibly boobs, but I think it's fine and
dandy.
Age one.
He's got to learn.
He's got to learn some time.
It's fine.
That's what I want.
I want old Uncle Paul to be in charge of my child's sexual awakening.
If he ain't awake now--
He's got to learn some time.
Yes.
If he ain't awake yet, it ain't happening.
He's 12.
I'm sure he has membership to--
He's awake.
Yeah.
That's awful.
He's got his own OnlyFans.
He's got a subscription to Jugg's Magazine.
Jugg's Magazine.
Nudie magazine day.
Dad, do you mind if I get the mail?
Any discrete packages for me?
Just go get the mail.
I'm looking for a rather discrete package.
Hey, but it's been a huge help having you get the mail.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I love to do it.
I camp out there now just to make sure I don't miss the mailman.
We're good friends, he and I. Can you imagine--
He brings me comic books.
Can you imagine--
Just the man with a wink like, here you go, pal.
Some good editorials in the back.
Here's another issue of Powish for you.
Boy, these circles really kind of look like tits.
You won't believe it.
These circles are so fucked up.
Now, every time he goes to get any basketball or soccer ball in the garage, he bunches.
Oh, no.
Forget it.
Yeah.
It's a very basic shape with sexuality.
He gets a protractor out and he's like, "Oh, it's roundish, bwaaang."
Yeah.
No, I fucked up.
No, but--
Boy's 12, so he still yells bwaaang every time.
Bwaaang.
I raise it.
We have to communicate in our household.
Bwaaang.
When you're 12, it makes that sound.
It is that strong.
Oh, I miss it.
I know, right?
Those were the days.
Now he goes, "Bwaaang, bwaaang, bwaaang."
See, the whole time I thought something was wrong with Matt's car.
Turns out there was a sexual awakening happening.
I also was reading Powers.
Bwaaang, bwaaang, bwaaang.
I already fished out a few of my copies in 50 Cent Den, but they were in another section.
But we're hopping into this new comic shop to go browse around a little bit more.
I was like, "Yeah, you know, I'm sorry.
I might have overstepped."
But I really was like, "He's got to learn sometimes.
It's fine."
It's just a round little boob.
Both?
You're ping-ponging between two incorrect things.
But then Matt's like, "It's fine.
He can have it.
No problem."
Which is great.
What other choice did I have?
Right.
You're done now.
Then Keeler goes, "I'm trading for Paul as my dad."
And I said, "You are going to regret that decision so quickly."
I said, "But you are going to enjoy your meals more."
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
You're going to love the food.
The food plan?
Top notch.
Cologne and cheese, hot dogs, mac and cheese.
Forget about it.
Pizza?
Every day, if we want it, who cares?
But that soccer game?
No.
Forget about it.
No, no, no.
What time does it start?
What time?
No, no, no.
How hot will it be?
No, we're not doing that.
Oh, no.
Will I sit in the sun?
In a folding chair?
You want me to coach what?
Eat shit.
A plasticky folding chair?
Here.
Here's two Game Boys.
Leave me alone forever.
And then we were in the second comic shop, and when I stayed away by the near shot, he
turned to the guy who works there, he goes, "Do you have anything more adult?"
And he slid a $5 bill across the...
Do you have any of those Tijuana Bibles where Mickey's like really slipping it to all kinds
of kids?
You got any books?
You got some Tijuana Bibles back there?
Because that's what I really...
I'm hungry for that poor art.
I didn't think we were going to get an episode title out of this story.
You're familiar with Tijuana Bibles, aren't you?
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I've never heard them called that.
I'm not familiar with the term.
So a Tijuana Bible is a bootleg comic usually involving big brand name characters doing
pornographic things.
And it's...
They're usually published out of Mexico.
Mickey Mouse fucking Cinderella.
Yes, exactly.
And so...
Where is it?
Where can I do this?
Instead of us, see?
Oh, boy.
We've peaked visit.
Oh, it's like I was young again.
Holy shit.
Fuck me.
Oh, Tijuana Bibles.
No one call me up to the chalkboard to solve some math.
Oh, no.
I'll just be back here with my inconspicuously wrapped package.
Nothing to see here, Mrs. Johnson.
Oh, I got a divorce mini.
I'm back, Mickey.
Paul cemented his love with my children.
Yeah.
I'm sorry if I'm cutting off Paul's narrating of a Tijuana Bible porn.
I was telling a dumb joke.
It's...
Mickey goes up to Donald.
I got a scratchy Funko pop for my other child.
Yeah.
Keeler's not so much on the reading tip right now.
I feel your pain of your children loving Paul more.
Right.
Because Uncle Paul is fun uncle.
Yeah.
You know?
He's like, you know, no limits.
He knows his job.
He's no limits.
Yeah.
Yes.
No limits.
Well, because I am still there.
Right.
What?
No.
Yeah.
What?
I'm still there.
What are you talking about?
Peter Pan.
Yeah.
Do do do.
Fly me to Neverland.
This is what Peter Pan really looks like.
Yep.
I am...
Paul has a habit...
Sorry, Wendy.
He's wearing green tights.
...of giving gifts to people, like, of things that he likes and therefore things you want.
Well, like...
Yes.
Most people who don't have children don't understand, like, how different they are from
year to year...
Yes.
...in terms of what they can and can't watch or take in or whatever.
Yeah.
But Paul got your...
So I was explaining this to you last night.
So when Eve was two, for Christmas...
He always sends stuff for Christmas.
Yeah.
Sure.
Which is great.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
And he sent the entire DVD full collection of Looney Tunes.
And he's like, "Now you and Eve can, like, watch all the Looney Tunes."
And I'm like, "Great.
She's two."
And I'm like, "There is no understanding."
She's not going to use sign language for more Looney Tunes.
No.
Yeah.
She's like...
But...
I want more food.
I need to be burped.
Yes.
Also, can we watch all of Looney Tunes?
Yeah.
Right?
But now, almost 10 years later...
[gibberish]
Hello, Eve.
What was that?
That was the Tasmanian Devil.
Thank you.
Man.
Okay.
That was better than his Donald Duck and you still don't know why everything's better than
my Donald Duck.
We'll let the listeners decide.
Do you think anybody's still listening?
No.
But then...
But...
But it comes around.
Yeah.
So, almost 10 years later, Shelly was out of town, and I had the girls.
And I was like, "All right.
We're going to have movie night.
And let's go rummage through my old DVDs and see what we found."
Okay.
Because I was like, "We're going to watch The Three Amigos."
And so I was like, "I'm going to introduce you to the great Singing Bush."
It's all of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Just a plethora of wonders.
Great movie.
A plethora.
And so we go through there, and we find it.
But on the way to finding the Three Amigos DVD, we also found the box edition set of Looney
Tunes.
And they know Looney Tunes at this point.
They've seen a few.
And they're like, "Oh," and they flip their shit.
And we watched Looney Tunes, and I introduced them to the Coyote Roadrunners for the first
time.
And it was one of the greatest nostalgic, awesome moments with my kid.
Because they're freaking cackling.
Chuck Jones, baby.
And it's the best.
So it comes around.
But I hear you're...
The listeners are familiar with the amount of movies that Paul says I should watch with
my kids that are just not appropriate.
Just not appropriate.
It's the same thing with my kids.
To be fair to me, I made a big list of movies I thought could be appropriate for the last
time Honk brought the girls out.
And we've landed on Back to the Future.
Oh, and it crushed.
It did, right?
It crushed.
She's still loving it, right?
Eve was like...
Eve's in that...
She's 11.
So she's now starting in that area of being able to understand the uncomfortable humor.
And so when Marty's mom is hitting on Marty, she was, I mean, contorted in the chair.
But it's a testament to how good that movie is.
It makes you feel some shit.
And to how much incest still affects people.
And I guess how healthy your children's internet porn searches will be, since that seems in
vogue on the internet.
It's everywhere.
It's so bizarre.
But that's good.
Because she's still like, have you done the follow-ups yet?
We haven't done any of the follow-ups yet.
Yeah.
But...
Well, that's great.
We should.
For sure.
Nora was still a little too freaked out when the Libyans came and shot up Doc Brown.
She was out.
She's like, "Oh, that's too much for me.
I'm good."
She's gone.
She's like, "Nope."
But Eve stuck through and really enjoyed the Libyans.
But yes, I would definitely at this point have shown, had I had children, they would
have seen way more inappropriate material than being supposed to, way more inappropriate
stuff.
Now, John, how much are you looking forward to next year, Paul bringing your then 12-year-old
pornography?
Are you looking forward to this, or do you have a little trepidation here?
As long as the quality is a little higher than eyeball boobs, maybe it's okay.
Circle on a circle?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, but I mean, he's sort of...
You've given some stuff, like a couple years ago, you gave her the entire ElfQuest series.
Right.
Now, that's not super out there, but it's a little more violent and mature for my 10-year-old.
But my girl's there...
I guess the mall seems a little brutal.
ElfQuest.
Eve is a voracious reader.
That's why I got it for her.
She does not stop.
Now.
And she really loved it.
She will read anything.
And so she devoured it.
She loved it.
Yeah.
It's a big volume.
To the point she reads so much that she will oftentimes come and she'll just be talking
to us, and then she'll say a word weird.
You know what she's saying, but she pronounces it weird because she's just read it.
She's only seen it.
She's only read it, and then she's read it as it's phonetically spelled or whatever.
And then she'll come and she'll say it, and then we sort of laugh, and then she gets mad.
And we're like, "No, no.
It's crazy that you know these words, and it's pronounced like this."
And she's like, "Oh, okay.
Well, it looks like this."
I've had a hard time explaining to my youngers, basically, I don't know how to... busting
chops.
When we laugh at the thing that you're known for, we're not trying to hurt your feelings
or ridicule you.
We're not trying to make fun of you.
Maybe that's the thing, because early on here, it continues through your whole life.
But within funny people, it's love language.
And that's the thing.
As soon as we're on that group chat with Jonathan and Brad, and Brad starts busting my balls,
I'm like, "I'm fine."
I'm like, "We're good.
Nope.
We're going to have a great show.
I got nothing to worry about here.
He feels comfortable giving me shit.
That's all I need out of a comedy partner.
That's it."
But I guess it just takes a little while to know, to learn that.
But maybe you can explain it to them like that, that it is love language.
Yeah, we're trying to.
I know.
It's hard.
In the moment, it's still like, it's like, "Urgh."
Well, when it's the first time, right, when it's the first time you've ever been called
out on something silly, and you go, "Oh."
Yeah, yeah.
I take it great every time.
But also-
We're going to talk about the bucket show in a minute.
Thank fuck he can feel a little bit of shame, because that's what's wrong with the world.
Nobody feels shame anymore.
That's funny.
That's true.
You know?
It's a control thing.
Sure.
You're not in control.
You're not in control of people's narrative of you.
And it can be a little jarring.
I'm like, "Oh, shoot.
This is how people talk about me, and I can't do anything about it."
It also depends on their age.
Oh, for sure.
I don't know if you've noticed that.
Because when they're younger, it's just ... But now, my oldest is reaching an age where her
appearance is becoming more important to her, and the way she ... You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I mean, a little bit.
I have two boys.
She's becoming aware of other people's-
If you go further, it just becomes a nightmare for me.
Go keep going.
Yeah.
But anyways, so it just-
But you got boys.
Yes.
Yeah.
Different.
You got the easy pass.
Easier to buy porn for.
Yep.
That's true.
That is true.
Way easier.
The sapphic comic book is a rare beast.
It's weird.
I think it's backwards.
I think boys are harder when they're younger.
Well, traditionally, they're harder when they're older.
And then-
Boy, ay, ay, ay, ay.
And then it reverses because little girls are just evil.
I didn't know that.
Right.
In their 40s, they're really difficult.
You know who else got Matt's children some pornography?
That's the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Maddie's Ice Cream Social, is brought to you by Greasy Al's Parmesan
Scented Deodorant.
Ooh.
That's right.
That's Greasy Al's Parmesan Scented Deodorant in 2022 from Dungeon Scoop and Dragon Scoop.
(singing)
Hey, Paisan! Why don't you get your face up in this pit right here?
You're gonna smell a frickin' pizzeria! (sniffing)
What do you think? Oh, that's nice. Yeah, that's my parmesan diode!
Mmm. Made with only the fresh grated cheese. It goes right on. Guaranteed to stick to your pit hair.
Oh, I got that. I also got gorgonzola flavor. And for the ladies out there, I have tampons made of
prosciutto. Enter H. Scoops Checkout! Lord! Paul's pronunciation of prosciutto really got to Matt.
Matt did not like that pronunciation. It's not an all-Caps version of boy-o-o-o-o-o-y. I remember,
whatever, the early days of accessing celebrity porn on the internet. Oh, right. Clips from movies
that already exist, but you're like, "What?" Oh, like Mr. Skin? Mr. Skin before Mr. Skin.
Yeah, Mr. Skin before Mr. Skin or whatever. What was that like? Cave drawings? That's right.
What was it? Circles on Circles. Penelope, what was it? Who was it? Who was it? Penelope Cruz?
Was it Penelope Cruz? Penelope Pitstop? That's it. Penelope Pitstop from Wacky Races? That's it.
Latin actress who was briefly Tom Cruise's Penelope Cruz. Yeah, she spelled it with a Z though.
That's right. It was Tom Cruise and Penelope Cruz. Did she put them on a glass at some point?
So, early, I'm showing my age here by describing the porn I'm looking at.
It was in a comic book. No, it was a screen grabs of, and so it had subtitles on the screen grabs
of her taking her top off or whatever, and she referred to her nipples as slices of pepperoni,
and I was like, "Oh." He took it right out? Yeah, I was like, "Oh, come on." I'm out.
Whatever the opposite of boy, shang-a-lang-a-lang, whatever the... That's it.
Is that Pac-Man dying? Yeah, the last thing I want to do is be sucking on a nipple and get
a little garlicky aftertaste. That's going to throw it off real bad. I don't want any aftertaste.
I just want regular garlic taste. You want full-flavored garlic nipple sauce?
I'll take any nipple I can get at this point. John, let's go get it out, buddy. Pickled nipples.
This Papa John sauce. Garlic buttered nipples. That's my favorite shot.
Last night we did the Bucket Show. Yes, we did.
It was super fun. Matt, Mattingly, Jonathan, and Brad.
Yeah, Jonathan, Mangum, and Brad came out. I just had someone mess with me now and do the thing I
hate the most. He goes, "I didn't realize it was Brad and Jonathan." I was like, "Dude, there was
never..." That would have made the difference. Come see the show or don't. Also, every post about it,
every ad about it had all four of you out there. I wasn't keeping Jonathan off anything. He was on
the poster that Eric made and we mentioned in the video. He didn't get billing last time because it
was a last-minute thing. Yes. Right. We talked about it. He didn't get as much billing. We talked
about him after the show last night because he was a last-minute addition to the last Bucket Show.
I actually paid to boost the post, the video of Brad and I talking about the show. It's not
because I was concerned with turnout, is that I hate the like, "Oh, I didn't know you guys were
doing that." Shut up. Facebook makes me pay to talk to my friends. I'm paying the money to make
sure that none of my friends fail to know that it had happened. I didn't know Jonathan was in it. I
was like, "No, just stop it. Just stop it." Super fun show. Great turnout. It was July 5th of the
night, the night of July 4th. Not the biggest theater going. It's hot. It's hot. It's Vegas.
It was a Saturday night. We don't usually do stuff on a Saturday night. There are other
things to do in Vegas on a Saturday night, turns out. But it was packed. We had to get extra chairs.
We got extra chairs out like four or five different times. It was so much because we got there. We had
rows all set up and everything. Then as soon as we opened the doors, we're like, "Well, those chairs
are full." Yeah. Yeah. So fun. Great crowd. We were Destination Tourism. Multiple scoops.
Yes. People actually ... I mean, John came out for it. John came out for it. Lee Popsicle came out.
That's right. Ben Sherman. Yep. Yep. It was wonderful. It was really fun. I mean,
Sarah Boyle and Bat Scoop, but they live here. That doesn't count. But-
It counts though. They keep showing up, doing the thing. They're diehards.
Yeah. Another scoop. Oh, shoot. I'm blanking on his name, but he flew out from Northern-
Milkleg Scoop. Yes. Milkleg Scoop. Oh, yeah. From Northern Cal.
Yep. Oh, Milkleg Scoop. That's right. He's the guy that-
Yeah. Did you miss him? He was out there last night.
He beat you in the costume contest at ScoopFest. He beat me in the costume contest.
Close. I'm glad you didn't see him. It would have been so awkward.
It would have been. Yeah. I'm glad I didn't see him.
Fucking fight. Throwing down.
It's on site with Milkleg. On site.
And my children were there as well. And it was just a super fun show.
It was a super fun, crazy show. It was. Brad had some really great
ideas in the way we generated our information for our scenes with Hot Seat, having it mostly
come from interviews on three different games. That was the key way we generated-
So we typically see a short form improv show. It's like, "Can we have a location?
Can we have a relationship?" We were doing that. And so Brad's idea was like,
"Let's really chat with people and then take whatever we want out of the interview and do
the scenes off of that." And one, that was successful. And two, our most ambitious
swing on that ended up being great, which I was like, "Instead of doing a scenic game,
let's use an interview to set up Jeopardy and we'll get our occupations from the interview.
We'll get our categories from the interview." The fact that you got those great categories
was great. Those were juicy. She said she wanted to do the Four
Horsemen of the Apocalypse cartoon. I go, "Great. What are those four again?"
And she named the four and was like, "That's our category."
Well, her idea was really, really good. It was about the four horsemen of the apocalypse
having to deal with the ramifications of taking care of all the souls that came up during COVID.
Oh, that's what she said.
Yeah. She said the four horsemen are forced to deal with all the idiots that died during COVID
because they didn't take proper precautions. So that's her whole idea. The pitch is like
dealing with the dumbest ghosts you've ever dealt with in the afterlife. I thought that
was really a fun idea. That is a fun idea. I was in and out of the
room while you guys were interviewing her. Yeah, so I only heard little bits and pieces.
I heard the four horsemen part and then I heard something about COVID.
But yeah, that makes a lot more sense. That's a good idea.
It's a good idea. The gem was her talking about her
sort of relationships. Yeah, we're getting there.
Oh my gosh. I stumbled into gold.
Gold. Diamonds, I would say diamonds. These two people were sitting right in
front of where I was standing to the degree that when Matt said at first when he picked out this
young lady, he pointed back there and I was like, can Matt not see me? Is Matt pointing at me?
Am I a shadowy figure in the back of the room? What's happening? What? Okay. But yeah, so she
was there. Her boyfriend was not there with her. That's what we discovered. Her friend, her friend
who is a long time friend. Yeah, was there with her. We all know what that is. Yeah. Yeah. No,
we definitely stumbled onto. Well, because in the order I said, you know, do you, do you have a
roommate? I live at home with my mom. I said, oh, okay. Do you have a boyfriend or a girlfriend
order? She goes, I have a boyfriend. I go, how long has it been out? And he goes, five years.
And the audience went, oh, yeah. The audience did the math real quick.
If you ain't shacked up after five years, something's up. And then I said, is your
boyfriend here? She goes, no. Right. I go, oh, who are you here with? And she goes, a friend.
And the audience went like, oh, I let her go to the audience. I go, relax. I think I'm going to
actually authentically extinguish this by going like, and you have a girlfriend or a boyfriend?
He goes, nope. And then the audience just went raw. Just roared.
Wait, you thought you were genuinely knocking that out? I mean, I was going to be still playful
with it, but I thought it was building fast. I thought you were egging it on.
No, I thought you were actually trying to make her more comfortable because the audience was
like flipping. I was like, okay. They were going really hard on her and she was going hard.
I was trying to spread it out a little bit. I definitely thought you were playing the dumb
a little bit to egg the audience on. Well, I was going to ask him the question I asked him
no matter what, which was, if you were dating someone for five years, would you think you'd
move in with them by now? And so I knew I was going to that question next, no matter what.
But she was a great sport to have a good sport about.
And he was great. I talked to him a little bit after the show and yeah, I was like, you guys were
fantastic. Thank you so much for being good sports. And they just had a great time.
Yeah. And so for the occupation, what's great, what I loved about it was that in Jeopardy,
it takes a while to set up, right? So you decide whether you're going to get categories or not,
but that's another round of suggestions and you get three occupations and then the audience has
those occupations and you have to come up with it. And then you have to worry about their
expectations with the occupations. You have to be the funniest plumber, the funniest whatever,
bus driver. Horseman of the apocalypse.
So all we do is interview her and I said, well, you're not going to believe this,
but you've inspired this fever dream Jeopardy. And then boom, we start playing the game and
Brad plays a guy who works in the back at Nordstrom Rack.
Cause she, uh, she works at Nordstrom Rack. Yeah. That was part of her interview.
Jonathan played, uh, the guy in the back, the guy in the back, the friend in the back.
That's right. The back rack. Yeah. And then, uh, Paul played the mother that she lives with.
Yeah. And then the Jeopardy categories were, uh, conquest, war, famine, uh, and the other,
and the other one, uh, and so pestilence and pestilence and the other one and the other one.
Yeah. I kept all five. Yeah. I thought it was war. She listed death is one famine and pestilence,
but she named, she didn't name death as one. She said conquest and war specific.
Cause I made a joke. I go, good. You got to keep those separate. Right.
Conquest and war. I'm like, what? No, it's, it's war, famine, pestilence, death.
I did us traditionally. I did think it was wrong, but that's fine. But who knows?
This is why her cartoon's not going to get mad. That's right.
Can't even name the four horsemen you're making the cartoon about. No, the four horsemen are
Ric flair, aren't Anderson. No, no, no. The four horsemen are Mickey Mantle, uh,
Lou Terry, Tully Blanchard.
There's Greg Maddox. Schultz was in there. Uh, Steve Avery. It was Mike Singletary.
Are there four horsemen in every sport? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Well, the, uh, what was it? The,
the, the 90s Braves pitching staff, they, yeah, they were the four horsemen. It was what Greg
Maddox, John Schultz, Steve Avery. And there was one other guy in that, in that line. That's when
the Braves won the wonder division, like 20 years in a row. They've said all the pitching, uh, uh,
conquest, war, famine, and death. Oh, she did do it. Yeah. No, she got them.
Well, she didn't say death. She did. She said war and conquest. She said pestilence. Did she say,
she said pestilence? She said pestilence. She might've said pestilence instead of famine.
Okay. Well, but she didn't say death. She said death.
Okay. Well, the white horse is interpreted sometimes to be conquest or pestilence. So I
guess, okay, I thought there was death road. I'm going off of chat. GPT. So she could be wrong.
Don't ask tap GPT. If it made you feel better, I think Paul was going off of the movie tombstone.
No, there was a pale horse coming and you tell him I'm coming. The pale horse is death. That's
not the white horse. The pale horse is different. The pale horse is different than white. Trust me.
In my Irish household, pale is different than white. It's also known as the bucket horse.
The black horse is famine, right? The red horse is war. I'm going to go ahead and ask him to make a
Penn and Teller jokes out of this, out of the four horsemen. That'll, that'll sing.
Matt is typing into his phone. It was a faster joke to make than to type. So that went really well.
All the, all the scenes went really well. We had a great time doing songs.
Spadoni came through again. Oh yeah. Dropped it like it's hot. Um, which was great. Uh, he's just,
he's just on it. And I think that was lovely. And you know, Spadoni is such a gift, man. That's what
I'm saying. Like he, he's no small part of why we shine a hundred percent. I try to explain Spadoni
to other, to other, uh, performers in town and other, uh, comedic performers in town, especially.
I really, and I mean this is Spadoni will listen to this, I'm sure. And this is just blowing smoke
up his ass now, but, uh, he is so fucking good at that. Get a job, Spadoni. Oh, Tasmanian Spadoni.
If you want to break it up, I can read a Penn and Teller joke about pestilence. Uh, Penn,
this one comes riding out to conquer the world just like Teller here when he discovered TikTok.
Oh boy. Boy. Chat GPT. Well, you know what? Job security. Riding jobs. Officially safe.
Horseman spreads plague. Teller spreads 15 second card tricks that cost us actual gigs.
Teller is a burden, you guys. Oh boy. And, uh,
chat GPT's stake on the Penn and Teller relationship is that Penn is dragging Teller
along. And, uh, also this joke is really the future is I'm pretty sure Teller is still yet
to discover TikTok. So we'll just, uh, but when he does, it's going to be a mess. No, I mean, Spadoni
did, uh, my, my shows for the fringe festival and you know, one of the things we did was, uh, you
know, we, we tried a big swing and then we made an adjustment together, like on a fly over like one
phone conversation. And then it was just flawless, uh, for the final two shows. And, uh, I was like,
it's just great to have them up there. Right. And my wife was like, well, it's just like having them
for the bucket show. Right. That's a special unique thing. Like to just have like someone that's just
the fingers of the glove. Right. Like I just went through those shows effortlessly. He got his laughs
for adding awesome musical references and stuff and absolutely building my tricks to a crescendo.
And I did this without any, we did no major rehearsal, no major notes. She's just, he just
does it. Yeah. It's a, he, he catches things that you do and adds, adds things like the flashback
stuff. Yes. He is perfect at, at finding those moments and doing the, you know, and even though
he did it last night. And, uh, what was interesting about it is that, uh, I think it was, it was Brad,
it was Brad and Jonathan. No, no, I had to tag in because they didn't know it.
Correct. But you were right there and hit it. And then as soon as you did it, then it was perfect.
He's like, of course. Then, and then, you know, yeah, Brad and Jonathan, who don't work, he played
flashback during their scene and they both froze and I tagged out Jonathan and said to Brad and go,
Hey, it's me. You're dead. You're younger. You're younger than you were. Yeah. And we kept going,
but it was, it was a fun, that was a fun moment. But, uh, yeah, I mean, I was driving the car with
Paul last night and I just said, like, honestly, it's like the first time we, we, we did it. We
jammed together in 2008 at the, uh, you know, uh, what was that theater called? Onyx. Onyx.
Use your microphone, please. Onyx. Thank you. Uh, his microphone in his mouth or in his lap.
At the Onyx, uh, through the sex shop into the back. If we, if we, if we took a photo of a packed
theater with Brad and Jonathan performing with us and send it to us in 2008, we would be like,
this is awesome. Right. This is, this is badass. Um, and it was like, who are those old motherfuckers?
Yeah. Like, am I dying my beard? What color is that? Um, and, uh, and it was fun. I mean,
all these guys, I mean, it's just, it's just so fun to play with those guys. Brad's so smart.
It was a gift. So quick. And Jonathan's just so playful and so fast and just always is ready to
push anything off the rails and make a bit out of anything. And it's great. Even backstage,
Brad was being, I think Brad was nervous. Yeah, yeah. But Brad was like, uh, uh, uh,
expressing it through like, like little, little fastidious activities, right? So we had like four
liquid death cans and he's like, well, how are we, now we're going to know which one's which or
whatever. And so I wrote my name Slopley on mine. So he decided he was going to write his very, uh,
uh, precisely on his candy, but little bees, little bees all along the lip. And it was like,
make sure you don't put it too close to where your mouth's going to be. Very strong marker
taste of water. You don't want that. Yeah. And it was totally bidding and it was very funny.
And then Jonathan came in and did the same thing to his water can just picked up his own water
cans. Oh, sure. No problem. And just started writing the same bees all over, just like a half
an inch, not even like a quarter of an inch lower, minor, a little bit lower attention. It was so
funny. They just, it just bits for days and just, oh, it just ready, ready, ready, ready, ready.
It was good. It was good. And again, and huge thanks to Troy for giving us the majestic,
unbelievable. Uh, let's think it's like last time was just everyone doing art for art sake, right?
Jonathan flies in his own dime just to do an improv show. This guy does tours with Wayne Brady,
right? Brad and Colin play thousand, 2000 seat theaters across the nation, right? But they come
out just to do improv because just to do something else, just to do another improv show. And you know,
Paul flew out and I, I guess I had the easiest job here. I'm already doing it. Um, and then Troy,
you know, gives us an amazing deal, uh, to be there. And that's the thing is like, we're all
doing art for art sake. That's right. And that, that, I felt like that, I feel like that doesn't
happen when you're older as much. Right. And, and, and, and Paul, um, and Troy is doing the lion's
share of art for art sake. He's not making a lot of money at that theater and that theater being
open. Uh, but Troy just wants, this is what happens. Troy was such a good deal. I simply go,
what dates open, right? Like what, how can we not interrupt any flow of your actual money making
endeavors in that theater? Uh, and, uh, and he just gives me a date and, and that's like a really
cool agreement to have, uh, with him. And, uh, so when he said July 5th, I was like a Saturday night,
what, what, what, what? Uh, and he said, yeah, it's July 4th weekend. I go, oh, right. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm dumb. So I was really worried that we were not going to, people are not going to come out,
but it was a great, great house. There were at, uh, so it was an 80 o'clock show at about, uh,
seven right about seven o'clock. I had to walk outside, uh, just to, just to go to the car for
something, maybe put something in the car or whatever it was. And, uh, there was just a guy
outside at 7:00 PM. It was like, Hey, you guys open in the house? I said, no, no, no, the shows,
the shows not until eight. Cause I don't know. I know. I just wanted to make sure to, to get here
and have a good seat. Oh, great. Yeah. The house will open about half an hour. Um, yeah, no problem.
And then he goes, great. Yeah. Thank you so much. I was just going to finish cooking these eggs on
the sidewalk. No problem. Yeah. So he walked off and it ended, but sure enough, like he was back
15, 20 minutes later and he was first in line at the door and he was, he's ready to come in.
I was like, man, as soon as I walked up there, getting ready to open the house, there was a line
down the sidewalk. All right, this is, this is going to be good. This is going to be a good night.
Paul was up and down off of the ground. Paul was rolling around. Paul, Paul was so, uh,
physically I am ambulatory once more in the show. It is revolutionary. Well, and, and I'm, you know,
I credit, I credit myself. No, I credit my fantastic doctor for fixing my hip, but I also
credit myself for continuing to press forward with a somewhat physically demanding day job.
Even though it's part time, I am up and down, stocking shelves on the ground, back and forth,
lifting heavy boxes, dah, dah, dah, dah. And it has really helped keep me cooking. I am, I, and,
and that's why I'm going to send my kids to work in a factory. It's a good idea. Good. Yeah. But
yeah, I'm, I'm as soon as they turn 12 and a half, it's really just turning a corner for me now.
Like honestly, I've just getting back into teaching, just getting back into just being able to drive
around and feel like, okay, I can get out here and walk. Like even just at the airport, I park in the
far off space to try and save a couple of bucks for the company because it's not that much further.
But when I was walking with that fucking hip, right, it was like going through the desert. I
was like, and just walking the other day, heading back in, I was like, man. That's why I like Paul
as a business partner when he has a bum hip, he's still parking at the back. I do saving that six
dollars. I do it. I do it for the company. Company man. Company man. Company man through through.
But it was- Just to be clear, I'm not as good as a company man. That's all right. No, no, no.
I only park in the very front spot. Okay. Valet. How much is it? I don't care. I don't care. But
of the three of us, I probably need the steps more anyway, so it's fine.
SJ does ask every night, she'll be like, is your company paying for this? Yes. Why don't you just
spend this? It's my company. It's not someone else's company paying for it.
It's not a different- It's still our money. Yeah. We have 900 amazing bosses out there.
They don't want us getting the valet service at the airport. No.
Whose money do you think I'm spending? Exactly. Exactly. The three of us went out to brunch
yesterday. So good. We came back- Makers and fixtures? Makers and finders. Makers and finders.
Yeah, yeah. I thought it was fixtures, but it's fine. Either way, the name makes no sense,
who cares? But neither one of those words mean empanadas, and that's what it's known for.
When I first saw Makers, I'm like, that's like a poop analogy. That's what people say to their
kids. Does baby need to make? Oh, you haven't heard make? Oh, I don't like that. I've never
done it though. I've never done it, but I've heard of it. But it's gross, right? Yeah. That's when I
heard Makers and finders. I'm like, oh no. I find- Then you got to find- Oh, if it's a sinker. I find-
Makers and sinkers? Because if you make and then it sinks- You can make a sinker. Then you got to
find it. You don't want it to sink. Right. If you're healthy, it's floating. Makers and floaters is
what you want. That's what you want. That's it. Our health expert, Paul Mattingly talks about
the proper poops. I just remember- This guy walks more than all of us from his parking space at the
airport. It's true. And shits more than all of you combined. I'm just up there dropping off the car
at valet and here comes Mattingly. Just a sweaty mess in the back of the parking lot. I'm not a
sweaty mess. That's the other thing too is like, I have some endurance again. I have some stamina.
I wasn't winded during the show at all. I was like, this is great. I can do this show. I made a point
of during the week, the two or three weeks before the show, I made a point of doing a lot of singing
in the car because I hadn't been using my voice. So just singing a lot just to get my voice up.
Crap. Keep that mic in front of your face. No, I'm what they call a performer. Yes, that's right.
Who calls you that? Anne. She says, what sort of performative bullshit is this? And I say,
thank you. I thought I was eating pussy. And she's like, well, why don't you tell your mouth?
Sideways like a typewriter. God damn it. Always with the sideways, just running a bit into the
ground. I'll tell you who else was not impressed by Paul's cuddlingus. And that is the following
sponsor. Slappy tears. That's right. Drive through funeral services. Say that final goodbye to your
loved one from the comfort of your car. One, uh, with one slow speed slap on their urn or casket
before going on with the rest of your day. That's from little Sally scoop in 2024, slappy tears,
drive through funeral services. Hey, everybody. It's, uh, it's the Elvis, uh, it's Elvis from the,
we know where you're from. It was, it's okay. Hey, yeah. Well, that's right. Yeah. That's where
to below depending on which there's only one of you, right? Well, no, there were two of me.
Did you know I was a twin? That's true. That's true. My baby, my baby brother died. My baby
brother died before I was born before you were born. He died. He died. Born. He born died. Yeah.
Anyway. So I've been prepping for this my whole life. Essentially I was prepping for this before
my life even started. Oftentimes we have to say goodbye to our loved ones, but we don't know how.
So Elvis here has made it easy. I made it real easy for you. I got to get in your pink Cadillac
and drive, drive right on by and give it all there in a slap. Just come on by and give that
earn a slap. Say goodbye baby brother who died in the womb with me, who I hung out with dead in the
womb. That was something. Boy, not much of a conversation with my baby brother. He's dead.
Yeah. He was stillborn. Yeah. She's not going to talk. Yeah. That was the funny thing of my mom.
Mama said, that was the funny thing. Mama said, mama said your brother was stillborn. I said,
well, yeah, he came out right. And she says, yeah, but that means he's dead. I said, oh,
I thought you meant he was dead, but then he was stillborn. She's no, he was stillborn. Me's dead.
That's a real clever turn of phrase of us. Good work. Good work talking to your mom with that.
Thank you very much. I came over that one on a fly. Me and mama, me and mama were having a little
conversation about, you know, it's always fun to hang out with your mama and joke about your dead
baby brother. That's what you do. Yeah. Well, speaking of gallows humor, come on down to my
funeral home. Elvis's slappy, slappy goodbyes, slappy goodbyes for your dead baby brother or
whoever else might be dead. And you can slap them and just go, you don't have to stay and listen to
some bullshit about the Lord or whatever. Just go home, go home, go home. Thank you very much.
Enter. Hey, scoops to check out. Boy, I'm glad Paul was doing that vocalizing in his car to warm up
for that. Yeah. I'm as they say, performative Paul would have. Oh, look at that. Look at that
circle on that circle. God damn. That's, that's the finest looking titty I ever saw.
Hey, uh, Hey Priscilla, you might get a little bit of work done. So you
booze look more like circles and circles. Okay. Okay. Great. You don't like these pepperonis?
No. Oh, well, yeah. You know what? I'm going to put a little fried manner sandwich on him,
on him nipples, fried manner nipples. I just don't want to see the translation in the screen grab.
Uh, yeah, we've not talked about this. Okay. If the magic dragon. Oh yes. This
SJ and the ruckus winners, winners of best comedian and best bands. Yep. That's right.
From the Las Vegas weekly. Uh, and, uh, you know, uh, a lot of that was that we, we, we,
we launched a campaign, launched a campaign and our scoops. We talked about it on this very show.
And, and, and they got our friends, yes. Put them over the top. That's what scoops do. That's right.
Our communities, they come through, um, and change the subject for a moment. Congratulations
to city cast of Las Vegas for winning best podcast in Los Vegas. Congratulations. To be fair,
we have had David Jan Fiegler on the show. How is that fair? How does that help the argument
of fairness? We know the winners. Yes. We are, we are, we've been on their show. Right. We helped
them win. We are winner adjacent, but I will also say in this, it doesn't feel like winter adjacent
Paul. They're in Las Vegas. It's Las Vegas awards. Of course we're adjacent to them. We're also in
Las Vegas. In this situation, I feel okay because David Jan Fiegler that makes one of us is the one
who helped Jimmy slow Nina out. Yes. His pinch David figure is a, is a, is a, is an attorney,
legit fucking hero. Yes. He is representing all the people who've been wrongfully arrested
during protests. Right. He's been helping people get out of jail. Uh, he, he's a, he's a better
person than us, but is he better podcaster than us? We're not disagreeing that he's a better person
than that. Right. It's just, is he a better podcast? Right. And maybe the answer is also yes,
it might be still, does he need this award more than us? Yes. But even still,
I'm okay with it. Well, that's good. I'll get there. Okay. Paul's okay with it. Yeah. And you
know what? I'm not planning on stopping this. So no, I am now that we have one best podcast
I'm out. We did win back in 2016. Exactly. We peaked and I'm done. And that was, that was,
that wasn't just best podcast Las Vegas. That was just best podcast. Yeah. Period. Yeah. That's the
problem. The category is too narrow. That's what it is. That's the problem. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. You guys consider yourselves a Vegas podcast. I consider you universal. Yeah. That's right. They
found out Paul is in Pittsburgh, disqualified us. That's right. I mean, David's podcast is about
Las Vegas. It is a Las Vegas podcast award. Like his show is about Las Vegas. Our show is just
happens to be in Las Vegas. Uh, so it's just another way that he's better than us. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, David has a law degree, you know, like a real sub this show, we don't have to keep
listing ways that he's better than us. We just, I just don't have anything. He can hang his diplomas
and degrees on the wall. I can't, I need awards. Right. I need awards to hang on the wall because
I don't have any other things I've ever accomplished. Matt, Matt, don't say that.
We got some pictures. Yeah, we have pictures. Put some pictures up from last night to be like,
look, I performed with some great players. Actually, one of the guys we got up was a
photographer. I will shout out his Instagram because he, he took a lot of great photos,
but let me find him. Uh, I leaned up because I had to put a microphone stand out, but Paul
thought I was trying to show him my phone. Uh, yes. Uh, third, third I viz, V I Z third, I viz.
Yeah. It took a lot of great photos of us. Yeah. Uh, we'll put them up on our socials as well.
And he does a lot of, uh, a lot of comedians in town. Yes. Yes. Pictures of comedy shows.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was really fun hanging out with me. Me hung out for a bit last night.
Yeah. I got him a poker chip. I brought poker chips to hand out to people. Good. I know everyone
I tried to give a chip to already had one. So weird. I was watching Matt would go around and
be like, hi, can I give you a poker chip? They'd be like, Paul gave me one. Yeah. Sometimes that
does happen, but that didn't happen last night. Okay. All right. All right. But there are plenty
of times I've beaten you guys at a punch on a poker chip thing. Yeah. Because you have, that's
right. There is that you are chip for. Well, I'm trying to promote this goddamn podcast. Get some
more ears on this shit. I want the award to do that. We're out here spinning gold. I'm going to say
it's been an Elvis gold. Uh, you got some more chips. Yeah. You still like in general or on me,
you had a discovery of some, well here. Oh yeah. Yeah. They're chips. I need to grab some. You were
doing some construction in the wall. You found some old chips from like the fifties and someone
task of a Monte auto chips. That's right. I thought I had buried these, I thought I had buried these
forever and they are rediscovered. Do you think we've got some red ones now? Yeah. There's some
red ones out there. Sweet. Yeah. I think we've got red and black. I love it. I think those are two
general colors that we have. Yep. Speaking of SJ and the ruckus. Oh shit. Here comes SJ. Everybody
give it up. Winner of best of Las Vegas. Good morning. It's like back in the day when SJ would
just pop in. That's right. Roll out of bed. Go see what the boys are doing. Pretty much when we had
now she has my mic. I know. Yeah. SJ just walked in, took Matt's microphone and then walked away
from that. It's okay. Well you did hand it to me. Yeah, but I didn't know where you were going. We
can share. Yeah. There you go. There we go. John, give SJ the mic. There you go. Yeah, yeah. We can
share. There you go. What's going on y'all? Winner. We're looking at a winner right now. We were just
talking about you winning the best of Las Vegas. No. And how we didn't. Yeah. A winner is a winner.
SJ's. I got to tell you guys. SJ's pity tone just made Paul spit. I got to tell you,
it really changed our relationship in the house. Our relationship in this house has not been the
same. SJ just patted his podcast on the shoulder and said, we're really good friends. You're like
a brother to me podcast. He told me, he's like, Hey there, um, Pip was here and you know, he wants
to win this thing. And, but on the same page is like you best band and, um, uh, best podcast. So
we were like, Oh, this would be cool. Like, let's just do all of it. Yeah. Yeah. So we almost did
two out of three. Amen. We won the, uh, like a derby in the preakness, but failed at the bell.
There we go. We also didn't win a best patio. Yeah. That's okay. Also, you might have though,
because I don't think I got like, they found me through Facebook. You might have one,
but Jacob's whiskey pit doesn't have a Facebook page or a phone number to call real. We didn't
follow through on the bit. That's what we're saying. We should've made a Facebook page or you
should've made an actual Jacob's whiskey. You might, you might've won. You just didn't know.
We don't know. We don't know. You'll never know. Uh, but, uh, uh, uh, so what's it like? What's it
like being a winner? What's it feel like to win in life? We want to know. You already know you've
won stuff before. I think we've won. I think we have won the weekly. I think we've won. I think
we've won the award we're talking about before 2017. Yeah. The year after we won the first one.
Cause that was, uh, Corey helped us out with that one. That's right. Getting us, uh, yeah.
Cause like we went to the event, uh, for that actually went to the event this year. Yeah. It
was up at the Mandalay Bay at the time. Oh yeah. It was at, uh, uh, founders. Uh, what's that place
called? Founders room. The post party. That's it. Yeah. The post party was cool. Founders room is
the room at Brian brushwood's place where all the founders hang out. That's where I went. Yeah.
I try one. That's right. I went near the break studio. It is. Okay. You guys got it. You know
what it's like. Uh, it was, uh, the resorts world this year. Ah, so yeah, it was really cool.
Honestly though, seriously, it was like super, I, I forgot about it. Jacob told me about it and I
got this call from this guy and he's like from the weekly. Yeah. Yeah. From the weekly. And he's so
excited. He's so excited to tell me. And I'm like, what are you talking about?
Give me a lawyer. I know. Right. It was really great. Um, but yeah, we went to the,
the band was like, what we won. Yeah. They like, I was like, yeah guys, like this happened and
everyone's just like freaking out. Right. So a couple of them went to the party with me,
but it was just like, I don't know when the band it's, it's great because it all ties in so nicely
because the band knows the scoops because the band plays in front of the scoops at scoop fest. Yeah.
So like they were excited not only to win the award, but they were excited that the scoops had,
uh, had banded together to support them and everything. Like, so they're the guys, especially
I think we're just gin genuinely touched by the whole thing. Yeah. So we're pretty pumped. Yeah.
So thanks guys. I think the, the, the, the awkwardness of feeling is that you're not
leaning in and I think you guys should walk around like we are the best. We are the best.
Yeah. So we've been posting like obnoxiously about it and like you, you got, I don't know,
you guys probably don't have it, but like in the Vegas, like entertainer world, like everyone's
already throwing shade at us. Like good. They're like someone posted, Oh, isn't it cute when like
Vegas people just give each other awards? Like right after we were like going off about this
and people were like, yeah, I know it's so stupid. I'm like, you're not getting hired again. You're
not getting hired. These are people who like sub for us. These are musicians. What are you doing?
I know that's really dumb. That's just shoot yourself really stupid. I know. I know you guys
probably didn't run into that, but we run into that stuff all the time. We only have, we only have nice
Saras and Ross and Brenna Folger were like, fuck those guys.
We, uh, we really, we, you know, the scoop community is the outlier community of the internet,
which is wonderful. We are, we are insulated from all that, that crazy shit, but also personally,
and I think you as well, I think all of us ascribe to this, um, I am okay with applauding
being happy for people and giving them their flowers when they are rising. Right. Even if
I'm not doing so great. I mean, because it's, maybe it's just not my time right now. It comes
around. But if you don't about not my time or whatever, don't be an asshole. Right. But,
but if you can't celebrate other people's victories, what do you expect is going to happen when you
win? Exactly. You know what I mean? Like you gotta be, well, they're not going to win because they
just talk themselves out of that. But high tide raises all boats, man. Right. That's an improv
thing too, though. I mean, like we, we literally have each other's backs because if you, because
that's all you got out there on the stage. And if you're not just ready to be like that motherfucker
just nailed it. No, I have some, I also have some hack bits I can go to any moment. Oh yeah, you know,
you do. I keep some stuff in the back pocket. Yeah. Well rehearsed, clever bits. Oh, you have
a clever ones too. I didn't bust them out. So saving for a rainy day, but you got all those away.
You gotta be happy for other people's successes. Yeah. It's also business. Unless it's a business,
unless it's like, unless it's like a billionaire won something, then you're like, well, fuck you.
Even then it's just people giving each other awards, but it's always going to be like people
in the same industry giving each other awards. That's what awards are. Whereas the Oscars are
very much more globally merit based. They're very external. Right. Well, even if you're not
super happy for them, don't come out and talk shit. It's like, just let it be. That's so dumb.
Whatever. Like we're like, obviously, you know, just moving on, but I just thought it was funny,
like throwing shade like that, but wow, come on guys. Yeah. Well, basically like the, the,
the whatever's darkest, uh, not darkest, the most like, um, detached or whatever.
What's the emotion for like, not wanting to give a shit about nonchalant. No,
the most nonchalant you should be is go, oh, well they're going to get more work. Like that
should be the most like, Oh, good for you. Good for them. More work. I actually be the, like the
most, the limit of whatever you'd be like, how dare they reward locals stuff for doing a working
local band. Want an award. Fuck off. Yeah. I scroll through those awards and I go like, oh great.
These people won. Yeah. And that's the end that I, that's, that's the last that I think about.
Exactly. And by the way, like in terms of like, for you guys, like it actually does, like if you,
if you put a best of Vegas sign up, uh, out before on the, on the casino, before they go into the
lounge, they're going in, they're going to be a little more curious about like, who are these guys
and maybe give you a little more credit. It's so interesting. Like we're yeah, exactly for that
reason. So anyways, um, I know it was like funny for you guys, but thanks. Oh, we're glad with no,
it's it, but it's, you know, it gives us a good band at scoop fest guy. Damn it. That's the best
band in town. Hey, I know. So that's the other thing too is, um, we actually got, um, asked to
go to Loughlin that weekend for like, it's a big concert weekend out there. And I was talking to
the boys and I was like, guys, we gotta play scoop fest now figure out a way to handle it.
If you had to go to the guys, she, the guys, the guys decided to do scoop fest. They were like,
we gotta do scoop. That's a much more fun gig than, uh, than anything else. We actually didn't want
you to lose out, uh, uh, uh, on the scoop fest. And so we, we went on the Loughlin message board
and said, I guess I'll let anyone play Loughlin now. Uh, see if we can just get them to pull the
offer. Oh, look at Loughlin people giving each other awards. Loughlin all the way to the bank.
Yeah. Did you guys see speaking of Loughlin, uh, did you guys see the plane emergency landing out
there? So Loughlin, Nevada is right on the border, uh, with, uh, Arizona. It's right there on the
Colorado river. It's beautiful, beautiful town out there, uh, right there by the Arizona border,
uh, right on the other side of the river. This is Jacob. All of us who's watched Viva Loughlin
with Hugh Jackman when I was on TV. So they know and so they don't need to explain Loughlin.
So they know all about bullhead city over there on the other side of the river. So bullhead city is
like Loughlin, just a small Arizona city right there on the, on their side. It's the Nevada
border. An American airlines flight. The other, uh, the other day earlier this week is crazy as
wind. It was all the crazy storms, crazy wind, an American airlines flight, you know, like a, uh,
seven 37 size plane, whatever type of plane it was had to land at the bullhead city airport
in Arizona, which is just a landing strip. There is no airport. There is no airport staff.
There's nothing. So a plane full of passengers had to land in bullhead city, Arizona, uh, to,
to divert there. There was, there are no other planes for them to get onto the crew on their
plane timed out. So they weren't able legally to fly anymore. Yeah. And so a plane full of people,
come from away style. Basically it was, it was the come from away in Arizona.
What's interesting is that Loughlin is actually, and this is a true, uh, thing. They're, they're,
they're lobbying to get, uh, support from the state because basically we're going to be building a new
terminal. Cause our airport traffic is getting crazy and they want to be an overflow terminal.
Okay. And so they want the resources to quickly shuttle people from there. Oh, it'd be great.
Oh, that'd be amazing. I mean, if you do that, you can build out Loughlin. You can make it a
suburb. Yeah. It just, all you gotta do is put a billion dollars into a, uh, uh, high street rail.
Well, I guess, uh, maybe in 20 to 50, maybe, maybe, maybe, um, but, uh, best in Loughlin now.
But so, but I bet like, but, but basically like that helps them make their case. Right. See,
see, we're right here. We're right here. We're the closest airport. Yeah. And it is like an hour
drive. I mean, it's not, it's not very far out of Vegas. No, but that's, but, but if it had high
speed train, if you get there in 20 minutes, exquisite Paul, no one is not, no one said high
speed rail. You're the only one who said high speed rail. You're right. It is much more pleasurable
to just drive to Loughlin. That's the only option on the table, Paul. Yeah. Gorgeous drive though.
You're the only one who said there's going to be a high speed rail, but you're going to do
no other. I didn't say it. I'm demanding it. I'm demanding it. Yeah. And then you just shat on it.
Drive that fucking drive. Eat shit. Cars. I don't want to do that. No, it's a beautiful drive where
you see nothing garbage. And then once you get there, you're in Loughlin. So that's the upside.
Oh yeah. This is where we're launching the SJ and the ruckus party bus shuttle from Loughlin to Vegas,
45 minute concerts. See, once you get a few things, yeah. Once you get a few things out there,
yeah, then you can do it. Yeah. Lawless Loughlin, all law. It is, it is the Loughlin's for scofflaws
that you can have them for free Loughlin. Loughlin's for scofflaws. Give them time to
get out of bed. Just like Virginia's for lovers. Loughlin's for scofflaws. And are there whores out
there? Is that the thing? Is that the other direction? I mean, sure. I'm pretty sure whores
are in every direction. Uh, but uh, I mean, you know what I mean? You want me to find your whore
in Loughlin? Legal whore. I know. No, I'm not thinking about, I'm thinking about Loughlin. Paul's
always thinking about, I'm trying to get Loughlin on the perump man wagon here. I don't know if
Loughlin has legal prostitution or not. See, and there should be because just like everything
technology based porn goes first. Where porn goes, technology goes. We are fucking so out of pocket.
No, I don't know what he's doing anymore. I'm just so glad that he warmed up his singing voice. We
want to train. The only way you can get a good train is if you run high speed rail on some horse.
You know where they show like the, the, the public access meetings and the one guy gets up and talks
and everyone's like, what is he talking about? That's this Paul's like the second guy at the
Loughlin. I'm just 10 years ahead. I'm just 10 years ahead. You're light years ahead buddy. Okay.
But honestly, that's where technology is always guided by pornography. That is the truth from the
printing press to the Tijuana Bible to the speed train between Loughlin and Vegas is an overflow
airport. Poor leads the way. Absolutely. Absolutely. As always. And in conclusion,
in conclusion, split some rails on these horse and get this train built governor town meeting
adjourned meeting adjourned, adjourned. Hey, sharks, did you know the sex industry is a,
if you can, if you go to your industry, you build a whore train, people will come
get on the whole train. You can ride train. The whole train to Loughlin would be sold out every
day. And I'll fuck you at the station. I can't believe you're putting SJs new band name on blast.
Listen, I think that sounds fun. Just a party train full of loose, loose men and ladies.
I'm actually not here. I'm just me. I'm watching season two of severance, but I just like the
atmosphere. You're one nerdy guy on his laptop while there's just balls swinging bullet train
to Loughlin. That's what it would be anyway. Just a bunch of loose people. It would be people who
like the Colorado river. But the other thing is, man, that camp, it would make a bunch of these
people feel so like, because it ended up being, if it's a good high speed rail, 25 minutes tops,
Oh yeah. Plenty of time to clean up done. Don't have to be overly performative with your lover.
It's the rushing of cleaning. That's really what's been holding back the industry here in Vegas.
Don't rush me, but you've only got 25 minutes. So you better just get to the business,
do your business and clean up. Grab your copy of powers, get on that train and go.
Well, I hope everyone who has a governance over Loughlin's listening, I hope the Arizona
and Nevada governor have taken notice. They know what, you know, and you know,
isn't the founder of Loughlin, his name is like Ted Loughlin, right? Don Loughlin.
Have you even been on the cruise that tells you all this stuff? I've been on it twice today.
It does seem like a fun town. I've never split any horse there, but it's been, it's been fun.
Loughlin is for scoff laws. I mean, I'm going to tell you right now, if next year we had scoop
fest in Loughlin, it would be awesome. I'm on board. It would be on board the whole train to
Loughlin. I'll fuck you. We already have another location. We do. We do think it's maybe premature,
but I think we're pretty confident. I do. Yeah. This is our last year at the Orleans. I think.
I think so. Yeah. Don't tell him that yet. Okay. Don't let the Orleans know yet. They don't listen.
Oh, you think I actually, they probably really grateful. We are happy with the Orleans. We love
the Orleans. Whoever's listening for the liens is working somewhere else in two months.
It's true. There is turnover there. The one tech guy, the one tech guy. We've had the same guy.
He's got it easy over there. Yeah. He's great. That's hard to replace. That's like probably
being like, like, you know, where the, the rats chew the wires. Oh yeah. Right. Yeah. Yeah. When
like the lights turn off, he's like the rat got to the wire again. Hold on. Exactly. Well, we're
coming to the end here and I just want to just say that let's go around the room and let's all just
say things that we could teach some, we could teach the people of Laughlin. Let's go. Laughlin
lessons is what we'll end on lessons. All right. Uh, take a fucking bath, you stinky cheese assholes,
learn to wash your ass. You Turkey track underwear motherfuckers looking like you fucking fast and
furious in your drawers, fix it up. Don't just be fucking Paul Walker and write down your ass
crack all day long with your burnout, peel, peel poopoos fucking wash that crack. You dirty Laughlin
bitches. If you want a high speed fuck rail, wash your ass and balls. Uh, Paul took mine. So
sorry, I didn't listen for all of it. Did he say the thing about wash your ass?
Okay. I'm good. Yeah. Okay. Thanks for this. Everybody. I want to thank Ben's left great in
this podcast. If, uh, you want to support this podcast, why wouldn't you? People of Laughlin.
Make episodes like this one. There's a few clean people in Laughlin. Uh, we could use your support
now. Uh, we're trying to, uh, save it for a new studio, uh, moving to a new studio. Uh, we can use
your help right now. So, uh, go over to preaching fun.com and support it today.
We know why they have to be waterproof. We know I'm spelling out between the Laughlin dirty asses
and all the spilled jizz. Wash them trains.
That's farts in a bag dot biz. If you want to support the hay scoops railroad that's going out
to Laughlin. Head over to farts in a bag dot biz and preaching fun.com there for as little as two
dollars. You can be part of the railway to Laughlin experience. We're going to raise,
we're going to raise the bonus episode amounts to two billion. And if we hit it.
So many bonus episodes and a train to Laughlin. And just mouthfuls of boxcar wheelies. You're
just going to be choking on, on hobo rail riding wiener all day. I don't wash my ass or balls.
I've been fucking on the railroad. All these Laughlin whores with dirty seats and sweaty
beats. We're heading out to Laughlin. All right. Can you smell that Laughlin train?
It's coming down the track. You can smell that dirty underwear. There ain't no coming back.
All right. Thanks for this everybody. We love you and we'll see you soon.
You filthy Laughlin bitches.
There ain't no sensitivity when it's business and it's business.
Fucking whores in Laughlin. That's all I ever do.
It's fun down there. Y'all don't even know. I bet. I was trying to get in there. I don't know if
we're still on there. I don't know why I pulled my mic forward, but we're still there. I was trying
to get, I was trying to see if I could do magic shows out there. I love it out there. I think it's
so cool. Is your underwear stinky enough to get in? That's what they asked right away. Yeah. They
hand them over. And the answer so far is no. You'll get there. I guess the Febreze method works.
Oh, covering it is oftentimes just worse. See ya. That's the joke I made. That's what I, and I
- I followed up.
- Follow up.