Oh hello there! I didn't see you there but I am so glad you're here because I'd like to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers! These are the folks that head over to PreachingFun.com.
That is where they go to sign up to be Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Bearded Scoop 3, Blue Line Scoop, Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Christine Elsestor, Christy Salidas, and Darren Cunningham.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com, go there, sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
And now, a show!
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
Hey Scoops.com, right there there is Scoopfest Swag!
Over there at HeyScoops.com from this last Scoop Profession.
The beds, you can get the roads, you can get the t-shirts! HeyScoops.com, Scoopfest Swag!
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting at C, it's Matt Donnelly!
Sitting at Pittsburgh, it's Paul Mattingly!
Sitting at Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy!
We're PreachingFun!
Hey guys!
Hey, by the time you hear this, tomorrow night, Friday night, I'm playing Sparta, New Jersey, two shows, Sparta Avenue Stage.
7pm is sold out, but my 9 o'clock is not.
So if you can be anywhere near Sparta, New Jersey, or know anyone near Sparta, New Jersey, tell them to come on out for a really fun show at 9 o'clock in Sparta, it'll be awesome.
Where do they get tickets?
If you look up Sparta Avenue Stage, you'll find it there, or it's in the link of my MyNoodlerBio on Instagram, you can find the link there.
Oh, and just to confirm, if they can't come, but they still want to buy tickets, they can do that too, right?
Yes, if you love the performance art of buying tickets and not showing up, go for it.
Also, Paul and I, our shows are starting to sell pretty well here, but we're--
Yeah, fuck yeah! Let's go!
We'll open Tierney's Tavern, a lot of scoops are coming out.
I know, which is fantastic!
It's going to be another good scoop gathering October 23rd, that's for sale on our website, that's at heyscoops.com/comedynight.
Tickets are 20 bucks.
Yeah, and we've definitely moved a few tickets for that, that is going to be a nice little scoop event.
It's a steal, get yourselves out there if you're in that tri-state area, make the magic happen, you won't regret it.
Tierney's in and of itself is an experience.
That's true.
Are we going to be up in the upstairs again?
Yeah, we're going to be up in the upstairs.
Oh my fucking God, that spot is just--
Get you a can smashed burger!
It's going to be good, good times, baby.
In the old days, when our improv group was in the Twilight phase of our improv group, we kind of would just throw shows together up at Tierney's and we would just do sets.
We would just do a set and stop, have some drinks, hang out, then go like, "Ah, let's do another set," and we would kind of get up.
I'm kind of envisioning something as fun and kind of casual as that.
Oh my God, I can't wait, dude.
Kurt's coming by.
We're just going to get him to do some free-for-long form?
Yeah, Dion's coming by, do some stand-up sets, I'll do a couple of magic tricks.
Matt, this is a bad idea.
This is a bad idea, Matt, because after you sit down for a couple of minutes, Paul's going to be like, "They've seen funny stuff now, we don't need to get back up again."
What are you talking about?
You're going to do a couple of sets and then you're going to sit down and start talking to people and you're going to be like, "We don't need to do any more sets, we're good."
Are you crazy?
No, man. You don't know. No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know if you see the reaction from your other business partner, but we both know.
What are you talking about?
No, man, we've been doing double bucket shows for the last few Scoop Fests.
It's been great.
Who knows what it's all about?
Yeah.
I know, I know. I'm not going to ... It's going to be so good.
If we go late enough, we might get a cameo from a New Jersey celebrity. We'll see.
Fantastic.
I'm not going to put the name out there, but ...
Bruce.
I'm not kidding. I am down to improvise until the wee hours with new players and players that I know are good. That's going to be super, super fun. I'm hungry for that shit.
Yeah.
Hungry for that shit, yeah.
And can smash burgers.
Just starting teaching this week. The 20th will be my first class, officially, outside of my free classes that I've been doing, which were great.
They've really been serving the job of getting my improv muscle back in shape, and especially my teaching stuff.
Very good.
Yeah. Yeah, very excited.
Well, in two nights, yeah, I got my improv jam reunion at the Smod Castle.
Oh, yeah.
Kevin Smith is also doing an event that night where he's going to do something with mall rats, so I might run into my old buddy, Kev.
Yeah.
I might be able to ...
Hey, man.
Get you a selfie.
Get me pleasantries and ...
Yes. Toss him a chip, baby.
A friend of mine wrote me, he said, "He's coming." And he goes, "Wait, can I get a picture with Kevin Smith?" And I said, "I mean, I can't help you with that, but yes."
As far as I'm concerned, you can.
You know, I don't know. I think, honestly ...
Either Kevin Smith doesn't remember who I am, which is very likely.
Yeah.
Right.
Or if he does, he seems like he'd be like, "Hey, let's get a photo." It's not going to be ...
I don't know, man. I don't know.
He has become incredibly sentimental and sort of water under the bridge about a lot of stuff, especially after the big heart attack event.
Yeah. Right.
And that's only been like five years.
All right.
I think you might ...
There's no reason to light this candle of hope for me, Paul, but let's go for it.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is the role I play. I sit down and say I've done enough, and I tell people ...
To go and make up with their mortal enemies.
I've done enough.
I've already been funny today. I don't need to be funny anymore.
I mean, there comes a certain point of diminishing returns, Jacob.
Don't I know it.
I'm getting some good guesses on who the New Jersey celebrity is.
Southside Johnny.
Chris Christie.
Oh, Chris Christie.
Oh, man.
I feel like we could get Southside Johnny.
I feel like we could get Chris Christie.
I should maybe just make some calls right now, just to put a cap on it.
God damn.
I think the Asbury Jukes might just be the house band.
We were going to be there for dinner anyway, so why not?
Thanks.
I guess we could tack on a 15-minute chip.
Southside Johnny is slowly becoming bit worthy.
I have more scoops, like right me, be like, "Wait, who is the guy that you guys always talk about?"
And I have to always be like Southside Johnny.
I keep forgetting the name.
I have been trying to get Southside Johnny to be a bit on this podcast for years.
It is finally reaching critical mass, where it would be a bit to get him to show up somewhere as a thing.
Yes, for sure.
Did we say this on air or no?
But there was someone I was trying to get for the variety show that was going to make the crowd go wild that I couldn't get.
Oh, we did not say this on air.
That is, we took a swing for Scoop Fest, and we weren't able to hit it.
I could not get in touch with Monroe.
I was trying so badly to get Monroe, the retired garbage truck driver, to come sing a song.
Come sing a song? You couldn't get him, huh?
I was trying very hard to get Monroe to Scoop Fest.
You were.
I didn't know anything.
Matt really worked to try to get Monroe.
I just could not find him.
I was like, "I don't know how I'm going to dance on this thin ice that we're going to dance on to get him in and out of Scoop Fest without him knowing.
The joke is that he fucks my wife."
He was going to try.
I mean, you keep playing with that kindling, you're going to get a fire.
It's up to you.
Monroe is either going to show up and sing it in the villa or fuck Matt's wife.
That's what I mean, or both, buddy.
Or both.
Maybe. That's true.
It can never happen, Paul.
I'm always home.
What's that in the background?
Oh, you're out of both.
Kate, I've been away since the very end of Scoop Fest.
I've been away.
Yeah.
There are other semen you need to be worried about, my friend.
Good gravy.
Now, that's going to be exciting as hell.
This week, I'm still just rolling from my eye emergency bullshit, which I think is going to just turn out to be much ado about nothing, tempest in a teapot type shit, I hope.
I get an x-ray next week to see what's happening.
And then I fly away, wee, New Jersey, the next day.
So, but, you know, never stops.
You guys know, everybody's busy, busy, busy.
And between all my other little shit that I'm doing, we're getting our house finally painted and has been desperate to get the house painted for years.
Whoa.
And yeah, it's a big thing.
It's a big change.
So our house was created in the '80s, and it very much is that...
I like that Paul's house was created.
Other houses were built, but Paul's house created.
This was created in the '80s.
I like it.
And it's very much the same color as the Ford Tempo I used to drive back in the '80s.
And it is...
I picture every Ford Tempo as being a shade of brown.
It is two-tone brown.
Good.
This is where it's beginning.
And here's where we're going.
And it's already...
This is why you want to be on Zoom and on Twitch right here.
That's right.
Because you get to see pictures of Paul's house getting painted.
Yes.
It's already happening.
Watch pictures of paint dry.
Has anything been more interesting than that?
Nothing could be more exciting.
But it's turning out...
iPhone videos of paint dry.
It's turning out beautiful, honestly.
It's really going to be gorgeous.
And you can see how much brighter interior it already is.
You know, just with one little application.
Oh, that is nice.
It really is nice.
And we're going to get white trim, and the brick's going to get worked on.
And what do you call that?
They're going to lime wash the brick so it's kind of light and all kinds of things like that.
So it's going to be really nice.
Oh, is that how they do the light, the scrape brick look?
That is oftentimes what is utilized, the lime wash.
Yes.
And so we are hoping that that all continues to move forward.
We've got all the paint and everything.
But the guy yesterday, as he's leaving, they had to leave early to go work on another job.
And I was like, okay.
And then he says, oh, I'll be back at 9 tomorrow in the morning.
So Ann and I both get up.
I get up early on my off day instead of sleeping my little butt away all day like I wanted to do.
I get up and make sure everything's ready to go.
Get the garage door open.
Get the paint cans set up and everything.
Let the snakes in.
And nothing, nobody, nothing.
Wow.
Nobody showed the whole day.
Finally, at right about one o'clock, the project coordinator called me up and was like, hey, yeah, nobody showed up today because blankety blank blank.
And I'm like, OK, well, all right, great.
So but at least they touch base.
This is far more communication than any other contractor in this Berg.
But that's true.
Just always the way it is.
But it's fine.
We're already happy with how things are going.
But man, oh, man, if it ain't one thing, that's looking good.
Yeah, yeah, we're really we're really happy.
And Ann's over the moon.
And I, for one, cannot wait for you to get that white trim.
You're going to be so relaxed.
I just need I need my white trim.
Well, we took they took down the shutters.
They took down all the shutters and these shutters, these cheap old little plastic, fakey things.
They're fake as hell, right?
They're not even.
What if a tornado comes through?
Then these would be the first things to go.
They're not even they're just pieces of plastic.
So as we pulled them all down, we must have got 10 different calcified ancient wasp hives.
Oh, yeah.
Out of the backs of those things is wild.
Yeah, yeah.
But we've got we've got an excellent anti wasp plan.
Now, have I told you guys about Ann's fake wasp nests?
No, we have fake wasp nest strategically placed all over the yard.
We in that what's afraid of wasps?
I mean, besides humans and then I would like a human wasps was for afraid of other wasps.
If there is a wasp nest already constructed, they will they will make a point to not build a wasp nest within 40 yards.
I think it is of.
Oh, that's right.
Because wasps wasp use imperial measurements.
I have heard this before.
Yes, yes, yes.
They will not use the metric.
They do not use the metric.
It is the USA and wasps 40 yards.
So these nests that she got the nest, they are they're basically Chinese lanterns, you know, without the lantern component.
But it just expands with a little wire frame inside loose little wire frame inside.
And it looks like just a little it looks like a wasp nest.
You hang them up in the trees and stuff.
And like our neighbors were like, oh, my God, you got and I'm like, no, no, no.
Fakeity fake.
This is keeping the real deal at bay.
You are overrun.
It's true.
There were like three others, three of them in the backyard.
It's like you need to move immediately because they're about to be inundated.
We're like, we're OK, we're OK.
So, yeah, my aunt had I so I never know the the right terminology for this anymore because back then it was the the Africanized bees.
You know, let's stick with that.
That sounds right to me.
Yeah, let's don't change it from anything from that.
I just don't know what to actually I don't know what the real name of it is.
What the fuck is the real name of that?
Would you have like technically, technically Zimbabwe?
Whatever the real fucking name of that is supposed to be, that's what they called it.
That's what they called it.
I'm not saying that.
That's what they called it in the 90s.
And my aunt's house got overrun with bees.
What?
To the to the point that they had to sell the house.
That's one of Kurt Bronner's best comedy bits.
He closed out one of his specials.
He talks about my aunt's house.
It might be.
Yeah.
He talks about a house being overrun with bees and how when they get in there, they discovered what was it?
Ten million bees or something like that.
Oh, this wasn't that bad.
Still, I don't think this is I don't think this is Kurt's story.
But that's how Kurt closes out one of his comedy specials talking about just how the fuck do you ignore that your home has 10 million bees in it?
I mean, when it happened in my aunt's house, it was there was just a constant swarm of bees around the house.
It was horrifying and no one knew why.
Well, that's the thing.
If you're from Zimbabwe, you don't notice.
That's right.
Where the walls are paved with honey.
I am not comfortable with that.
Yeah, Penn's old place, the slammer was overrun with bees before its demise as well.
I do remember that.
Yeah, they had they had a bunch of nests all over the place in that place.
You could see like honey honey running in from anywhere.
It was really strange.
I just drove past this last week.
I drove past where the slammer was.
I was thinking about the slammer this week.
So sad.
Yeah, yeah.
Just you can't even get just a big bunch of bunch of houses.
You can't even figure out.
Yeah.
Did they develop?
It's a whole development now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little little block in a neighborhood now.
Yeah, there were two.
There were two really cool houses right in that area.
It was Penn's house and there was this giant white house that had like four windmills on it.
And yeah, both of those houses are gone now.
Those were like two weird houses right next to each other.
And it made me sad that they're both gone.
Yeah, yeah.
Yep.
So I was just down in one of my stops was Boston, Massachusetts.
Uh huh.
So we were.
Oh, I heard all about it.
I talked to your wife the other day and she was like, I am doing this.
I'm doing this and that's hanging out in Boston.
There's no getting around it.
This sucks to be her.
I don't know how.
Sorry, Sarah.
And so like, do I just like call it every day?
Be like, it's miserable for me to I'm doing nothing.
No, no, I think you're playing the right.
No, because she's not buying that.
She's simply not buying it.
Playing the right movie.
You got to just lean into it.
So one of the comedians on board is a guy named Rondell Sheridan.
Okay.
I know Rondell Sheridan.
He's hilarious.
That's it.
He's a very funny.
He's on board your ship right now.
Yes.
Incredible.
And so, uh, Rondell has been amazing, right?
Yeah.
It was funny because I once saw his show.
It was funny.
And then, uh, this guy on board, Tom, who knows like everyone who does Virgin Ships,
he goes, you never see Rondell Sheridan.
You see him do his shows and you see him come down for food and you never see him, uh, around.
And then the second night, like we made conversations with Rondell and, uh, we started talking sports and stuff.
And then, uh, uh, he started hanging out, started hanging out with us.
Oh, yes.
So Rondell, most people know him as the dad from, uh, that's so Raven.
He was, he was Raven's dad.
Okay.
And he's directed up, he's been and directed a bunch of shows for Disney Channel.
But you look at his old stand-up bits, there are old stand-up bits that you don't realize are his.
You go back and look and you're like, oh, that's, that's his.
Um, like the famous, uh, parachute man who survived after bouncing on the ground twice.
I don't know if you remember that bit.
But, um, so, uh, we're supposed to go to Maine.
The seas are too rough and the currents are too strong for us to go to Maine.
So the, the, the ship pulls an audible and just says, Hey, let's go to Boston early.
Let's haul us to Boston and do an overnight.
Yeah.
Overnights are so rare and they're the fucking best.
I've done, I did one in Tenerife, Spain.
And it's just like, you, you, you just, the whole, the whole ship's just excited to roll into town and go out, go out for the night.
Right.
So it's just the buzz in the air or whatever.
Well, what do you mean?
What's an overnight?
You get, you get to Boston at nighttime.
Your ship basically becomes a hotel.
You are now in Boston for the night.
Right.
Okay, great.
You don't have to come running back at 4 15 to make sure you don't get left behind.
Right.
Okay.
You got a floating hotel in Boston.
Floating hotel in Boston.
Everyone can stay out all night.
Right.
Great.
So, um, uh, Tom, that was one of the best things.
I still talk about that from the, from the Bermuda scoop cruise.
That was great because that boat just parked at Bermuda and we had a hotel at Bermuda.
It was perfect.
It was so fun.
Yeah.
Killing out every night and stumbling back to the ship.
Yes.
So, uh, you know, I haven't spent time out in Boston since I was like in my, like twenties.
Like I, I, you know, who would, who would want to indeed.
So Tom does the research and turns out there's this magic lab, Boston magic lab.
A magic open mic.
Uh, open mic with a wink face.
Cause I, so as I was out shopping, I was like, I'm going to haul that.
I'll haul, haul my ass back to the ship and throw some, throw some fish in a backpack
and let's go.
You know?
Uh huh.
Matt shows up with a fucking rolling suitcase.
All my, all two full cases.
Let's go motherfuckers.
Um.
Open this mic.
But Tom does some advanced research as it turns out.
No, it's open mic.
It's a sign up.
It's beforehand.
Okay.
Not day out because people have to work on their tricks obviously or whatever.
And so, so, uh, we were told that, no, it is a set lineup.
Um, I mean, they should definitely have a couple of spaces put aside if somebody just
shows up.
This is, this is the debate.
This is the debate that we were having.
Okay.
Yeah.
Tom did his due diligence because it's not of everything I do.
Just being the cohost of Penn Sunday school is the big one.
I mean, sure.
Almost every magician listens to Penn Sunday school.
Right.
And so like, uh, um.
You were known in the world of magic if for no other reason than because of that show.
And then one of the guys in the lineup has done Fool's a couple of times.
The guy named Tyler Twalby.
So you've got the connects.
Yeah.
And so, uh, but I, uh, I, I, uh, but no, no, no, we, we make no waves and there's no,
there's no scuttlebutt that we are there.
We just, we just buy tickets.
We watch and then we watched open mic and it's an open mic.
It is.
It is an open mic.
Like, like comedians have an open mic, like musicians at a coffee house have an open mic.
It is the same open mic.
That's not, not better or worse.
It is as good as an open mic.
The level of goodness is open mic level.
It is an open mic.
It is an open faced mic.
Hot and brown.
But what's cool is because it's like this open mic, like concept is that no one was
just doing a trick they bought.
And no one was doing like a, and no one was just doing like a, uh, you know, an off the
rack trick.
Like everyone was going for something different, original or something with some kind of intellectual
bite, something with some kind of narrative, something with some kind of feel.
So I did like, I did really like that a lot.
Um, and my buddy Tyler did kill it.
He did a really fun, uh, couple of routines and stuff.
And that part was great.
Uh, but there was a guy who was so socially awkward.
I mean, they were all like college professors and shit like that.
Um, you know, it's like a magic club basically.
And, um, uh, he was this older Asian professor who dressed up like Marty McFly from back to
the future.
Oh, I love this person already.
I know.
And this is like, he was so like shy and like, you know, like just, but he worked on his
script within an inch of its life and it was really well written.
Yes.
And he was doing time machine stuff with a, uh, an hourglass, like different little, mini
hourglass.
And then he was doing coin stuff where coins were disappearing and returned to his hands
based on the hour.
Oh, he just dressed like Marty McFly.
He, so he wasn't doing like a Marty McFly bit.
He was doing a time traveling bit.
Oh, this is good.
This is a good, this is a fine bit.
I'm, I'm very happy with this bit.
And sometimes wasn't, wasn't laughing at some of his jokes because he was just delivering
so like, like, like stone cold across the board.
I just turned to Tom and I was like, I love this guy.
I'm in love with this man.
I fucking love him.
And I was laughing at all of his bits and I was loving everything he was doing.
Yeah.
And he was making fun of himself for dressing like Marty McFly.
And when you want to do time travel, that was like more significant.
He got a bigger hourglass.
Like I got to go further back.
Hold on.
I just was like, I was like, no notes, man.
Let me just buy this routine off of you.
This is great.
All you're missing is decades of social skills.
Other than that, you are fucking nailing it.
Golden.
He was, but he was actually so likable and everything.
Wasn't even like, I'm being harsh, but he was, he was so likable and funny.
But yeah.
But then afterward, like it was funny.
Like I went up to one guy and Tom went up to another guy.
No one decided to hold court.
No one decided to say, Hey, you're here.
We should introduce you to everybody.
We should get a photo.
No, no one did that.
No one did that.
Right.
That's what I'm saying.
That's nice.
Oh no.
I thought that they should.
I thought we should have all got a big photo.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Okay.
Yeah.
Fine.
Because I put a photo up of it saying had a blast tonight at Boston magic lab and got
all these notes saying, I didn't know you were there.
Holy shit.
I would have said, hello.
Oh, I got all this stuff.
And I was like, Oh, I did.
I threw my name as much as comfortable as I am throwing my name around.
I threw my name around.
Right.
Uh, which I guess, I guess, I guess as I was saying, it's surprisingly less than you'd
think.
But then, Rondell wants to come out.
Right.
Does he come with you to the magic thing?
We find, we find, uh, he says he's too tired to go to the magic thing.
Sure.
We all are Rondell.
And, um, as a comedian not wanting to rush through a magic open mic, I totally understand.
Yeah.
Well, we decide we're going to go to a comedy club in the middle of Cambridge at the college,
the college comedy club.
Okay.
And so we roll up with Rondell Sheridan and guy recognizes him right away.
Cause he's comedy royalty.
Right.
He's standup royalty.
That guy, is this that guy from Boston commons?
Was he there?
Who's that cat?
That cat that came up with that TV show.
He was a standup.
Oh, I don't know.
I haven't heard of him for like a decade.
Yeah.
Oh, I need to look that up.
But he, uh, Paul brought up a story.
He doesn't know what the ending is.
I just don't know the guy's name off and we sit down and that was the only part of your
story.
It's the, uh, they, they of course come up and say, Hey, we can, we can get you a slot
if you want to do time.
And I go to comedy clubs, get it.
These magic clubs could learn a thing or two from these comedy clubs.
They know.
I could easily had a spin pad and a couple of fish in my backpack.
Anthony Clark, Anthony Clark was the comedian I was fishing for.
Okay.
Clark, who started.
Oh yeah.
Thank you for bringing it up.
And just, just to be, uh, just to make sure we're being clear about the story, Anthony
Clark, not involved in the story whatsoever.
Okay.
That's what I want.
But I thought perhaps he might've been because I don't know what he's been doing besides
possibly hiding in Boston, hosting open mic nights.
I also don't know what Anthony Clark has been up to lately, but he might have been up to
something with the following sponsor.
I don't know.
He might've been up to something with the following sponsor.
It might've happened.
I simply don't know what he's doing.
Um, this was, this was a regular lineup night.
This was not an open mic night.
This was a following sponsor.
Oh, sorry.
I was, I started reading the chat clever for my own good.
Yeah.
Go is brought to you by the fine people of go, go phone, go, go to the website.
I think I'll just say, uh, four floors of whores.
If you've got the balls, we've got the whores for floors of whores.
That's from scoop me hard, uh, in 2025.
So there you go.
I was at this place last night.
Hello everyone.
That's me, Vincent price.
I'm here to tell you about my newest attraction for floors of whores is open the doors.
There are the whores doesn't matter what floor you choose because there they are.
Come on in.
Would you like some porridge?
I've got some on the stairs story.
When you enter the first floor, you may notice many whores, but I'll have you know the second
floor contains more.
Open the door to the second floor.
You'll find more whores.
They a bore, a bore.
So be exciting and give them something more.
Oh, what's in this closet over here?
It's not a storage.
That's just storage for the porridge.
That's porridge storage.
You found my porridge storage.
So did I have some porridge?
Sure.
Now go up the door to level three whore.
Guess what?
More whores are you surprised?
You shouldn't be because the name of the place is four floors of whores.
Sam Elliott.
I'm just waiting till we get to the fourth floor.
This is Sam Elliott for whores original, cool whores original whores whores.
Sam, who would have thought you would have been barring the door for floor four?
Here in my house of many whores.
Can I get by you please?
No.
Sam?
Nope.
Oh.
Well, I guess this is where our tour ends.
No more tours of floors for the four.
You'll have to find out what's on floor four.
I can almost guarantee you it's just more whores, but still, don't forget to try the
porridge.
I swear, honey, I go there for the porridge.
And the conversation's with Vincent Price.
I eat porridge and I talk to Vincent Price.
You should come.
The Nevada DMV doesn't know what happens to snitches, apparently.
Have you heard about this?
No.
What happened?
The Nevada DMV has started a program to what they say.
So Matt knows this.
Oh, I do know about this.
This is fucked up.
This is stupid.
So Nevada has a problem, especially Las Vegas has a problem on the roads, and that is unregistered
vehicles.
Unlicensed?
Just out there with you.
Yeah, there are tons of unregistered.
Yeah, yeah.
No license plate on them, nothing.
And so the Nevada DMV, I suppose in conjunction with Metro or whatever, they have started
a program where it's just a tattle program.
They have a thing on there where you can now report cars that are unregistered to the Nevada
DMV.
And I saw a report today that they got 1,500 reports on their first day.
Jesus, 1,500.
I don't know, but there's nothing to be done about this.
I think this is just a thing about people leaving old cars in their yard.
I mean, that's some of it.
Some of it is absolutely neighbor snitching on neighbors for like, I'm tired of that junker
sitting there.
Yeah.
There's a lot of that.
But there's also just a lot of just snitching.
That's not a good idea.
It's a bad idea.
They don't fucking know that snitches get snitches.
Yeah.
Ain't nobody told them.
It's a terrible idea.
I like that the DMV was basically dismantled through a hack and took a month to recover.
And they're like, all right, now that we're back, let's start ratting people out.
Yeah.
Sorry, we couldn't get shit done for a month.
I've been getting hammered for this real ID thing.
I traveled with a passport.
Do you not have a real ID yet?
No.
I have a real ID and I went in and they're like, oh, we got hacked.
We can't, we can't do anything.
We can't get you set up.
Oh my God.
Right now.
We have to make another appointment for you.
They're like, we're not recovered from the hack yet.
And I was like, oh, well, I'm glad you guys kept the appointments.
Thanks for letting me know before I got here.
What a bunch of, yeah, our appointments didn't get hacked, but everything else did.
Yeah.
But sure.
Sure.
Let's let's do that.
The Nevada Department of Motor Vehicles has recently added a Nevada registration spotter
report form on their website, which is intended solely for the purpose of reporting motor
vehicles operating on Nevada roadways with expired, invalid, or no registration, including
Nevada residents operating vehicles with illegal out of state plates.
So they want, they want neighbors to report on each other.
They say that this report is not intended for abandoned vehicles, traffic violations,
stolen vehicles, parking violations, or other DMV related issues.
This is only supposed to be for cars on the roadway without a registration.
And we all know that's not the only thing that's getting reported.
Yeah.
Why?
Why doesn't make any sense?
I never understood driving around Las Vegas.
You will honestly see tons of vehicles with just no license plates and every time I would
see that I'm like, why would a police officer not pull that person over immediately?
A friend of mine got pulled over for fucking expired registration just the other night.
And I was like, how, why, why did, why did this cop decide to finally pull you over for
expired registration when there, there must've been 20 cars that drove past while you were
stopped without license plates at all?
Yeah.
I know that happened to you, Jacob, to another friend of yours when your friend's son was
in your car.
That is true.
I do.
I had a friend of mine's son was in my car with me and then my friend got pulled over
in his son and me and his son went, huh, Jacob had to talk my son off the ledge.
I was like, no, no, no.
Everything's going to be fine.
Everything's just fine.
Yeah.
Yeah, galactic president scooper star is exactly right, it's like, when else does the government
ask people to start informing on their neighbors?
I'm sure it's fine.
Yeah.
Probably not historically relevant in any way.
Baby steps to some real bullshit y'all, just crack a book once in a while, you motherfucker.
All I do want though, is to see all of these reports roll again.
I just want to see just every single report that comes in, I want to see how it's worded.
I want to see the report itself.
I want to see all of it.
What's the closest to like citizen's arrest we've really gotten here, which is like.
I'm doing a citizen's arrest, doing a license plate to a concealed carry for your expired
registration.
How about that?
I mean, what this is going to, this is going to cause big problems.
And I'll tell you what it's going to do.
This is going to cause a fight where somebody is going to get killed in like a grocery store
parking lot because two motherfuckers are going to start arguing and one of them is going
to start like reporting it on the, on the web or something like that.
And then somebody is going to get fucking stabbed in a parking lot all over, all over
this shit.
Yeah.
It's going to be bad.
This is, this is a bad idea.
If anybody from the Nevada DMV is listening and I know you are, this is a bad idea.
I mean, we're the number one Vegas parking and weather podcast.
So of course that's right.
They're tuning in to see where the car is getting parked.
No one does it better than ICS, especially not the Nevada DMV.
No.
Get your shit together.
You're absolutely right, Jacob.
Thank you for bringing this to our attention.
I also have been seeing through the national media, what little trickles down that Vegas
had some serious flooding this last week.
Oh yeah.
We had a, we had a crazy rainstorm blow through here.
We had hail at the house.
We had, we had hail at my house.
Uh, yeah, it was, it was, uh, this does not sound like much anywhere else, but, but we
had over an inch and a half of rain in about an hour.
Get the fuck out of, no, that's, that's insane.
I didn't realize it was that bad.
That's major for, for Vegas.
That's a death.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, multiple, multiple people died.
People died, right?
Yeah.
They found multiple bodies, uh, drowned and yeah, yeah, all that terrible stuff.
Um, yeah, it was, it, it just like, it came out of nowhere.
It blew in and it was horrible.
Apparently it was off of a tropical storm, uh, Priscilla.
I think they said it was a remnant of a tropical storm.
Queen of the desert.
Like I believe so.
Queen of the Mojave.
Yep.
Well, she did bring water.
Yes.
She left her.
That's a good question.
I think president scooper star McScoops a lot was the obelisk damaged, uh, in my, in
my backyard.
The obelisk has been put away.
So thankfully the obelisk was safe.
Good.
Weirdly.
Uh, my wife didn't want an obelisk just sitting in the backyard year round because she is
a party pooper.
Clearly.
Boo.
Her boo.
My wife.
Uh, don't boo.
She'll punch you.
When we last left off, Matt was just getting into a comedy club with Rondell Sheridan.
Yes.
So Rondell Sheridan goes in and this is a different open mic.
It's a comedy open mic.
No, it's not.
It's a regular lineup.
It's a lineup.
Oh, it's a regular show.
Yeah.
This is after the magic open mic.
This is regular comedy show.
Friday night in Boston.
We're not doing open mics on Friday night in Boston.
We're doing, uh, we're doing a lineup of, of, uh, Boston's best Colin Quinn, uh, just,
just Colin Quinn.
We can get your spot up on stage because right now we just have Colin Quinn.
We actually need openers and features as well.
Colin Quinn on a series of iPads on sticks around comedy clubs all across Boston.
That'd be great.
Colin Quinn performing at every comedy club in Boston simultaneously.
Um, we were in a college town and so the comedians are all like thirties, you know,
late twenties, early thirties, kind of, kind of folks.
Collegiate.
Rondell gets up and he announces that he is 67 years old and he starts doing bits and
he just plows through like 15 minutes of just assassinating, just fucking killing and crushing
across the thing.
He finds this one guy, he did a little crowd work.
He finds this one guy and he's like, uh, he goes, uh, uh, what do you do?
He's like, I'm an MMA fighter and he's like, oh shit, I should stop talking to you.
And he goes, what's your name?
And the guy says, I think, I think I have it right, he goes, let's remain Montgomery.
It's like the old Kian Peele bit, Rondell goes, man, could you have a blacker name than
that?
He goes, ain't nobody going to fight you.
No one's going to sign up to fight with remain Montgomery.
That's it.
You're the champ.
He goes, you're a legit fighter and he goes, yeah, I have my Texas fighting license.
Oh, oh, that is legit.
And the whole crowd is, you keep that with your fishing license, with your hunting license,
with your fishing, fishing, only using guns, license, using guns, it is a special license.
But Rondell killed it and then man, people lined up.
We couldn't leave.
People just light up.
Everyone in the photo with them.
Sure.
Finally get them out of there.
We pile into a pub.
Everyone in the bar makes out who he is and the waitstaff is all taking photos with him.
I had no idea how popular the show.
I just said it.
That's so Raven.
That's a raven.
Was.
Different generation.
Yeah.
It's a different generation.
It's after all of our, it's after all of our time.
I'm aware of it.
It's another choice of a new generation.
Since then, I've been hanging out with Rondell.
So we went out yesterday in Charleston, South Carolina.
Oh, that's awesome.
And I'm just going past Paul's joke and good, good, I gave it a thumbs down.
He was.
We were stopped constantly.
Like I walked.
I got on the boat without him for like an hour and I came at him back and we walked
from the boat and I walked right back the path that I walked up and we couldn't catch
up to our friends because he was being stopped so often by people who were filming out that
it was him.
And I was like, my God, I had no idea how, how, how famous this guy was.
But he's been an absolute gem.
We just been hanging out and joking around on the boat.
It's been so fun.
It's nice.
Are you parked next to Disney cruise ships too?
We're not.
So say, cause that would tip it over to like insane everywhere we parked, uh, we, we, uh,
we've been by our, by ourselves.
Uh, why, why would the Disney thing be a different thing?
Cause it shows on Disney channel.
Oh, I see.
That's so Raven is a Disney thing.
Gotcha.
Um, yeah.
But so it's that super fun, super fun adventures with Rondell Sheridan.
Yeah.
Nice.
So did you get him a chip?
Yep.
Sure.
Do you think we might be able to get him on the show sometime?
Yes.
I got him on the show.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
He's not going to listen, but he'll come on.
I don't care if he listens.
Correct.
Yeah.
I said that as a joke, but we all know it's, it's, it's just true.
It's just true.
Yeah.
Uh, I'll tell you who else we might be able to get on the show sometime.
If we work really hard at it and that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by four floors.
No, I'm kidding.
The fourth floor.
Columbastro private investigator in space.
That's Columbastro.
That's from the Microscoop in 2021.
So it is.
It's, it's requested from 2021.
This is a bit from Geekshaq.
It is.
Next commercial.
Excuse me, excuse me, I'm, I'm, I'm sorry to, uh, come into your, uh, your, uh, uh,
space here.
I mean, I want to get into your airlock just for, just for one minute, you know, I, I don't
want to deplete any oxygen systems here.
Okay.
Of course.
You know, but I got to say, you know, one more question there.
When you first encountered, uh, Mr. Zambalaxes, uh, did you actually realize he was the president
of this alien world that you were hoping to invade or was that just a coincidence that
you two just, uh, happened to hit it off?
He and your, your, your space daughter, do I need a space lawyer right now?
I look, sir, I'm not, I'm, I'm not a professional in any sense of the word, but I, you know,
I just, I like to watch, I like to listen, I like to hear even in space, I can hear you
scream.
You know what I'm saying?
But, uh, and look, okay.
Uh, if you tell me that there's nothing to investigate here, I'm going to be on my way.
Uh, but, uh, you just let me know if I can, uh, park my shuttlecraft, uh, over on your
aft docking sport, uh, later, I was just going to leave it there for a half hour or so.
One second.
I'm space texting my space lawyer.
That's fine.
I'll do do do do do do future sounds, futuristic sounds as I type it.
Beep boop boop.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, all right.
Well, I'll let you know.
Hello, Matt.
Natalie.
I am your robot space lawyer.
What can I do for you?
I'm being questioned here by, was it Columbus?
You said Columbus.
Astro.
I'm just a private detective.
So out in space, that's, uh, you know, kind of what I do.
Yeah.
Just, yeah.
Whatever you do, don't try to walk away from him.
He will have one more thing.
He wants to talk to you about, uh, no, that can't be true.
I'm going to walk away.
Right.
I mean, that's, that seems a little, a little presumptuous of your, uh, your robot.
That's quiet.
But, uh, just one more thing before I do go, uh, I'm just going to, I'm going to float.
I told you so.
Good job.
You're low gravity.
I get to float around, but I did want to know, uh, just wanted to, are you yourself, sir,
an avid collector of, uh, phaser rifles?
Do you, uh, do you have a lot of phaser rifles in your home?
Do you keep those loaded?
Do you keep the, uh, phaser ammunition separate from the phaser rifles?
Cause that's an illegal to hold phaser rifles in your home.
Not at all.
But you know, you do want to have a safety precautions.
You want to make sure that this, all right, I did it.
You got me, you got me again, check out every time I still think like we are not far away.
I should fucking write that treatment because I don't know if you know.
Do you know?
Do I know how much time is being made right now?
Yes.
Right.
You're right.
But, uh, are you talking about the movement?
I'm talking about movement.
I'm talking about Katherine Janeway, Captain Katherine Janeway.
Um, what's that actress's name?
I'm fucking blanking on her name.
Everybody drink.
Katherine Jones.
No way.
Kate Mulgrew.
Thank you, chat.
So I don't know if you know, but early in Kate Mulgrew's career, she portrayed none
other than lady Columbo.
So it's not that far to have a space Columbo happening.
She is a space detective.
I think it would be great.
I would love, let me text my space lawyer right now.
Oh, get ahold of him.
Oh, he doesn't sound.
You rang, sir.
Oh, yes.
There's a lady Columbo here wants to talk to me about.
Oh, just got one more thing please.
Just give me one moment.
Just one moment.
Oh, Jacote.
Jacote, you are my rock.
I can't.
You know what I need?
I need a stiff cup of coffee.
Hot.
What's going on with Seven?
Where is she?
I like that sparky young boy.
Did you see the movement to replace Christopher Columbus statues with Columbo statues?
Yes.
And I'm 100% here for it.
Man.
It's a great idea.
I am watching Task on HBO.
Okay.
And that is a very dark, dark show.
And the makers of Mayor of Easttown, which is already a very dark show.
So you've been able to stick with it.
We bounced off so early.
It is so good.
It is so depressing.
And it is so dark that I get anyone making me depressed.
Yeah.
It is amazing acting about a very depressing area of our country.
It is so sad.
And it's math, right?
There's a, there's a thing with the, I mean, the plot line.
The plot line's a little meth-y, but I don't know.
Got him!
It's more of a history and science than math.
Gotcha.
No, no, no.
There's, there's kilos of, I think it's heroin in it, that play a key plot point.
But it more ends up being about like, kind of like, is the system, like other corrupt
people in the system kind of thing.
So, but Mark Ruffalo just is Colombo, like he just, he just is Colombo.
He's just doing a Colombo impression.
Channeling Colombo.
He's exactly like Peter Falk, mosing in and out, like he's an older, you know, out of
shape.
He definitely has the disheveled thing going on.
That's it.
He's got this big disheveled hair, which is exactly like Peter Falk's hair.
Yep.
He's got frumpy, wrinkly shirts.
Oh, that's great.
He's the guy who's been out of the field, he gets called back in the field because it's
an emergency situation, and so he gets called back to head of task force, and he doesn't
know who he can trust on his own force.
And so he does things where he starts questioning people, trying to break them down.
And I am laughing.
I'm like, this is just, he's like mosing in, he's aching, you know.
Just one more thing.
It's a few plot points.
He's having like a head injury and a back injury, and so he's just, you know, touching
his head and moseying in and seeming kind of out of it, and then questioning people
and making them want to confess to things.
And I'm like, this is just, this is just secretly high end Hollywood white trash Columbo at
the same time.
This is just all, and I, it's really distracting because it's such a dead serious show.
I bet.
Because he's so good.
Yeah.
But no, it's a tough show to get.
I love it, but it's a tough show to get through for sure.
If I wasn't on a cruise ship alone, constantly staying up from four o'clock in the morning
watching stuff, I would do it.
I'm also watching Peacemaker, which I really love Peacemaker.
We just watched another episode of Peacemaker last night.
This new season is kind of amazing.
Yeah.
The writing in this season is just really, really good.
Oh my God.
There's a running gag.
It is so ridiculous.
Tim Meadows plays a character in this season.
It's so great.
And Tim Meadows says he has a condition called bird blindness, where he can't distinguish
any kind of bird from any other kind of bird.
And they find ways for this to come up.
Like all, like you forget that there was like a bird in the equation and all of a sudden
Tim Meadows talks and he just says something totally wrong.
And then everyone looks at him.
He's like, what, are you going to be prejudiced against my, my, my bird blindness?
You cannot use my disability against me.
His bird blindness is one of the funniest things.
Whoever came up with that in the writer's room was just like, oh man.
There's probably James Gunn.
I don't know.
It might be James Gunn.
I don't know anything else about his character.
And I don't care.
I know.
It's fine.
Like I know he, I know he works for the, the, the agency in some capacity.
I don't know what he does.
I don't care.
He is bird blind.
Everything else matters and they make it important to the plot.
I've got, I've got to see it.
It's not just an aside.
It is plot crucial.
I love it so much.
So good.
Every time it comes up, we just howl.
It's great.
Yeah.
That sounds awesome.
Oh yeah.
And gives everybody terrible nicknames too.
That's true.
That is true.
Yeah.
But, but that's still, that's, that's all fine.
That's, I'm really enjoying that as well.
But yeah.
Yeah.
Uh, also, uh, we wanted to get into it, but holy shit, John Oliver is just perfect.
I had to catch up.
John Oliver's show is just perfect.
Yeah.
I have to catch up.
I was watching the season at South Park.
I'm enjoying that.
Yep.
Um, but I have to catch up on John Oliver.
Uh, yeah, it turns out, uh, and we all know this.
We all comment on this every time it happens, but it turns out when, uh, the political leadership
in the country is terrible, uh, the comedy does get really good.
Yeah.
That is the upside to all these things is the comedy does get really good.
I have to, uh, not good enough to make it worth it, but still good.
Sorry.
I'm just getting a call.
I have to take this.
It's Hollywood.
Excuse me.
Oh no.
It's a space lawyer.
I'm sorry.
Just got one question for you.
No, I, I'm doing a podcast right now.
I can't, I, I'll have to call you back later.
Okay.
You say that.
Oh, that was easy.
Hey, you guys want to do a little scoop mail?
Let's do a little scoop mail.
Kurt is texting me right now, so I'm texting you.
Fantastic.
Oh good.
Tell him I just brought up his awesome house full of bees bit.
I plugged his house full of bees bit up.
Special.
That's why he's texting.
He's texting that to, uh, to thank him for you bringing that up.
He suddenly saw a giant influx of a bee.
I really do hope we get Kurt back on the show.
You don't know Paul, but he's my comedy partner and he loves the bee thing.
Yeah.
Exactly.
No, I hope, I hope we get Kurt on the show again sooner than later.
We got an email here from nincomscoop.
No, really ICS is making me smarter.
That, that seems impossible.
What?
My family has decided to visit Japan next year.
We are all trying to learn some Japanese.
I have been taking a deep dive into learning the language because I've always wanted to
and why the fuck not?
One thing about learning Japanese is learning the kanji, those, uh, logo graphic characters
representing words and ideas.
I believe it's pronounced kanji.
Kanji.
Thank you.
Uh, there are tens of thousands of them and learning them, you have to remember the concept
and they usually have more than one pronunciation depending on context.
It's kind of a bitch to learn.
One helpful memorization technique is creating mnemonic pictures in your mind.
Uh, I've created a handful from ICS concepts.
Here's my favorite.
Oh, the kanji looks roughly like a man sitting in a car with what would be an, or what could
be an arm sticking out.
That man is actually Matt.
He's got his hand out.
Oh no, it's full of coins and he's about to throw it at another car shouting be the change.
Yep, this kanji means change and on and on of the, uh, primary con, uh, pronunciations
is ka.
Thanks for the help, Matt, I guess.
Loving you all sexually.
That's nin come scoop.
It's the least I could do, quite frankly, the least I could do.
Literally.
Yeah.
Uh, we got one here from Big Sexy, hola mi amigos.
I am loving the streaming and wanted to chime in on the red flag stories, but I was in the
lobby of a hospital waiting to see cardiologists at that moment.
Uh, so I didn't do it right then.
So I decided to write in, I was dating this woman we'll call her Evelyn because that's
her name.
And she was this beautiful, hard of hearing mother of two.
The hard of hearing part was new to me and it rekindled my interest in learning sign
language.
Oh, we got two language emails right off the bat.
That's cool.
The red flags came from two different areas.
First, she was incredibly disorganized and her apartment showcased.
Things were everywhere with no rhyme or reason.
It made going to her place a nightmare for my OCD brain.
Books were piled on floors and dressers, clothes placed willy nilly and nothing in the kitchen
made sense.
I just have to back up for just a second here.
Uh, Big Sexy, I might've just messed up your email.
I said it made it a nightmare for his OCD brain.
That isn't actually what he typed.
He typed as his OC brain so I don't know if he's referring to his Orange County brain
or his OCD brain.
I suppose those are two very different things.
So Big Sexy, if you meant Orange County and I corrected it to OCD, I apologize.
It was hoarder status, but the kitchen made sense.
It was, oh sorry, sorry, I'm reading two different lines here.
Books were piled on the floor and dressers, clothes placed willy nilly and nothing in
the kitchen made sense.
It was hoarder status, but for books and clothes, we couldn't have sex without me kicking over
a stack of Judy Blume novels or self-help guides.
The bigger red flag flying from the highest flagpole though, was her parenting.
First and foremost, like Paul and Jacob, I have no kids.
I did work at a boy's home at the time so raising kids wasn't a new or unknown concept
to me.
I also understood the notion of boundaries, which apparently her children did not.
As the boyfriend, I made zero attempt to play daddy at all.
Not my place.
Deeply known by me, having had several stepmoms in my life and knowing they couldn't tell
me shit either, I made no attempts save for one.
Evelyn and I had just returned from a dinner date and had leftovers.
As we put them in the refrigerator, Evelyn clearly said, "Do not eat my food."
Later she went to run an errand.
As soon as she left, her daughter, around sixteen at the time, promptly made her way
to the fridge, cracked open mom's food and finished the meal.
When she pulled it out, I spoke up and said, "Hey, your mom said not to eat her food."
I did feel some kind of way since I paid for the meal.
Her daughter said, as most teens would, "Don't worry about it and you aren't my dad."
I had learned via the boy's home to pick my battles with the youths wisely.
This was not worth the fight.
I did however mention it to their mom when she returned, and instead of reprimanding
her daughter, she said it happens all the time and she just let it go.
Growing up, that would have been a stern discussion and punishment in my home.
The fact that it happened often said that her kids have little respect for rules and
that they would have zero respect for mine were we to get even more serious and/or get
married, which is why Evelyn gave me the ultimatum, which is why when Evelyn gave me the ultimatum,
either this is moving to marriage or we need to break up, there was no hesitation when
I said, "Well, I guess we're done."
Yeah.
Which took her by surprise.
She walked it back, but it was too late.
Decision made.
Each of my relationships has had red flags.
Sometimes it was me.
Luckily, the red flags around my current relationship were able to be overcome and our marriage
is wonderful.
Yeah.
Glad you stuck that in there, Big Sexy.
Currently in the running for America's Favorite Couple Vote on Facebook, Shameless Plug.
Fucking you in the face and ignoring your boundaries.
That's Big Sexy.
Thanks, Big Sexy.
Yeah.
Those are things.
That's tough.
I have not had that situation myself.
If any of you have seen Toast of London, one of my all-time favorite BBC comedies with
Matt Barry, holy shit, there's a hoarder girlfriend that he gets.
God damn.
It's remarkable.
They have to crawl into her bedroom over just 10 feet high newspapers and shit.
It's wild.
It's fucking wild.
It's such a funny, funny episode.
I think it's like the second episode.
It's really early in the series.
If you guys haven't seen Toast of London, highly recommend.
If you're what we do in the shadows fans, jump on Toast.
So fucking good.
Winner scoop.
It's amazing what men will put up with for some strange.
It is true that we can be blinded by a lot of shit sometimes.
It is true.
That is true.
Yeah.
Speaking of being blinded by shit, you ain't going no shit because it's Jock vs. Nerd.
That's your claim.
I'm here to debate it.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock vs. Nerd.
It's time for Jock vs. Nerd.
Of dating women with kids.
We got a scooper today from BeardedScoop3.
The categories are B&A song titles, B&A movie titles, B&A people, and B&A potpourri.
Do I know what B&A means?
What's B&A?
Breaking and acquiring?
No.
Oh, before and after.
Okay.
BeardedScoop3 sent an email along with it.
Yeah, this scooper is entirely before and after.
So before and after song titles, before and after, what were the others?
Movie titles, people, and potpourri.
Oh, wow.
Matt, you're up first.
This is going to be Matt's.
Matt's going to crush.
I know.
Matt's really good at the before and after ones.
Yeah.
All right.
Way to jinx me before 16 questions.
Let's do before and after movie titles, please.
Let's see here.
Luke Skywalker gets to know his father while Marty McFly gets close to his mother.
Empire Strikes Back to the Future.
There it is.
Wow.
He is so good at these.
Right?
Oh, Matt is so good at these.
Paul.
Uh, I will try song titles.
Let's see here.
A 1980 Queen hit and one of Kansas's most popular songs.
1980.
I can't think of the song by Kansas now.
Yeah, I just say there's a lot of Queen hits, but I don't know any.
I know.
I know Kansas is a bunch of hits, but I don't know them.
Right.
We Will Rock You, Crazy Little Thing Called Love.
Bad Bottom Girls, Bad Bottom Girls.
Yeah.
I can't think of enough Kansas songs.
I'll have to pass.
That's me.
Let's see.
Crazy Little Thing Called, hmm.
You know any Kansas songs off the top of your head?
Like Carry On, Wayward Son, that's probably their biggest one.
Uh, I think that's some others too.
I don't know.
I pass.
Matt, you're really good at these.
What is it?
Pass.
Another one Bites the Dust in the Wind.
That's a good one.
That is a good one.
I'm mad.
I don't know Kansas songs.
Dust in the wind.
Let's see.
I'll try People for 400.
When this Cleopatra actress gets criticized for her numerous relationship, oh, I get it.
Numerous relationships, she just shakes it off.
So this would be Elizabeth Taylor Swift.
That's right.
There you go.
Yeah.
Matt.
Um, I'll go with People.
For 800.
Lead singer of Blondie meets the 33rd U.S. president.
Debbie Harry Truman.
You are so good at these.
Paul.
Uh, I'll try, uh, song titles again.
Song titles for 800, a popular anti-establishment song by CCR and a major hit for Dusty Springfield.
Uh, uh, Fortunate Son of a Bitch.
No, gotta be.
Yes.
Now it's Fortunate Son of a Preacher Man.
Ah, shit.
I was thinking of somebody completely different.
Oh, buddy.
I was thinking that now y'all messing with a son of a bitch.
By Dusty Springfield.
By Dusty Springfield, which is not Dusty Springfield.
I'll try movie titles for 800.
Rufus Sewell wakes up in a hotel bathroom with no memories, is saved by a heavenly being
that looks a lot like Nick Cage.
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Hold on.
Uh, who is that actor?
This is from, uh, uh, uh, um, oh man, boy, old brain creaky Lee working Creek Creek Creek.
It's not inception to run faster.
It's not inception.
It's, uh, what the hell's the first Nolan movie?
Uh, memento.
That's what I was thinking.
It says memento, uh, but I'm trying to make, I can't remember that actor's name.
Memento.
He's like confidential too.
So is it names?
It's the names of the names, right?
I think so.
Yeah.
Does movie titles or names?
I thought it was, I don't know.
Oh no, I think it has movie titles.
Oh, so I was doing the wrong thing.
Why?
I already said pass.
Oh well, Paul, I'll have to pass.
Dark city of angels, dark city of angels.
I don't know.
Dark city at all.
No.
Dark city is interesting.
Yeah.
Huh?
Uh, Matt, you're up.
Um, movie titles, please for 1200, the story of Westward and Bernstein breaking the water
gate.
Westward.
Uh, the story of Woodward and Bernstein breaking the Watergate scandal plus an agency tasked
with hiding aliens on earth.
Um, it's a, wait, I keep on playing that movie.
It's a, it's not, it's not deep throat.
Um, it's what I was thinking.
That's a whole different movie.
Excellent move.
I'll pass.
A whole different one.
I've got this one.
I'll pass.
Paul.
The president's men in black.
Yes.
That's a good one.
That is a good one.
Yeah.
Uh, Paul, you're up.
I'll close out movie titles, please.
All right.
For 2000 daily double.
Oh, now is my chance for redemption.
Redemption.
Tony Stark first dons his armor while Henry Cavill plays Superman.
Iron Man of Steel.
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
There you go.
Good job.
Oh, now Paul is in the commanding lead.
Yeah.
Score check.
Paul has 2400.
Matt has 1200.
I have 400.
How do I only have 400?
Uh, I guess I'm bad at this.
Matt's really good at this though.
I'll do, uh, people for 1200.
The director of Bullets Over Broadway plays basketball with the answer.
Oh, I don't know who the director of Bullets Over Broadway is.
I will pass.
Matt.
Um, let's see, that is, um, uh, uh, Woody Allen Iverson.
There it is.
Oh, of course.
I'm mad that I didn't know that Woody Allen directed Bullets Over Broadway.
Matt.
Um, let's go with, uh, people again.
People again for 2000.
First Week Tonight host has dinner with the Lord Protector of the United Kingdom.
Oliver, what is it?
I don't know who the Lord Protector of the, uh, of the United Kingdom is.
John Oliver, Oliver Clothes Off.
John Oliver Clothes Off.
Good guess.
Uh, pass.
Paul.
John Oliver Cromwell.
Lord Protector of England.
Good job.
Bordens.
1592, then 1628, September.
It's a Monty Python song.
I've got those dates, I'm sure I got those dates completely wrong, but, uh, Paul, you're
up.
Uh, potpourri.
For 400, the sweetest and sparkliest breakfast cereal races against the looming deadline.
What was this one?
Just potpourri?
Potpourri.
Yeah.
Sparkliest breakfast cereal.
Oh, Cinnamon Toast Crunch Time.
Cinnamon Toast Crunch Time is just correct.
Wow.
Paul is also really good at these.
I was about to say Fruit Loops of Fury, but then I was like, no, that's not what that
is.
I'll try song titles, I don't know, for 1200, I'm getting whooped in this.
A 1978 hit for Bob Seeger and the Moody Blues song about bedsheets.
A song about what?
And a song about bedsheets.
I have no idea.
Pass.
Well, this is so hard, it's not even a figure out, because what I have is I'm thinking of
Knight Moves, and then there's Knights and White Satin, but you can't do Knight Moves
and White Satin, so that doesn't work.
Knights and White Satin Moves?
No.
So I don't know if it's a Seeger song that ends in...
Wait.
Was this the song that Bob Seeger did about werewolves?
Oh, no, I was getting confused, he didn't do a song about werewolves, he had the Silver
Bullet Band.
Yeah.
Um.
I'll pass.
Paul!
Oh.
Moody Blues about bedsheets.
Pass.
Well, let's see.
Hollywood Knights and White Satin.
Hollywood Knights and White Satin, I said Hollywood Knights.
Halfway.
Matt, you got song titles or potpourri?
I got to chase Paul here, yeah?
So I'll go 2,000 potpourri, please.
Okay.
Ooh.
A documentary series detailing this singer's sexual abuse aired in 2019, hosted by the
woman who replaced Kathie Lee Gifford on live.
Huh?
Whoa.
A documentary series?
Uh-huh.
Who replaced Kathie Lee Gifford?
Old Scrawny Arms.
I think she changed her name, though.
I just don't know.
I'm gonna pass.
Paul!
Paul Mattingly.
I'm thinking it's not from Justin DeKelly Ripa.
What?
A documentary series?
From Justin DeKelly?
Is that sexual abuse?
A documentary?
From Justin DeKelly, it was a different type of abuse.
Yeah, exactly.
It was like Kelly Ripa, Jack the Ripa, Kelly Jack the Ripa.
I don't fucking pass.
That's it.
It's Kelly Jack the Ripa.
A documentary series detailing this singer's sexual abuse aired in 2019.
Was that Michael Jackson?
Michael Jackson Kelly?
Michael Jackson Kelly Ripa?
I can't remember what- oh, maybe it's P. Diddy?
No, I think it's the sexual abuse of the singer.
Oh.
Yeah, that's what I'm assuming.
Ah.
Oh.
Like, if Megyn Kelly were a singer, it'd be like Megyn Kelly Ripa.
Okay.
Oh, maybe that's it.
I don't think Megyn Kelly is a singer.
Who?
Is it R. Kelly, then?
R. Kelly Ripa?
Oh, it's R. Kelly Ripa.
That's exactly it.
It's gotta be R. Kelly Ripa.
R. Kelly Ripa.
Ah.
Got there, y'all.
We got there, y'all.
Got there.
Took a village.
Lord.
Took a big- took a village on that one.
A big dumb village.
Paul.
You're up.
Me.
Us.
Three.
Idiots.
I agree, Lauren, by the way.
Those points should be shared.
However, there's not a button for that, so they're mine.
Song titles, please.
Song titles for 2000.
Yeah.
I hit from the Doors, self-titled album, and a 1970 hit for James Taylor.
Oh, boy.
Oh, God.
Like L.A. Woman.
I don't know enough-
It's the James Taylor part that's gonna slow me down.
I don't know enough to- Oh, come on, let me light your fire and rain.
Oh, good job.
Light my fire and rain is absolutely right.
Yeah.
Damn it.
I had that one that I thought you were gonna pass.
It's over.
I did, too.
It's over, everyone.
Go home.
Isn't that one Daily Double left?
No, there's one more Daily Double still in there.
Yeah, doesn't matter.
I think there is.
Doesn't matter.
Look at the scores, guys.
It only matters if Paul gets it and misses it.
Right.
Oh, I understand.
Oh, which I don't think- I don't think he can.
Oh, no, I can.
I just answered my last question, so haha.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, never mind.
Yeah, it's over.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, but it's the Daily Double.
See?
There's the Daily Double.
If you get this, won't that take you over?
Uh, no.
Oh, okay.
Paul.
I have 2,400 points.
You have 6,800 points.
If I double my points, how many points do I have?
Yeah, but don't you also get the 1,200?
Okay.
Brace yourself, everyone.
Paul's doing Kentucky math.
All right.
Go ahead.
The steamy BDSM Best Seller if it were set in Big and Little Eddie's Crumbling Hampton's
Mansion.
Oh, my God.
I got this.
Oh, I got this.
What the?
Yeah, I got this one, too.
I know the first part.
Fifty Shades of Grey.
There you go.
One more word.
Has to do with--
I know.
Has to do with taking care of plants.
It does not take place in Madison Square.
Right.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Fifty Shades of Grey Basketball.
Oh, boy.
Grey Garden.
Yeah.
Fifty Shades of Grey Gardens.
All right.
We really helped Jacob today.
This has been a good day.
We did.
We really helped Jacob a lot today.
Matt, close it out.
The category end the game.
Potpourri for 800.
If I get this right--
The second place, it takes a village.
If I get this right, I'm in third, and if I lose, I'm in third.
Yep.
High stakes.
And if I pass--
Prince's iconic--
And if I pass it to Jacob, and he gets it, he's in second, and if he loses, he's in
second.
Or if you pass it to Paul and he misses, he's still in first.
Yeah.
It's high stakes.
But if he gets it, he's in first.
Prince's iconic movie/song needs to reschedule for another time.
Aw.
Oh.
Bassey just typed it in.
Purple rain check.
Thank you for that.
Just by typing it in the chat.
Oh!
There you go.
Much easier game if we just do that all the time.
I was thinking it was going to be something like Under the Cherry Moon.
I'll see you next Tuesday or something.
Well, I knew it was Purple Rain, but I didn't know the other one.
I really thought it was Under the Cherry Moon.
The movie Under the Cherry Moon?
I still think it's Under the Cherry Moon.
Yep.
Good.
So, Bassey, good job on that question.
I mean, I didn't get all my questions right by myself either.
But don't worry, Matt.
You're still really good at this.
Paul wins though with 6,800 points, I'm in second with 4,800, Matt is in third with 3,200,
but don't let that fool you.
He's very, very good at these.
Excellent.
And that's from BeardedScoop3.
Thank you, BeardedScoop3.
If you want to send us a scooper to your price, a Skryte jock versus nerd, or an Obelisk jock
versus nerd, head on over to HeyScoops.com.
That's where you can go, HeyScoops.com.
You can make a thing, you can send us the thing.
It'll be great.
We'll do the thing.
We will.
BeardedScoop3, thank you so much for that.
That was an incredible game.
We appreciate the interaction from each and every one of you scoops.
We're so happy to see so many people in the chat right now, hanging out with us here and
on Twitch.
So cool.
Yes.
I want to thank Penn Gelettick for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I want to thank all the people who are coming out to my show in Sparta, or the following
week to my show with Paul at Tierney's.
Yeah, so good.
It's going to be a super fun show.
Don't miss it.
And I also want to thank other people here.
Jacob wrote me a list.
I found it.
It's right here.
These following people just have to answer one more question before they get in the airlock.
That's William McDonald, Will Kellner, Will Beardydan, HootadScoop, What Was Like Scoop,
Wes Culligan, Wendy Bumgardner, Wendy Cooper, Water Ice Scoop, Warren Breaux, Uncle Don's
Woodshop, Udo Gerhards, Tyler Scoop McDuck, Tyler Bartlett, Tuba Scoop, Troy Anthony Townser,
Tristan Guevara, and Travis Murray.
The following people are about to participate in their very first Open Magic Mike night.
The Upside Down Underscoop, the Spirit of the Latin Club, the Scoop Lockean, the Salty
Squid, the SCWOP, the Nano Scoop, the Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, the Lapis Lagomorf,
the Ice Cream Headache, the Ice Cream Headache again, the Going Over Our Friends podcast,
the famous Ball, the Didgeridooche, the Devil's Lettuce Scoop, the Damsels of Dorkington,
the Civic Crew Scoop, and the Cincy Scoop.
The following people have all called in their next door neighbor's registration to the hotline.
Travis Jurgwai, Tony Scoprano, Tony Cowley, Tom Stott, Tom Mancreddy, Tom Krieger, TK4201
Scoop Please, Timothy Sutton, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thomas Beach, the Man, the Myth,
the Scoop, the Dirty Scoop.
Thank you so much.
The following people are a lot like rain in Las Vegas.
An inch and a half might not sound like much, but it can fuck you good.
The Bad Humor Man, That Thing in the Attic, Turn the Page, Temporary Dot Reality, Pierce,
Technical Scoop Hort, Tamara Hamilton, Take it Evie Podcast Scoop, Swedish Scoop, Super
Geek 13579, Sugar Rush Socio, Strap a Chicken on Scoop, Strange Uncle's Podcast, Stuart
Wilson, and Stephen Biggs.
And the following scoops all love overnighting in Boston on a cruise ship.
That's Stephen Landon, Stephen Clively, Stephanie Young, Streets, Asteets, McGreets, Stacy Coleman,
Stab and Dash Scoop, Spring Loaded Scoop, Sound Man Scoop, Soulless Scoop, Solar Powered
Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Slurpee Ki-Ai Motherfucker, Slightly Slutty Scoop, Scholar Wall Scoop,
Six Foot Scoop, Sir Scoopy McScooperson III, Esquire, Silverfist Scoop, Silicon Scoop,
Shoeless Scoop, Sean, SF, Sebastian Robbins, Seanathan P., Sean Kellner, Scott Shofield,
Scott Muldrig, Scott Headington, Scott Ashlock, Scott Ashlock again, Scott Andrews, and Scott
Ayy, thank you all so much, Scott Ayy.
Ayy, if you want to help us out and if you want to keep this podcast going, we need your
support month after month, year after year.
Head on over to PreachingFun.com and find the tier that suits your budget right now.
Or if you don't want to do any of those things, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's right, fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com takes you over to our
Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
You think this show is worth more than $0?
PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those are the places you can go to help support this
show and we do need it.
We have a weird amount of bills for such a small podcast, so head on over there.
And they go up, which is annoying.
They keep going up too.
Things keep going up.
What do you know?
Thanks, Obama.
Love you guys.
Take care of yourselves up there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the cone.
I don't know who needs to hear it, but it's true.
And there are whores on multiple floors.
PreachingFun.com.
All these whores on multiple floors.
It's only somebody who's here to give me a tour.
See ya!