Oh, hello there! I didn't see you, but I'm so happy you're here because I want to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Right now, I'd like to thank Jake Schneider, Jason Klepper, Jeff Harris, Jonathan, Lori Ellsworth, Leon Kassab, Malia, and Mike!
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, just like these fine folks, PreachingFun.com is where you can go.
Head over to PreachingFun.com right there on the page, sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver,
deliver that fucking ice cream straight to people's fucking ear holes, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own!
Here's the program!
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Hello, from a secret location.
I mean, it's Jersey.
Right.
Oh, shit! Was that a secret?
Damn it! I suck at this!
It's time for Matt Maddenley's Ice Cream Social, sitting in New Jersey together!
It's Matt Maddenley, Matt Donnelly, and Paul Maddenley, sitting in Las Vegas at Speed, check out the audio guy!
We're PreachingFun!
We're not in Jersey, but we can't say where we are.
We are sneakily outside.
Oh, that's right! You are post-Jersey.
We're post-Jersey, yeah.
We're at something that we'll definitely be talking about in the next episode, but we are not allowed to talk about it yet.
But we have other things to talk about, which is like, Paul's really upset, so here, Paul, here's five bucks, I'm sorry.
Keep that one.
Oh, it's just like really on me about those five bucks.
He came at me last night and he's like, "Hey, you got five bucks for the vending machine, they don't have any change at the front."
I'm like, "Here's five."
And then this morning he's like, "Oh, yeah, I owe you five bucks."
I'm like, "Get the fuck out of here."
I told you last time I was also good for it, which I'm a man of my word.
I know, you're good for it. I don't, I'm good.
I just feel like it's been a subtext this entire morning, we just haven't, you know.
If I don't have something to hold over your head.
Paul's just...
It's acquiring interest.
I did scare the living shit out of Paul this morning.
Paul thought I died.
Yeah.
Oh!
So we had planned...
Were you guys sharing a room?
No.
Okay.
No, that's a key...
In that case, I have even more questions.
That's a key factor.
That's a key factor, actually, is that we are not sharing a room.
No, we parted ways last night and everything seemed to be fine.
I went and got my sleeps on.
We had said 10 o'clock meetup in the morning.
And I get ready, do my thing, 10 o'clock rolls around.
I look around.
No Matt.
I go out to check the car.
Okay, that's odd.
I'm chilling for a little bit.
10, 15.
Okay.
I get on.
I text Matt.
Let it sit.
You know, nothing.
Don't hear anything.
Yeah.
That's weird.
You know.
And I let it go and Ann calls and we're chatting.
And then it's 1030 and I'm like, well, shit, I better call Matt.
So I call Matt.
Nothing.
It goes right to voicemail.
I call him again.
It goes to voicemail.
So I'm like, oh no.
And then I look at the phone and I start looking at the text.
He sent a text last night and it was in a chain text and he hasn't responded to anybody
else's stuff.
He hasn't liked anybody's stuff.
I'm like, he hasn't touched this in hours.
He's in communicato with me completely.
So I'm like, okay, I got to go check on.
So I go to his door and I knock and I wait a little bit.
Nothing.
I knock again.
A little more urgently this time.
The fucking tomb of Imhotep.
I'm like, well, I'm going to the front desk to report my friend's dead.
We were supposed to meet at 10.
It's like 1040.
So I start walking to the desk and sure enough, I'm almost to the front desk and I get a buzz
on my phone and it's Matt.
And he's like, oh, I slept through my alarm.
Yeah, you fucking did.
He thought I was the housekeeping again.
Yeah, the knocking.
I thought it was the housekeeper being like, well, my alarm isn't going off yet.
So the housekeeper is too early and I'm just going to go to the housekeeper.
And knock twice.
Hard.
Yeah, that's true.
In the same bit.
I was expecting the door to open, you know, in housekeeping.
All right.
Yeah.
So I put the door to open and just go like, no, thank you.
This is the door open, you know?
Yeah.
And then it never opened.
So I was like, oh, all right.
The housekeeper took a hint.
When my alarm goes off, I'll talk to the housekeeping.
Then all of a sudden my brain is like, there's no way I slept through my alarm.
And then I got up and I sure enough slept through my alarm.
Turns out when you actually only have three hours of sleep and then you go right from
the airport to Tierney's Tavern and then to, you know, two hours of comedy shows and then
drive a significant distance after that to go to a secret location and check into a hotel.
You're more tired than you thought.
You're more tired.
Where is your out?
It turns out.
Where is your ride out?
And I could see, even in Paul's retelling of it just now, I could see how stressed he
was that he was never going to get that $5 back.
Exactly.
That was the first thought on my mind.
I was like, I'm out.
Son of a bitch.
I'm going to have to get that $5 from the estate.
This is going to be a huge pain.
I promise you in the four minutes it took me to walk down the hallway, not even four minutes,
three minutes it took me to walk down the hallway.
I'm going down the hallway through different things.
I'm walking towards the front of the gate and like I get to the second like hallway gate
change and I just, my, my face just drops.
I'm like, Oh my God, this is it.
I was like, I was like, first of all, how am I going to explain this to Sarah?
How am I going to explain this to his kids?
What's my responsibility from this point forward?
And then I was like, this can't be it.
This would be the end of everything.
Not to mention the cars in my name.
Oh my God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Forget it.
All that shit.
I was just like, fucking forget it.
I wasn't even worried about it.
I was like, I was kind of going, well, I'll be stranded here for a day or two, but we'll
figure it out.
But that's not what's important now.
What's important is my friend is dead and I need to attend to his affairs.
I'm going to have to adopt his children.
I mean, I might have to, you know, move back to Vegas for a little while to help out.
Certainly, I'm sure that's where services will be held.
I don't know.
Do I need to contact Tierney's?
Who else needs to be notified?
Who do I notify first?
Is Tierney's Bats official next of kin?
Sarah.
Tierney's.
That's the order that you...
But no, don't act like that's some bullshit move.
He knows like 85 people that work in that fucking building.
It's not far off from next to kin.
It is the right move.
I think if I told the Tierney's second, that would have been totally fine.
It would have gotten out to the entirety of Jersey in like five minutes.
But then, of course, then selfishly it starts to overwhelm me.
I'm like, I'm just getting on my feet.
The house just got painted.
Jesus Christ.
Just getting my income straight.
This is one of the few outside gigs.
This is because of our partnership that I'm able to do these things.
It's all, I can't fall apart like this.
Collective president in chat is saying, you know, I'm laughing, but this isn't funny.
No, me being dead is not funny.
The amount of planning Paul did in four minutes is amazing.
I was all the way.
I mean, I was raised in a house of catastrophizers.
So, you know, that's where that's where my brain goes real fucking quick.
It doesn't take me any time to be like, I'm destitute.
The podcast has been to stop.
I don't know if I can even improvise anymore.
We've already you guys have already made it very clear that you felt that I was very replaceable on this show.
You guys already we've already done.
I mean, I've even done this before.
I've been the one to call and text Matt in the mornings when we're doing all these things.
And Matt's like, no, he's asleep.
Matt sleeps through shit sometimes.
It just happens.
Matt is a heavy sleeper.
He sleeps through shit sometimes.
That's it.
I'm a heavy sleeper too.
I've got a point where I have to have my door propped open and everything.
But in a hotel when it's a different place, I don't sleep nearly as heavy.
I don't have my white noise going like crazy.
So yeah, when Matt's in a hotel and not near his kids, he does sleep heavily.
Oh, yeah, that's absolutely true.
That makes sense.
Also, the night before I came, my cats were dickheads, right?
So sometimes I've done things where I leave our doggy door.
It's a cat door.
I have cats, but it's a doggy door that's built in our house.
I leave our doggy door.
We have a little slide and I leave it open at night.
Other cats have come into our backyard and sniffed around that door in the middle of the night.
And all of a sudden they'll be like a big cat fight.
And that's woken me up a few times.
And Sarah down stairs just yelling, you bitch, you bitch, you bitch.
I had to get up at 5.15 to make the flight to Vegas.
OK.
And my cats woke me up at 4.15.
Ah, assholes.
And then I went down to be like, did I leave the fucking cat door open?
And I get up in a panic because Sarah gets up every morning with the kids.
And so waking her up early is just a much larger mistake than me and my little flight.
And so I get up right away to what I think is close the cat door.
And I came down and my cats just fighting each other.
That's it.
The door was closed.
I did everything right.
They just decided to be fucking assholes at 4.15 in the morning and fight each other.
They normally get along.
Yeah.
They decided to fight each other at 4.15 in the morning.
And then I was up.
Right.
It's like, that's it.
I got three hours of sleep and that was my day.
And so then I was off to the airport all day and all that stuff.
So yeah, I was more tired than I thought.
My cats are dicks basically.
And then have you discussed with Paul what you're going to have to do from now on now that you have pets that do hate each other?
How Paul keeps all of his pets separate?
Yeah.
How you're going to have to start doing that now?
I have to build some kind of like Panama Canal of fences and things in my house.
That's right.
It really is.
It is a fucking lock system.
Now here's the thing.
So before I left, we had to go take Giz out to grandma's so that she wouldn't be more trouble than Anne can deal with.
So Anne's just got to record.
But that was an extra trip that we had to do on and off.
When you leave town, you take one of the dogs to the dog sitter so that Anne doesn't have to deal with all the animals that hate each other being in the house without you there.
I didn't know that.
That is very sweet.
And Matt, I want you to know that I will not be taking one of your cats next time you leave town.
You would love the Deeks.
You would love Schmicky Deeks.
Come on, Schmicky Deeks.
She's such an attention hound.
It's only a three hour round trip to go take the dog and drop her off and come back home.
It's really nothing.
It's really no trouble at all.
Yeah, it just eats up the great majority of your off day.
Especially because one of those 90 minutes is with a dog in the car.
Honestly, we don't mind.
With a classically well behaved dog.
A dog that we talk about all the time how well behaved it is.
She is really well behaved unless she's around Adora.
That's it.
The shit of it is Adora and Giz are very similar in temperament and everything.
And that's why they hate each other.
And they really get territorial around Ann.
That's all there is to it.
All I have to say is we had a really good show at Terry's Tavern.
We sure as fuck did.
That was the main crux of yesterday getting to that.
And we did it.
And I'm very, very pleased.
It was super exciting for me to perform with these players that I hadn't played with in a long time.
I played with Didgeridoo in the past, but in a minute.
And he fucking brought the fucking fire.
Everybody was just top of game, man.
Everybody was really good.
Pat Shepard drove from the shore.
Steve came out from West Jersey.
Probably about 30 scoops came out.
There's probably about maybe 20 other people just from town.
One guy who read about Only Me being a magic show and was disappointed that it also had Dion Flynn from The Tonight Show.
And Kurt Braunhauer and all this pesky improv stuff.
All this hilarious comedy that the entire room is enjoying except me.
This is a good sign, though, Matt.
This is a good sign.
That means that people are getting back into magic and they're taking it seriously.
Because what the mind noodler wants are people that take magic very seriously to watch his act.
That's it, right?
So this guy is this douche.
I'll just call him a douche.
This douche shows up and he's there with his wife.
This hero.
This hero shows up.
He's a douche.
He's like, I'm not here because I heard you're doing magic.
I'll be doing some magic for sure.
But this is more of like a comedy night.
Now, like everything that I put out said random comedy night.
Yes.
That was the name of the event.
Yeah.
And it's an improv stand up and magic blast.
Yes.
Right.
And so I know for a fact that I didn't overly emphasize that this is going to be a magic show.
But I guess on Tierney's social media, one of the posts was like, it's going to be a magic show.
Ah, gotcha.
Right.
Well, let's be fair.
This was proudly displayed on the dumpster.
Okay.
So that is a banner they made just for the event.
And it was located on the dumpster of Tierney's Tavern fence around this dumpster.
It is a picture of Matt Donnelly in front of a banner there.
What does St. Paul's banner say?
What it says on the banner is.
Join us October 23rd for an intimate night of my noodling with Matt Donnelly.
It doesn't even say magic.
It doesn't say magic.
It still doesn't say magic.
Intimate night's weird phrasing.
And it's brought to you by Guinness.
Yeah.
Guinness sponsored it, so I'm official.
Matt Donnelly will fuck you if you come by on this night.
And I laughed.
So basically we said doors at seven, but that's just because I just wanted people in there.
Because I knew that we had to drive a long time after the show.
So I was like, I'm going to, you know, I just want to get everybody in.
And I was like, and I got up and I told everybody the whole situation, why we're there, why
this night came together, that two people were coming literally from writing for Jimmy
Fallon and literally taking a car from the city to Tierney's to make it to the show.
I said, they're going to show up whenever they're going to show up because Jimmy Fallon
can keep them for as long as he wants.
Right.
And so I was like, we're going to do some improv.
We're going to have some stand-up sets.
I'm going to do some magic.
It's going to be a cool hang.
Right.
Get everybody on the same page.
And so at like seven fifteen, we did an improv set with Paul, me, Steve and Patch, the four
of us, without Dion and Kurt.
And we really had a great set.
It was really good.
The audience was just eating it up and laughing it.
And we finished and the douche is sitting there going, I thought there was going to
be a magic show.
I thought there is going to be a magic show.
In my head, I just explained this, actually, as a matter of fact.
I was just on stage talking about this.
I go, yeah, there is going to be a magic show.
I was like, when?
I was like, next.
But he was the one tool bag in a sea of lovelies.
That's the other thing.
Everybody was.
We had a great night.
It was amazing.
It's a podcast.
I'm only talking about the one dumb thing.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
So I go, next.
He's like, well, good or whatever.
And I go, I literally go, I mean, did you not enjoy what you just saw?
And I say that because I was so comfortable.
The audience was roaring through the whole thing.
It was just confusing.
So I literally was like, can we chill out?
And I thought he was going to laugh it off.
Maybe I'm interpreting him too hard.
Maybe he isn't a douche.
At this moment of the conversation, how many feet from the stage that you were just performing
on are you?
15 feet.
Yeah, great.
Okay, okay.
This is not down the road.
This is not in the next building over.
This is next to the stage that you were just on.
Yeah.
And so I expect him to laugh.
They'll be like, oh, yeah, no, that was great or whatever.
And he goes, hmm, improv.
And I was like.
I was having a conversation with the scoop when I first got in there.
This is great.
When I first got in there, I was talking.
And I'm talking with this scoop and they're telling me some heartfelt stuff about what
the podcast means to them.
Great.
And that motherfucker came in and inserted himself right in the middle of me talking
to the scoop.
Oh, great.
I'm like, asshole.
And so from that point on, I wrote that motherfucker off.
Right.
He was a shitbag.
And I think he's come out to other events there that we've done.
I don't think he was.
I think I recognized him from previous things.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Was it Brogan?
No, no, no.
It was not Brogan.
Brogan was awesome.
Okay, great.
Full side note.
Brogan fucking flew in from Scotland to see the show at Tierney's Tower.
Insane.
That's insane.
Yeah.
Brogan's the best.
They brought me.
Carolyn and Paul came out.
Yes.
Carolyn and Paul.
Oh, good.
They were very upset because they definitely had traveled the furthest to be at Tierney's
show of anyone.
Right.
And then Brogan torpedoed them.
Almost.
Not fair.
Yeah, yeah.
They let us know that they met at our second Tierney's event.
That's where they met each other.
That's where the connection happened.
That's right.
I forgot about that.
Yeah.
So that was really sweet.
And they're still together.
I think so far that's the only successful coupling now.
That's not dwelling on the past, Paul.
It's focused on the present.
It's not the only successful one.
We've had a few successful ones.
We've had some unsuccessful ones.
That's also true.
Whatever.
But yeah, Christine came out and...
Winner scoop successful in quotes.
Carl and Amy showed up.
Yeah.
And...
Nicky?
Nicky was there.
Yeah.
And then...
This is the part of the show where Paul names people he saw.
Look.
And then we get in trouble for not naming the people that also came.
Michael Scoop was there, of course.
Good, good.
Yeah.
Tens of people were there.
And it was awesome.
And what I really loved was at the end of the show, I came up to a couple who was sitting
there at a table and they had had a blast.
They loved it.
They're like, "This is our first time we've ever come out to a thing.
We just wanted to come out and see what's up."
I thought there was going to be more magic.
No.
Where is the more magic?
These guys were like, "This was the funniest thing.
I'm hurting from laughing."
I'm like, "Fantastic."
This was very funny.
It would have been so much better if there had been magic.
Thank you for taking a chance on us.
I got him a chip.
We're Obelisk King people left and right.
It was great.
A couple came up to me and said that, "We love the podcast.
We're going to head out."
They said, "We love it tonight.
We'll check out your podcast.
We're going to head out."
I said, "Oh, do you have chips?"
And they said, "No."
I was craning my neck for Paul to look at me as I went over and got two chips out.
He's learning the ways of the Obelisk.
Matt pulled his shoulder, pat himself on the back.
Learning the ways of the Obelisk.
I'll tell you who else got chips from Matt Donnelly last night, and that is the following
sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Matt Donnelly's Magical Manual for Manipulating Matt's Cats.
It's from 2024.
It's from big, sexy digital nomad.
Some of you may know that Matt has two cats, Shmeeky and Shmookey.
Both of them are certified assholes, bird killers, and general no-goodniks.
They will cause bullshit after bullshit.
But if you have cats that give you trouble, Matt has a way to solve it.
Yes, in fact, it's Matt Donnelly's Magic Manual for Dealing with Cats.
The wonders of this book are that it can enclose said felines.
All you need to do is lay it open on a coffee table, hanging towards an edge, where they
are tempted to knock the shit out of it.
When they come up to try and do that on the book, they will fall into a great abyss of
a hidden compartment inside the tome.
You can quickly slam it shut and you have trapped kitty.
The book itself is just an animal trap.
No pincers, nothing sharp.
The animal will not be harmed, merely contained.
So if you're having trouble with your pussy, why not lock it up in Matt Donnelly's Magical
Manual?
Yeah.
And you can use it manually.
And our hay scoops at Checkout.
There you go.
Paul, I think when we left, you were listing off people that you saw yesterday.
Okay.
So then I saw Kurt Prowler and oh my god, Kurt's stand-up was hilarious.
He really had me losing my shit.
So fucked.
Oh, he's got it.
He figured it all out.
He got it all put together.
I think he's finally figuring it out.
I think he's really coming.
Good.
Good for him.
He's so fucking good.
No, he was saying that he doesn't have to do stand-up as much because he got the gig
working for Fallon and it takes up so much of the week that you don't get out.
So he was very happy to be doing stand-up last night, but he crushed.
He was so funny.
And we were able to cajole him into playing with us for the second half too, and he was
very happy that he did that and it was awesome.
He was so funny in the improv too.
So I just put some buttons on the douche.
So I do a magic set.
I thought it went really well.
I really enjoyed the magic set.
This was one of the better magic sets I've seen.
I wish the whole show had been like this.
No, he said nothing.
He said absolutely nothing.
No, he did not say nothing.
He said nothing.
He did not do all of that and did not say anything after the magic set.
He did not say nothing.
The only thing that was bringing...
Come on, dude.
I mean, everyone else having a great time, but specifically what brought me a lot of
a joy was his wife was having a fucking blast.
His wife was laughing at everything while he was stone-faced.
And so I'm going through a magic set and I did a magic set.
I did some cool magic.
Matt, I believe that you did good magic.
I believe that you did really good magic.
Your magic was great, Matt.
At this point, I'm like, what was he expecting?
If this...
What I'm doing, right?
I did the fucking ring bit, the arm chopper bit, and the straightest jacket escape.
And the ring ones tends to be most magicians' favorite little magic thing is the ring one.
The ring one is an excellent one.
The arm chopper is one of your newer ones and it's very good.
The straightest jacket, a classic.
It's got good comedy.
It's got good magic.
What do you want?
And I was just like, did he want doves or a floating bar stool?
What was he looking for that he needed that he was not getting?
He was looking for intimacy, man.
That's right.
He was looking to be intimate.
Maybe he was just looking for just love, maybe just a human connection between two people.
Here's the thing.
For those who were in attendance, he ended up being a focal point for part of Matt and
Dion's improvised two-man set.
So Dion Flynn, right?
Dion, who plays Obama on Fallon, like Dion is a, I would describe a beautifully intense
person.
Like he does, he has no kind of aw-shucks-y bullshit mode.
He's only...
Oh, I love that.
He's only talking real like all the time and that's why I love hanging out with him.
Like he just, he just cannot, he does not small talk.
And so for his bit, he was like, hey, everyone, I don't even know what I'm fully doing here.
Like he came in like in the middle of my intro and he goes, yeah, I just felt like where
you were in your intro, that felt like a good time for me to come in and sit down.
So I'm going to start talking now.
And he just kind of comes in and he makes the whole audience move chairs and like move
closer and come up.
Great.
And he's like, we're going to go to different people.
He's like, I'm just going to have you raise your hand.
I might not have been calling you.
You might not even talk.
And then he called on someone and then he did have him say something and goes, and that's
all we're going to take from you.
That's not to say we're not curious about what we're saying, but we're moving on.
And he just, he just started bouncing around the room and we kept doing scenes whenever
he felt like it off of information from the audience.
It was just beautifully fluid.
This is great.
I loved us.
Yeah.
And so after we did a couple of scenes, he's like, I'm going to look for the most stoic,
least involved person in the room.
Right?
At that moment.
Did you already know who it was going to be?
Well, yes, I did.
And then, and then he pointed to a woman and he goes, and that was going to be you, but
then you just laughed at what I just said.
So it's not you.
And then he just goes, but you, you, you've, you've had no, no smile the whole time.
And he points to him.
You haven't looked up.
Well, and then the answer is ask him questions like you went to high school, tell me something
weird about your high school or whatever.
And he, and the guy goes, I went to high school where we had to wear school uniforms.
But when we, uh, joined the swim team, the first day we all had, we just swam naked.
We were all naked in our, for our swim team.
All right.
They made all the boys swim naked for P.E.
Yeah.
Well, that's just going to increase drag.
It's true.
That's, that's not even good swimming practice.
Yeah.
That high school had the worst swim times of the state.
And so, uh, but, but the thing was like, as soon as it was about him, he was fucking eating
it up.
Like he was loving talking.
Oh, I gotcha.
Yeah.
And I.
Oh, is that what he wanted from the magic?
Did he want to be a helper for, for one of the tricks in the magic show?
Maybe I looked out.
I asked, I mean, you know, I use a lot of audience volunteers.
He didn't know.
Yeah.
Sure.
Volunteer himself.
But, uh, but I was like, this guy is like basic 20% of my cruise ship, uh, people.
Guys a little older than me have a couple of drinks are like, I'm pretty awesome.
Why don't, why don't you use me more?
You know?
I am great.
So we did, we did bits with him or whatever.
And so, you know, at this point I'm like, fine.
I'm done with the amount of attention he has.
He is.
Yeah.
We're, we're done.
But Kurt goes up in a standup and, uh, in it, he, he, uh, sets up a joke about how terrible
his dad is by putting them in the same category as Trump and like Pol Pot or something like
that.
Okay.
And then, uh, uh, that's, we actually identified maybe one of the issues why he wasn't having
the best time.
Oh, cause he's a big Pol Pot fan.
He's huge.
Pol Pot.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
He is wearing a Pol Pot 2028 shirt.
Yeah.
I should have noticed that.
And Kurt had a dead canvas shirt on.
So it was automatically like, ah, that.
And then he did a bit making fun of Black Rifle Coffee.
And he was like, he was like, good, cause we really need to know the politics of every
product that we have.
I'm glad coffee is finally letting people know that they're pro-gun.
He read this hilarious email that he wrote to the Black Rifle Coffee Company and just
at, you know, in this very, he actually, Kurt posed for the cover of one of Mike Sack's
recent books, uh, called Passing on the Right.
Have you seen that?
No.
So Kurt worked with Mike Sacks on this book, Passing on the Right, and I think Kurt did
the audio book for it.
Uh, and it's this very, uh, you know, like, uh, faux infiltration of the very right wing
media sphere, but, but that's kind of what, the way Kurt wrote this, this, uh, he wrote
a letter as someone who is a fan of the politics of Black Rifle Coffee and saying they aren't
taking it far enough.
Yeah.
That's the premise of the thing.
But he read the actual email.
He sent Black Rifle Coffee.
Black Rifle Coffee had a mocha flavor and he was like, Matt, a mocha flavor.
There's a, there's a, yeah, there's a, there's a copy that has Kurt on the cover, uh, if
you look it up, but there's a version that has Kurt on the cover, um, uh, and Mike Sacks.
In the middle of this letter, our friend, uh, decided it was time to go and he left.
Oh, was that when he left?
Yeah.
Oh, hilarious.
Hilarious.
That's enough for me.
Okay.
Perfect.
He might've been a stockholder of the coffee company, I think, or whatever.
Yeah.
That was Ted Rifle.
He couldn't stand being the rifle butt of the joke.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, so, uh, Kurt was awesomely unapologetic about it.
He was like, "Did that guy walk?"
And we're like, "If he thinks so," he's like, "Okay."
If I had known, I'd have been like, "Thank you.
Thank you, Kurt."
No, totally.
Because literally, I'm, you know, I'm writing this because the podcast is just, it's fun
to focus on this guy, but there's a very small part of everyone else was just eating up fucking
everything we were doing.
I mean, here's the, here's the other part, of course, we had a very nice contingence
of scoops.
Yeah.
And scoops always elevate every fucking event.
It was the thing of, I've been doing some improv now again, uh, in PA, and it was just
so lovely to step on stage, throw out a line, and get hit with a round of laughter.
Just like, boom.
I'm like, "Oh, yeah, I'm here with friends and support.
This is, this is going to be great."
Yeah.
You know?
It was really, really lovely.
Which made it even worse later when he thought Matt had died.
It did make it worse when I thought he had died.
I was like, "Oh, fuck."
And all these scoops, I was like, "Oh, it's going so well."
Oh, yeah.
Exactly.
Everything's going.
Everything's starting to work.
Wait.
Oh, well, at least I got to see him one last time.
I'm telling you, man, I went from zero to a bajillion in like eight seconds.
Yes, you did.
It did.
But, but what would you, what would your assumption be?
You're in a hotel.
You haven't heard from your, you haven't heard from him.
You can't text him.
You can't call him.
And he doesn't respond to a knock on the door.
And if I-
Paul, this has happened to me.
This exact thing has happened to me traveling with Matt Donnelly.
I don't have to tell you what would have come into my mind.
I can tell you what came into my mind.
Oh, shit.
My assumption was, Matt is sleeping through this.
Okay.
Well, that will be my default assumption from now on.
Raptured.
It finally took today of all days.
Oh, that guy was only off by a couple of weeks.
If I had slept five more minutes and I would have been woken up by a wellness check, that
would have been a very bizarre start to my day.
I am so mad that the hotel did not come.
Yeah.
He got me before I got to the front desk.
That's all.
Oh, I'm so mad about that.
Because I've done everything in my power.
I was like, text.
Call.
Call again.
Knock on door loudly.
Knock on door loudly twice.
Matt's dead.
That was it.
No other possibilities.
Matt has died.
My friend and business partner has passed away unexpectedly.
I'll tell you who else was more concerned than you would have imagined about Matt's
death.
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is, by the way, when we come back for the break, I had the voicemail Paul
left for me.
So I'll play it.
Oh, good.
Good.
I feel like I'm so stressed.
Today's show is brought to you by Sand.
That's right.
It's from Clever Scoop name from 2021.
The product is sand.
Hey, motherfucker, why don't you pound me?
Pound sand.
That's right.
Yeah.
Pound sand.
Sand in one hand and shit in the other.
See what fills up first.
Sand, you are pretty feisty.
I thought we were going to get like a fine product here and I don't know if I should
even give you any money.
I'm going to silica slap your ass.
You know what?
I become with enough heat.
What's that glass?
Okay.
Should I put that in one hand instead of shit?
I'm just telling you to see through my message.
Okay.
Is it clear?
Clear.
Is it painting you?
Yes.
Sand.
Enter Hey Scoops, check out grit.
That ad spot was granular.
It was granular.
I got down to the nitty gritty.
Oh God.
Here we go.
All right.
So while he's finding that, I also texted Ann and while I'm texting Ann, I will tell
you what else was going through my head texting Ann.
I was like, because all Ann and I do in case you didn't know is the small times we get
when we're sitting together and watching TV, I try to make it about what she would like
to watch because I get to sit and watch TV a lot more time than she does.
And what does she like to watch?
True crime murder mystery shit.
And so as I'm composing this text to my wife, I'm like, does this sound right?
And could this come back to bite me in the ass as I killed Matt?
So here's what I wrote.
I wrote, okay, I'm a little worried.
Matt and I were supposed to meet up at 10.
I've texted and called, no response yet.
Hopefully he's in the shower.
And to me, I was like, okay, I think that covers my basis.
But in my back of my head, I'm like, that could still be me just setting it up that
I've killed him in the shower or wherever.
Especially since you were actively trying to establish an alibi at this moment.
Hello.
And my wife, note the time I'm texting you.
Exactly.
That's it.
I was like, oh man.
Hey Ann, I just wanted to text you and let you know that the last time I saw Matt Donnelly,
he was perfectly happy and healthy.
No reason.
I really replayed the last moment of our last exchange where I told him not to get the
Doritos from the vending machine cause they were stale and he laughed.
And that was it.
And I was like, is that going to be the last thing I ever said to Matt?
He could have choked on a Dorito on a stale Dorito.
I warned him against them.
I begged him not to eat those stale Doritos.
I did everything I could.
I did everything I could outside of not lending him $5 to go to the vending machine.
No, tell them what your vending machine selection actually was.
Oh man.
They had cans of you.
He chugged a you-hoo at midnight and then was like, Oh, I'm not getting the best sleep
tonight.
What the fuck?
I woke up at 7 a.m. with a huge fucking raging heartburn issue.
I ate like a thousand tums.
He tumbled himself back to sleep into a tongue coma and then I'm left here dealing with the
dentist and trying to put my life back together like how many partners did I have to adopt
his children.
Here we go.
He's playing it.
Hey dude, it's 1030.
Just trying to get a hold of you.
Hopefully you're just taking a shower or whatever.
I'm in my room.
Give me a shower.
Bye.
That doesn't sound like a concerned person at all.
He's not, I'm trying to sound as authentic as I can and not be pieces of your murder.
He's establishing his alibi, Matt.
That totally sounds much more of an alibi establishing voicemail than a voicemail by
anyone concerned.
That's what I did.
There is no concern outside of Paul going to prison in that voicemail.
The other side of that is, Oh man, I hope you're okay.
And that reads of, I know you're dead because I killed you because I've watched all these
shows and that's what they are.
It's all these guys calling them over there, I don't know what happened to my wife.
I just came home and there's blood everywhere.
This is a fucking Karen Reed reverse logic shit happening right here.
I am.
I have reverse logic myself into the place where I had to be.
That was me being nonchalant.
That was you with the prosecutor going, does this sound like a man concerned for his friend
who doesn't know his whereabouts?
Sure.
Hope everything's all right there, pal.
Hope you're just in the shower and just taking a little extra time with yourself this morning.
Yeah, I know we're supposed to get together at 10, but hey, it's 10.30.
You do what you want to do.
And I hang up and I'm like, Dear God, they know, they know.
I'm like, fucking, what's his name in the bathroom?
Oh, the burping, they know.
But that's the fucked up thing.
I didn't kill him.
As you can see, I didn't actually have anything to do with his not death and yet the Catholic
guilt in me puts me already into the place of on death row.
I am already.
And if you had murdered, if you had been blamed for the murder of New Jersey's favorite son,
who knows?
That's right.
Some of the chat scooping over girl wants to know if it's actually me, an imposter
Paul has founded up here and that's going to put me on the show.
That's right.
We're only seeing Matt digitally.
Paul just because I have Sora.
This could be just an elaborate AI thing.
Paul is weirdly better at AI than any of us would have guessed.
Jeff Loomis has taken the voicemail should have been, hey dipshit, did you oversleep?
I've been waiting for an hour for your lazy ass.
It's my alibi voicemail.
To be fair, it only been a half an hour and I, I try to be, I try to be really, I don't
know.
I try.
I'm just caught in this shit.
I'm trying not to be mean.
I'm trying not to be.
I, yeah.
You know?
Yeah.
All, all, you know, all, all bits aside, I feel terrible that I scared the shit out of
Paul.
I feel terrible.
I feel really bad about it.
Not me.
I mean, it made for good.
I'm very happy about it.
And I definitely, that's absolutely my second thought.
One is I felt horrible that I scared Paul like that.
And then the second was like, well, we know what's kicking off the pot.
Podcasted birdies.
Winter scoop podcasted birdies.
Ah, Jesus.
Oh shit.
So yeah.
Don't want the angry mess to play an open court.
That's exactly right.
You know what I mean?
Where the fuck are you, man?
I just killed you.
I mean, I just saw you like five seconds ago and I'm like, I don't even know what's going
on.
I just killed you.
I mean, I just killed you.
I mean, I just saw you like five seconds ago after the bullshit from last night.
You're going to fucking bullshit me again today.
Fuck you.
After the nonsense you pulled yesterday, you're going to pull this now?
You son of a bitch.
Shit.
Oh man.
No, other than that, I got to show Paul all around Newark on the way to the show.
It was a cavalcade of Matt's old haunts and places that he hung out.
I did get to point out the stuff.
We drove past the Starbucks I worked at where I did all my bits.
I learned where the origin of the clackity clack crab man came from.
And also, Pat, who happened to improvise with us, when we were driving in, we went past
the bowling lane.
And he goes, "Hey, that bowling lane," or not Pat, Doug, we were driving past the bowling
lane, Matt goes, "Oh, that bowling lane we used to go to a lot and one time my friend
Doug wore some shitty shoes to the bowling lane, rented out the shoes and just kept the
rented bowling shoes."
He didn't go back for his sneakers.
He just kept the bowling shoes and left.
He left his sneakers.
And then we met the guy who actually did it and he's like, "I think there's two of those."
So that was pretty funny.
I definitely still have the pair of bowling shoes that I stole from a bowling alley in
college.
There you go.
One of our bartenders was Grace Tierney.
Whoa.
Yes.
Well, the real reason everyone was there.
Lineage.
No.
He was like, "I used to watch you clean ashtrays when you were eight years old and now you're
old enough."
Which is the job that all eight-year-olds should be doing, starting to run the joint.
She is indeed.
She is the inheritor of the crown.
She is slowly and surely running Tierney's Tavern and was the bartender for our event
and that made me feel old as hell, but also pretty awesome.
Billy Tierney came out.
It was so great to see Billy again and his wife as well.
They had a great time and just so nice.
I mean, Tierney's ... And I had a fucking burger right from the jump.
We all got fucking ...
Can't smash burger, baby.
Can't smash burger.
We all got can't smashed.
God damn.
It was a good hamburger.
It was a good burger.
God damn.
It was good.
It was the first thing I'd eaten all day and it was just really fucking good.
Really good.
Ugh.
Yeah.
Other people sat down.
They were like, "What are you looking at?
You're getting a bacon cheeseburger.
I don't know what you're ... "
Yeah.
Bacon cheeseburger.
That was it.
We ordered like six of them.
Boom.
They were all perfect.
Ugh.
So good.
So fun.
Do they still use the same can?
Yeah, which is unfortunate.
Yeah.
That is disgusting.
It is an awful ...
It's the same nasty old can of green beans that smashes the burgers.
It is long expired.
Yeah.
It's funny.
It is funny that I make burgers for my boys at home now because they now are old enough
that they appreciate a better burger.
So I do it.
I make a proper hand patty for them and it is funny.
It involves me scouring our kitchen for the largest can I can find that I'm like, "Wait.
I got a can smash it.
How do I do this?"
You don't just have a smasher?
I don't.
I should have a smasher.
Yeah.
What products ... What do I search for on Amazon to get a smasher?
Smash burger smasher.
I don't know.
I have one.
I'll send you a link.
Smash burger smasher, I think.
Yeah.
I think so.
But it is a key.
It is key to how the burger cooks.
You want the core more tightly knit than the outside of the burger.
Mm-hmm.
But ...
Oh, yeah.
There was ... There's something about ... That place just warms my heart.
The whole place, yeah, it just feels good.
Climbing up the stairs felt like my grandma's place.
The smells.
Yes.
A little musty.
Yeah, yeah.
It's kind of great.
Yeah.
It's not dirty.
It's just lived in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's fucking great.
The place is just awesome.
It's just casual.
Oh, yes.
It was just like ... Yeah.
They came up.
We all just started putting the stools down.
We all put the chairs where we wanted.
Yeah.
That's great.
The chairs, everybody helping out, cleaning up when we're done.
It was super fun.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How many of the guest improvisers came in that really got obsessed with the chair placement
for the audience and really spent a very long time sorting all those chairs out?
No.
None.
Oh, weird.
Weird.
Yeah, yeah.
No, no.
It was great, man.
It was funny.
Because he and I just did the Improv Jam reunion last weekend together.
Oh, right.
Sure.
Yeah.
So we were 16, 17, 6, 7, and it was funny because Pat and I left that show and we became
long form people, right?
Yes.
So Pat was just like, after the show, was like, "God, that was so much more fun to do
the long form man and then play and then do moving bodies and a couple of space jumps
and everything else."
Oh, right.
He was more in heaven than ever.
He had some really great moves too.
He was really solid.
Oh, he was.
And Pat's still, there's a legendary group called the Baldwin's that still perform at
the pit.
He's still out there doing it.
And he still goes into the city for that show, and they've been together forever.
Well, you can tell he's got the chops.
Yeah.
He wasn't rusty at all.
Nobody felt rusty at all.
It was great.
No, it was really, really fun.
Really fun.
Jeff Loomis in the chat wants to know, "What is the secret to keeping it a cool hang and
repelling the angry, trouble-making drunks?"
I think it's the second floor.
Well, the second floor was certainly helped for our gathering because Kurt made the observation
when he came in the door at 745, people were just yelling at each other.
Downstairs.
Yeah.
You guys have like an angry conversation.
And he said, "Fuck you, and fuck everyone you know."
Or something like that.
You see, second floor is where it's at.
Second floor is where it is.
Kurt was just like, "Ternies goes hard.
It is 745.
You guys are already way into your cups.
This is shit."
Just mad.
I would say, honestly, the stairs together upstairs are steep and creaky.
Yeah.
Like there's a banister, but the banister's almost at your knee.
The banister's almost at your knee.
Yeah.
Like you can't quite use the banister.
I remember that banister.
That banister is the most likely thing to cause a fall in that building, is that banister
on those stairs.
Well, it's definitely a drunk repellent.
That's for sure.
Yeah.
So I think a drunk tries to go upstairs, like, "What's going on?"
And like halfway he goes like, "This is a mistake.
I might not return."
And they turned around.
I can't go any further.
But I told you when I was a part time there, it is literally the town's tavern.
So like you can't get 86th there because someone from your family will tell you to meet you
there in a few months.
And so you can't be like, "Sorry, dad, I've been 86th from Tierney's."
Like that can't happen.
No, no, no.
On the other side of it, you don't want to show your ass in front of the whole community.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it.
I was going to say it's self-policing a little bit.
And yeah.
And I feel like Tierney's also knows that if they start 86ing everybody who acts like
an asshole, that's just not going to work either.
And also, I guess another thing is it's a fancy town.
I think if it was a town tavern in a dump, I think there'd be maybe like more problems.
But it is really, really Tierney's is a blight on the otherwise really pinkies out fancy
pants town that Montclair is.
We made a turn down one street.
Hold on.
I've got Billy Tierney on the line.
He just wanted me to write that down for the billboard.
Tierney's is a blight on the otherwise fancy town.
No, but we made a turn and we took this road and all of a sudden this street was multi-million
dollar mansions with Halloween decorations.
You know those giant skeletons, Jacob?
Oh yeah, like the Home Depot huge ones.
Yeah.
This house had two of them plus one coming out of the ground, two giant skeletons.
Highfalutin.
The giant house is also on giant properties.
Yeah.
And the houses were so big, the giant skeletons didn't look that big.
I was like, not only...
The nice thing about those houses is they're surprisingly affordable.
Any of us could buy any of those houses at any moment.
No, I really...
I don't think we can afford the landscaping.
No.
That's true.
It was insane.
I was just looking at these giant properties and I was like, "Man, just what they charged
to mow the lawn here must be astronomical."
I was just...
I was flabbergasted.
Good God, we drove by billions of dollars worth of real estate.
Billions of dollars worth of real estate.
That was the strangest thing, right, because Tierney's is just on the edge of town.
Yeah, and then Tierney's ain't far from that, yeah.
And then Montclair State's up the ways.
And to me, even when I went to college there, it was so strange that you went from Montclair
State past this beautiful giant houses that are jaw-dropping to get to town.
And you're like, "It's so strange that the university's on the high side of the Ritzy
area, usually the university's on the edge of the downtown or dark side of town, right?"
Yeah.
Whatever.
But so, yeah, that's also part of the equation.
Is that one of those things?
I wonder if it's one of those things where somebody who had some property left it to
the university or something like that.
Yeah.
Scoop and Overgirl says, "McMansions."
No, these were not McMansions.
These are old houses.
These are regular mansions.
And they're all unique in their architecture.
Exactly.
They're not so...
That's great.
Yeah, that's really great.
No, no, no, no.
You go by a Tudor to a mid-century modern and just huge.
And probably, I would say, 80% of them 40-plus years old, maybe more.
This is an old...
It was old.
Probably, yeah.
Yeah.
Probably 40, 50 years old, most of them.
So it was not a McMansion-type situation.
Speaking of 12-foot skeletons, when I came home from my three weeks on the road, my children
and my wife had decorated our house for Halloween.
Ah!
Good.
And we have a zip line on our little driveway.
Of course.
We always, the second year in a row, we strap a skeleton, like a six-foot skeleton, to the
zip line, as if he's zip lining.
Perfect.
But I pulled in, and there was a 12-foot giant skeleton taking up basically our entire front
yard.
Did Sarah get the skeleton?
Yes.
And I laughed.
And I said...
They basically warned me, like, "When you get home, you'll notice a new Halloween decoration."
And I came in, and I was like, "What the hell is going on?"
And Sarah was like, "Ah, you know, they're never available.
People usually buy the skeletons, you know, right off the jump."
But I went online, and I saw that there were skeletons available, and I thought, "I'll
get one."
And I thought I clicked the 7-foot one, but I guess I clicked the 12-foot one.
And she's like, "And then, like, when we're putting it together, I'm putting it together
with the two kids, and like the instructions say specifically, you need two adults to put
this together."
So she went across the street...
That doesn't...
One adult and two kids.
That's fine.
Just put a trench coat on.
Yeah, yeah.
That's close enough.
Now you're two kids as one adult in a trench coat.
And I laughed, and she told me the whole story of trying to put it together and getting a
neighbor to help, and how she didn't mean to get a 12-foot skeleton, and how just they
tell you not to throw out the box, because that's how you need to put it away in the
box, is actually taking it...
It's literally sitting on top of all of my magic stuff like a hat in my garage.
It's just a giant box.
It's a hat on top of my stuff in the garage.
This is the best thing that's ever happened to you, Matt.
I laughed so hard.
This skeleton.
Yes.
Because I said...
This is the best thing that's ever happened to you.
Yes.
Go.
I said, "If you wrote down every detail of the story and how it progressed and how it
happened and the twists and turns, you would bet 100% that this is my story and Sarah's
coming home mad."
Right?
Yep.
I was like, "Every word coming out of your mouth is my words.
This is absolutely something that I would do."
I am hearing you tell this story, and I'm still not entirely sure that you didn't buy
this skeleton.
No.
Right?
It just sounds like...
It reeks of me.
Yeah.
Every detail of it.
Even the skeleton...
Guess what?
It was late because it overslept.
No.
This is the greatest thing that's ever happened to Matt and Natalie.
So I was giddy.
I was like, "I love all of it."
I love that I can't get to my magic stuff because of the box.
I love every piece of it.
I don't care.
I love that something that Sarah bought is in the way in the garage now.
This is great.
Because I thought I was going to get shit...
Because I did go overboard.
I bought...
Do you get targeted on social media for those things that cover your garage door, like a
spooky...
Oh, yes.
Ooh.
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't gotten targeted for those.
So I bought two of those because I got one for the small garage door and one for the
big garage door.
Okay.
So it was an complimentary and whatever.
And then once Sarah had that 12 foot skeleton, I was like, "Hey, guess what, everybody?
Let's get the shit up on the garage door."
I was going to yell that.
There's not a single way I'm going to get in trouble for these garage door things now.
No way.
Let's go.
And so now...
How do they look?
Do they work out?
Oh.
So now this year's trick and treat is going to crush.
We have our 12 foot skeleton.
We have our zip lining skeleton.
We have...
Got your levitator.
We got...
I'm going to be levitating kids.
Yeah.
I got this magical duck where you bob the head and it picks your card out of a batch
of cards.
Holy smokes.
Right?
I'm going to be surprised at the people...
Surprised at the shit out of people with that clown, with that creepy clown that Ryan built
for me.
Oh, yeah.
That thing's crazy.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, good.
Yeah.
No, we're ready.
We are ready.
Yeah.
I'm jealous.
Also, you know exactly how much room the things that you bought are going to take up in storage
for the rest of the year.
And you know how much room the thing that Sarah bought is going to take up in storage for
the rest of the year.
Yeah.
And Matt's life is going to be good this year.
That's really 90% of why we don't have a giant skeleton, because Ann's like, "Where are we
going to store it?"
Yeah.
And she's right.
But I do try to make the argument that we could just keep it outside like people do
and decorate it all year.
The Autobot Society will frown on that.
Well, Ann's been showing off the pictures of the new house, right?
Yeah.
And at the front in the planner box, I've got all my dog skeletons set up with one little
pumpkin, and that's been getting lots of compliments.
But also, to a man, people love the color of the garage door.
They love it.
They love the pop of color of the garage door.
It's a little brighter.
What is the new garage door color?
It's a wood type color, but it's got the slightest hint of red inside of it.
You know what I mean?
All right.
Mahogany.
Yeah.
It's a bright wood color.
It's a little lighter than what the designer had set for her when she was picking out colors.
It's the color that she asked for, because she picked the Sherman Williams color that
the designer sent for, but it just comes off a little brighter, and it really makes the
house look great.
It really does.
I think it's awesome.
She's coming around to it more and more.
At first, she was like, "Oh, no, it's too bright," but it's...
Oh, that is nice.
It's not.
It's really nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just found Ann's social media here.
The house looks great.
Yeah, it looks fantastic.
It's such a cry from where it was.
As Ranch Slunk asks, "Wait, Autobot Society?"
And that's it.
If you get a skeleton that can just turn into a motorcycle, then you can get in the higher
rankings of the Autobot Society.
Oh, hey.
I don't know if you guys are aware.
Probably not.
Fantastic news on the Autobot front.
Oh.
Wait, do you want to tell them or do you want me to tell them?
I'll tell them.
Okay.
So you guys are...
Wait, no, this was in my note to talk about later.
Oh, fine.
We'll skip ahead.
We have one, Mr. Robert Kirkman.
Yes?
Yes.
So, creator of The Walking Dead and the comic and also creator of Invincible.
Okay.
So, Invincible, you may well know as a very successful Prime series on the old Amazon.
Yeah, Kirkman has just locked down a deal that's in production now.
He's got three comic book series that are out right now.
New run of GI Joe, new run of Transformers, and this series called Void Rivals, which
sort of incorporates a lot of the stuff.
It's all Hasbro toy properties mushed into.
So they're putting out a cartoon series with those three properties, so it's going to have
Transformers and GI Joe.
So even though they couldn't really get it going in the movies yet, Kirkman is going
to do it in an animated style, and it's going to have a more adult slant.
So I'm really excited.
It's going to have like more of a-
Like they'll fuck the shit out of each other.
Yeah.
I did Costco myself again the other day.
What'd you do?
So I remember the story when I thought I was buying like a bag of chicken nuggets, but
then in the cart you see a big Costco, you're like, "I just bought a regular bag of chicken
nuggets."
You get home and you're like, "Oh, this is gigantic.
This is actually two and a half bags of chicken nuggets, and I cannot fit it in my freezer."
And so I had to buy Halloween candies, of course we were at a Costco for Halloween candy.
And we're doing not only trick and treat in my neighborhood, popular neighborhood, and
also we have a trunk and treat this year, trunk or treat at the school, kids' school.
Ah, great.
And so my mom was like, "We should sign us up for that."
I said, "Okay."
So we got to get enough Halloween candy for- It's a lot.
For us.
What was your peace campaign?
I was just going to buy bags, so Paul already asked a very intimidating question, right?
Well, I mean, we get around 300 trick or treaters, so I got around 300 pieces of candy.
I ended up with closer to 400 just to be safe, and I'm asking my sister-in-law to bring another
bag just in case, because some of them little motherfuckers are greedy.
Yeah, they do the bit the claw.
Yeah.
Well, let me tell you something.
The claw is welcome this year at the Donnelly household, I'll tell you that much right now.
Everyone can claw it.
Oh shit.
So I literally- And also if anyone would like to store a 12-foot skeleton, please inquire
with it.
So I go in, and Costco really simplified things this year.
There's normally, they have a bunch of varieties and you try to figure out, you can get the
big bars, you can get the little pieces, whatever, they just had two variety packs.
They had favorites and a thing called goodies, and the goodies were the more fruit-flavored
stuff, like Twizzlers and Skittles and that kind of stuff.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
And then the other were favorites, which is-
Chocolate?
Yeah.
Reese's Peanut Butter Cups and that kind of stuff.
Almond Joy is in there, which is no one's favorites, and Twix, Snickers, the whole Milky
Way, the whole bit.
And so- The superior candy bars to Almond Joy.
I have my giant Costco cart, and so I grab six bags of the favorites and four bags of
the goodies.
Holy fuck.
So I'm figuring three and two for Halloween and three and two for the-
Okay.
For the Trunk or Treat.
Holy shit.
And then I go like, "That's not enough."
Oh no!
And so I grab two more bags of the favorites, two more bags of the goodies, and then I got
like allergen-friendly Mott's Apple Packs for people who hate themselves but still go
trick or treating.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I mean, that would be unsafe for a peanut allergy person to go trick or treating, right?
And I knew I made a mistake when I was going to check out and the guy goes, "Oh, I'm going
to your house for Halloween."
And I was like, "I don't think I should- I thought I was- I should look like I have more
than the average amount of candy that someone might purchase for Halloween."
Well, you know, if it's two events, then it looks double.
Yeah.
Technically, it's double.
Which would make anybody go, "Holy shit, you got double the Halloween candy."
And then Costco, I bring it up and they told me the price and I was like, "Geez, how much-
what?"
And then I still was like, "Ah, fuck it."
I bought- I was like, "$300 worth of Halloween candy."
Jesus fuck!
Yeah.
Halloween candy is incredibly expensive this year.
And I was like-
I got a deal on Target's website with a BOGO.
Yeah.
So, you know, besides my 15% off, it made it affordable, but still very expensive.
Because I usually get six or seven bags from the supermarket.
Yeah.
And it's crazy money at the supermarket.
Right.
And so I thought, "I'll save money," but then when I'm home with the prices, I'm like, "This
doesn't feel like it's saving money."
And then I got home and I started to unpack and I was like, "Nope, I get it now."
And they're probably bigger-
Where I stored the Halloween candy last year, I couldn't fit it all in where I stored it
last year.
Wow.
I'm stacking it up on the top shelf.
They're bigger bags, too, because they're Costco bags, right?
Each bag was five pounds.
I didn't read until I got home.
What was your price count at the end of the day?
So how many pounds of candy?
Yeah.
I bought 60 pounds of candy?
Okay.
That's a lot.
That's a small child.
Just to say, we do these episodes on Twitch and I'm looking at all of the reeling faces
and the ... Yeah, I now have a metric going forward to measure future purchases.
Good.
60.
Too much.
Well, it's 30 pounds each, 30 pounds on Halloween, 30 pounds on Trunk or Treat.
This Trunk or Treat, if I end up just having only 12 kids come to the trunk, I'm going
to be furious.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I got a text from my oldest before I went to school, he was like, "Hey, there's a cross-country
final meetup today.
Can I bring some candy to the knees?"
Please.
"Yes, son.
Help yourself."
Take it.
Take a whole bag.
"Final means, please."
Grab a bag.
In fact- Paul, how many pieces of candy did you say you had?
I estimated, like I said, we get about 300 people, so I estimated to get close to 400
on my own, and I'm hoping my sister-in-law brings another 100, so around 500 pieces.
So about 500 pieces, all right, and you got two people working on getting 500 pieces.
That's good.
I've just done a little bit of quick math here.
According to Google, one small chocolate bar weighs about 10 grams, and so Matt has gotten
approximately 2,721 and a half pieces of candy.
Okay.
So that's four times what I have.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
So you may have gone a little overboard.
Here's the great thing about it.
I want to squeak.
I have a very popular neighborhood.
Same with me.
You do.
That is true.
You do have a very popular trick-or-treating neighborhood.
But last year, what I believe probably was maybe 14 pounds of candy, now that I'm looking
back, I bet the bags I bought from the supermarket were two pounds and not five.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe even three.
There was this thing where a guy drove up with a truck, and the kids were hanging off
the truck, and they're doing the later rounds of Halloween, and he ran up to our house.
We were cleaning up.
They're getting it there.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, just take it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And they were just filling their bags with it.
Yeah.
And that happened last year, too.
My oldest saw that.
He was upset.
And I literally, I said, "Don't worry about it."
And I walked into the garage, and I grabbed the last bag of candy, just opened it, put
it back in the bucket.
I was like, "We're fine."
Yeah.
Everything is okay.
So now, I hope that truck comes by like three or four times, I think.
No.
You're going to have it pre-bagged for them.
The dark reality is, Matt, you should give that all to a food bank at the end of the
day.
What if there's leftover?
Oh, that's a good idea.
That's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll do that.
Do they want it?
I am so happy right now.
Here's the thing.
This is the first time that I've ever been happy that we don't have a churn, because
every Halloween, Matt brings all the leftover candy into the churn.
That's true.
It happens.
There's not a churn right now.
That's right.
And this is, honestly, I think that should be a national move is extra candy goes to
the food banks, because people don't ... That's one of those things.
People talk shit on like, "Oh, what are you doing, person who can't afford food, buying
candy?
Fuck you."
No.
Everybody likes fucking candy.
Give some candy.
Let the kids have some candy.
Let the adults have some candy.
Fuck it.
Just because it's a food bank doesn't mean it has to all be pasta and beans.
Candy.
Go for it.
Yeah, yeah.
How much would you love going to get some name-brand candy from a food bank if you're
hard up?
Yeah.
What would that be?
AI is also mentioning Ronald McDonald houses and things like that.
There you go.
All right.
I don't trust AI, but okay.
I asked AI, "What are good places to donate leftover Halloween candy to?"
Oh, and it said, "The collective consciousness of the computer brain."
And then the second suggestion was Ronald McDonald houses.
They said, "You drive the houses of copywriters, of illustrators, everybody losing their jobs
to me.
You should go bring them a bag of candy."
Exactly.
Real artists.
They can get cheered up.
Yeah, I'm going to need a list of like 10 places.
Sneaking into Home Depot's and throwing candy into the dumpsters.
Exactly.
That is so much candy.
We've still got a little bit of Halloween candy from last Halloween.
Yeah.
I think the record number of trick-or-treaters that we've had at our house in the years that
we've lived here has been three.
I think the most we've ever had in a single Halloween night has been three.
Yeah.
So we don't purchase Halloween candy.
We just give them whatever is around that we give to them.
That sounds good.
We just become the weird house.
Sometimes we get a couple of candy bars.
A slice of Little Caesars.
Yeah.
Sometimes.
A slice of Little Caesars.
Well, that's what- Here's a sandwich.
My sister-in-law, she'd been living in a very rural area for a long time.
They got no trick-or-treaters.
A scuba nova girl, I definitely give mini bottles of booze to any adults that come by
the house.
I absolutely do that.
That makes their night, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Well, that's a good idea.
She's coming after this.
What we got is we got some individually wrapped doggie sticks because some people do come
by with their puppies.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah.
So we're going to give out- That's a good idea.
The first 12 dogs will get a delicious chicken stick from our house.
We tried to find individually wrapped stuff, but they were sold out everywhere, but we
got these little chicken sticks that were individually wrapped, and that was good.
I said, "Let's just get 12 of these."
They were like 20 cents a piece, something like that, and I was like, "You think that's
enough?"
I said, "That's six dogs an hour."
If we get more than six dogs an hour, something's weird with the timeline.
I also did buy two fresh Transant gay rights flags to tape up my sign this year.
Nice.
Oh, that'll be good.
That'll be good.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get those freshened back up just because-
Are you going to give away the old flags?
They get weathered pretty quickly.
We go through them, just the way Vegas weather is and how cheap those little tiny flags are.
Oh, yeah.
They get weathered pretty quickly, so I have to replace them pretty often, but I'm making
sure to make it nice and fresh and bright for Halloween.
Hell yeah.
When people are coming by, that'll be good.
I should get some chalk and do a Day of the Dead skull on my driveway.
That would be really cool.
I almost got roped in this year, and I held off because I get targeted for those custom
rollout, bright carpets where you can roll out a carpet that looks like it's a hole with
skeletons crawling out of it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, right.
Uh-huh.
Next year.
Like a vortex you could fall into?
Yes.
When you're walking, it looks like you might fall into a hole.
Cool.
Yeah.
That's going to be next year.
That's the whole thing.
Every year I try and add on.
This year, I've got my shysty mask last year that goes under my skull face, so you can't
see anything but skull face.
Yeah.
What is a shysty mask?
A shysty mask, it just grips your face.
A lot of times it's got a face print on it that's really freaky.
Look up some shysty masks.
Those creep you out, but you can't see anything.
It totally blacks out everything except for you just only see the outside mask.
And then I got some black gloves this year, so my hands will be under black gloves.
And then I got those extendy fingers.
Oh, a shysty mask is like a baklava or a bala, how do you say that fucking?
Balaklava.
That's it.
Not a baklava.
That's a food.
I actually freak kids out by wearing baklava on my face.
I just cover, I take Greek dessert and shove my face into it.
Yeah, Tim skimpets the same mask this year, but now I've got skeletal fingers as well.
Yeah.
Every year just add a little something.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Speaking of adding something, it's time for Jack vs. Nerd.
So it is.
We're going to add to your loss total.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time!
Time for Jack vs. Nerd!
Explosion.
Too much candy.
Bleh.
Never enough.
So much candy.
We've got an Obelisk Jock vs. Nerd coming to us today from M.L. Kennedy.
$200 all the way up to $5,000.
We've got double downs.
We've got steals.
We've got super steals where we steal each other's points.
And we've got 50/50 to make the answers a little bit easier for us.
The category is, "Oh Canada?"
Paul, you're up first.
Okay, let's see.
Which of the following SCTV actors was born in Canada?
Joe Flaherty, Andrea Martin, Catherine O'Hara, Harold Ramis.
Just a reminder, you have a 50/50 you can use, Paul.
I'm going to go see Catherine O'Hara.
Catherine O'Hara is correct!
Boom!
Stages control the board.
I thought Joe Flaherty was too.
I know.
I thought Joe Flaherty was also.
That was the only other one I thought was a little iffy, but I somehow remembered it
was Catherine O'Hara.
So there you go.
Paul, you're up!
What's the question?
Oh, wait, I'm forgetting what game we're playing.
Oh, that guy.
Here's Paul's question.
Help!
Actor Kevin McKidd from Trainspotting and Dog Soldiers can't escape from Grey's Anatomy.
How many episodes is he currently credited with on IMDB?
Oh, for fart love hell.
181, 254, 336, or 368.
Oh, boy.
Paul, you were just talking about this.
Yeah.
He loves counting episodes.
This is right up his alley.
I feel like it's between A and B.
Okay.
That's 181 or 254.
Is Grey's Anatomy still happening?
It probably is.
Shit.
Matt, is Grey's Anatomy still happening?
Oh, yes.
Is it?
Yeah.
Okay, B.
254 is incorrect.
It's 368.
Oh, wow.
That's a lot of residuals.
368.
That really is.
That's money.
Matt, that goes to you.
The $600 question, Mr. Ed.
Anybody want to steal?
Anybody want to do anything?
No?
Here we go.
That Talking Horse Show had numerous episodes wherein celebrities met Mr. Ed.
Which of the following is not a real episode of the series?
Okay.
Clint Eastwood meets Mr. Ed.
Mae West meets Mr. Ed.
George Burns meets Mr. Ed.
Or Charles Bronson meets Mr. Ed.
My instinct first was like George Burns because I feel like he's better than that.
But George Burns, you just stick in to make anything funny.
Yeah.
I feel like he got into it.
And it's also a comedy and I feel like George Burns probably knew half the writing staff.
Yeah.
I think Mae West might have been dead.
When Mr. Ed was made?
She might have been trampled to death by Mr. Ed.
Yeah.
That's it.
Trampled to death.
I'm going to...
I don't think Charles Bronson was a big enough star.
Oh.
Oh, I'm here to kill this horse.
He was a Western star from the Cheetahs.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
That very much fits in with the horse show.
That was my logic.
All right.
But I don't know.
It's your question to fuck up.
Don't blame me.
If I get this right, I will kill myself in the shower and pin it on Paul.
Mother fucker.
I knew it was coming.
Can't go one day without thinking Matt died.
All right.
I'll go Clint Eastwood.
Hey.
It's Charles Bronson.
Oh, you were so right.
Fuck you.
You did me dirty, man.
I did you dirty.
Perfect.
Yeah.
I wouldn't have got it right because I would have thought it was Charles Bronson.
It comes to me.
Wayne's world.
Anybody stealing or anything?
Yeah, I'm stealing.
Oh shit.
I fucking love Wayne's world.
All right.
Matt stealing.
What is the name of Wayne's gun rack buying ex-girlfriend in Wayne's world?
Stacey, Becky, Shelby, or Cassandra?
I think it's Stacey.
Hey.
It's Stacey.
Her mom's got it going on and she was in Wayne's world.
Nice one.
Matt, you got movie stars, thousand dollar question movie stars.
Paul, yell out if you want to steal.
I will steal.
God damn it.
Paul's stealing.
Which of the following actors was not in a 1989 slasher comedy, cutting, what does that
say?
Cutting class.
So, which of the following actors was not in a cutting class?
Brad Pitt, Roddy McDowell, Martin Mull, Christopher Walken.
This is, who wrote this?
They did a good job.
This is a very...
This is ML Kennedy, I believe.
Yeah.
Paul, this is your question.
I'll go Walken.
Christopher Walken is correct.
Yes.
Give it to me.
Wow.
Give me points.
$1,200 question, Star Trek.
Oh baby, I'm in my power pass.
I of course will be stealing.
He's doing it, he's doing it.
Not counting the maid for streaming section 31, which Star Trek movie has the lowest rating
on Rotten Tomatoes?
Star Trek, The Motion Picture, Star Trek V, The Final Frontier, Star Trek Generations,
or Star Trek Nemesis.
Those are all front runners for a shit ass movie.
I know that Star Trek, The Motion Picture, that's the really weird one, right?
That's the one that doesn't seem like any of the rest of Star Trek?
No, it's too Star Trek, and it is coming into its own now.
So that's the only one that I wouldn't put on the list.
I would leave A out.
The other three are fair game.
I don't remember Star Trek V really at all, or Star Trek Generations.
I also don't really remember Star Trek Generations, I think that was the crossover one, right?
I think that's the one where both, where the old-
Yes, Generations is the handover, it's where Kirk dies.
I think it was Nemesis.
I don't think anybody liked Nemesis.
Certainly didn't help the experience.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go Nemesis, D. Now it's Star Trek V, The Final Frontier.
What does God need with the starship?
Paul controls back to you, Bloodhound Gang, it's the $1,400 question.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Matt, I know you love Bloodhound Gang, did you want to super steal this one?
I don't even know what that's referring to.
It could either be, it's probably the music group, but me, it refers to the 321 Contact
short within the show of-
Oh, shit!
"Whenever there's trouble, they're on the double, they're the Bloodhound Gang."
I can't believe that you just brought that up, and I can't believe that I actually remember
it.
What is that?
It's a 321-
It was a short on 321 Contact, and it was this very ethnically diverse group of young
kids who solved mysteries.
Uh, yeah, I'm not stealing this one.
But it's gonna be about the song.
According to the song, "My dad says that's for pussies, what would John Wayne never do?"
Wear a condom, vote for Obama, use a surge protector, buy an extended warranty.
I'm torn between A and D.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go with D.
Oh, and see, I think C is great.
C is pretty good, too.
I'm gonna go with D.
I ain't using a surge protector.
That's for pussies.
I'm gonna go with D for extended warranty.
John Wayne wouldn't use a surge protector.
You're going D?
I'm going D. He's nuts.
Ah, there you go.
It's C, motherfucker.
You have the right vibe.
Surge protector.
Yep.
Shit.
You should have stolen that one, Matt.
Oh, this one goes to Matt.
What's that name again?
Double Downs?
Super Steals?
Anybody?
No.
Nope.
What is the name of Wetleg's Grammy-winning song from 2021?
I just told Matt.
I just told Matt this.
Paul just told me this in the car, like, an hour ago.
Shays' Lounge, S-H-A-Y, apostrophe S. Shays' Lounge, C-H-E-Z.
Shays' Lounge, C-H-A-I-S-E, or Shays' Lounge, C-H-I-A-S-E.
This is interesting because Paul said Shays' Lounge, but he did not spell it for me this
morning.
So this is still a hard question.
Paul, do you know the spelling?
Brand new one.
If, were I a Benton man, I'm going to 50-50.
It's D.
The really funny thing is C and D.
But C and D are exactly the same, aren't they?
No.
Oh, no.
They have lounge spelled differently.
All right.
Let's do a 50-50.
That got rid of B and C.
Oh, now you know it's D.
I told you it was D.
It's D.
Yes.
Paul just put the new album in the car.
They're great.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
The new Wetleg is top-notch, top tier.
I'll check it out today.
Okay.
$2,500 question.
Smoothies.
You know, I got to be honest with you, I would have stolen any of these if I had known any
of them.
I am not holding onto my steal for strategic reasons.
I'm holding onto it because I don't think I know any of the answers.
Right.
Anybody want to steal?
Anybody want to double down?
What is this category?
Smoothies.
Let's double down.
Let's go nuts.
Matt wants to double down.
Whoa.
He knows his smoothies.
In 1998, Eve Six had their big hit with the Heart in a Blender song.
What is the actual name of that song?
Is it Beautiful Oblivion, Rendezvous, Inside Out, or Faith in Nothing?
Oh, Jesus.
I used my 50/50 already.
You did.
I would help you if I had any idea.
I definitely thought that song was called Heart in a Blender.
Beautiful Oblivion seems like a good song title.
Yeah.
Rendezvous.
I feel like there's already songs named Rendezvous.
Okay.
But that's the one they ... I think that's it.
Oh, you think it is Rendezvous?
I'm pretty sure.
Inside Out.
It's either Rendezvous or Faith in Nothing, but I'm pretty sure it's Rendezvous.
Faith in Nothing.
Yeah.
I believe in you, Matt.
Because remember the breakdown?
They go, "Rendezvous."
Yeah.
Well, all of these are lyrics in the song.
Yeah, but there's a breakdown where they're saying Rendezvous over and over again.
All right.
Oh, do you remember the part in the song where they say Faith in Nothing?
And the very end of the song is Rendezvous, then I'm through with you.
That's the very last line.
Okay.
Last time, Paul Charles Bronson.
Charles Bronson.
I don't know.
Final answer, Charles Bronson.
Charles Bronson.
B.
B, B.
It's C, Inside Out.
Oh, well, fucking shit.
Fuck both of us.
Yeah, I was going to be wrong no matter what, though.
That's fine.
But I did double down, so I lose all my points.
Let's see.
You sure did.
Oh, shit.
Goddamn it.
That's precisely what happened.
Oh, my God.
It comes to me.
Hometowns.
I'm not doubling.
I'm super stealing.
Whoa.
Super stealing.
I have zero points.
Matt is super stealing.
I'm taking all of Jacob's points.
It's the only option I have.
Chris Chavis, better known to WWF fans as...
Tatanka.
Tatanka was born in which city?
Oh, wow.
Buffalo, New York, Pembroke, North Carolina, Winnipeg, Manitoba, or Muskogee, Oklahoma.
Well, this whole thing was Canada themed, right?
Well, he was Native American.
Mm-hmm.
Pretendee.
He wasn't real.
Oh, that was his wrestling bit.
Yeah.
Oh, I remember this guy.
He would like...
He'd get up there and go, "Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye."
Yeah.
This sounds super weird now, but he would get up and do rain dances and shit, right?
Yes.
He would.
Pretend to.
Yes.
It was the epitome of cultural appropriation because he wasn't actually a Native American.
He also wasn't actually a wrestler.
Not much of one, but he was around forever in a day.
He had a long career.
Yeah.
That's what most people remember about Tatanka, his long career.
Well, he was a mid-level jobber, which is, you need that.
Yeah.
So he went to Tatanka, and then he went eel for a while, everybody was like, "What?"
I don't know if you guys know, but Paul's working on the Netflix documentary at Tatanka,
so you guys can get a nice breakdown of all these details.
He's in the middle of writing it.
I was sure I was going to be talking about toy trucks, but then it's a surprise.
I thought I was just dedicating myself to that one scene from Kevin Costner's Native American
film.
"Dances with Wolves."
Poor Graham Greene just passed away.
He did.
Yeah.
Aw, he's...
Now, there's someone who had a long career.
"Stands with a Fist."
That's what his name means?
That was what Tatanka did in the locker room.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
Well, I think you've stalled for me enough times, even though I tried to guess right
away.
I'm going to go with Winnipeg, Manitoba.
Winnipeg, Manitoba?
Winnipeg, Manitoba.
Is incorrect.
It's Pembroke, North Carolina.
Pembroke.
I played all of my options, and I have nothing to show for it.
There you go.
It's correct.
It's me, Ravishing.
Rick Rude.
Paul?
I mean, it's got to be...
Ravishing.
Rick Rude.
I guess...
I'm asking you if you're stealing.
No, I'm going to wait until the next one.
All right.
Then I'm going to double down.
What sort of movie was Rick Rude's finishing maneuver...
Oh, what sort of move was Rick Rude's finishing maneuver, "The Rude Awakening"?
A Canadian backbreaker rack, a shoulder neck breaker, a DDT, a sleeper hold.
Okay.
So Rick Rude, he was in "The Rasslin'" at the same time as the Million Dollar Man, right?
Wasn't he around then?
He had a sleeper hold.
He would fight with Paul Orndorff all the time.
Rick Rude was a long-time member of the Heaton family.
There he is, and I was grabbing his shoulder.
So DBSI had the sleeper hold, so I don't think he had a sleeper hold.
Well...
Jake the Snake had a DDT.
It wouldn't make sense for "An Awakening" to be a sleeper hold.
That's true too.
I have distinct memories of him and Paul Orndorff doing a flex-off contest for the audience
and it being the most homoerotic thing I've ever experienced as a child.
Welcome to "Rasslin'."
And I was an altar boy.
Yeah.
Welcome to "Rasslin'."
There's a reason why it will never go away.
Well, there's multiple reasons why it will never go away.
Now because it's fucking endorsed by the United States government.
Whose question is this?
This is me.
Jacob's.
All right.
So sleeper hold and DDT, I feel like are out.
Yeah.
I feel like that's Jake the Snake and the Million Dollar Man.
I do believe it was a DDT variation.
But I could be wrong.
I don't know.
I'll say B, a shoulder neck breaker, because I've never heard of a Canadian back breaker
rack.
Okay.
Boom.
Shoulder neck breaker.
Oh my goodness.
Nicely done.
I ran right through Paul trying to fuck me up.
You see Paul trying to fuck me up?
Me?
I'm super stealing.
I'm already doubling down.
I'm too late.
WrestleMania $5,000 question.
Paul is super stealing.
Oh, wait.
No.
I think taking it by the rules, Jacob later writing can he supersedes, but Jacob doesn't
do it.
It's too late now.
Oh, I think double down does count, but I like the idea of just jumping in and yelling
those.
Okay, great.
Braun Strowman won the tag titles at WrestleMania 34.
Why was this noteworthy?
A, he didn't show up at the event.
B, his tag partner was his ex-wife.
C, he didn't have a tag partner.
D, his tag partner was a 10 year old boy.
D.
Oh, Paul just knows it.
His tag partner was a 10 year old boy.
Let the record show that Paul Mattingly knows his 10 year old boys.
That is correct.
There's a reason I bought four bags of candy.
And that is the game.
Matt and I both have zero points each.
Paul has 10,200 points.
Jacob, did you draw that scary face?
No.
I don't know who drew it.
That's a zoom thing.
I don't know how people do it.
I haven't figured it out yet.
I love it.
We just don't know what the fuck's happening.
No, no.
Things happen.
I don't know what they are.
It was Mike Nelson.
Thank you, Mike Nelson.
Thank you.
Paul, well done on your victory today.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
You probably would have got that last one.
I definitely would not have.
Okay, great.
Thank you, ML Kennedy.
No, that's not what...
Thank you, ML Kennedy, for writing a fine obelisk.
It was a great one.
Yes.
I have some people to thank here.
Yeah, you do.
Yeah.
One, I want to thank Penn Jillette for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I just want to thank the following people.
All would have knocked on my door and then gone to the lobby to get a wellness check.
This is John Glore, John Carter, Jimmy Slonina, Jill Short, Jesse Rain, Jeremy Hudson, Jenny
Ebar, Jeff Loomis, Jeff Libby, Jeff Harris, Jeff Faust, Jeff Taksin, Jay Shapiro, Jason
Yadowitz, Jason Victor, Jason Vasquez, Jason Street, Jason Speckland, Jason Horpacitus,
and Jason Klepper.
Thank you so much.
I want to give a big thanks to Matt Donnelly for not dying.
All of the following people here work at the front desk, actually, and they have a 10-pack
a day cigarette habit.
Hatchet Scoop, Gwarthok, Guy Wade, Grill Sergeant Scoops, Green Wolf Scoop, Gravel Scoop, Greater
Sunday Scoop, Gizmo Scoop, Gerardo Garcia, George Guskov, Genetic Scoop, Gene Zink, Gelato
Steve, Gelato Problems, Gaspacho Scoop, Gas Man Scoop, and Garrett Godfrey.
I want to thank the following people who all want to get their cans smashed at Tierney's
Tavern.
Janet Lankard, Jameson Fisher, James Hubble, James Dawson, Jake Schneider, Jacob Dickalaker,
I want a Scoop, baby, Ice Blue Scoop, Ice Cream Manwich, Ian Soto, Ian A. Chapman, I
don't have a Scoop name, High Lion Scoop, House Dead Scoop, Holly Marshmallow Lightly,
Heather Divine Hanson.
Thank you so much.
Big thanks to these fellow people, these wonderful patrons, who actually know for sure that Tatanka
actually means the good land.
Galen Diggs, Galactic President Scooper, Star McScoops a lot, Galusha Scoop, Fudgy the Whale,
Frozen Cusser, Frozen 49th Scoop, Freeze Dried Scoop, Freehold Scoop, Frankie Stinky
Scoop, Flat Kidney, Ben Stephenson, Fifi, Fade Out Scoop, Evil Monkey, Erotic Scrape
Scoop, Eric Nielsen, Elkton Magic Scoop, Alyssa Walsack, Edward Bender.
And the following Scoops, of course, we're all hoping there will be more magic in today's
podcast, Ed La Scoop, Ed Wagner, Ed Andre, Ed Marcus, Dwayne Webb, Duke Scoop, Duck Flambe,
Dr. Tobias Scoopy, Dr. Scoop Little, Dr. Science Scoop, Doug Lay, don't say Scoop name, Don
Doty, Doc Scoop, Doc Scoop, Distiller Scoop, Dirty Old Scoop, Dippin Dot Jack, Dole Whip
Scoop, Derek Dozier, Dead Lazlo, David Walker, David Sorenson, David Peterson, David Kaye,
David Gravel, David A. Small, David Johnson, Dave Slusher, Dave Hanson, Dave Serial, Darth
Scooper, Darren Cunningham, Daniel Wine, Daniel Mattis-Ferrer, Daniel Loeser, and Dan Martin.
Thank you all so much.
Hey, if you want to be thanked on air, if you want to join us for a Zoom session and
draw dicks all over our screen, head on over to PreachingFun.com and find a tier that you
can support today.
And of course, the people that don't know what we're talking about, they have not gone
over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
That's right.
If you think this show is worth more than $0, head over to PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz.
Right there, you can do all the things that will make you a supporter of this show.
You can be an ice cream truck driver, you can get high fives for life, you can get cool
stuff in your email, you can do Zoom hangs with us off the show, off the air.
We're going to do our first one this week.
I'm figuring out how to make Paul the host of it.
We're going to do it.
It's going to be amazing.
And yeah, Paul, when are we doing that?
It's on Monday at what time?
Monday at 1030, my time, Eastern time, I believe that is.
Eastern time.
Monday at 1030 to 1130.
And we're going to hang and just talk and have a good old time and we can do this kind
of doodly stuff like that.
And that's going to be great.
Just chop it up.
It's going to be really cool.
Hey, here's a bonus for those of you who have tuned in because you are already Patreons
and you get the invite to come and watch us record this live.
It turns out that there is a sale going on right now at our shop.
So if you jump over to HayScoops.com and you click on our shop, it will direct you to the
T public spot that has a sale that is happening right now, and that's only for a day or two
for right now.
So it's probably done by the time you're listening to this.
HayScoops.com/shop.
However, yes, HayScoops.com/shop, jump over there and get yourself some of our swag on
the cheap.
It's 35% off right now.
You can get t-shirts for 16 bucks.
Another thing you can do over there at HayScoops.com is we are running out of jock versus nerds.
So if you have been wanting to put together a jock versus nerd for us, now is a great
time to do it.
Head on over there, HayScoops.com.
Make us a jock versus nerd.
Make us a scooperty.
Make us a Price is Right jock versus nerd.
Make us an obelisk jock versus nerd like the one we just played.
Yeah, you can do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
Also send us some scoop mail.
Oh, the people are crying out for the store jingle, Jacob.
Oh, let them cry.
Let them cry.
Store jingle, a big store song, we got a store.
By the way, what Jacob said and that song are both Hootie and the Blowfish references.
So there you go.
So it is storejingle.com also will take you, boom, right to the sale page.
Oh yeah.
100%.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Absolutely.
All right.
Thanks folks, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Bang on the window.
What the fuck?
That's somebody doing a wellness check on the mat.
Are you a liar?
We should just exchange hotel keys just in case.
That's the grossest idea I've ever heard.
I can think of nothing worse than having Matt come in unannounced, "You okay, buddy?
Everything all right?
Everything okay, Matt?"
Oh, if you're not on Zoom, you're not on Twitch, you didn't see the disgust, the actual real
disgust that came over Paul Mattingly's face when Matt said that.
It's not, it's, yeah.
Oh no.
Are we oversleeping in here?
Oh shit.
I am definitely checking Paul into all hotels from now on, and I'm getting Matt and I spare
keys.
That could end the podcast.
Not my death.
But this.
Yeah.
No, but a breach of trust.
See you everybody!