Oh, hello there. I am so happy you're here. I want to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers? Well, these are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
It's a new month. We don't have a new list yet, so I don't have names to thank.
But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver before this month is through.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver and help deliver that ice cream, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver.
And who knows? The life you save may be your own.
Here's the show. Woo.
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great. Let's go.
Suck on a Capri Sun.
Oh, no, I'm a Kool-Aid Jammers guy.
Oh, Kool-Aid Jammer. Those give me a little strange agitator.
They give me the agitator. I just had a boxing juju.
Time for Matt Madison's ice cream social. Soon to be in intestinal distress. That's Paul Mattingly.
Come on.
Sitting over there with his Kool-Aid. That's Matt Donnelly.
I'm here. I'm Jacob. It's PreachingFun.
I'm here and I'm Jacob.
Happy New Year, gents.
Happy New Year.
I tried very hard to go see my wife on New Year's Eve at one of her gigs and failed so miserably.
What happened?
It was terrible.
It was terrible. I had the early show at Absinthe over at Caesar's Palace.
I got done at 10.30 PM. My wife was less than a mile down the road doing a gig with several of our other friends,
several other close friends. Some of them have been on the podcast from the Spice Girls show that she does.
So I was going to go down, see part of her show, hang out with her, hang out with our friends on New Year's Eve,
ring in the New Year. It was going to be great. Well, my plan was to walk.
No, no.
And then it was, well, I was like, oh, it'll take me a half hour to walk down there, but that's not a big deal.
I wasn't too worried about the walk.
Normally.
Normally, normally. Well, no, even with the foot traffic, I was like, it'll take me a half hour, maybe 40, 45 minutes.
But even then, that's okay. I'm not worried about that. It was raining a little bit.
It was raining.
It was raining beautiful weather for two weeks and then New Year's Eve.
It was raining, by the way, did not seem to affect Las Vegas tourism negatively at all.
The earlier reports I saw actually were that it was a record record numbers for New Year's Eve.
That's right. Oh, wow. Yeah. Yeah. Even record numbers of trash.
Twelve tons of trash cleaned up on the strip after it was all over.
Jacob, how did your mom get down to this trip?
I'm not twelve tons of trash. I'm Jacob's mom.
Yeah. Well, you keep eating them pies, you're going to be 13 tons of trash.
I know that my mom listens to the podcast. Hi, mom.
13 tons of trash.
So I walk outside after the show. I gotta go drop off my bag and everything in the car.
So I go over and drop everything off and it's sprinkling rain a little bit.
I'm like, you know what? This might help me out.
This might be a glass half full moment because this means that nobody else
or not as many other people are going to be out on the actual street.
Way to silver lining it, Jacob. That's really good.
It's going to clear the path for me.
Did you think about using your scooter?
I thought about using the scooter, but then I would have had to park the scooter somewhere.
Also, the scooter, when it is wet at all, is a death trap.
I guess that's true.
Yeah. It is horrible to ride that thing if it is slightly wet.
Oh, God.
Because it's just not heavy enough. It doesn't stay on the ground well enough.
So I go outside.
No, your mom's on it. Yeah.
Put down the pie, mom.
Boom, boom, boom. The hits keep coming.
Boom, boom, boom. It's my mom walking down the hall.
So I walk outside. I'm like, OK, it's misting rain a little bit.
I'll be a little damp. That's OK.
I won't be soaking wet or anything. This is doable.
I'll be all right.
So I start walking down the street. I'm out on the strip.
It's great. It's New Year's Eve on the Las Vegas strip.
It's all that stuff. It's all the people watching that goes along with that.
Dreams, a lot of dreams in the air, a lot of hopes, a lot of hopes and dreams.
A lot of deflated pornographic dreams floating through the ether.
And then it started raining a little bit harder.
Call that 696969 number in 2026.
I'm going to get a hold of that dead billboard lady.
I'm going to see what that's all about.
Hey, which one of them is dead?
All of them send her to six for the Rio, please.
I was talking to my friend who's a Uber driver.
He's talking about how many how many tourists come to town
and they take the Uber to massage parlors and go like, oh, I guess.
Oh, I don't know if this is the place or, you know, it's like song and dance.
They try to alibi it like about like, oh, I guess I'll get out here and figure it out.
But, you know, I don't just like I do any time I'm getting dropped off by an Uber
at a place that I don't think is my destination.
I choose to go ahead and get out and figure it out when in Rome.
How many I guess most massage parlors in Vegas are connected to human trafficking in some way?
How dare you? How dare you?
They're legit foot tension specialists brought here.
You leave massage envy alone.
I very much do.
They recruit the top graduates of all the leading reflexology schools.
Is that reflexology school in a giant shipping container?
Because I wouldn't call it a giant shipping container.
Look, you say accredited, I say seaworthy.
These are maritime degrees, maritime degrees that are given out.
Maritime degrees?
Burn your diploma at sea. You can get your diploma at sea.
I just came here to get a manicure, but sure, I'll stick around.
Stick around forever.
Oh no.
Now you're in a shipping container.
Shit. It's not even a giant one. It's a regular size one.
I should do a Bernie Sanders.
It's misting a little bit and then it's no longer misting.
Now it's lightly raining.
There's more water coming from the sky now.
I know this because I had a gig and I drove to Utah, no problem.
Did the show and then drove back trying to make it back to this party
in time to be with my kids and stuff.
The rain between 10 and midnight was pretty heavy.
Yeah.
It was a record rainfall for Las Vegas,
which is kind of like having the highest rated show on CW.
Really, what are we talking about?
But we had record rainfall.
We did.
I finally gave up.
I basically walked from one end of Caesar's Palace to the other outside.
Don't mind me, guys.
I'm just drinking our Christmas gift from Soundstack, our hosting company.
They didn't send three months, just one.
We're going to pass that around.
It's going to be a travel.
Let me look at that.
Is that their emblem?
Paul can have it in January, Jacob in February.
No, I want it on Wednesdays and Fridays.
We'll ship it that often.
Yeah.
It looks like three styles of circumcision.
That's right.
That's what they started off as.
It's much like the Kraft food company.
It started off as a little niche industry and grew and grew and grew.
That's right.
So I walked from one end of Caesar's to the other.
I watched Matt take a drink out of that, and I said, "Matt, is that coffee in that mug?"
He said, "Moil less."
All right, we last left off.
Jacob was soaking wet.
Sorry.
You're getting soaking wet.
But Jacob, did you take the advice of the MythBusters and just stroll calmly and serenely
through the rain, or did you try to run?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I stroll.
I have a stroller.
You were shoving people at the right goal, like, "It's raining," and just shoving everyone.
It's raining.
Oh, my God, it's raining.
I'm going to melt.
I threw my fists out in front of me and just flailed them around and ran, yelling, "It's
raining!"
Forearm elbow sweeping, just the whole...
Yeah.
Jeff, in the chat, is asking a very valid question.
"Do people even own raincoats or umbrellas in Vegas?"
I don't know if people do, but I know that I do not.
I never did.
I keep them in the trunk of my car.
You do?
Uh-huh.
I do.
Who are you?
Because you're a Jersey.
I need to get an umbrella and just keep it in my car.
That's it.
It's your old Jersey habits.
Which I definitely used to do.
I never did growing up in Kentucky.
I'm just following off on it.
We didn't get that much rain in Kentucky.
No, I was...
Living in New York was always the funniest thing, because they sell umbrellas at all the
little bodega shops, and they're always like three or four bucks.
Then all of a sudden it starts raining, and they're $10 to $15, and they just price search
umbrellas all the time.
But yeah, that's what I was going to ask.
If you have a utility umbrella, even at work, I thought maybe you might keep one.
Someone might have one at a desk or an office.
We keep a pile of them at work, but they stay there.
Those are...
They're decorative.
Those are just the ones.
They're a bouquet of umbrellas.
Some people have stuffed animal heads on their walls.
We have umbrellas.
I've seen the umbrellas employed at Absinthe during inclement times when people have to
be ferried from stage to tent and what have you, back and forth.
Stagehands have gone out.
We have giant golf umbrellas to get cast members through wet areas and everything if we have to.
Big Sexy actually makes a really good point.
The reason why we have umbrellas handy is not because I'm always thinking about the rain.
It's because my kids play outdoor sports and you use an umbrella in the desert just to give yourself shade.
So what kind of umbrella?
Is it a black umbrella?
Is it a...
We have multiple.
We have a super wide golf umbrella for keeping two of us under the shade watching sports.
Color.
Blue and white striped.
Then I have tiny maroon umbrellas that I have for just in case for rain or an extra kid in tow or whatever.
I can give some kids shade or if it's raining.
I keep those.
Smart.
Yeah.
Kenny in the chat.
Yeah, you can't coach soccer without an umbrella.
Matt, was that your issue with your soccer coaching?
Did you not have enough umbrellas?
Well, as you remember, we won our first game and that's because I entered like Mary Poppins.
I took the umbrella and I descended onto the field.
Sure.
I gave everyone a spoonful of sugar before they hit the field.
Isn't that where the...
That was cocaine.
That's why they won that first game.
That was just a spoon of cocaine.
The Umbro brand, right?
That's just a shorthand for umbrella.
Umbroella.
That's why it's such a big thing in soccer.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, Paul's second worst joke of the day.
So far.
So far, exactly.
I have yet to start.
So what happened, Jacob?
Well, I walked from one end of Caesars to the other outside and I was wet.
Drippy drip.
So finally, I gave up on that.
I went back inside.
Oh, the one silver lining of the whole evening was I stopped at...
They had all these extra bars and extra little shops set up.
So I stopped at a little extra shop because I noticed they had the little airplane bottles
of Jameson.
I was like, "Oh, I'll get myself a little airplane bottle of Jameson for this, what has turned
into a very long walk?"
So I got up and got the airplane bottle of Jameson.
New Year's Eve.
There are no prices on anything.
That's right.
Same thing with the Bodega umbrellas.
Oh, God.
I mean, a bottle of liquor on New Year's Eve in Vegas is a Bodega umbrella in New York.
What was the price for that?
Yo, a little shot bottle.
A shot bottle.
Shot bottle of whiskey.
The airplane bottle of whiskey, New Year's Eve at Caesar's Palace in a little pop-up thing.
These are normally just a few bucks at a liquor store.
Yeah, this would normally be like $3.
Right.
I think about how these drinks around town are usually served in very ornate designer
thingies.
Oh, sure.
They put in like some spiraling unicorn deal.
Jeff, you're exactly right.
Dynamic pricing is what they call it.
Ends up being like a $30 or $35 thing, maybe a little more, depending on how much alcohol.
But this is just the simplified thing.
But still, New Year's Eve, my guess is...
Is this just a bottle?
My guess is $18.
My gut initially was going to be like $10 or $12.
Uh-huh.
But then I went to Disco to see it one last time with my kids, and we bought two bottles
of water on the way out, and it wasn't even New Year's Eve.
And it was $10 each for Aquafina bottles.
$10.
Stop it.
They should pay you to drink Aquafina.
That's the devil's dick water.
That is the nastiest shit ever.
You got to walk outside.
You got to just walk outside and find the guys selling the bottles of water on the street.
They sell them for a dollar or two.
And it's just a case of bottle of water they got at Costco.
Who cares?
I said, at least put a different label on it.
So at least put Aquatina on it.
At least let me think I'm getting a different spring that's nicer.
Or put a casino label on it or something like that.
Something.
But when you know it's Aquafina, you just shove it in my face.
$10 a piece.
It was like a damper in the mood.
Sure.
I just went to Costco for under $4, Matt.
I walked away with a brick of 40 waters.
Exactly.
When it comes to Aquafina.
Four zero waters.
When Ann and I bought that water at Costco the first time, we went up there.
Because it's right up there next to the toilet paper and everything else.
I was like, oh, OK.
Here we go.
Get some waters.
And she goes, I go, how much do you think it is?
She goes, it's $4.
I was like, no.
She says, yeah, it's $4.
My god.
You know who knows that?
The guys on the escalator selling the bottles of water for $2.
They do.
I nearly had an out of body experience.
That was amazing.
So the prevailing average seems to be around $18 to $20 here in the chat.
That's what I'm feeling.
$18.
Yeah.
Less than $10.
Oh, OK.
I was so pleasantly surprised.
Yes.
Wow.
I handed the guy a 10.
I like that they're gouging people for water.
But when it comes to liquor, they're like, no, no, no.
Stay true to yourself, fam.
Help yourself.
We've got to keep you on the straight and narrow.
I handed the guy a $10 bill and that included the tip and it genuinely, I mean this sincerely.
I felt better about Las Vegas.
Somebody gets it.
They're still charging three times, four times what they paid for this.
They're still making an amazing profit.
It was a genuinely markup.
I was like, I can live with this.
Because I was ready for him to be like, oh, that's $25.
Right.
That's what I was prepared for.
Oh, I was, I was so, that was, that was the only good part of my night.
So I drank my little baby bottle of Jameson.
I did.
I just, I just, I sipped on that as I walked through and, uh, well, this is not a good way to put this.
Now that I, now that I hear myself saying this out loud, I sipped my little baby bottle of Jameson as I walked to my car.
I hear that out loud now as I say it.
And, uh, so I went to my car, so they closed off the strip.
Cops cannot ask you to open a baby bottle.
That's a fact.
It's just a constitutional fact.
They can't, they gotta, they gotta have a warrant if they want to know what's inside that baby bottle.
That's what makes it different.
No, no, officer.
I'm not using my baby bottle there to conduct business on a federal highway.
So I don't need to have a driver license.
It's fine.
What do you say?
I'm a, I'm transporting.
Look at my binder of paper.
I'm transporting this baby bottle, not driving it.
And I'm not doing it for interstate commerce.
So I go to the car and they close off all the roads around the strip.
You can't drive on the strip.
It's all pedestrian and everything.
And the problem is SJ's gig is on the other side of the strip from where I am.
That's a big problem.
And so I spend about an hour driving around to different roads that the map says is open.
And they are all closed.
And then finally at about 11, 15, 12, 1130, 1140, some, somewhere like that.
I finally just say, fuck it.
If I turn right down this road, that will lead to my house.
So that is where I'm going.
So I drove to my house.
I let the dogs out.
We watched the fireworks from the backyard.
It was fine.
And then SJ came home a few hours later and brought friends home.
And then I was up until six 30 in the morning anyway.
So I did all of that and then didn't get to sleep early.
That sounds like a pretty good night overall.
It was fine.
It was perfectly nice.
I love how true SJ is to herself.
I love that she can always, always rally people after hours.
No problem.
Two 30 in the morning, here comes SJ and friends.
It's like call it a night.
It's blood money when you work on New Year's Eve, especially on the strip.
And no, no.
And SJ had been out since like, I think she left the house at like 1 PM that day and was gone.
She took a shower and got into full makeup at like one o'clock in the afternoon because then she had multiple sound checks and multiple gigs and everything.
And then two AM, two 30 in the morning.
Here she comes rolling into the house with people going like, get the whiskey ready.
I got people coming.
I'm doing a show with your wife.
January 14th, Sarah Hester Ross is hosting a variety show downtown.
Oh, wow.
Oh, nice.
I didn't know about this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just got the.
So good.
She sends you slides for you to post on social media.
She makes them herself and gives them to you, which is so nice.
Oh, and this is is great at the socials.
We know this exactly.
We flip through it.
I saw SJ out there and I was like, oh, great.
I'm doing the same show as SJ.
Nice.
January 14th at the composer's room, I think it's called.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's a nice.
That's a nice room there, too.
Also a friend of the show.
She had a Christmas is doing that show, which I'm very excited.
Excellent.
Yeah.
So it should be a fun one.
I haven't seen her in a long time.
Yeah.
I'll tell you who else walked around all night on New Year's Eve and didn't really get much
done.
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Manley's Ice Cream Social is brought to you by from the makers of dangerously
inaccurate AI generated medical school textbooks.
It's Robot Timeshare Salesman for cryptocurrency based feeding tubes, IVs and ventilators.
That's from the Gorilla Dentist from the Bjork video in twenty twenty four.
I'll say it one more time for the makers of the dangerously inaccurate AI generated medical
school textbooks.
It's Robot Timeshare Salesman for cryptocurrency based feeding tubes, IVs and ventilators.
Hey, how are you?
I hope your day is going well.
Are you in the market for medical equipment?
If so, come and buy some from me.
I'm a robot who sells medical equipment that's been made using AI technology.
The needles kind of work.
The tubes also sort of work.
Also, I will.
I'm basically a euthanasia robot.
That's the whole thing.
You buy equipment from me and it malfunctions.
Giant quotes around malfunctions.
I make murder tools for the medical industry.
Are you tired of granny?
Are you sick of Uncle Joe?
Wait, you're going to kill them?
No, not directly.
I will sell you faulty medical equipment that will lead to their demise.
Hello.
Yeah, I'm here.
My grandmother is she's a little she's a little sick.
She's got a little cough, but she's also just a pain in my ass.
Do you have anything for that?
This is gauze made with AI.
It's basically hemp rope, tie it tautly around her neck and leave it for four to three hours.
Her head scoops and checked out.
Four to three hours.
Here's an amount of time.
That robot is dumb.
That's actually robot in jail's cousin.
It's not the same guy though.
Oh, good to know.
Good to know.
Good.
Different.
Tracy, the bus driver scoop.
It is Tracy, the bus driver scoops birthday today.
Longtime supporter of the show.
Tracy, the bus driver scoop.
Love you.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
Heck.
So that was my New Year's Eve, gents.
How was I was yours?
I hope yours was less wet.
Mine was soaking wet.
I was in bed by about 8 o'clock.
With passion.
Yeah.
Paul's was soaked with passion.
I was in bed early and I wasn't feeling great and we got a crazy snowstorm.
We ended up with over six inches and I was like.
Yeah, you did.
This is some bullshit.
I was up and down all night not being able to sleep because I wasn't feeling well and
I got up at one o'clock.
I got up at 1 30 to let the dogs out and we were in the middle of a squall.
So I opened up a squall, opened up the door and it was just whoosh snow just I was like
just come straight into the house.
This is just too much to do.
I'd say it'd be one thing if I didn't feel 100 percent, it'd be one thing if the roads
could possibly kill my Kia.
I can't deal with both so I called out for New Year's Day.
I was supposed to go with four.
You do not have an automobile that is built for intimate weather on the roads.
No, not at all.
You have an automobile that is built for perfect weather on the roadways.
Which is why it served me so well in Las Vegas but out here in the PA things get dicey and
even when there's just a little bit like I was slipping and sliding even today driving
home.
So the last time we had a really bad storm like this and I pushed through.
I think we need to get Paul Mattingly a Silverado.
I pushed through and I went through and I almost put it into a wall but Ann's got that
newer Honda and it's got snowmode so she fears nothing.
Oh, Ann's got snowmode.
We know this about Ann.
Do you tire shop out there Paul?
What kind of tires do you get to make sure you're...
Mine are just all weather Kumos, they're top notch Kumos.
Okay, all right.
They're fine.
They're the tires that came with the car back in the day.
So yeah, but...
I just drive with snow chains on just in case no matter what.
Yeah, just constantly chewing up the roads.
No, I just, I couldn't, I was like no, I'm not going to risk this for a five hour shift
where I could die.
So I went back to sleep and yeah.
Oh, Mike Nielsen in the chat is correcting you Paul.
Just pronounced Kumho.
That is the massage parlor I go to when I drive.
What?
How did I end up here?
I had no idea.
I just typed Kumho in the Googles.
How did I get Kumho?
My goodness.
I'm looking for just some kind of nice massaging thing.
I was just looking for a reasonable massage.
I'm not going to drive this place.
I was going to massage tires.
I was going to rub tires and see which ones were the best.
That's what I came out here to do.
That's what I was going to do.
Kick the tires like the fire.
I guess I'll go check it out though.
I guess you can leave.
I sent Paul a picture with me and his old stage manager for New Year's Eve.
That's what I did.
It was very sweet.
Yeah.
Old stage manager from what?
Second City.
Nice.
My friend Brooke Walquist.
Yeah.
So yeah, I ended up making it back.
So I went out to Utah to do a show and a factor that made me nervous in the beginning and
thankful at the end is that I forgot there's a time change between Las Vegas and Utah.
Right.
Now I was leaving to be over two hours early anyway, just in case.
So I ended up getting there just like an hour and a half before my show, which is still
plenty of time to set up and do everything.
Still.
But it was the Springdale Community Center in Springdale, Utah, which is just outside
of Zion National Park.
I never came to any of those cute little towns.
There's a bunch of cute little tourist kind of cabiny towns.
Yeah, they're very nice.
And we did a show there and so my show was from 730 to 830.
It was actually 630 to 730 Vegas time, which meant when I finished up even packing and
everything and taking pictures and all that stuff, I still was able to get back to my
family's New Year's Eve party at a local neighborhood.
And I guess Paul's old stage manager lives in my neighborhood.
He was over at our mutual friend, the Camusso's house, and getting to talking, he was like,
you know, Paul Mattingly.
And I was like, I love Paul Mattingly.
To know him is to love.
And I was like, more than know him in the biblical sense.
We spent a good 20 minutes just raving about Paul going back and forth about Paul.
And then I took a little photo with him.
But I did the show up in Utah.
I'll just real quick on that.
That's really sweet.
I just want to keep talking about me for a minute.
But no, that's really, really nice.
And no, Brooke, Brooke really helped me out early on.
And she really did help lobby for me early on getting on the stage.
I brought it up.
I go, I can't believe it.
Like I said, it took a letter campaign to get Paul on the Second City main stage or
whatever.
She goes, oh, that was such, you know, whatever.
And she just talked about the politics of Second City and how annoying it was.
And all the things she navigated and stuff.
Yeah.
And she was very sweet when she left.
She wrote notes to everybody.
And the note she sent to me said, I might not always be your boss, but I'll always be
a fan.
And I thought that was really, really sweet.
Oh, wow.
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
She really did champion me getting onto that main stage spot.
So I appreciate that from Brooke big time.
Yeah.
Well, she was good.
Her and her husband were great.
I got to chat with them a little bit.
It's cool.
Super fun.
But yeah, so the event up in Utah was simply for locals who want to come to CUNY Center.
They could be taught to country line dance, eat a nice meal, and then get an entertainment
event, which was me.
How did the line dancing teaching go for you?
Man, I'm trying to set up and it was like I was playing like Frogger, right?
Like I'm trying to run stuff out and like everybody's just moving like all over the
place that I'm trying to carry.
And I don't want them to look at the props, see all your stuff.
So I'm like, you know, just trying to like keep all eyes on my eyes.
Like I'm looking up at anyone looking at me, like, you know, seeing your fish.
Yeah.
And it was like, it's like a like ninja camp for misdirection.
It was like, I like this a lot.
Can you get all these people to not look at the stuff you're carrying your hands?
And so and then it was funny is that like someone was teaching them the steps, but she
was just shouting over the top or whatever.
And so like while I'm in my little changing area dressing room, IE someone's office, and
I just keep hearing just shouting like, and left to right tip and just like just screaming
instructions and I was like, this is going to lose her voice.
That's so wild.
Now, I guess were they able to respond properly to these commands?
Do they know what they meant instinctively or did she have to be like, you know, a little
more descriptive of the, I don't know, I was too busy putting weird shit in my pockets
in the right order to, to figure it out.
But and then they had, yeah, they had dinner and then I did the show and it was fine.
Like the, my went up there, my mic didn't work and I switched the other mic and that
mic also was feeding back and then I just said, you guys can hear me.
Yes.
And then I did the whole show kind of just really kind of talking loudly in the room,
but it worked.
It worked out fine.
It was a great show, super fun, great audience.
You know, the thing about the secret thing about love playing shows in Jeff Lewis and
chances if Matt had real magical powers, he wouldn't need to load things in his pockets.
I just saw, I just saw a tick or tick tock where this lady was said my, what's that thing
they say my hot take or what have you, you know, my hot take is that some magicians are
actually magic and they just start practicing magic because they can do magic and it's easy
for them and they just, and they hide the fact that they're magic by doing magic.
That's the, that's a great, it's a, that's the logic that made me think I could fool
Penn and Teller is a, you know, with a, with a trick that Penn showed you, yes, maybe,
maybe I could have double bluffed it and I would have gone my way.
Oh my God, this is, this is going way too far back.
That's first appearance.
I'd fool us if you had somehow just put something in there to make it try to appear as though
you were doing a different method on it.
Yeah.
He was paranoid.
Penn was paranoid that I was, but about halfway through it was like, no, he's not.
I was only, I was only 14 months into magic.
It's not like I had to throw any bells and whistles on something.
You know, all you are now, all you had to do was dress up like a horse and cut off your
thumb.
You would have gotten a one who's a pretty, pretty price.
I didn't do proper misdirection for Penn and Teller, which is actually injuring yourself
and feeding blood to European magicians.
Yeah.
So I finished the show and a woman comes up and she's like, you work with Penn and Teller
and she starts talking to me and she seems like as, as politely as I can phrase it, something
has happened with her brain at some point in her life.
Oh, okay.
I don't know.
I don't have to say anymore.
I don't have to get an injury anymore, just whatever the way is to say, something's something.
Something happened.
I don't know.
With this person.
Was she a football player?
Yeah, she was, she was, she just finished up the season.
She just lost her starting spot in the Miami dolphins to Quinn yours.
And so she had free time.
His lady's name was Richie incognito.
So she's like, I really like them.
Oh, it's good.
She was, I was wanting to see their show in Vegas.
I said, now's a great time to see it.
You know, it's like, it's a, it's, it's, it's, they just finished.
Right.
It's the 20th year at the Rio.
It's their 50th year as a duo, but they just finished up all of their 50th anniversary
obligations.
And so they're, they're, they're hunkered down at the Rio for the time being.
Oh, good.
And she goes, I'm, I'm a little out of it because I just had major surgery.
And I go, Oh, no, stop it.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
And I'm glad like today, like this, this procedure just happened like a few hours ago.
Are you fresh?
The things that were happening in the, in the place that was line dancing, there was
magic.
The doctor is, Oh, ours, the trunk of my car took the turns a little fast on the way here.
No.
I said, Oh, I'm sorry to hear glad you made it.
You made it out.
I hope you have a recovery made it out to the show.
You know, you made it out of surgery, die flat operating table.
She might've pulled, pulled an RJ Owens and her companion is with her.
I don't know who her companion is, but the gentleman companion is a guy with her.
I don't know.
It could be brother.
It could be whatever, but male companion, at least male presenting companion.
It's his job here that I'm, I'm more concerned about.
Like for example, if he was like, Oh yes, she would love to see Penn and teller, right?
If I felt like I had like a, an accurate wing guy, I might've been like, all right, well,
let me see if I can help you out kind of thing.
But I did not feel like that I could accurately exchange information with this woman in order
to facilitate tickets.
So I just said good luck or did you trust this wingman and that thing he didn't step
up, right?
So I was like, he's hanging back.
So he's just letting her hang.
I'm going to let it hang.
I don't know.
All right.
She has the ability to travel.
That's always a lot.
Yeah.
A long way to go for not necessarily any dividends there.
So she starts talking about our show.
I agree.
We said again, Jacob, a Penn and teller show.
It's a long way to go to see a Penn and teller show without a whole lot of benefit.
Well, now wait.
So she starts to talk about her operation and this talk about how her nose lit up red
when the surgeon missed his mark and I said, I'm glad you're better or whatever.
And I'm kind of give a glance, not a, not a, not a knowing glance, but just a quick look
over to be like, cool.
Like do you want her to keep talking about this operation, right?
Like do you want this sort of everybody's still happy with this interaction?
Okay.
So she is just hands and pockets on his heels.
And then she lifts up her sweatshirt and lowers her sweatpants to show a gigantic scar across
the entire torso of her body.
Oh, they, they opened her up.
I was like, wow, you have believed you before.
I hope you didn't note skepticism and the major operation.
Did she say I, uh, I love Penn and teller because I like when they saw the lady in half.
It reminds me of my operation.
It reminds me of lunch today.
I think I could fill in for the cut in half lady.
Take that on my resume.
How, how fresh did the, uh, did the incision look?
Fresh.
Oh no.
Like not today.
But it was, was it, uh, was it gliss, was it glistening?
Was it oozy and glistening?
Was it moist to want to focus on this?
Okay.
But were there, were there like black stitches in it?
Yes.
Oh, it's fresh.
Oh, that's like, that's like within a week and a half, dude.
Yes.
Those things don't hang around long.
No, it was maybe, Oh my God.
Oh Lord.
What is she doing at a magic show line dance combo dancing?
I hope she was sitting down for the dancing.
My doctors told me not to, but you know, me, I can't, I love me some dancing.
I, I'd like to compliment your show.
Best compliment I can give you as a comedic magician.
I found you truly side splitting.
Look at my open wounds, you split my sides open.
You bastard.
Yeah.
I really enjoyed your show today.
It was a, it was a very nice show.
I, I, uh, in lieu of a tip, I am giving you a kidney.
You ripped me asshole to appetite.
You opened me wider than the mammoth cave.
You cracked me like the Liberty bell.
Oh, Boston.
I just was like, Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yes.
She was literally in stitches and he literally like, he like very generally was like, okay.
Like, but he still, there wasn't like, you know, Hey, you know, like, let's say, let's
keep it together.
You know, whatever.
It just was like, let's keep it together.
I don't know.
I thought that the associate, yes, or, uh, uh, whoever, whoever, whoever the person with
her handler, romantic other.
What do you think?
Did you get any vibe for the relationship?
My vibe, if I had to guess was romantic other, do you think because he was romantic other
during this, what can I say?
Reveal of delicate damage body.
Someone else has it already said a million times.
Do you think that he was also like, Oh God, what am I married to now?
Was this like a Frankenstein moment?
Was he like the sepsis got to her noggin and things didn't go right?
Like, like, is this, is this like a, is this like those times?
I have been begging her to show me this car and she would not, and then you fancy pants
magician come walking in here.
Right.
All of a sudden, Matt just gets punched.
See, did you, did you get the vibe that he was like a scar filiac?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
He just was really good.
He revealed the scar.
He just buddy armed me.
It was like, huh, oh, oh, he comes over, he's like, I've got it.
I've got a cut of the lion King where it's only that lion with the scar on his eye.
It's very short, but very gratifying.
This guy just, he lives for flesh wounds.
He was simply just, that's what floats his boat.
That's what gets us passive.
He just was simply so like, yeah, yeah, you know, like we had a good time.
You know, it was very, it just, he just was, well, maybe he's, he's had his way with that
new scar and now he's like, well, now I just got to wait for the next operation.
Why do you think it was still so pink?
He can't get turned on anymore.
She got that operation a month and a half ago, but he's keeping that scar fresh.
It just totally overwhelmed and now he's over it.
Yeah.
That's how it goes.
Y'all, you always want, which you can't have, he just, he's just an Uber driver who waits
by the hospital for this phone to do, Hey, how'd it go?
Oh yeah.
Stitches pop in because, uh, you know what, you know, the old saying stitches lose britches
on your phone.
This one's on me.
This is not me.
Stitches lose britches.
Get in.
I'll tell you who else has turned on sexually by surgical scars.
That's the following sponsor show is brought to you by goose.
The musical it's from Mike Nielsen.
It's goose, the musical, uh, give me some music, Jacob music.
Would you like?
I don't care.
All right.
See if I could even hear it, the surgery didn't go exactly how I wanted it to go, but I'm
here at the dance hall slash magic show.
I want to show off my belly, the stitches to the magic man and let him put his fingers
into my severed care.
That's out.
Goose goes the wound in my belly, goose, goose, goose goes the sore on my side, goose, goose,
goose go.
My stitches inside me, goose, goose, goose, I've turned into a slip and slide.
Goose.
This is where my, my mental note is.
I can't share this episode to Instagram because we'll get demonetized cause Paul was singing
the goose song.
Are you kidding me?
That's a number one hit.
The goose song, goose.
There it is.
Multiple vomit emojis from the scooping over girl and chat because it was so good.
But she comes back with goose episode title.
So this is the thing you got to understand about me, Matt.
I think you do understand that I will take it there and make you love it.
This is like, this is where I hope someone's like at the, like the drive through pharmacy
or the bank, right, right, or, or receiving a traffic ticket.
Goose from the scar of my belly is just blaring out as they exchange money.
We have confirmed ruined at least one scoops dinner.
The best thing about goose, it doesn't tell you it could be anything that is genuinely
the best thing about goose.
It's something emanating from a wound.
I leave the rest to your fertile imaginations.
There are multiple things that can emanate from a wound.
Well, here I am just writing the whole fucking musical.
I better pump my brakes.
TM, TM is right.
If you can do a musical called corn, I can do a musical called goose.
Oh, I would watch, I'd watch goose over corn or whatever, 10 times out of 10.
You have that correct?
That is correct.
That's what I mean.
People that made that show.
All right.
Time for goose goose goose out of hell, goose out of hell.
Yeah.
It probably does have a meatloaf vibe.
Oh, there's, there's also the, the, the, the big hit song from goose.
Yeah.
Something happened to my brain at some point.
That's the torch song number at some point, something happened to my brain for intermission.
And of course it's the big, the big surgical race goose lightning.
There's an operating room in the back of my car.
It's very hard to steer while he's operating on me in the car.
Cut me up.
Cut me down.
In the car, Ooh, it's a nice goose lightning.
Something's emanating from that scar.
Goosh.
Feed me.
What could it be?
The scar goes quaddo slash Audrey.
Audrey T.
I loved, did you guys see the, the Christmas ad with Travolta in it with him doing the,
the grease lightening thing with the Santa sleigh?
What was that?
You notice how they didn't even, I have no idea what it's for.
Did you notice how they didn't even try to match up the lyrics with his mouth movements?
No, they were like, it seems like they had for like three hours is like, yeah, we got
that shot moving on.
No, sir.
We didn't get moving on.
We don't wheels up in 10.
Let's go.
Like his mouth is not moving close to what the words are doing.
It's weird.
And yeah, I have no idea what that ad is for.
Uh, I forgot.
Did I talk to you guys about the club gray skull She-Ra hat, or was that another thing?
I don't think you talked to us about it.
No, I think it was about us.
Okay.
Well, I guess I talked about it at during the scoop chat, but yeah.
So if you go on Mattel creations website, Mattel creation, all the time, which I do
all the time.
I do.
Uh, but, uh, you know, they have club gray skull, which is their little thing and they,
they sell merchandise and one of the things they sell is, uh, a new hat that they've created
just in the last couple of weeks.
It's She-Ra's 40th anniversary.
So they decided to make a She-Ra hat, but what they've done is they've created Schrodinger's
ball cap.
It is a red baseball hat, which given today's political climate has ramifications and yeah,
it means something, right?
Right.
However, this red baseball cap also, there it is, has the words She-Ra princess of power
written on it.
So I don't know that a lot of She-Ra fans are going to want to go around in a red baseball
cap.
This might be the target demo.
This is just for Sidney Sweeney, just for Sidney Sweeney, that's absolutely, I would
assume is some kind of, I would, I, if I saw that hat, cause the She-Ra's thoughts
very small.
Yeah, it is.
And the wings are pretty big.
That's the weird thing to me about it is that it's not that it's red, but it's like, that's
her helmet.
From far away, I would have thought it was a, uh, military background Republican.
Uh, that's what I would think if I saw that hat from afar.
Yeah.
Right.
So I don't know what Mattel is smoking that they would choose a red cap.
I get it so far as color coordinate, but you could go white.
You could go blue.
You could go pink or whatever.
Many years ago was why I went to like wine country and we bought, I bought this red
trucker hat from his diner in, uh, uh, uh, Northern California.
And I was wearing it around and I was at first getting compliments, make America great again
on it on my cool diner, like vintage diner, trucker hat, right.
And then all of a sudden, one day I got mistaken for a MAGA hat and it was a guy giving me
a thumbs up from across the coffee shop and my friend being like, he thinks you're wearing
a MAGA hat.
And I was like, what?
I was like, no.
And at that time I was like, how many people are really wearing those?
Um, oh, you sweet summer child.
Oh, I was, I missed it by a mile and, uh, uh, but yeah, I eventually had to stop wearing
it because everyone was starting, everyone was starting to think of it was a MAGA hat.
Oh, you got a, you got one of your hats ruined because people said it looked like a MAGA
hat.
Oh, that's, that's tough shit.
Jacob has absolutely been victimized by that on camera right here with his Las Vegas hat
that is Las Vegas aviators.
That hat is much better than the one I'm talking about for my trucker trucker hat.
Beautiful happens, happens to look weird.
Uh, there's a guy, there was a guy driving down my street and, you know, that, that sketch
and, uh, I think you should leave with the call, like the, the driving crooner or whatever
it's called, where he puts the stickers, makes it look like he's smoking a cigar and wearing
it.
Yes.
On the window.
Yeah.
Uh, in the back of this guy's truck, in the cab section behind his main cab, he has,
you know how you can put a little sticker on the window.
Yes.
He's got, he's got our president in the back seat, the neck and head of the president,
you know, looking like, oh, he's sitting in the back seat and he's tooling around in there
for good.
And I casually yelled out the window, he didn't hear me of course, but I warned him, you've
got a pedophile in your truck.
Look out, careful.
He's behind you.
Um, yeah.
So may have fallen on deaf ears, maybe, maybe, uh, feel free to always give Matt a thumbs
up if you see him wearing a red hat from now on to thumbs up in his scars.
It's like, it's like where I've had to wear my Hooters jacket and, uh, cause there's too
much weight in my, in my bags.
And then I get some, I get compliments on like nice jacket and you're like, no, no,
it is not.
Please don't, let's do a little joke versus nerd, I'm on the hunt for balls on the hunt
for balls.
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the,
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the
hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the
hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the
hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls.
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the
hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm
on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on
the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt
for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for
balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls,
I'm on the hunt for balls, I'm on the hunt for balls.
Let me know that the word basically was doing a lot of heavy lifting in Matt's sentence.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com takes you over to our Patreon page where for
as little as $3 a month you can upkeep this show on the air.
Like Matt said, we are dependent on our Patreons.
We love each and every one of you.
Thank you so much.
Just show the Patreons the email we got for last month for like, "Hey, money's coming
your way."
And then I clicked on it and went like, "What?"
From the ad revenue.
Put it this way, our podcast company could not buy Jacob and Jameson on New Year's Eve.
Oh no!
And they're pretty reasonably priced, they're pretty reasonably priced.
Oh no.
That's right, we are dependent on our Patreon supporters out there.
It's as little as $3, you can do the support every month, you can do it for the year, if
you do it for the year you get a little discount on there, and it really helps us out, it lets
us do this thing that hopefully you're enjoying as well.
Yeah.
And if we break over a certain month, rather than give you a bonus episode, we will go
to community college for geography.
That's what we will do.
We'll take a CSN course.
Speak for yourself.
I'd rather a bonus episode.
Thanks for this everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
We're sending out preaching smarts.
Never claimed to be.