here we go stop it solo scoop oh hello there people are putting emojis of tits
up in the chat now i zoom here it's very distracting but i like it i want to
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers um let's see who are the ice cream truck drivers boy see i'm so
distracted who are the ice cream truck drivers those are the folks that
deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes i don't have a
new list yet but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver before this
show at a future episode this month if you want to be an ice cream truck driver
and i sure hope you do preachingfun.com is where you can go preachingfun.com
head over there sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life
you save may be your own
oh a show hey johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah i'd love to
let's go shout out to when matt donnelly discovered the best manual nose hair
trimmer that i've still ever used the eagle
welcome today's a little nose hair it's time for matt maddenley's ice cream social
sitting in los vegas it's matt donnelly also sitting in los vegas it's me jacob
the audio guy sitting somewhere we'll figure it out later it's paul we're
preaching fun yeah paul's not here uh you know it's funny we got a couple of
uh compliments recently this thing our recent episodes have just been have been
on a good in a good spot we've been there what better way to bring it to a
screeching halt than simply not knowing where paul maddenley is on this earth i
think it's maybe a good way to just uh just slow it down we'll show you but the
chat is continuing to find different ways to portray boobs in emoji form in
the chat which is very exciting lori else off the two sunny side eggs very
nice very nice everyone's so creative oh uh just got a text from paul breaking
news oh hey be home soon so it wasn't sleeping oh well we don't know that you
might have been like on a park bench somewhere just just dozing just feeding
the birds and just nodding off on a park bench in the middle of january in
pittsburgh no problem it's so nice out it is freezing uh for las vegas right
it's uh 44 degrees or 40 degrees uh it's dropped down to 38 which is celsius for
our our foreign listeners is i don't know five i've we're terrible at
converting fahrenheit celsius i have no idea uh but uh it's negative 30 i don't
know yeah um but i go to the gym and i'm my gym right now it's just like our
little community center because my actual gym gym closed my gym gym
closed oh gym gym top of the morning to you my gym gym closed um so my uh my
regular gym closed it's going to be taken over by a crunch gym eventually
it's a coming soon what which is always so funny right like pizza places just
become other pizza places right like gyms like what else are you going to do
that space it has like it has a pool and workout equipment are you just going to
so it's going to be another gym oh yeah i forget about the pool sure that makes
sense the pool does it's why it's why i had joined that particular gym is
because all right because you could go in there and and uh and and stare at the
young ladies who were swimming exactly i mean you can go swim exactly but i have
those glasses that look like eyeballs that are looking up and so therefore you
can't tell that i'm staring at the spring ones yeah but i i taped them so
they just look like they're looking up good smart so that way that way i'm not
creepy that's right that's why he's the best folks
that's why he's the best and i uh uh go so what i do is i go to the community
center it's called the multi multi multi-gen multi-gen center multi-generational
center right okay so they have you know kids camps they got swimming lessons
they have like uh classrooms for uh to teach classes for adults it's a big it's
a big big outfit over there and one of the houses is a gym and a walking track
and a pool but a big like okay it's like where the where the competitions are
where the swimming competitions are uh locally for for for the schools got you
and so i go to the gym in the evening around like 5 30
which means the sun has just gone down and it was super windy yesterday like
really windy crazy breezy yesterday and i look out the window and there's a
fucking swim meet happening
i was like what fucking hell on earth why why it's it's still january i know
we live in the desert but it's still january
yes why on earth is an outdoor swimming meet happening
i mean best case scenario in the pool and i assume an unheated pool in the
desert in january it's not pleasant it's not nice
no like without a breeze it's just it still was a cold day
but it was like that means like you know like oh man when when you get wet
and then there's a breeze i mean that's all right yeah
i couldn't believe it's all these kids it's honestly the reason that i don't
swim half the time i don't swim it's because
right now i'm i'm just not swimming in case a breeze comes up
i mean it's been a minute but i that story where i was hired to be a
bathing suit model by accident i think i've told the story on air
it's been a while it's been a while though but uh yeah so so they'd cast just
off of headshots and then it was me three male models and four gorgeous
women models and then a bunch of bathing suits that didn't fit on my fat body
and then that's right i forgot they had the bathing suits
so i stuffed into one of them like a sausage and then yep good
we had to go do like a pool shoot and there's literally like two pools like a
giant lap pool and this beautiful kind of
circular fountain pool for like um hanging out and renting cabanas
right and so they set this really fancy camera
and they art directed me to the furthest place away from the camera
they put a fake that that is good art direction
they put a fake drink in my hand and put me literally
200 yards away from the camera all right so they had the hotter people closer to
the first pool i was just supposed to be decorative
like background in the second pool here's what they did they put all the
they put all the super hot people in the close-up pool
and they put me behind the camera with a jib
can you can you hold this this bounce this light bouncer
this reflector can you hold it i don't think i'm even on camera over here no
you are you are don't worry about it you're fine
the look i remember still in the art dresser's face when i was trying to
squeeze into a bathing suit and him just going like why
why are you here what have i done to deserve this
hanging out in the tent and listen to all the hot people talk about all the
different things they have for their veggies vegetable smoothies and which
blenders they use and stuff i was like i was like i know what a
blender is
i just put snakes in mine but it was freezing cold it was like a free it was
it was like uh it wasn't as cold as today but it was it was probably like
50 degrees still very cold to be in a pool and so
i uh being the only person in pool b uh really took my time getting in trying
to not even let it ripple it was like even if i just got up on my on my
stomach like the wind was blowing and it would just freeze right
so i was staying like perfectly still in the water to like not like to
establish a level and not change it right that was yeah that's what i was
doing and then at one point they want to shake
things up i'm gonna shake things up and decide to move people around
except me they said to keep me right where i was
well they had taken the first shoot to uh build a wall
but they set the wall up between me and the camera they told one of the hot
guys pretending your friends with fatso back there right so they sent him back
there and uh and you said that's not how you
pronounce my name
and uh and he was a big old beautiful dummy
so he ran great and just jumped in the pool
yes ran and just leapt into the pool and i was like no
i've established i've established a level
you're interfering with my level you're ruining it for both of us
you're gonna be mad about this too and then he gets up he's wet and then we
start staying still and pretending to talk and gesture one another while they
do this right and uh and he is like man it sucks uh it's cold
i was like yeah sure does buddy uh he was like because the wind's
blowing i was like no one of us has already figured that out
yeah the other of us knows which blender to have to make the best vegetable
smoothies and the other knows how wind works on
cold skin but we both got this gig didn't we
we're both getting the same check buddy
uh i still remember that shoot came out uh it was uh
it was it was not uh i was not in the pool stuff
i was in the uh at one point they like decided like
center attention on me and like do things with like they were pushing me in
the pool right and that was oh okay those were the those are the final shots
the pool was me getting pushed in the pool
while girls with their dad showed up like
give us money and let us gamble go away
the those those didn't make it because they probably looked over things like it
just looks like we're picking on someone right now i was just fat this time i was
still young so i didn't come off as their dad i
just came off as like i don't know their gay best friend
or you know someone they went to high school with you know that kind of a
thing this is our cousin who's with us for the
day this is a make-a-wish guy that said he
wanted to hang out at the caesar's pool before he died i didn't know they did
exchange students to the caesar's pool but i guess they do
that'd be great like you're dying like you want to i want to you want to hang
out with famous magicians now i want to know what it's like to
get bottle servers and have models hang out
that's my i want you to just buy me a table
at omni oh i want to hang out at the craziest nightclub make-a-wishes like
we can't i cannot afford this i want a poolside
cabana at towel all right give it can we just buy you a pool
we'll just buy you a pool uh someone in chat saying to try to
distract me with their zoom background their zoom background is the
crucifixion it's just it's it's three people on crosses
on the hillside but i'm not sure if that's the real one
i don't even know if they had cameras back then i mean
you know not to put the car before the horse here but that's a beautiful
sunset i mean it's perfect perfect sunset how can you see that
sunset behind three people hanging on crosses and not
believe in god wait someone said do you see the letters
is there letters on there oh just says it says titties or tits
oh good oh the crosses the crosses spell titties
now i get it great boy did that take me too long
and not help the audio version of this podcast at all
um all right but uh yeah i think we're doing great
hey when you were growing up jacob did saying the word
sucks like that sucks was that considered like extreme
oh that was definitely considered that was a that was a word we could get in
trouble for yeah me too yeah my kids throw out like
it's nothing all the time really yeah
do you smack them just give them a one point give them a taste of the back of
the hand at one point i was like you know i offer to
make a breakfast whatever and they're like oh do we have it you know do we
have waffles and look i was like no we're out of waffles
and my youngest goes well that sucks and i i didn't go like hey time out
let's hold up that was an extreme thing to say
when i was a kid you guys throw it out like it's nothing
and when you directed at me it's very jarring and it makes me really angry
sorry i'm making you breakfast sorry your spoiled ass has done up waffles
today mother right but uh yeah so my kids say
sucks like no problem i hear other kids say it
so i guess it's just okay to say sucks maybe maybe um
i definitely have a memory of me saying something sucks to my dad
and him stopping and just just looking at me and saying something along the
lines of sucks what go ahead what does it
suck
you're like it was definitely something along those lines was like i put point
taking titties dad titty
uh yeah sucks saying something blows definitely couldn't say shut up
although you can't you still can't say shut up
my kids now just say shut up um we got in trouble when we were little for
stupid if we if we called somebody stupid we got in trouble for that
i remember really getting in trouble
uh the first the first time i thought i had to like get caught cursing and had
to confess to my dad i said up yours
which i don't even think people understand
i don't even think that's like even on the radar as an insult anymore
that was huge i i said up your nose with a rubber hose
paul mattingly is here paul mattingly everybody
paul mattingly everyone paul mattingly hey guys
well paul you're late so up yours buddy oh boy
now i'm getting it now i'm getting it nose with a rubber hose
you know what it's absolutely fair the boys told me we adjusted for the time
i wrote it on my calendar uh for some reason this morning i woke up
and i go oh yeah two o'clock podcast do do do do do
fart fart fart just tootling around that was part of it
okay the other part was i'm doing my morning business
getting ready to take a shower uh-huh and i'm scrolling on my phone
and what to my wondering eyes should appear
but the local toy shop going out of business sale
oh no yes oh we never had everything we never had everything must go
the fact that he came back is just uh i'm honestly surprised he's here now
i know no no i would tell it's only 10 minutes away from my house
so uh i was down there it was basically the bad signal went to the sky
yeah yeah i had no choice i answered the siren call
and went to the toy store and just was zombieing out for an hour
just oh what can i get you know i got i got a couple good little little
trinkets nothing too crazy and go too crazy too crazy local toy
stores also go get a business so pour one out yeah
no this was uh this place this place is called toy land
if anyone has ever thought paul isn't that selective with his rage
okay no i this place is uh okay you guys have you guys don't have
you guys don't have ollies on that side of the world all this
was ollies so ollies for the us east coasters
is this discount chain that's sort of like big lots was in its heyday
i'm from the east coast so is it like a newer east coast thing i think so
yeah okay so uh you remember big lots when it first popped off
yeah you could get some really amazing as a kid
you could get some amazing deals you could take five bucks down there
and come home with something significant yeah you know
oh yeah yeah so ollies does this they get warehouses full of
old toys and things and put them at pretty deep discount and
sometimes they you know clearance them out even there
what this toy store toy land was doing was clearing out the best of ollies
sales oh bringing them to their store and repricing them
above and right at msrp or higher so i was kind of like well this isn't a
business plan that can work i mean there you go so their business
plan was take things out of the bargain bin
mark them up and then try to resell them yes
that's already called ebay i know i don't know why it's basically like an
ebay but but not as many good items
now occasionally i found some deals at the when stores start doing corporate
dumpster diving uh things are bad all over things are
bad all over and i hate to see a small business go under
but i also know that they are straight up just resellers
and they put everything at a price that no one could deal with
and they were doing big time pokemon scalping as well
so i'm just like man do you think it's possible that they're just faking the
out of business sale and they're just going to be one of those stores that's
perpetually going out of business that's just their new thing
no uh i the owner was there and i heard you guys are listening to the last
episode of matt and madely's oh shit see this is how it goes
now the owners the owners were there and they were talking about
the next chapter or whatever so clearly they've got some other scheme up their
11 is the next chapter chapter 11 you're right
you're right uh that's yeah there's two locations in the pittsburgh area that
are going under uh wait again it it uh makes me sad
but uh you know not that sad because it was a dumb model
and i would go like i'd been there like four or five times they'd only been
open about a year and i'd been there a couple times to
try and support them and the last time i went i just walked
right out with nothing because i was like there ain't shit here you know it's
just sad did you ever talk to him like did they
properly nerd out about toy products were they no it's not like that they're
not in it for the love he's not in it for the love he's just a scalpy
he's a scalpy scalp this is it paul needs some heart in there
i imagine he has i imagine he has probably
one fixation i don't know what that might be
most when you come back to vegas you always go to the same toy spot around
the corner from my house yeah ralph's name right well ralph's
is the comic book shop okay oh right right and then and then
ralph's just happened to have a new toy store
rogue toys built a place right in that same slot
that's a total nerd cave now man it's got rogue toys
it's got that uh smashing grounds rogue toys has always been in that uh in
that ballpark though they they've always like when they were downtown and
everything they were always that like real nerdy
spot like yeah no rogue toys is great i had
wonderful i always i always knew that if paul got a divorce
and then got remarried i could go get his remarried gift
at that rogue toys you could you could buy
half my collection i sold nearly four thousand dollars worth of toys to them
and oh and that was at a loss for me so you know uh when i was moving i had to
get rid of so much stuff but they were cool about it
the only thing that really bugged me is i went back in and i'd sold them some of
my uh mega blocks turtle stuff and i
i let go of a piece that i came back and i was like what are you charging for
that that i gave you for ten dollars jesus
so yeah there were there were one or two things i was like go back and look again
well i mean well that was the thing i went back and i was like oh look
it's my entire collection on display uh that's what sj will do sj will do that
when we go to concerts she'll like we'll be in our spot and then
she'll i'll see her on her phone and then she'll be like hey what
what did we pay for these tickets again i think we could have gotten cheaper
no i mean what are you doing hey look no regrets you gotta
if you're a collector you know collections come and go
that's what it is you know it's it's just uh and i've i've been
so fortunate to build back so much cool stuff here
in the new space and i don't know i showed you guys last week last time
the amazing uh uh enterprise that i just got which was you know alazlo i showed
them the video uh of the enterprise that i've set up
it's just it's a gorgeous so i've got i've got more
collectibles and i know what to do with it's lovely you know it's just fun
spending time so i apologize that uh my forgetful brain and my
blindness in toys uh led me to be a half hour late so
uh we all assumed you were dead and uh that's the right assumption to make
you know and then we started a podcast anyway
there will be a a wellness check at your door just the police will come knocking
that was what matt texted me he's like i can't knock on your door so
good luck hope you're not dead
he's so funny yeah man i'll stop paul might be dead but they would end in a
podcast anyway that's the following sponsor today's show
oh i just had it up where'd it go god damn it
today's show is hold on i'm gonna go to toy store i'll be right back
all right today's show is brought to you by i'll let you go
smirnoff's fabriz flavored vodka presents booze cruise on the trash barge
uh that's from nathan's hot dog scoop in 2021
paul i'm just gonna go ahead i shouldn't speak for nathan here but i think
smirnoff for breeze as practice is also good enough to be its own
commercial but if you want to also just commit to
the booze cruise on the trash bar i agree i think we're good with smirnoff
for breeze oh yeah for breeze is our sponsor
hello comrade do you have horrible breath in morning from drinking from
urinal where only water is available then solution i am having for you
we are providing new smirnoff smirnoff for breeze
bringing delicious clear booze right to face
and then no stinking mouth from from from breeze chemical to wash your teeth
and tongue oh so good spray on furniture when done
spit on pet and children to make less smell horrible
whatever need smirnoff for breeze now available in pina colada
and linen crisp take choice what want linen crisp pina colada shot
you tell you tell me i know your boss i know your boss you air control have
drink have great breath i i guess i'll take
the pina colada one pina colada coming up sir
good choicings here you go two whole big bottle
that is two i get two bottles of vodka for that
that is the shot that is what we call shot out here
in in georgia two whole bottle of vodka is shot one shot
three scoops to check out
oh georgia is georgia still around
still intact i don't know hour to hour you don't know we don't know
right now what do we know whatever we know
is god's will whatever's happening it's the way the lord wants it
leon in the chat he's rushing out to the liquor store to buy a case
hey there you go uh i already have uh jd uh
maker of the scoop documentary uh says he is coming out to see
the show uh that i'm doing with your wife jacob on on the 14th with sarah
has to go good wednesday june 14th the composer's
room come see a nice variety lineup with sarah has to ross
uh sj shana christmas and more um jd says he's coming just because he
wants me to show him the uh the doll video from the john wick
experience that's why he's coming he's paying i'm sure he does
he's paying money to see a show to hang out with me
so that i can show him my phone and i can just show him the video that's why
he's coming i mean that's out that's a piece of vegas history right there
checks out that's real vegas insider history we've got that's pretty awesome
it's it's it is a very valuable uh commodity to have for sure
uh i leave tomorrow for a gig in south bend indiana
it's a private show it's a corporate show so if you're
oh in indiana so i can't come kick rocks
yeah no come see me come see me eat in chicago
on the 27th or in wabash wabash indiana um i forget which day but
jokers of magic that that last week of january
into february we're doing a nine shows so
so sorry corporate gig i will come right back it's a corporate gig yes
for cool for a company um i had to i still haven't done my homework on them
yet but for yeah it's like a company well i hope it goes like a white
supremacist group yeah yeah something about like pure race
and uh sure controlling the banks i forget
but yeah all the companies are that way nowadays so what are you gonna do yeah
you can't tell one from the other they're throwing a party of the
chattahoochee they're throwing a party and they're throwing uh
they're throwing the letters dei into a burning dumpster
oh damn it to hell damn it all uh but i uh yes i gotta fly out there
and i'm flying to chicago and driving from there's a two-hour drive
and i figured with the weather and stuff i'd be better flying to a major
airport and i wanted no connections because of my baggage
so i'm yeah doing a fly she has a name and it's sarah
but uh yeah uh new year's resolution was to start learning spanish
and piano i haven't started piano yet okay
because i but you're studying spanish now yeah i've downloaded two apps
all right matt let's see well you let me put you to the test
let me grill you good number of apps let me grill you matt
go ahead juan es alto como es juan
juan es alto si
all right okay you've passed level one you've passed level one
for people who aren't on the video side of this podcast
paul was so genuinely happy when he said c
he was so pleased with himself
uh i don't they call me paul duolingo manningly okay they do call you that
that's what i've done one is jump speak and one is duolingo
yeah okay uh and they both it's a 21 jump speak
21 jump that's it right and this is eventually the goal is that i can go
undercover into spanish high schools and hunt down drug dealers
so that's what happens if you graduate you go into a recruiting program
hola fellow students
donde esta la cocaine factory como es juan
we we speak english oh de nada you're clearly an old white guy
come on i'm trying out for the track team tomorrow
oh i'm sorry but uh in that case you've got that bichman button shit
so one of the things they ask you is they say you know can do you want us to
uh download your contacts to see who else is doing
this oh and they could partner you up do that
and normally i say no to all of those yeah
things uh but because they're gonna bombard your friends with shit
i was like oh let's give it a shot no and i haven't heard from anyone else
yelling at me yet but i woke up to my first kind of social aspect
text from duo lingo oh oh hey your buddy rick pesano is studying
spanish on here do you want to connect with rick
and i couldn't write back to duo lingo to be like rick's been dead for six years
but sure like if you god if you can connect me to
my dead friend rick like yeah wait a minute it's like a
fucking ouija board kind of feature the dual the only way
promising the only way to talk to ghosts is spanish
then yeah let's let's commit let's do this
what is the spanish word for ghost have you been wanting to talk to your
dead friends and relatives come try duo lingo duo lingo we guarantee
that you can talk to your dead friends and relatives
duo lingo it's a it's a side it's a side
app called you will linger
it keeps you in contact with all your dead friends after you expire
you will linger uh lets you chat to everyone you've ever
know you will linger yes we use ai generative
bullshit to make your friends talk back to you from the grave
it's not as scary as it sounds except when the ai takes
over and starts talking all kinds of racist trash because that's what they do
all of your dead family members will be racist
they're all racist now oh my god damn it's what happens when you die you become
racist i guess so
i'll tell you who else became racist and that's the following sponsor
today's show is brought to you by stiffy's wood service that's right from
kiss me where it smells funny in 2024 stiffy's wood service hey there i'm
stiffy don't you know i got me some wood for
you you want me to bring some over to your house
i'll sell to you for a good price i've got a bunch of wood
a bunch of wood in my back trunk stiffy puts wood in the trunk if you know what
i mean you want some of stiffy's wood from the
trunk come and get it stiffy got wood stiffy got all the wood you need
stiffy got sticks and twigs stiffy got half trees
stiffy got wood stiffy got wood
stiffy got wood stiffy got wood stiffy got that wood
wow break it down
it all comes to check out what the fuck is happening
i don't know there's too many ads too quick in a row
my brain my brain's not working well today well
maybe one of us caused this first ad to be a little late in the program
oh oh now we're shifting blame around well okay
so we're not shifting it around i think it's been in the same place the whole
time oh really all right matt all right matt
let's let's let's shift some other things around how
about this one how about this one donde esta la biblioteca
uh si one es biblioteca sure great
one s biblioteca in the chat
biblioteca looking motherfucker
biblioteca looking ass you stack of books
i'll knock you over like a stack of books i'll take you out like a stack of
books fucking wand always looking like a
biblioteca new fucking and rice collection looking son of a bitch
you know in steven king novel section and then in the biblioteca
looking so do we decimal have an asshole
you card catalog located motherfucker
do they even have card catalogs at the library more
yes i don't know sure because we've all been to the library recently
um i have why i was late to the podcast i have
everything was 50 off i think i take i take my kids to the library but we
rarely we don't usually use the dewey decimal system over there
no i guess most of it's all been transferred to
computer but i wonder if they ever i guess did they
i know there's no reason to keep all that data i guess on cards
uh i wonder what the i should look online i'm just asking questions into the
fucking void but what can you consider a good repurposing
of those dewey decimal card holders all those huge those huge like very
specifically sized drawers well what would you imagine would be a good
second use for those spice rack comes to mind a very large
spice rack i mean for a for like a for like an industrial kitchen
i don't i mean that's a lot of spices it would take up a lot it does take up a
lot of space gun rack could you fit a rifle in some of
those long boxes probably oh be kind of cool to just pull out a
shelf of guns i've got it i've got it what do you got
don't even move them out of the library turn them into beehives
in the library just in the library beehives an apiary i mean they would
work as hives i suppose yep no no i think that i figured it out
canada library crystals saying business cards
uh ravi saying storage of chinese medicine yeah that's how i think uh
rhino penises would slide in there pretty good
um well once you dehydrate them of course j i wasn't talking about non
dehydrated rhino penises those are what you're always talking
about hydrated rhino penises paul
you won't shut up about hydrated rhino penis
just because it was my band in college you'll have that one single we did have
that one single it was good the shirt was the thing that
kept us going we had a really cool shirt for hydrated rhino penis
oh yeah yeah what was the three-dimensional aspect of it that i
think people really appreciate it people liked it it was made of that
remember that puffy paint that was such a rage back in the late 80s
it was all puffy paint puffy paint shirts were terrible
puffy paint dehydrate or hydrated rhino penis shirts
were all the rage at my school
modern day apothecary tables yeah that could be cool
oh my god they could store pokemon and magic cards holy shit
that'd be an awesome way to store your pokemon and magic
card i like all these suggestions like we have a giant card catalog what could
we repurpose this as oh a card holder i know i know it's dumb but it would work
exactly right exactly okay all right yeah you're right
all right what else what other thing could you do
that i already said beehive already got the right answer what about
a bunch of weird long ways aquariums
but that would have to be just fish that like living in the dark most of the time
or or he left the drawer oh eels eels that don't want to turn around
drawers of eels and snakes that don't want to turn around
eels that hate turning around
oh my god oh it would be great for organizing lego
yes would be awesome for that i keep waiting for paul to move on to
anything else but he just keeps listing off things that people are saying that
you can do with a card catalog i think it's a great topic we're not
talking about enough because think about the thousands of
libraries that are out in the country right now
and think about the disused uh-huh dewy decimal card catalog holders
i mean it's our universities those probably took up a room
sure right sure and did this is the problem we need to be dealing with are
we just destroying this furniture are we just throwing these out is that
what's happening no they repurposed it a very long
aquarium repurpose recycle reuse into very long aquariums for eels that
don't need to turn right yeah or we could you need directional
eels we could put uh beta fish they don't move around very much
or is that just because people are cool to them the who kind of fish
the alpha fish uh alpha fish don't don't aren't that's not real
that the guy who wrote about the alpha fish regrets his paper about the alpha
yeah but you got that whole gig you you got that whole gig teaching alpha fish
how to talk to people i did i did but i misconstrued it and i
thought it was part of the whole alphabet i thought it was a alphabet fish
but you do love a bit i do yeah don't get me started omega fish
the alpha fish oh mega oh mega me
oh i can't believe i'm gonna move on from this but let's do some scoop mail
message for you son you you can move on all you want i am continuing to come up
with repurposing ideas for disused card catalogs
and i'm continuing to use greek letters with aquatic animals
next up zy dolphins
zy dolphin sounds like a fucking new medicine for ed
i would like to introduce everyone to this my epsilon seahorse
i was like uh i got targeted on instagram for
like basically like don't get the wrong ed meds if you have to pee urgently
after you have an orgasm do you like do you sprint to the toilet after
after you have an orgasm there must be there's a greater
there's a greater scientific uh uh area of concern uh going on
and i was like wait wait isn't that isn't that the whole thing you orgasm and
then pee like that's the whole thing it's like
it's that's your doctor paul that's your doctor it's just one continuous stream
right you just wait for you for you guys orgasm
and peeing is different
wait what's happening the ad is like why is the world spinning
do you think you're into golden showers you're not
you have a scientific health issue that needs addressing
oh no boy oh boy that the the amount of treatment for that shit
i mean i guess it's whatever well no i know for me i was like wait i'm not
i'm not even at step one of this medical thing yet so like why are we
how did i end up how did you get on that targeting on the long end of the arc of
that yeah that is that is very specific
like yeah do you find yeah have you experienced slight green
discoloration in your balls after ejaculating using this
medication you might be using the wrong stuff
you have food coloring you have food coloring you've been eating green eggs
and ham we got an email from scoopy ramon
hey gentleman of the churn and possible guest
nope uh through a series of random mental connections not worth detailing
here i recently found myself regaling someone
with a story of enthusiasm over experience from my past
it made me think that one or all of you might have a story that fits this
category okay most of my most of my stories are
enthusiasm over experience wait a minute are we are we insinuating
that our enthusiasm outpaces our experience
well when you when we say i love boobies what does that sound like does it sound
like we have experience or does it sound like we're just enthusiastic
enthusiastic yeah i mean we are enthusiastic
in that respect my enthusiasm far outpaces my experience there you go
so here's my example of enthusiasm versus experience in high school
i first caught the acting bug by doing the school plays a friend of mine i'll
call him chuck because that was his name had played an extra as a freshman and
had told me repeatedly about how much fun it was and how many girls were in the
school plays one of those two things convinced me
to audition fast forward a bit and chuck and i are
now both extras in the next school play the play was the crucible and as
freshmen we were both relegated to extras in a
scene where two or three other characters are talking
chuck and i were to play jail guards or something but they were of course
non-speaking parts but shouldn't we do be doing something
dumbass attention starve 16 year old me asked that exact question
fine just don't steal focus was the reply and thus in the production of the
crucible in my high school there were two puritanical jail
guards who so fervently believed that the rest of the world
was too chill about armageddon and stuff to stay in england
did their best to not make any noise as they shot dice in the background of the
salem witch trials also i can't tell if it makes it better
or worse that we uh all my calls check up i'm doing
scoop mail there you go sorry i can't tell if it makes it better or
worse than we fashioned our own dice out of play from the art room
so that they would be period in hopes that the director would let us do more
in the play that is way worse definitely worse but
definitely hilarious that is hilarious period dice
and there's no way no way those dice rolled true
right so they could have rigged some kind of gambling scheme
because they certainly always rolled you know six or something like you know
right there's no way they built great evenly weight distributed clay dice
probably you uh you guys want to get into my dice game here i got a i got a
dice game going on over here i got a special homemade dice i just got to sell
them hard on the whole you gotta sell them hard on the
crucible thing and that these are you know era appropriate gambling
that's right once once they pre-script me for a craftsman we could take them for
all the money we have you remember how back in back in the
day it was all dice in the alleys down those
puritan streets that's why they were
anyway ever get it over your head on something with enthusiasm
for something that now you have some more experience and it was an obvious
rookie mistake much love f-y-i-t-f-y-d-a-t-f-o-w-i-a-t-f
that's scoopy ramone thank you scoopy ramone
thank you and i appreciate this on a deep level
uh i had this experience when i was in kindergarten
and was in a school play and i was an elf
sneaking onto the stage backing up and i was to bump into santa claus and be
surprised and i insisted i insisted that i hold
a toy and then drop it in surprise and shock
i was like how about i tell you i was i was giving i gave myself business
i was like how about i take a toy and i and i well
when i bump into santa oh that's good that's good i dropped the toy
and they were like fine whatever you know and i did i was obnoxious and i was
you know 18 19 is my freshman year and only year
of college um we did rosa krenz and gilbert also your senior year
is it yeah uh we did rosa krenz and gilbert are dead
yeah and i got cast as just polonius right it was just really
in that show like not you know in hamlet and vital character but still like a
you know like a a tertiary role kind of thing and
rosa gilbert are dead i really just came in to illustrate that what's happening
throughout hamlet right and i did so much business
and i tried to get so much laughs for being like a baddie old man like i
was obnoxious looking back i'm like so ashamed
like if i if i were me now in a play with me then i would be like
can you chill the fuck out and play your part can you just
accept that you didn't get cast as rosen krenzer gilbert's turn
can you just move on uh you know it was uh it was it was it was
obnoxious i i got to bust out
during my mad donnelly has a question that's correct that's exactly
that's exactly the level it was at during my college freshman year i got to
play roland maul in present laughter and i that character is just
annoying and crazy and so i just got to go
ballistic as a young ham and it was fucking glorious and i killed it it was
it was really really really fun but then also i was like well
fuck i that i was in a main production with all the graduate
students i think i'm done here oh boy i was like i don't know
seriously i got like third from the top billing like what the fuck
what else what else is going on it's six more years to do this again
no thanks i'm fucking out of here i really that was really one of those
things i took away from that experience was like oh okay
i can go do other stuff now
and he did i sure did indeed go do other stuff and still is doing
other stuff and unless he's died between the recording
of publishing of this episode you never know
and i'm still doing uh the uh more enthusiasm than experience
when i got to do the the warm-up gig for p&t yeah exactly
that was ridiculously crazy but it worked out worked out real good
but that i was just very lucky right place right time
and boy oh boy was that guy previous to me just tanking it
i mean yeah you initially had like a different job right or whatever
were you there when he got fired or yeah i was there as pen stand in
yeah i was doing i was doing right yeah you were doing standing work yeah i was
doing standing work and then i kept doing standing work and the warm-up
right for that season that was wild that was a lot of work yeah it's fun
though i think every job i've ever taken was
definitely taken with enthusiasm over experience
yeah yeah i mean at least up until i was
35 right uh including including when matt called me and said you want to do a
podcast i mean i would say that would definitely
be enthusiasm over experience for all three of us
except for me paul that well yeah i mean well but not not really
i don't i don't have any experience i i had experience talking into a
microphone that's about it oh i don't i still don't know diddly
squad about putting together a podcast properly
not true i mean i know a little bit but not not a ton
i don't get on the feeds i don't when other podcasters ask us for advice they
are disappointed often exactly
like i don't know record it and throw it in the ether
yeah release the episodes on time i don't know yeah right
yeah i can't i can't don't show up a half hour late
i can't start off my ted talk with be friends with pen
why not it'd be a hard one to do
it's not easy to execute advice but it is that it is advice that can be executed
can be can be done we got an email here from
anonymous uh here's a what would you do story
so we had a little what would you do action it starts when i visited
a dance scene that i hadn't gone to in about 15 years
i hit it off with a guy i used to know and like a scene from a film
we danced together for most of the late night
blues party it was romantic and incredibly hot
when we left he carefully asked i might be reading this wrong
but would you like to have coffee sometime uh to reassure him on several
levels i answered yes that is the perfect thing to say
that is much better than my suggestion which was to go to my hotel room
and fuck whoa it's a good answer it's a solid answer
when we met for a date i was glad to find uh we were both vaccinated atheists
he's 15 years older than me though which put me on edge because of a bad
experience i had with an older guy i started worrying we wouldn't be
compatible and saw a red flag when he mentioned a right of center newspaper
still he was kind and empathetic and the chemistry was hard to ignore
at this point what would you do at this point
i could continue on the day you keep on getting to know each other right
do we know the gender of our writer we don't okay
i feel like gay or straight if an older man came to meet you if you
wanted to say let's let's cut through the bullshit and go fuck i feel like they
would do it well i think the writer was was saying
that to be funny more than more than like an actual
suggestion right the other person the other person they had been dancing with
said like hey you know we've been dancing we're having a good time tonight
would you be interested in going to get a coffee
and they're like i we i am interested in getting coffee
i was gonna say we should go fuck but yes let's go get coffee right
so then the question is how we feel about if they started mentioning right
wing newspapers all right yeah like kind of just where
we're at at this point with it i guess so there's a little bit of a little bit
of uh stuff that they're worried about a little bit of stuff that writers
worried about age that made the newspaper i guess um
but still kind empathetic and had good chemistry
so yeah uh we did our best to be respectful and with full consent
uh that it might be a one time only thing we spent the night
okay uh turned out he's good in bed oh and and we have a kink in common
so i got very excited at the potential to explore this
which would be a first for me okay shipping right that's what i'm guessing
toesucking shrimp let's go
over the next weeks we spoke on the phone a few times
in an impressive backfire of complimenting me
he said he only wants to date women at least 10 years younger
because women his own age look old what i called him out on this casual
sexism and he apologized guys where's the empathy
here so next know that i'll be breaking up with you in nine years
yeah right i said good day
don't get comfortable universal all women age the same
all men don't don't worry about it uh wow no problem
i called him out of this casual sexism and he apologized
next it came out that he voted for a political party that i don't like
but i don't want to be an i hate people who vote
x person finally uh like he was quoting a sound bite
he said it's hypocritical to believe in global warming
and still fly yep he doesn't believe in global warming come on
i got the feeling he didn't always think before speaking
most people wouldn't call their promising sex partner a hypocrite
with a cell by date uh oh with a cell by date right
and this is all just making this sex hotter yeah
you know like oh yes for sure that's the kink the kink
it's just oh tell me more horrible opinions
oh yeah shut up and keep fucking me you big dummy
go having my first peri-menopausal mood swings i crashed hard
and ended things spell dei with your tongue on my toes
go
hey that sounds like a good night
uh having my first peri-menopausal mood swings i crashed hard and ended things
damn it i get very uncomfortable with debates and didn't attack his beliefs
i spoke my piece he listened and it and it didn't become an argument
he apologized properly and was shaken by how much he had upset me
it was the most respectful breakup call i ever had
shortly after that time three people i knew got terminal diagnoses
and depressing political stuff was happening at a low point i asked myself
what would i do if i only had six months left
my reaction was i would call that guy and tell him don't say anything about
anything let's just have some fun
this is really hard right it is this is really hard
because it's hard to meet anyone that you're simpatico with
in general yeah oh that kind of hard yes that's also hard
and then to try and navigate especially currently
just how polarizing opinions can be sure but what how important like we've made
everything so important when i was uh
single i remember being an atheist like factored faster than i thought it
would like i was certainly willing to not give a
shit about that person being christian uh and the early dating parts yeah and it
just it kind of it would come to a head faster than i
than i thought it would yeah time you know yeah well that's just a
younger generation thing i mean they don't they don't view blowjobs
as a thing that you need to wait on as much anymore
but it's it's true in relationships if you you know if you find out that your
partner is prone to magical thinking then
it opens up other doors and if you find your partner is prone to saying
off-color possibly bigoted shit there's probably other shit behind there
too right like that's well also i mean maybe if you
you know i think it's i think it's hard to examine like
male loneliness uh white male loneliness has like its own
thing but like the truth is like this is an example like
wherever this guy is getting his echo chamber yeah there's no such as global
warming right you're breaking up with him sends him
back to that space right yeah but but yeah but i don't know
yeah but it's not and it's not your job responsibility to save yeah it's not
woman's responsibility to save all of stupid white male america
like i mean you know i've been i've been uh i've been out of the game guys
uh no but uh you know whatever we're all married
but the thing we want we want i found a woman who would save me
the thing that i do for my single friends is you know like write down
everything you want in a man right so in this case if you
wanted to say awesome in bed believes in science like
you know like like what happens is like when you write that list down it is not
crazy to look at that list that list is not like there's no one on earth who
could fit this bill no not at all and like and i did i did
that before i ended up uh dating and i made my specific list of
things i wanted in a partner and it not only does it reinforce
what's important to you but it narrows your field of vision
and you don't just go wild off the handle looking at people who
it just quickly nullifies possible bad choices
right it sharpens your head man it's it's it's what i talk about in improv all
the time too you know the the real key to improvisation is focus
that's it where's your focus okay and so that that's it that's it it's
really just focus like i can teach a lot of different stuff but focus is what it
really a lot of what it really comes down to
and with anything decide what's important
decide what you're truly looking for get clear about
goals and uh things that are important to you and
the [ __ ] falls away yeah but it's hard to keep focus
it's that and that's especially true now and that's why we see a lot of what's
going on within our political spectrum it is designed to destroy focus
sure yeah yeah for sure uh i don't want to i'm gonna go back to
other point but what you're i don't want to yeah no no no please do yeah that
point is valid but i think so many times like our ability
to be flexible to be giving to want to
put things on the line to like our willingness to possibly change to help
to bend for other folks yes uh i think you can get lost in that ship
yes and and then and then you combine that with the sunk cost
fallacy uh yes good example my membership massage envy
and you suddenly and you turn and you're like wait i've been i've been in this
shitty relationship you're like i can't get three thousand dollars with the
massages in a month i can't do it
and and you you think you're gonna get out of relationship you're gonna be
embarrassed you think your friends are gonna think oh my god you put so much
time in your friends won't care at all uh uh you know uh it's it they don't care
about you but they won't care that that that you put more time or less time in
they don't you you anytime you take a step towards being
healthier your friends are going to be grateful that you're in a better space
no matter how long it took you to do it um that's worth saying on its own also
uh if they're your real friends right and not your frenemies and that's it
and that goes another saying saying that goes from what we're talking about also
you can be you should be also be more selfish about your friends
you should be you know if you if you have a dysfunctional relationship with
your friendship group or you feel like you're
you know not truly like uh jive on a mute it's not truly mutual
with your friends group you should get new friends you should try to find it uh
any kind of hobby any kind of club any kind of meeting yeah you're right
any kind of bar oh there he goes here we go
you know what he can do better than us paul jacob can do better than us and
i'm glad he's gone i i wait a minute i i looked around
i turned out i couldn't do better that's a double edge right there
he could do better than that's what i'm glad he's gone i actually know that i'm
saying i know that i'm saying as a guy who
lives in like you know an urban and suburban
environment uh you know we have numerous scoops right us you know
where they have basically stayed in their religion longer simply because
they would know they'd be completely alone in their community
sure right become atheists like i understand that this is an uphill battle
and bigger things uh i'm only saying in your heart
don't think that like compromise compromising all of your wants is the
only way you know right right i think you made the
right choice in uh put the kibosh on it because fool me once shame on me shame
on you fool me twice shame on on me and oh wait what do you what kibosh
is has happened here well she she broke it off
and the writer you mean they broke it off what
uh i haven't finished reading this email yet oh i thought i
i thought they broke it oh shit oh no oh oh no we've just got we've gotten
sidetracked my friends there's more email ah fuck me in the bottom
what would i do if i only had six months left my reaction was
i would call that guy and tell him don't say anything about anything
let's just have some fun oh no that thought stopped me crying
i asked myself seriously am i that shallow
and my brain said yes oh wow you asked what i want
and i told you if you can broker that deal i'm in
after a cooling off period i arranged to call him we agreed that being friends
was a disaster and i said i had heard of the concept of
sex clubs where apparently you don't discuss politics
how would he feel about meeting as if we were at a sex club
he said i can be there in an hour and a half
he added if i turn up and you decide no i'll drive home
and i'll not sulk about it which was a helpful reassurance
oh so this this guy definitely had uh had has
some reassuring uh qualities to him sure this is smart
this is yes we had a better night than the first
at the time of writing we meet every couple of months always checking we're
still okay with it and enjoying it while it lasts
we've had some amazing times and he's said and done some very kind and
thoughtful things the kink exploring is going very well
can't believe it took me this long to buy some sex toys
i found he's a fan of uh tim mentions poem
uh storm and of pennanteller's bullshit so he has critical thinking awareness
it's just well behind the times and certainly not helped by the media and
politics that he follows maybe some of my attitudes will rub off
on him maybe some other things will rub off on him too
as i try to avoid generalizing or being negative
and i really try to understand rather than judge so
am i naive liberated morally challenged making the world a slightly happier
place or all of the above thanks for reading fucking with the
faces in a private sex dungeon after a good spanking
tied with easy escape cuffs that's anonymous
anonymous thank you so much for sharing and being so open with us
uh that's this is a lot of fodder here um to think on go through those options
again am i go ahead jacob am i it was it was a b c and d
do you remember uh let's see am i let me find it here
uh as i try to
uh as i try to avoid generalizing and or being negative and i try
to understand rather than judge so am i am i naive
you want to do one at a time yes am i naive no
i don't think so no am i liberated yes yes you're liberated yes definitely am i
morally challenged no no don't think so making the world a
slightly happier place yes i think so yes yes that's it no like
yes i don't think you're naive i don't think you're morally challenged i think
you are liberated i think you i think you are making the world a
slightly happier place both for you and your uh companion
yeah the like look you said you have kinks and fetishes right like that's
that's often a very difficult conversation to to broach on in a
regular dating environment you found someone who fits the bill
uh you want me to put this light bulb where and they agree to
everything right you put out everything you wanted again you just did we just
talked about without whether we got to it
you were like if it could be this and not that and always this and never that
and he said yes you both intelligently made an agreement
will that get sloppy at some points or we end up in the conversation at some
points sure sure but that happens in every relationship
no matter what you're doing anyway so like what you did do was actually you
literally came up with your most selfish list for this person to still be in your
life and this person said they'd happily
fit those parameters that's awesome you laid it out this person accepted
and it seems like it's going okay because now you might meet another guy
who's also dynamo in the boudoir and uh and and then decide i don't need
to meet this uh this this right winger for for private
sex anymore that might happen but you you've actually
allowed yourself to leave that door properly open
right right if you were dysfunctionally dating this person and you were going to
meet someone and be like oh but i'm dating someone oh but it might get messy
now you now you're fucked up right but you you have the exact sexual
relationship you want with this person you want to use this person he
says use me uh you're in that spot you've
appropriately set expectations yes and now you if you would now encounter
someone you could have a more fulfilling relationship with
you'd be able to move on to that thing no problem
right now i think this is a nice thing i think this is a nice thing anonymous
very much so uh speaking of nice things it's gonna be nice how about i beat
paul and matt and jack versus nerd
i'm on the hunt for balls
it's possible i just discovered that we've already played the scooperty that
i oh well better discovered early yeah i better
find it now than eight questions in
we're pros everybody we have an obelisk game coming to us today from yarn and
sticks in the chat thank you so much oh yeah the
yard and six in the chat nice what up uh this is the one where we
have the double downs we have the steals we have all those things
uh in this obelisk game that i had definitely planned for
before this moment that you're hearing all the better right now here to see it
that's great here we go all right so we got uh two
hundred dollar question all the way up to five thousand dollar questions
we have double downs we have steals we have super super steals and we can do a
50 50 lifeline one time a matt has control
starting off uh matt the category is celebrities it's
the 200 dollar question i don't think anybody's gonna steal from you
let's go let's roll name the supermodel who had a talk show from 2005 to 2010
cindy crofford kate moss tyra banks or christy turlington
let me see tyra banks tyra banks it was tyra banks okay i was gonna guess
that but i was i part of me thought cindy crofford maybe
it's any crop i feel like cindy crofford did shit something on mtv
where is yeah how is she doing style show uh cindy come in here we got
questions for you uh it turns out that mole has
overtaken 90 percent of her face oh my god it was it was a guado all along
i'm cindy crofford now bing bing i'm the crofford
uh it's a sport like cindy are you paul what you're not stealing sports are
you no i ain't stealing sports no category
sports matt on november 23rd 2025 the raiders played against the browns
who won the browns the raiders the colts or the lions
this is a good one as a reminder you have a 50 50 lifeline that you can use
i'm gonna go with the browns the browns is correct it is the browns
you i know the raiders only won two games so i had to figure out whether that
was one of them yeah 600 dollar question
food food anybody doing anything no food
name the main ingredient in a typical salad
lettuce cabbage chicken fries in pittsburgh answer is d
i'm not kidding they put it in all they put fries on things that go
gourmet yeah per manny's uh manny brothers yeah
to the devil's lettuce uh a please let's see it is a
well done matt you're on a you're on a tear yeah it's going pretty well
800 dollar question what am i oh what am i
whatever if i contain flour butter salt nutmeg ginger cinnamon eggs
brown sugar condensed milk pumpkin puree then what am i your mom
oh a jack-o-lantern a pumpkin pie a pumpkin roll or a pumpkin head
i
let's see pumpkin pie is obviously the lean to i'm just making sure it's not a
pumpkin roll uh flour butter salt nutmeg ginger cinnamon
eggs brown sugar condensed milk pumpkin puree
it's gotta go pumpkin pie pumpkin pie pumpkin pie
it is a pumpkin pie all right nothing's stopping me
no one can stop my little pumpkin pie thank you
i'll steal damn it paul is stealing super steel or steel
regular steel regular steel what am i part two my scientific name
is dihydrogen monoxide and i can kill you in many ways what am i
ethyl alcohol uh also ethyl alcohol mercury or water water d
water yeah paul loves that d keeping it wet loving the d sweet d yeah
what am i part three
okay i am widely distributed i am a widely
distributed animal with a pointed muzzle and bushy tail
i range in color from black white brown and red
uh vulpes vulpes vulpes vulpes vulpes is my scientific name what am i wolf dog
fox or mouse
oh i think that's a wolf but i'm not
a hundred now i'll go with wolf a wolf let's try wolf
it's a fox shit ah boo oh what does the fox say
now uh question uh earth and it's going to matt now fuck that i'm
stealing it what how dare you this coarse-grained igneous
rock is found in kitchens and driveways and has
a uh what is that mose m.o.h.s i never
mose hardness of six seven yeah six seven diamond shale sandstone or
granite uh found in kitchens and driveways i
mean granite gotta be granite for a kitchen countertop right
i think so i think i'll go granite d granite
yeah yeah the moon it's the 1600 dollar question and it's the moon
approximately how long does it take for the moon to rotate 360 degrees
on its axis an earth year an earth day an earth minute an earth month
it's uh wait the the rotation is that one
wait is it wrote is it the rotation of the orbit i think it's the full year
because we always see the same side so it rotates along with us
right i think you maybe yeah sure earth year i'll try i'll go i'll go year
no it's a month oh i'm wrong there you go yeah me too paul riddle me this
it's a 2500 dollar question let's riddle me this
i'll double down oh paul doubling down why not
i run but never walk have a mouth but never talk
i have a head but never weep and a bed but never sleep
that's a river a river rubber or volcano
it is a river a river runs through it a river does run through it a 3000 dollar
question oh steel oh no
oh oh is right matt stole it this author is known for the novels of
mice and men grapes of wrath east of eden and the winter of our
discontent to name a few
douglas adams pierce anthony or john steinebeck
i wish it was pierce anthony i can imagine a pierce anthony grapes of wrath
that'd be something great i believe this is steinbeck
oh no i'm sorry it's orson wells orson wells
we were looking for orson wells there we were looking for orson well no it's
course it's steinbeck let's see four thousand dollar question
snacks super steel damn it
what year were spaghettios first sold with the slogan
the best invention since the napkin wow that's a beating
that's a great one
1882 1975 1965 or 1860 i'm gonna use my little 50/50 action right here
good call that got rid of 1860 and 1975 oh thanks for getting rid of the
fucking 1975 spaghettios release
motherfuckers um i mean was it 1800s jesus
fuck no uh i can't be i mean we're gonna go 65 1965
gotta final answer it is yeah gotta be
so five thousand dollar question
i have to try i super steel wait what happens
oh paul gets a super still first
don't i get to double down first still hungry for the five thousand dollar
question paul did say it first
which two candles were named after horses
candies candies which two candies were named after horses
baby ruth and kitkat kitkat and snickers lollipop and saltwater taffy
snickers and lollipop 50/50 me please let's see here that got rid of
baby ruth and kitkat and kitkat and snickers
so paul has lollipop and saltwater taffy snickers and lollipop
which two candies were named after horses boy oh boy these were the two i was
debating over anyway
wait how do i have zero oh someone super steeled me god damn it
someone did super steeled you
i'll go see let's try lollipop and saltwater taffy
ah it's d snickers and lollipop paul got it wrong lollipop and snickers
boo i got zero again jacob wins with ten thousand four hundred points
pole and matter both tied at zero pole and matter tied which also means jacob
wins jacob double wins which means jacob loses
nobody wins oh my goodness game which means jacob wins which means
jacob wins shit thank you yarn and cats i should if you
want to sit as an obelisk jock versus nerd or a scooperty or a hey scoops
all the things over there at hey scoops hey scoops dot com that's where to go go
to hey scoops dot com that was a good one yarn and sticks thank you so much
thank you so much obelisk yarn and sticks i should have super stole there
just look at the hang of this game yeah well aren't we all i don't know
could you would did you know snickers no i knew snickers you knew snickers was a
horse i knew stickers had been named after a was named after a horse yeah
was the horse named snickers yes
wow all right that's what i've been told i don't know
podcast speaking of bed i have to get going so that i can
do a podcast with him uh oh yeah there's no more we thank uh people always
support us on patreon it's a new month we're still trying to figure out who
runs our patreon uh and so uh we'll get a list together
hopefully by the next recording next week oh sure i would hope so yeah we can
figure this out and we can figure it out by then
uh but uh if you want to be thanked on air or get other kinds of rewards from
us if you just want to support our podcast
in general and have the uh room in your wallet to do so please
head over to preachingfund.com it's like the fee a tier that fits your
budget today easy for me to say
oh i'm sorry i was at the toy store go to farts in a bag dot bits
that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preachingfund.com it takes you
over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can
upkeep this show on the air we are dependent on our patreon supporters
that is how we are able to do this show so if you think this show is worth more
than zero dollars preachingfund.com farts in a bag dot
biz those are the places that you can go to show it
three dollars a month that's all you have to do to help keep this show going
you can either do it by the month you can do it by the year and you can gift
subscriptions to other people you can do all those things right over
there at farts in a bag dot biz and and uh preachingfund.com yeah
absolutely thanks for listening today's show thanks for listening to any show
um that we make i should say not just any show in general
uh stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
uh
see ya