Oh hello there. I am so glad you're here because I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers right now
I'd like to thank Fifi Frankie's Tiki scoop Galactic president scooper star makes scoops a lot ice blue scoop
I want a scoop baby and Jacob Dinkalega
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks
And I hope you do preaching fun.com is where you can go preaching fun.com right over there
You can sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows?
The life you save may be your own
And now a program
Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
We had a party at the house last night I stayed up too late
I said, were you drinking?
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social sitting in Las Vegas
It's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pittsburgh PA. That's Paul Mattingly also sitting in Las Vegas. It's me Jacob the audio guy
We're preaching fun. We sure are yee-haw
Well, I did it guys. I taught my first improv class in a long time
In a well, I've been teaching other improv classes
But this is my first structured improv class in a long time where I'm having the same students over and over again
I got 12. The second woo was for the structure not for the improv class. 12 wonderful students
You got a good structure and I gotta say I'm I'm a little apprehensive because of course at the end of class
What do you think I did?
Fart. I obelisked all of them. I gave everybody I gave everybody a chip
So, you know everybody a chip. I'm either gonna have some people coming back being like, oh wow Paul
Okay, or be like who am I learning from good?
So anyway, yeah
Exactly, I took the gamble and we'll see but a big thanks again to Justin for getting things cooking again with skit and forgive me
Yeah, you know, it's it's it's gonna be really good it's a more good stuff happening you haven't figured it out
Justin Zell's not in it for the money. I don't know. I don't know if you have to figure that out yet
But or if he is he's bad at it. Well, no, and you know what? Well, the other thing is - neither am I I mean
You're not teaching improv to make you know, but it is helping me do less target work, which is great
That's exactly it. That's exactly it
Yeah, one less day of
Working at a target that is precisely it. I have cut back to basically three days a week now and
It's gonna save my ass cuz oh man. Oh
Cash grab Mattingly. That's right. That's good
I don't want you walking around target too much because I don't want that sweet sweet dairy air to fade away
I mean, it's true the word you got to keep them cakes
Maybe the words of sir mix a lot ringing my ears every day, especially days like today
But I'm slurping on a little chocolate milkshake. I know when you're sad bands or sit-ups, but please don't lose that
But no trust trust this this shelf is only intact. This is here, baby. Yeah
Matt Donnelly, you're back on dry land. Yeah, man. Yes. Yeah
Attend your party, but literally I haven't been home in a month. So it was like oh
SJ was like I sent Matt and Sarah
Text about the party. I didn't I didn't hear back from them
I didn't say anything to her, but I was like that they are not coming
Back on land they're not coming to our house
Two nights in a row got to be have all four of us home with our children
Yeah, and then of course, yeah, I was on full soccer dad duties last night
Which yeah, that's lovely around town or whatever. But yeah, how are the boys?
Did you notice any changes since you were gone?
Yes, yeah, they got an employment. Yeah, that's a six seven
Yeah, so I was in the car with my oldest and and
Somebody goes to school with driving them home and I told it was like, you know
My son now my oldest son now goes to performing arts middle school. So that means I'm probably impromptu games. That's awesome
Totally and so we were comparing because I just went home for what the last thing I did was I did it my improv jam room
Which I want to talk a lot about on the show. Yeah
But we were going over improv games and I said, yeah, these are games
I started playing when I was like 16 17 years old and they started laughing
And I said wait 16 17 counts as six seven. Ah
Did they did they get called out doesn't really like oh, yeah. Yeah, they're laughing. Yeah. Yeah good
No, no, they're not subtle about it. Like we're driving the car. My kid is like perfect time
I look at it says six or seven on the on the dad
Like it's not so it's everywhere. It's everywhere. Yeah. Yeah easiness
The new South Park is is all it's all of it. Also, they all know that it means nothing. Yeah, right, right
Yeah, it's just gibberish. This is just you know
They know that like it just happened to be in a song and then some guy did a little tick-tock and it's all out there
Yeah, it's just a vaguely annoyed some of their parents. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
so yeah, but I
went
Theotic clumsy they were just laughing at the idea of you being young. Yes, that part is definitely
Well, I don't think even we were putting together the improv lineup we're like, you know
I know it's been 27 years. We do this has been 27 years
We did that I go can we we should stop saying 27 years. It's definitely been 31 years
That's what's blowing my mind when I'm teaching again like 21 years
One of my students asked me straight up
I'm like 20 years and I'm like wait, I've been teaching like 22 years and if I've been teaching 22 years, I've been improvising
Oh my god, no, let's not go down this rabbit hole
This is no press rabbit hole for any of us to go down
But this is like what I'm just talking about like as my buddy Pat my buddy Pat
He's gonna be doing the Tierney's thing with us this Thursday
I found out that I've been spelling his name wrong for our entire friendship, which was embarrassing
He was like, I'm pretty sure we talked about this multiple times. I was like I have a
False memory of you telling me how to spell your name properly where I it's Pat Shepard
I've been spelling it with the second. I've been fun at Sheppard and
Okay, I thought for a fact. That's actually what he instructed me to do one time
He's like like it's like Shep and Hart and I was like great and I literally had a conversation with him
Like just like three days ago or he was like, nope
Never said that never starts to do that definitely been all ease on my last name the entire time. You've known me
Was like how do I make up for the fact that I've been spelling you like I can't
That's like there's no mea culpa. Like we're lifelong friends. Like we are
Retire improv lives and I I think the only thing that you can do here is tell him how to spell your last name
Incorrectly, yeah, let him spell it correctly the rest of your life
My braves really racking like possible like big-time solutions because it's so embarrassing
How do you undo 30 years of mistakes like like it's also like it's the number one bitch behind my back, right?
If you're like guys need to spell my fucking name, right? We're supposed to be brothers
You know, right like I have no defense for being like if there's any sense of like I am a fucking ogre selfish ogre
It's like I never learned how to spell. I was better than what I thought you meant though
I thought you meant you were misspelling Pat. No
PIT Pat
And it's not like we're casual friends
No, like possible side effects many press releases many articles many listings of who's playing in the shows
I've put out his name numerous times and shout it to the rafters with incorrect spelling just 30 years. I
I don't think I don't think that you can change it. I think the only way forward is to continue on
When he was like no, we've definitely conversations about I think well clearly I don't remember I go
I would I just want to say clearly one. I'm sorry and two
This wasn't some elaborate trolling that I've been doing up for 30 years. Like I don't
I know I'm capable of these bits
Oh man side note on the word bit
Fucking so jealous Amy Poehler great podcast and she's in two people about two elaborate bits
One is the guy Cole Escala who wrote the Oh Mary Mary. Oh, yeah. Yeah
So they are so fucking funny there. He has a bit where he calls someone and on their voicemail
He leaves a message as if he's talking to someone else's voicemail about the person so he's talking about having to kill the person
He's leaving a message for to another person
Yeah, so like if I called Paul, I'd be like, what's up, Jacob? Look, it's got to go down Paul's out of hand
Yes, yeah we have to murder Paul so that's a bit he does with all of his friends that he has to murder these
Colluding with their other friends to murder that person great
That's pretty I'm so jealous of that bit and then fucking Aziz and Zari
His bet on Amy Poehler was fantastic
so he found out Amy Poehler's kids the names of their best friends and
So when the kids would visit set Aziz and Zari would walk by on the phone
Pretending to talk to their best friends and ignoring them
Ha Amy Poehler's children's best friends. So he would not speak to her children
He would pretend to speak to their friends and it was it's like, you know
Dalton or something. Yeah. Yeah, but it was yeah, they're like, oh, yeah. Hey Dalton. No, I haven't seen Amy Poehler's kids around lately
Yeah, I don't know where they are. I'm sure they're fine, but I don't know where they are. Let's get together
Let's say this let's do that. Like he's just like
And I'm like, oh, that's a really good bit that is a really really good thing
But yeah, yeah, so
But yeah, so we got together
Hilariously at Kevin Smith's smod castle. We did the reunion, right? Yes
And so I just walk in and I'm just surrounded by Kevin Smith
Everything right they've decorated everything just a ton of memorabilia. I just saw there's a
He just got the the mall rats poster original art. Yeah, very very recently framed up
That's the Drew Struzan piece who just just passed away passed away a legendary artist Drew Struzan
Yeah, so he did I mean really it's worth looking up that guy
He did every movie Oh everything that we grew up with for sure. Yeah, he did. Oh, yeah
Yeah, that is that's something that I've been wanting to get into kind of quietly for a long time as old movie posters
And start collecting those but that is the bar to entry getting into that kind of collection is intense
Well, if you're getting like because I mean what he bought was the original
Painted work, right? Yeah
Right, which is even crazy. Yes, it's like 30 30. I'm not even looking at that kind of stuff
But yeah, it's even just the original prints though. Oh sure
in movie house
Because a lot of those are double printed right so they can be illuminated from the back and that kind of thing a lot
Of more double printed or a lot of them have like multiple things with the with the silver bay. It's all yeah. Yeah
Yeah, all right. Sorry to completely derail, but yes
And you're full of all this memorabilia
Even one part there's a the poster with like that's one of those stereoscopic vision posters for you. Oh, yeah
Yeah, sailboat the schooner. Yeah. Yeah, and so that James had a bob underneath and then Jay talking
I have a button that was misprinted and has Simon Bob talking with the comic book bubble
Oh funny. It's one of my like what's one of my like little piece of memorabilia
I'm keeping for it should be valuable in there. It's a misprint
So it turns out Kevin Smith decided to do a mall rats full cast reunion video
I mean the movie watching and Q&A with the entire cast on the same exact night as my
Did you get him a chip that's all I want to know that's all I know I
Know I know if I know if Matt got him a chip or not
No, this is this is I've already shared on this pot
I believe some of my friend wrote me like hey, maybe we can get a picture of Kevin Smith, and I said maybe you can
I'm all for you know forgiveness and sleeping dogs lies like that, but I'm not like about to initiate like hey
It's me not on that night not on that night, right?
Hey while you're back together the entire cast of all rights. Do you remember kicking me out of a film?
I just want you to know that I'm
By the way, I don't know if you've heard this thing called a podcast, but I have one here, please
You've heard of this thing called a podcast mr. 18 podcasts
So yeah, there's no in on me
That you remember kicking me off of a movie 20-something years ago
The only thing that was funny is that I basically ran right in
I was crossing the street, and he was rounding the corner
And then there he was and I literally just stopped dead in the sidewalk and the crosswalk
Walked backwards and just let I just like I don't even want to be able to
See me it happens to recognize me. I don't want this to happen right here. Yeah, I was like no
I thought I was gonna be okay if we just happen to run each other it literally happened. I was like nope
I'd rather just let it
My heart was like just you do your thing tonight, I'll do mine, and we'll just be happy, okay
Let's just get through the rest of our lives man
Worry about this no no we got plenty in our lives. We could just move on
Nothing is plenty of dirt on top of that hatchet right nothing buries that hatchet plenty
So I'm not saying nothing buries it to the point where it's not embarrassing the next time you have to have a conversation
Yeah, because the truth is it's a 90% chance. He doesn't remember at all
You know I mean like this is just a chance. He does not remember whatsoever
You know and I also have to remember that that film did not become like American Pie
It's enough to go on to do like I can't it wasn't all rats
I bring up the movie and people go what and you're like yeah
So so it's like it's not
I even you know the more important is that I buried the hatchet with Brian who wrote it and had to
Suffer you know that whole political situation is look at this movie made
Right, but even I hopped on one of his Instagram lives
And it was like he was going over how it just came out on on DVD now
You can just buy it. Yeah, and then I popped on his Instagram live
And he's just going over how amazing the cast was and everything was amazing and I was like no
Maybe I'm not totally over it. Okay. Bye, and I just kind of clicked off the live to be like that's enough
You know so I've still you know I've still spoken with everyone
In it we've all we've all done everything else with our lives. It's all fine, but I just was like oh god
What a funny curveball to just have
You know there's a lot around the block not for improv jam. You know there's a
bit right but
We got in there they set up a little stage for us in the movie theater and
We sold out we sold out the show and it was a house and
and I
Met holding a grudge. I'm shocked and surprised. I'm doing my best to not be a jersey stereotype all right
I'm trying to be an evolved person
You're doing great, buddy. You're doing great
It's only who doesn't hold a grudge the guy who ran improv jam because I left that in a very fiery political way
You know 20 some odd years ago
Yes 20 something years ago when I wanted to show Kevin Smith what what I took my college money and funded a TV pilot with
My in-buff group not our in-buff group mine. I left
my hometown in-buff group started my own in college and took the most inexperienced group and decided they were the ones I wanted to
Work with and we did a TV pilot with them again that became a real TV show
Maybe I wouldn't be invited back to the region, but again it went on didn't know success like the other like the movie
Just a bunch of people holding grudges throwing money around and no one's better for it
And in fact like there was like the original cool group of the show and then there was like the class that came right after us
we're all reunited right because
My buddy Pete never left the the group and so he stayed on and and and bonded with another the crew that came right after us
So it really was like two classes of the show reuniting
30 years later and I was laughing because someone's like where do these new guys come from and I was like
Well, they came from the fact that Tom Pat and I quit and started our own group and went up north to Jersey
so it created a vacuum of
availability for the cast so
You're like oh I can answer that question. Yeah hoisted by your own
Exactly. So it was a 14 person cast all of us playing games. We haven't played in years
I'm the most recent holy shit. That's a lie
And Jacob you're gonna laugh at this, right?
So they put together a game and Pete did a good job distributing all the games all the different people. Ah
And he gave to Jeopardy and he went to Jeopardy and he was like blah blah blah
He goes in Lance you'll host and Lance made a face and I literally froze. I go I go freeze. Oh Lance
I go yeah
Have you was hosting jeopardy your thing when you did the show that was not part of your your cast
He's not not really I go. Do you know how to host jeopardy?
And he goes no, I go, okay
Switch games with me. I will host jeopardy you you do this other game. Yeah
It's like and I said, I'm really sorry
I was like I don't want to like step on anyone's toes
I go but hosting jeopardy is super hard and I just made this mistake. I just made this mistake
I made our audio guy with no improv background host jeopardy and I forgot that the jeopardy host is the hardest job in that game
Right. It is to sell everyone's jokes. You have to repeat and sell everybody's jokes
And you have to move the show along based on the funniest answer and you have to get a sense of whether someone else
Might have a funnier answer. It is not you just throw somebody in to do it or whatever. And so I
It's a showrunner more than yes. It's a showrunner more than an imp like now. I know exactly what to do
Do it but like that day I was like, oh y'all want what now? Yes
We got on stage. It was like, oh, it's this. Yes. I see that. Yeah, even when it's the most like it's the most like joke like
Pimping you into making dumb jokes, right? It's it's even harder than 185 or those games. Oh, yeah, and so
I hopped on that grenade Jacob and I was like, no, I'm hosting. I'm hosting jeopardy how to go
Oh, it went really well. It went really well
I mean the most thing was that honestly like the thing was that Michael Keefe was the guy who ran improv jam when I was a kid
he was the funniest person I'd ever seen when I went and saw that show like he was so funny and
I was steal his bits and do his bits in high school and get attention for it
and then I finally got in the show and got to perform next to him and
When we all got together, you know, he's he was older than us and and so
You know, I could but I could see him like he had 14 people. He's bouncing 14 people and I could see that
He was like not like he was kind of champing up a bit a little bit to be funny
And he was kind of you know, all right, right?
He was kind of making sure everyone's getting getting fed or whatever. And so when dating game came around I just was like
He was explaining the three kids. I go. Nope. There's four contestants in this one Mike and you are contestant number four
And so I threw him in a dating game and then and then also I was up for jeopardy and I turned to Pete
I go I'm gonna do it again and he's like people up here. I go
Nope, there'll be four people playing in jeopardy tonight Mike for and you're playing in that one as well
We're doing this
Yeah, I
The only I was really happy for myself was
That like I because I had departed and even reconciled and departed multiple times on
shaky ground I actually just straight up after after his last game just said by the way everybody like all of us are here and
All of us went on to different things with our lives over the conference that came from doing this show
Please let's give Mike a proper round of applause for what he's done for everybody here and we got standing ovation in the theater
I was happy because I I
Really like I said, I I I was very driven and
Certainly at times very egotistical and I was definitely enough through my own thing and I had my own political battles with that
Of course when you look back, you're like boy, am I just a dumb 18 year old kid in those arguments, right? Yes
And that show just meant so much to me and I did not
realize the nostalgia
Factor I was too busy trying to make sure that we were getting 14 people into a show
I knew I was pretty experienced compared to some of the other people coming back. I was really trying to make sure
You were the most practice, you know the most recently practiced. Yeah, and so I was trying to really just kind of make sure
you know because our shows with Brad and
Jonathan, I mean that's like keeping up with fucking two amazing Titans, you know
I certainly felt like very in shape for this reunion, right? Yeah
I
Did not give myself like the I did not for a second
I was like, oh wait, you're going back to the epicenter of your entire creative life
Do you know what I mean? Like you're going back to where you were 16 17 and you started doing
I'm so young at hip
No, like so like my buddy Tom who had a stroke nine months ago and we were literally just told like check in with his wife
day up
like whether he would make it or not whether he'd want to play or not or whatever and
So
Tom walked in and my buddy Nick
Those are the guys that were in this show before I get in those the guys that I looked at be like I want to
Play on stage with those guys, right?
He just walked in the first person saw was Nick and I just saw Tom and Nick hug and just seeing those two together
I literally just started lose it like right there. It was like five o'clock the shows at eight. Oh, you were done
Yeah, I was like good lord, you know
Yeah, and I just wasn't really all this was like how the hell do we make this 14 person improv show?
The bunch of people haven't practiced go. Well, that's all that was on my mind
the entire time going into this this has this has to be good, you know, and
I was not prepared emotionally to be like nobody you're going back to like day one
You're going back to like the starter space on the game board
and it was really crazy to just feel those other people playing games and going like that that like I was feeling 17 was like
Oh, I love this game. I want to play this game, too
You know like I was like I want to all the games like all and I just was like right back to being a 17 year
old just like love on the show also like this weird thing like
Mike came from
sack beater in Orlando
They start they coach the crowds and they say
But before every scene seen in and the whole crowd goes five four three two one
Arts that's fun. It is fun
And none of us took it off on our separate improv endeavors
Like Elvis went off to do other improv endeavors and we never did that so we were all just waiting to be introduced and he coached
The crowd and doing it and hearing a full theater do the countdown again
We all all 14 of us back 13 of us mics on stage all 13 of us went home
like we like
We all just got hit in the stomach with a bowling ball like right off the bat like before we even hit the stage
It was like this crazy
nostalgia of it and
It was awesome
everybody really
Impressed me
Everybody was really held their own and did all the right things to start all the games and the crowd was into it
There's a lot of people who was their first improv show
Which I was going to see their first improv show. Yes, because it was listed on the Smodcastle newsletter. Oh
So like half the crowd was nostalgic people
We're just like oh, I want to go see some yeah, and it being fucking 30 years a lot of people brought their kids
Who were the same age as we were?
Like when we were watching the show a lot of people were showing their kids what they watched when they were their age
And that was a really big trip
And yeah, it was just it was it was just a blast it was just a crazy night out and yeah
we did all the old games and
It was it was it was a crazy nutty
Thing to do. I was really glad we did it. I can't imagine doing it again anytime soon
And then with that in mind we're only getting older right so like right to wait 30 years to do it is
Crazy, and then you're like, well 10 more years than I'm really weird because there was no way we can do all that shit
You know even when Mike went up we made him do a motion roller coaster
and
That was always like this is the strangest thing about this show is that that was our closer
Before we did a music we did we did we would close with a song at the very end
But the last game we'd play is emotional roller coaster which basically was a tip of the cap to whoever we thought was
Hot shit right that person got to do all the emotion changing so like our way of ending our show was like now one
Person gets a show off for you like it's really weird. It's like really weird to look back, so I was like oh
Mike is gonna change Mike. We'll make Mike change
I'll do the last game and they'll okay and to incorporate everyone else had everyone else called the different emotions
I just went down the line to every performer, and they and they all change their
emotions or whatever, but I was like
We made such a weird show that was oddly popular, and it was not like
It was not a wholesome
Improv everyone gets along we're all looking out for each other kind of thing
It was a very looking back on it. We were all like young hungry comedians
It was very competitive it was very much like I I've earned my right to do a motion roller coaster
Like those things came back into my head
You know like it's not like a and not a formula that you can just go and recreate
With a with a different group either it sounds like no I mean this is like I said
I've had the I've had the a very blessed improv life, right?
So I've gone off to many other places and seen short form along form shows everywhere
And when I say things like oh, we would close with the motion roller coaster people go like what like that's a starter game
That's like a one. That's that's a first three gamer and most people's repertoire. This is just a silly throwaway game
But like and I said and I've said this when I came back to them
I go you know every short form show basically becomes a review like it basically becomes a kind of a rehearsed deal
Where you do things with a certain energy you you you you perform it a certain way
And you basically also kind of maybe steal other people's bits and jokes to create like a greatest hits version of this game
Which this is inevitable it's inevitable it happens every theater that was everywhere and no one wants us to admit it
But basically but that's what right why why those shows basically when you come in you go
Oh because I love trying to sit in with every group and try to get everyone's vibe
And it was always very interesting to see like what elements of their shows were just like oh
This is just a piece like even though this is an improv game. This is a set piece that I can't help
I can't walk onto this I can't help this out
I have to hands off this piece for this particular group
They have a thing that they do on this one
And it's part of what made me hate short form for a long time
It's part of what made me resent it as not improv and and maybe like a long form zealot for a good
You know 15 years after the fact, you know, like it was like I'm doing actual improv and you're doing a review, you know
But as I get older and we learned Paul with our various endeavors in Las Vegas is sometimes putting together review is really fucking hard
Sometimes it can be really not funny at all. Yeah, very easy. It's very easy to fuck up games. Yes
I mean it they're gent. They're, you know generated to help you succeed
But if you don't know the tricks and if you don't know how to intro the fucking thing, right look out
Mike comes from snack theater. Thanks sectors. We're Jonathan Wayne Brady Nathan Fillion. All those guys came from
A lot of friends that Paul and I have came out of there. And yes, they'll be quicker money like oh when you intro this game
Don't forget this bit, you know, like so we did jeopardy. I forgot that we used human buzzers, right?
So we bring humans up and then Mike literally goes. Oh, don't forget
We have say before we start the game you put your buzzers down
And then I go. Oh, I forgot. I totally forgot about that bit and then I said, oh, yeah
All right before we start the game go ahead because just put your buzzers down and they all start insulting the people who came up
to help them
And it gets a huge laugh and I was like fucking bits man the fucking little show little zings
It just keep keep things flowing keep the energy high and and it's it's another one of the things
I've you know again, I love teaching level one because it always keeps me on my toes keeps me
Remembering that it's basics basics basics always and that's just it like just reminding people that it's a show
Reminding people that they can relax and we know what we're doing even though we don't that's it
It's that we know we're doing like Jonathan. You're in good hands Jonathan
Megan does a bit if you put Jonathan charge of writing something down you have to remember that he does this bit and
And I've only done, you know, however shows with him
but he he you start you start saying things for Jonathan to write down and
And then you wait and like the third one you go you get in all this Jonathan and he will go
Oh, no, I'm just drawing a cat and they'll turn over the pad and show that he's just drawn a cat and written nothing down
Yeah, and that and that bit if you nail it kills feels like if you do it wrong too too soon
If you forget he was doing the bit, he'll finish it himself
It goes okay, but you have to remember that Jonathan does the bit where if he picks up the bat, he's gonna draw a cat
And those are the things that make it a review and not a pure show
But it's the kind of thing that makes an art school like all these guys these guys have a back pop
They got together. Yeah little stuff
when we did our
our show on
Saturday the teacher show I just grabbed a few pieces like, you know, we're doing puppets
I'm just you know, the old make sure no one touches the bikini zone
that's just one little thing like that's a little throwaway line, but it just gets a laugh and gets everybody, you know going and
at the top of
We were doing to start and we did a little 20-minute lot or so long form, you know after an interview
The interview was pretty heavy. And so at the end of the interview, I was like, okay
So what we're about to do now is a little bit of a long form piece
It's gonna be a little more theatrical more scenic things might come in might go away might come back
You might see characters return in different times or whatever, but that's what's gonna be a little more theatrical a little more long form
And it's all intended to be comedic which I've grabbed from you
And then and it just ends it with them like and then they're been the audience laughs cuz they're like, you know
But it's good to remind them that yeah, we're trying to be funny here, even though we just talked about some really deep shit
Right is I've added to that before I go. I'll pause and go like I go like the whole time
It's gonna be comedic like the whole time
And I only added that bit because commies gotten dicier as it ever as we've gotten older, you know, that's it gotten different
Well, we were interviewing this gal and just stuff just kept coming up, you know
And and she's like, you know just some heavy stuff and and and she's like and I you know
she's in this meeting and like stuff is getting very
Politically charged and partisan for no good reason and it feels oh boy. And so I'm like and I'm like
No, I really appreciate you
Telling us that you know human rights are partisan now cuz I wasn't 100% but now I get it
Okay, this is good. Cuz yeah, because that's what you know
That's what she was dealing with was just these insane things that are happening because it is it's insane times. It's insane times
Cuz like Nick right like his specialty was to bring in political stuff or do a little satire
Uh-huh, and he was saying after the show that he felt weird that he couldn't play the way he normally played because no
Satire is dead baby. Satire is dead. It's just it's just too much to throw in an audience
How can you make fun of this shit? It makes fun of itself. I know it's beyond parody. Yeah
So yeah. Yeah, I mean
Yeah, just just just a fucking crazy I said, oh so
One of the games we play is a game called space jump and the way space
It's kind of a freeze tag ish game except that, you know
One person starts off dancing you call freeze you come and you make a scene based on the way that person's frozen
Two-person scene they keep doing something physical freeze something changes it third person comes in and you go
What typically our show we have five or six people in the ship in the cast
Six person would come in first and leave first
So you do you do a six person scene and then they find a reason to leave and you go right back to that five person
scene
You would keep adding as they come in you tagged out you just nobody tagged out
You just it just grew more and more it from the freeze. Okay, cool
So pkpels like we're gonna do a 14-person space jump
Oh, and I laugh really hard and he like he had like a moment daddy goes, right? I think oh, I'm sorry
Yes, we're definitely absolutely
I'm already laughing at it. It's great
yeah, I know my hand like this might take a half hour like like this might take up the majority of our things or whatever and
And it is intended to be comedic and instead everyone everyone may have like they're opening lines all of them
And so the guys either call or call in response freeze
big laugh on big laugh on the freeze and so it was like lightning fast all the way up to 14 and then it became this
Hilarious game of trying to remember all of them on the way out. Oh, right
I can that what we're doing. What are we doing? Yeah, everyone's gonna try to be like who's seen is it who's
And it was just and it just paid off huge and it's easy for like 14 and 13 maybe even 12
Yeah, you get down to like 11 10 and then you get like eight and nine. Yeah
They're frozen there were hands up holding a casket and when I see the physicality change
So they litters like six people staring at each other
And then one guy finally goes up we drop the casket
So
Yeah, just so many moments my dad came out check it out. Oh wonderful. Nice. And I said man, it's been a while
I've worked hard to get in this show. He goes. Oh, yeah, you were terrible when you started
I was like not wrong not wrong
He literally like betrayed like it was a vivid memory in his mind of me having stage fright the first time I was in the show
Really? Yeah, and he was like you were like and he posed as me like frozen on the sidelines
I was like, that's exactly what happened in my first show. I was absolutely
totally
stage-fritten
Past tense, but yeah. Yeah, I was I was just
Yeah, it was it was it was a really crazy crazy emotional experience to go for Wow
You know, who else doesn't know how to say the word frightened. That's the following sponsor
I like stage-fritten
Is brought to you by
Spanx for skanks. Yeah, sorry
Magic Shell scoop in 2024. That's Spanx for skanks
Hey, I'm crack hard
Jessica and I love me some crack. I
Also love to look fit and tight in my Louboutin's and my hot couture
So after I smoke some crack I throw on some Spanx but not just any Spanx
Spanx for skanks their number one customer is me crack or Jessica and my crack pipe
These skank Spanx are built for skanks like me. They got a crack pipe holder
They got a place where you could put your weed. They got a place where you can pee right in them when you're wearing them
Nobody see that's right
These things are made for skanks. You can skank these Spanx up like nobody's business and nobody will even know
Meanwhile, I'm walking the red carpet high as fuck and don't nobody blink because I'm wearing skank Spanx
Everybody thinks I got it all together. I don't the only thing that's holding me together
He's tight-ass undergarments, but I'm pissing in them and don't nobody know
So I say that's a win
You take that skank home and you just open it like like like a mattress that was just delivered you slowly get those
Spanx off
They only last for 12 hours, that's the Spanx can't guarantee 12 hours
But after that, it's like the fucking
It'll pumpkin your ass real hard
So watch it watch watch your time girls set your watches and shit cuz that stuff will explode
Enter a scoops of checkout
The worst part about that is her parents named her crack whore Jessica
Determinism
Yeah
Yeah, so I just got back from the doctor got my neck ultrasound good times
Oh boy. Yeah, you got the results of this neck ultrasound. The lady said things are running back
So it'll be like a week or two and I said well heading out of town now. She's like, well, that's great
So yeah, it'll be like probably two weeks. There's nothing with my neck. That means I can't fly because I'm gonna go fly exactly
That's the one thing I kind of thought I was like well if I do have any kind of artery problems
I guess the flights gonna just do a number of whatever who cares
You're gonna figure it out. I can promise you at 50 feeling the way I do
My blood is not flowing as perfectly as it should be I can say that definitively
I think it's I don't think there's any major blockages or anything
But but I could I could stick it stand to be better. I'm sure one of our friends came to the house last night
And he had uh, what he said at first was that he nicked his lip shaving and then it was bleeding profusely
Yeah, I thought that was odd. It turned out. It was the like the the beard clippers
Okay, the clippers like got in there. Yeah, like took a little hunk out of his lip
So there's like a deep deep deep dig there. Yeah
But it was bleeding for a couple of hours. It was my gosh like
Fusely for it because it was right on his lip. It was right on like the the not above where your mustache is
But like down on the lip. Yeah. Yeah. So anytime he would
Smile move his lip and move his mouth at all. You know, just open right back up. Oof
Yeah, this is this is how we live now
You can remind him that of course the
The area of the mouth and eyes are the first to heal. So there you go
Mm-hmm
I'm laying down and she she gooed
she put a towel under my neck and everything and then she she gooed me up with the jelly and then she did and then she
Ultrasounded me and I got to hear my heartbeat for the first time on the monitor
I really felt like I was my own baby. It was really interesting
Boy
We can hear a heartbeat we've got a heartbeat I could hear whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh, you know that that sound
Through with the heartbeats. I was like, oh she had to do that eight different times and find it just right out and it
Was like oh I can hear him. He's in there
It was really interesting to hear my own blood
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm like all that sweet baby boy he's bleeding inside. He's just a gushing and a swishing
But from my untrained ear sounded pretty much the same on both sides
So I don't think there was anything. All right. Did they tell you like what they're looking to diagnose? Yes
They're looking because again because it was isolated to my left eye
right because this is all from a few weeks ago when when they went to an eye exam and they had a
Moment of they did they saw something they didn't like in your eye and it was
Bleeding there is retinal hemorrhaging. Yes
So they went and they you know, I went to the eye doc the expert and they checked it out
I don't have anything going on with the right or I didn't at least
And so but I still have had no vision impairment. No vision changes still ongoing and you still look great
I mean, thank you. Thank you. But the concern was there are you know, the arteries that go back and forth there
They the concern was because it was isolated to one eye that it could be some kind of blockage or some kind of impediment as
To the going or coming of the blood in that area. So that's what they're flushing out and then and then
She's like, I'm gonna you know
Check both sides you got any questions or anything and I was like, well, I mean
I just I know that the focus is on the left because it is only isolated to the left and and and that and that was
Kind of the weird thing. She's like, well, they check both sides in order to kind of get a baseline of what is normal
And then I went all right. Oh, yeah, of course. This is the every
every day
Medical exam of the the the Joe layman, right you get up. You're like, oh shit that really hurts over here
What the hell and you feel it and then you feel the other side and you're like, oh, that's pretty much the same
I'll be okay. Yeah, right. That's the
Whole thing you do the symmetrical nature of our bodies. That's what we do. We go. Ooh my knee. What's it?
Okay, how's this one? No, that's pretty much the same. All right, we can always do like a to be comparative shopping
That's exactly right. Exactly. So that's why as far as I know my liver is fine
That's one of the tricky ones it's the internal stuff that gets really tricky
External stuff is a little bit easier to diagnose from the self
Quote-unquote, but yeah, that was what but I thought that was he checks his left penis than his right penis. Yeah
Yeah, well as a Klingon I do have to
Yeah, yes, it is the Echidna but well now that's exactly with you know checking everything
In fact, I think it is Santa Claus who was the very first to practice this
Symmetrical diagnoses. Is that right? Yeah, he makes a list. He checks it twice
Find out if it's an ass if it's an abscess or not. Yeah, Santa Claus is rectal exam
Yeah, that's it. I'll give a shout out to a Sparta Avenue stage who hosted me for two shows
Friday night before my improv reunion up in Sparta, New Jersey
I
Sold out the first show and then no one likes to stay out late in Sparta. No
sidewalks roll up at eight, huh? Yeah
But no, I didn't know about that out here first crowd
They I think they gave me a standing ovation. All right. Wow, fantastic
And they weren't just leaving. No, they weren't just standing up to leave. It was a legitimate standing ovation
I didn't say wait guys turn around just do it this way
You didn't you didn't say hey everybody. Let's give it up for children with cancer. Yeah, I blew garbage at them
Cancer babies, huh?
Stand up for cancer babies. Thank you. Good night. Oh
Side side note. I was on the cruise ship with this couple
there there there there there
Big time magicians, but they're now more social media people than magicians, but they're violent and misty night
Yes, and they also sure they work backstage
With blame when blame comes to town. Oh, okay on Blaine's crew. So I told them that I
Michael Blaine, I was a so you were in the theater Chris angel was there and then we start talking about story and I surprised
The next day I gave him Chris angel as a question stickers
So I give those out at my shows to any Penn Sunday school listen, they love it
They they asked for an extra one for David. So I gave them. Oh, that's great. Good. Good. Did you give them a chip?
I they are all chipped up. I don't we can obelisk David Blaine. Our life is complete
How funny would it be to have David Blaine come do some crazy death defying shit at scoop fest some year at my show
I say do you listen to podcasts or whatever and I'm jokingly I'm referring to my own and then people feel like I like this
American life
And then yeah, nobody says that but I have my chips and stickers ready for that when I kick ass my show
So that's awesome. They do properly chip people. Oh, yeah, baby
Obeliskin, baby. No, no, no, but you know what that and that's that's the best way to do it
Well, that's good because that way if they get lost and somebody else takes them to the vet
They'll be able to know that they're yours. Well, but you're also your Matt Donnelly's audience. You're on the road
You've only got so much
So much capacity
All your chips at your disposal, so no, I can't literally I'm down to three three pounds of leeway
Got a good life for it and they are often exactly like 49 and like 47 pounds. Oh, yeah between the two of them
something goes up to 50 on me and I get man, but
Yeah, I've definitely multiple times been that guy at the airport
He's opening both cases and shoving one jacket from one case into the other. Yeah. Yeah all that stuff. So yeah
No, do you?
Do you feel a sense of betrayal or maybe this hadn't happened to you at the airport very often?
It's happened to me once or twice where the scale at the airport is obviously calibrated differently than the scale at my house. Yes
I'm not saying one of them is wrong and one of them is right because I don't know but they are different and that is
The most maddening thing that can happen on those travel days
No, it is and like it's not that it happens like I don't have a scale at home
I really do just lift it up with my arms and go like this feels about the time where it feels right and I'm actually
Pretty good, right? I don't want to brag but I will lift any of you up and tell you how much you weigh
But tell you if you're over or under 50 pounds. Carnival Parker blood. That's it. Just over under 50. That's it. That's the only task
You're good. You can get that you can get down there. You'll be fine. Oh, you're at least 53
So when I pack the same exact stuff and it also is like 51 pounds at the airport when I'm going out
I'm like, no, I packed this exact same case on the way in and it was 49. You jerk. Yeah
Yeah
Okay, that's close enough
Do my original foolish
Foolish trick but for real just to get a calculator start guessing people's weights
And then when they say this this thing is 53 pounds
I rip open my shirt at 53 pounds on a piece of duct tape on my chest and then I rip it off and hand it to them
Yeah, so wait, what's your question Jacob I
Don't remember great moving on Jacob. Yeah. Yeah curiosity for you. Actually hit me a guy I came out
I was unloading groceries
I left my trunk open and then I got caught in the backyard talking to my family and then okay a guy knocked on the door
And and I went I came up I was like, I bet my truck is open still and they open he goes
Hey, why don't you know your trunk is open? I said, oh, thanks. He goes he'd help with your groceries
No stranger. I do not
And they goes hey
We're walking around the neighborhood and we noticed your windows and you beautiful home and we wanted to sell you discount
Discount windows if you're willing to put our sign in your front yard that I was you're willing to do this and I go wait I
Turn this down all the time. It's probably the fourth time
I've turned the guy down with this effort that my house is a model house, but you did this deal right Jacob. We did
Yeah, did it work out?
Was everything good? Yes. Okay. Oh, oh, yes. I was everything. Everything was great
We saved a lot of money and they took some pictures of the house. It feels scammy
Yeah, right and I was trying to figure it out because I was like wait
I think Jacob did this and we never got like a bad report after the fact because I think I would have remembered if it
Went south or something, right? No, everything went great. The the bad the bad thing that happened after it was
Right out because it's still you know still cost us a pretty penny to do all of it
But it saved us ended up saving us like three grand maybe maybe thirty five hundred bucks something like that, right? So not nothing, you know
Yes, the the downturn that happened at the end of that story was right after we did that like a few weeks after we did
That kovat shut everything down and most of our income stopped coming in immediately after spending a lot of money on windows
I'm fine not swapping them out. That was us with fake grass
We like Paul to be like, can you not install the fake grass?
Like you already cut it so you'd save just the installation fee. It is done
I was like when you just have like a mountain of sand on your side of your house
Oh man, I guess go ahead
But so I'm trying to think of what I think I think it might simply be the the con of it is
Simply that Anderson windows are the standard Anderson windows are expensive and if you offer cheap windows
That aren't Anderson and people think they're gonna get shitty windows. And so the discount element just and by complementing your house
You feel flattered and then the idea that you have to hold an advertising thing to save money is like it's like the same
It's like as Paul would say taking the bottle of water for the meeting, right? You don't take the water. They offer you water
You know, it's like you're creating a currency exchange
Yes, so like I guess like it's simply about like if you want to compete with Anderson and you can buy price
competing by price doesn't work unless you do this bit is the best I can come up with I
Don't yeah, cuz ours were ours weren't Anderson, but they were another big brand. I forget what what it was
But they're they're like two or three brands in in town
No, it's like one of the big ones
That's it that's it they they sell windows and anvils never break
That's it
But yeah, so it was like another big brand and so he felt okay with it
He offered me six to seven percent off and then we just laughed at him until he left our yard. He didn't know what
new windows new windows
I'll say you also go get some new windows and they're gonna pay full price. That's the following spots
Oh my today's show is brought to you by
a
Greek yogurt. Yep. That's it Greek yogurt from scoop of Henley in 2022. This show is also brought to you by Greek yogurt
There's a bowl
And her hey scoops to check out I
Didn't just shit it I
Put it in a bowl
It makes a lot of good points not only it makes a good point good point
Jesus in the chat is pointing out that it's it's
interesting that they did take some money off of our windows to
Pay for advertising and now I can't tell you the brand name of the windows
Also why we thought it was a con is that your yard gets no
Visible there's no foot traffic. There's no traffic traffic that goes by your house. You live very you live very lonely
The the sign thing wasn't the big deal for for ours. No the big deal for ours was the pictures
Yeah, yeah pictures on the website. Yeah, yeah, that makes more sense because we have because we have a weird-looking house
That was that I think that was also why they liked our house was because it's different looking for a Vegas house
Yeah, it looks like a little cocaine compound. That's a cartel
That's precisely what it looks like. That's what everyone everyone comes to the the barbecue thinks that someone might just break out a machine gun to
Mow everybody down. Yeah, it's a fair concern. It's a fair concern
you've almost got like a
conversation den
conversation pit designed for the
Living room. Oh, yeah
I'm so I am doing the second show at the Sparta Avenue stage of its part of Jersey one of the theater community
run by awesome people
And also this is the late-night one sparsely attended
Yes
The sparsely attended one and is they boost that is by reaching out to their friends
Of course is the local magic community surrounding that so my
Magician to regular human ratio in my second shows a little off sure
And this is the things like magicians just don't you know as much as they want even the most respectful magician
It's just hard to be a regular audience member when you're doing magic, right?
So people who just don't want to do certain they give me look like you don't want to use me for this kind of
Kind of thing when I'm trying to get people from the audience. I use a lot of volunteers on my show. Yeah
This one guy was kind of like I busted his balls a little bit and he was a very chatty person
and then
So for when I have a small amount of crowds, I don't get new people, you know for for straight-ish Jack
He's the same folks over and over I just go to the two guys that have stood out the most right?
Okay, like yeah, it's basically like I can't I can't constantly get two other guys kind of thing
And so I just call by name they get up quickly to get on the show faster
and so
I bring a guy up who I've been messing with a little bit throughout the show and he'd been messing me back a little bit
But I go to raise the curtain and he covers my face and this is a bit that comes up
Oftentimes with drunk dudes on cruise ships, right?
I'm trying to do my finale and I do the joke where they raise the curtain too high to get them to lower it
I talk over it and then some people think it's funny just to keep covering my face and I let that laugh happen
And then I try to move on with the trick and then they keep doing it and then I point out to them
Hey, this bit's getting diminishing returns. Does he have people laughed at it now? They're not just just letting you know
You're not doing the bit. Let me go. It was a fine bit
It was fine bit a second ago and this guy won't stop doing the bit won't stop trying to say funny things won't stop
Trying to upstage me through the entire thing. It basically kicks the all of my jokes right in the dick
Yeah, I can't
Can't get it. So it ends fine. The show ends fine. I still short. I still get out. It's still surprising produced beers blah blah blah
and the show's over and
then
he comes right up to me after the show some signing posters right there and hitting on ships possibly and
After this motherfucker, right and he goes he goes. Hey just want to say I've really enjoyed your show
I've been a professional magician for the last 34 years. The fuck you have no
Fuck you have you've been a professional cocksucker. You've been a professional piece of shit
My head just goes that just can't be true. No
No can't be the information you're asking you're asking when his last paid gig was
People paid you to perform magic
The other magicians who helped me exactly
Pack up or like that was really weird. He was that was weird of him to do what he did to you
Yeah, I agree
Especially if he's coming to be a magician what a fucking asshole and then on top of that because you know
The way the guy introduced me it felt weird just go right into like whatever and so I started talking about how I became a
Magician to the second crowd. I was trying to know what's it up front
So I was trying to like endear them and to be like, hey sure we're hanging out
So I just told my story learning how to pen dare me learn magic and all that other stuff
And then I went into my show
I'll do that if I feel like an audience is like super cagey
I'll just tell my actual story becoming a magician to be like we're we're we're cool try to change the temperature in the room
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. So I guess that compelled him to like then he wanted to tell me his entire life story as well
Oh
This is great. And then I'm trying to get chips and stickers to two people
I recognize from coming to my show multiple times. Oh, yeah
And he almost seems like annoyed where like he gets through a part of his thing
I was like, oh cool
And I went like I just let me just get this thing real quick and he seemed like annoyed that I wasn't like hearing him
Tell me no, you can't
I'm fine with coming up to you and telling you a story. I'm fine with saying I'm a magician as well
I'm fine with all this you don't get to be annoyed when the group of people that you're doing the thing with is still a group
Of people exactly exactly nothing has changed here
Jeff lumis and Chad says that he has to be your apprentice Jeff in a way. He was asking me to become his apprentice
Basically was saying like and what did you say? I heard your story and just like you know, I'm way more experienced than you
You'll probably notice how well I handled you on stage that's just a little taste of what I can do
Yeah, I know you saw me fucking destroying on there during your fit taking your bit
Yes, I saw that you destroy my show
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was I it was that was the that was the strangest part of it for sure
Yeah, did you see chaotic clumsy's line? That's what is that in the future?
Tell me it's bigger tits to be that irritating
I am gonna steal that. Yes. Yeah, it's pretty fucking good. Pretty fucking pretty big though. Is there pretty big?
So you say he was justified yeah
Yeah, that was that was really really really strange, I'm sorry you had to go through that shit no no no
I mean I overall had a fantastic night. It was so bright and it was yeah, you know, even even though the audience was a little
Different, you know for the second show obviously if you do a show that's sold out and you're saying ovation
The second show is not gonna check all the same boxes. Exactly. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but you've got that one in your pocket rather than coming off a bad show trying to get the energy back up again
And it basically like I'm recording both shows
So it's usually it's I'm finding that the moments that I find most awkward for my shows are making the best reels on my social media
So I was like, well, this is taped and I'm sure there's more bits to come out of it this way
I bet I bet the clip of him upstaging me with the bid is gonna make a fine clip for the social media
But it was uh, yeah, so I just wanted a second show just like great another show. Let's just do it
But it's super fun super fun
Yeah, that was just the only thing would you say that you're I don't know roughly eight months away from your family have been worth it
It feels like it it feels like eight months anything more than two is just yeah
Everything feels a little weird at home. When SJ said last night she was she was like, oh, yeah
I texted Matt and Sarah about coming over I hadn't heard from him yet and that I was like, oh Matt has
You I don't know if you know this Matt has been gone since scoop fest
Yeah, and also choosing what the scoop us doesn't count as me really being a home either, right?
Right, you know, like I don't really see anybody
In the fam, so it was really in there being a really weird thing. So yeah extra week is shit. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, kids are all grown up. They
There was like there was like a crisis
Like my kids soccer team while I was gone that I wasn't there for that was annoying. Oh
Like
My youngest kids soccer team
They don't like they they always keep a certain core group players that always get new players every year
Okay, and my kid soccer coach is not like, you know, basically as teams get you know
Move on and say together or whatever some coaches basically recruit, you know
Basically, oh sure kids hop over to the other team and yeah, my kids coach does not do that
He just takes takes the random
Allotment like yeah, I believe that's actually fair to the league, right?
And probably the the healthier way to go about it as well
Right. So but what ends up happening is that we end up getting kids who aren't quite in demand for any other team, right?
And they're not in demand not because they may be bad
But that sometimes they're not in demand because they don't like trilla. They just don't they don't sure they're not reliable
don't make they're not reliable and
so
Basically my whole season my youngest has been playing with like either one man down or just enough to play the whole game with no subs
Tire season that's hard
Babies had a forfeit a game while I was gone and so it's been a bummer to not be there
For if you had been there for that one
Would they have let you suit up and and head out on the field to be the last player that they needed?
I mean, I have my cleats, you know, I have my shin guards
And I have a forged birth certificate saying that I am ten years old
Well, they just march it on out
I don't know if that kids tenure we need to see a birth certificate. You know what?
Let him play. Don't worry. Do not worry about it
Your kid can't outrun that guy
You'll be surprised to know Matt that currently what you just talked about cleats
Shin guards and a forged birth certificate stating your ten years old are also required to work in a bodega now in America
Not gonna work for you
We got an obelisk coming to us today from the upside down under scoop
This is the one where you have the the pyramid of all the different prices the questions start at two hundred dollars
They go all the way up to five thousand dollars. We have double downs. We have steals
We have super steals where we also steal the other person's money and it's a 50/50 thing
If you miss a question you lose control of the board and that's how the game works
The $200 questions coming to me first and the question is about famous dick famous dick. I'm not gonna double down
I'm betting nobody's gonna steal. So, let's see what the question is
Ron Jeremy was also known as
Be the hedgehog see the horse or D the whale
D the whale is a great porn name
My name is D the whale D the way
I would say the hedgehog. He was the hedgehog. Absolutely. Yeah
He's been just he's just bad bad bad. Is he in jail? Now? Did he die? I
Believe he's in jail. I don't think he's dead
Okay. Oh, yeah, he's he's been bad. He got bad. I
Got worse just he was bad from the jump. He got worse time went on sure and
Man, his his version of Miley Cyrus is wrecking ball is still fantastic though
I don't know hurt it separating art from artists there. No, that's right. No problem because wrecking ball is just beautiful
We can do that. Yeah, I'd see famous tits famous tits. Anybody want to steal?
I mean the category feel great about but it's too early in the game to steal. This is one that you know a lot about
I'm glad it's a low dollar question
This set of famous tits are held in place allegedly by a 40 double D bra
Dolly Parton Anna Nicole Smith Pamela Anderson and Kat Dennings
Pretty sure this is a Dolly Parton story. So I'm gonna say a Dolly Parton
It is Dolly. Hooray
And Nicole Smith was the only one that gave me Paul's famous tits
Think about with Dolly Parton
Famous farms famous farms anybody famous farms. No, here's the question. No McDonald's
Tyler Sheridan owns this famous Texas Ranch
Two sixes five sixes four sixes or six sixes. Oh my goodness. I don't know
I'm not using a 50/50 on this one
I'm at loss for Taylor Sheridan. Who is that? Is that a ballplayer?
Also known for his his tits and from the cell. Oh huge tits
I think it's let's say five sixes B five sixes
No, it's four sixes. I was one six off one six. So close
Matt that goes to you famous farmer. Anybody want to double down or steal?
I'm prepared to answer. Oh
This Canadian farmer supplements his farming income to the tune of around one million dollars a year with YouTube videos
Jabbering on about farming shit
Is it the new age farmer the millennial farmer the geriatric farmer or the Gen X farmer?
Huh?
Hey, that is the geriatric farmer
Gen X farmer the millennial farmer new age farmer
B and E feel right to me, but I don't yeah exactly. It's just it's like yeah this this the social media is conditioned
Younger people just constantly talk about their generation
Um
Let's see, I'm gonna go be the millennial farmer, let's try it
All the math was done it just worked out and one question Matt is now ahead
The thousand dollar question famous dick famous dick. All right, anybody want to do anything?
Here we go
This porn actor from the 60s reportedly had an 18 inch deenus a deenus dingus
adenus
funky cold adenus
Is that long long silver long John Delver?
long dong silver or long dong Delver
Come on Matt you were just talking about this guy long
dong
Silver deep seed you said C or D C C long dong silver is correct
There we go. I mean it had to be long dogs long
Silver that was me pretending like I didn't have all of his catalog number one super guy
Do you remember that Chris Rock portrayed long dong silver in us SNL sketch?
No, yes
There you go
Yarn and stick. What are you eating? You don't have to get on one. You can just type it. What are you eating?
Question we're back to famous tits famous tits do anything I'll steal what Paul's gonna steal regular steel
He loves them tits this modern-day Romanian porn star has a bra size of 34 M
Jesus Christ is it busty Emma busty jugs busty boobs
Or busty Elma. I'm gonna go busty Elma cuz she's Romanian D
Let's see
You're so close. It's busty Emma busty
Chocolate moose tracks ice cream. Well, that sounds delicious. Well, at least I don't lose any points
Super I still have a super steel credit to yarn and sticks for making this an actual ice cream social
Yeah, well done
I'm mad. It's back to you. It's a $1,400 question about farming about farming anybody want to do anything
It's back to me outside it. Well, yeah comes back to you Paul stole it and got it wrong. So it just comes right on back
Oh
With harvest not far away for us down under hours a day on average
Do I sit in the tractor doing my thing? Well 24 12 10 or 15 doing my thing is definitely masturbating
Right, and then these numbers must be minutes or second or a refractory period afterwards
Let's see here I have no idea so let's go 50/50 on this one. All right
That got rid of 12 and 10. So you got a 24 or D 15
Well, he's not 24 hours
Average 24 hours a day. It's harvest time to start messing for a few months
Try 15 D 15 and the 50/50 answer has never worked better
Here gathering my molars at harvest time
Holy shit $1,600 question Matt has 3,200. I have 600 and Paul has zero
Oh, but you still have a super steel. I do still have a super steel
You still have a dump. We all still have double downs. Yeah, and definitely not a cult. I'll try a steel
I'll try a regular old steel. All right
Protects my points it does this church doesn't officially have cult status
But it is the starting point for a few cult leaders like David Koresh and George spate
Scientology Catholic Church Seventh-day Adventist Church or Church of Latter-day Saints
I mean, I feel like we could just say the Catholic Church is the root of all of it
But I believe this is seven. Yeah. Yeah. I mean the Catholic Church doesn't have cool compounds. That's true. That's true
They have one is I mean the Vatican they have one cool compound
It's not really cool unless you're into fucking kids
Yeah, allegedly
We all just stopped and thought about the different jokes we could make and we all decided to just move on that's
Like no, no, no
I thought of at least four and I did and I'm passed on all of them
But here's my offer once again or many running people the Catholic Church fucks a lot of kids that I don't know
Why that's not if not a bigger deal for again sticking on this earth
it is one of those things that I will I will put my stake in the ground on that and I will speak about it because
It is infuriating to me and it has affected my life directly in a lot of negative ways. Fuck the Catholic Church forever. Yeah
Famous farms famous farms. Anybody want to do anything stealing?
I don't want to double down on farms
Here we go
This Australian station just a big farm shares a surname name with a famous Aussie movie star
Is it crow station Jackman station Robbie station or Kidman station on that tractor? I'm doing Jackman station. Yeah
for 24 minutes
Boy
I'm just gonna guess at this one. I'm gonna say
This feels like a Hugh Jackman. I'm going I'm going with the Jackman here
Let's go be Jackman station. Oh
It's Kidman station damn it Nicole Kidman in her big-ass farm
Shit it goes back to Madigan dick locations. I've got a super steel
Super steel you son of a bitch. I mean, I'll probably lose
This dick themed Aussie Beach located in Queensland is called a dicky beach be Peter Beach
See Todd your beach or d dick beach. I'll go see Todd your beach
Todd your beach dick beach private. Uh, I'm sorry. It's dicky beach dicky beach
Dicky beach. I would have done the same exact answer. I would have thought Australia's gotta have weird words for dicks
Todd your holy it goes back to Matt tally Wacker Island next to dick tit locations
Matt are you doubling down? Yes, I'm stealing I'm doubling down
Smart
This tip themed Aussie town in Victoria is called a tits Creek be titty song
See titty bong or D boob's head
I already used my 50/50. I don't use my 50/50. I'm a dummy. Yeah, you're done, but
From Paul's mistake logic dictates tits Creek, but boy does titty bong sound Australian is anything I've ever heard my really does man
That's what I was going for is titty bong boobs head and boobs head also feels Australian to me
Yeah, but titty bong like isn't bill a bong a
Aussie thing
Yes, so titty bong
Also that that could be mistaken for the universal greeting of the junkie ons
Bah we've grown our weep nitty bong. I was gonna say that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's the universal greeting
Yeah, I've done other things. Yeah, I'm just stalling for something to type the right answer in the chat
I'll go I know it's gonna be wrong, but I can't help it. I have to have to put all of my
Might behind titty bong. I just wanted to do that all the eggs going into the titty bong basket. Yeah
I would have got that right
always
Correct
$5,000 question I have to super steal it here at the end for a random question. This is the game
My favorite ICS episode is hit it's polarizing
Oh a Don Poseidon be Taco Bell Hospital see Bonnie's ball hospice
That's the milk leg episode or D Rod Stewart's bread surrogate
Those are all
Polarizing episode my guess would be A or C
Let's see either Don Poseidon or Bonnie's ball hospice
But I mean Taco Bell Hospital is that's the that's the gnarly one that has all of the it's got a lot of gross
Stuff in that one. I guess so and Rod Stewart's bread surrogate. That was wasn't that a
great night episode
Another great night episode bread surrogate was not no that was that way back in your house way back. Okay?
50-50 I'm gonna not be like Paul and yes mark use your 50-50 that got rid of a and D Don Poseidon and
Rod Stewart's bread surrogate are out. Yeah, I thought it was a or C
So, you know, I've wanted Taco Bell Hospital from the beginning. I'm going Taco Bell Hospital. Oh really final answer
See it's Bonnie's ball hospice I
Got that wrong losing all of my points Matt eat out the wind today
11,200 points versus zeros for both
That is from the upside down under scoop
Thank you so much upside down under school
Thank you
You want to send us a scooper to your appraisal strike jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd head over to preaching not
About that one. Hey scoops comm head over to hey scoops comm right there on the home page
You can do all of those things. You can send us some email you can you can do all kinds of things over there at hey scoops comm
Oh, you can buy the scoop fest merchandise
That's right. Go over there buy some scoop fest merch
Thank you. I guess we've said it explicitly but the the mystery item this year was a Fez was a scoop
Yes, and so a lot of those have been selling selling off our website as well
So yeah, it's been it's been a fun fun item to get your hands on. I don't think we'll be re restocking the Fez
So no, definitely no, no, no, it's a one-time thing
So these are gonna be yeah, this is gonna be very collectible very good while it lasts. Yeah
Yeah, and if you're doing this right now Paul I show tomorrow night very the morning it comes out Thursday Paul
I have a show tonight at Tierney's Tavern in New Jersey get there be there at the door. Go come on up
Come on up and hottest comedy spot on the East Coast that night right there
It's gonna be a really fun collection of people. It is gonna also be less than 14 people meaning
This is also gonna make more fun to play but
It'll be me Paul. My buddy's a Pat Shepard and didgeridoo from my old impossible side effects
My buddy Dion Flynn
Many people know from playing Obama and other characters on the Jimmy Fallon show and of course
Famous stand-up Kurt Bronner will be doing stand-up and improv with us there. That's tonight. That's here. He's in Montclair, New Jersey
Get there if you can or if you know someone who might want to might dig that show just come out and check out that show
It is almost guaranteed to be one of the funniest things you can do in Montclair, New Jersey that night. That's true. That's true
Yeah, and so
But sorry, they will not film it
That's just the rule of asking old friends to do in private in a while. We do not film it. Oh
Yeah, it's too dangerous to film it, yeah
but so
Yeah, come check it out. I want to thank all the people who check us out every week and put us in your ear holes
We thank you so much. I want to thank Pinch left creating this podcast. Thanks Ben
And then did you send the list? I just did. Okay, I will look at my phone
Good part of the show. I don't think it's all people supporters over at patreon.com
Slash hey scoops
these people all
Knew that it was long dong silver the whole time. Oh, that's a nice private parts nesticle scoop
Neil flash Neil appalachian neck pubes
Shockingly on theme for my credit
Nathan hooten Nathan clay Natalie Mcgee a teen
Mrs. Johnny, Australia. Mr. Head scoop Motor City Smitty Monica day
Monotonic scoop D D D D D Mohan there Mitzoula Mississippi churning scoop and milkleg scoop
The following people almost ran into Kevin Smith, but they changed the direction at the last minute
That would be Mack McKenzie Matt Glowacky Matt aka Stormageddon Matt scoop
Oh fail much. I much ice cream much ice cream Sunday. That's what that is Mark Wilson, Mark
Pickenheim Mark Mattinson Mark Gates Mark Dryden Mark Cohen Mario Rosa
Mark Sadowsky Marble tulip scoopy tree maple raisin scoop and
mama ninja scoop
The fun people all felt overwhelming paternal feelings when hearing their heartbeat from their own neck
That would be Mike Wenz Mike six Mike federally Mike Michelle geyser
Michael Michael Shaw Michael Martin Michael Calder Michael. Melissa are Chica Malia McTits and max the ginger scoop
These people will explain to you how they are superior to you at magic and what to tell you their whole life story
macho scoop Randy Sprinkles M hurts Luke Mellon
Logran see Linda Brandemere little red Leon Casab Leon Cox lemur screamer creamer
Lee forest Lee McCrae McGarrell Lee McGarrell Lee Drummond L'Oreal's Roth
Latter-day scoop and Larry Goodale
Matt Donnelly will do impressions of the following scoops at Tierney's Tavern
That's a man LAJ Kurt Hendrickson Kurt eggner Kristen claddock Colin Tony kiwifruit scoop King scoop
Can she do scoop Kevin Dory Kevin Chamberlain?
Ken Soto Ken Fargie Kelsey Kandari Keith Robert Corning scoop Keister Sunday Kay Mathis
Justin Robert Young Judy Schneider Juan Galvez J rock scoop Joshua Wilson Joshua tar Josh Roberts
Joseph Palero Joseph Foster Jordan Campbell Jonathan Johnny Parker John Jacob Schopenheimer Schmidt and
John Holshan. Thank you all so much. Hey you guys mind if I get in on this? That's my Kurt eggner
That's my Kurt eggner right there
Solid just give you a little preview
Yeah
Yeah, all these people that we thank they support us over at patreon you can too
Just figure out the tier that fits your budget either monthly or yearly and go over to preaching fun dot-com right now
Or if you would rather get a neck exam then listen to this podcast again head on over to farts in a bag dot-biz
That's farts in a bag dot-biz that along with preaching fun.com it takes you to our patreon page
Where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air if you think this show is worth
More than zero dollars patreon.com slash hey scoops. That's way too long preaching fun comm farts in a bag dot-biz get there
It's awesome. All right. Thanks. What's everybody stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
You