Oh, hello there.
I didn't see you there, but I am so glad you are here.
It's time to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Well, these are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now, I'd like to thank David Walker, Dead Laszlo, Dirty Old Scoop, Galactic President Scooper Star McScoopsalot, Ice Blue Scoop, Jacob Dinklaker, Jeff Harris, Jobeth Bowers, and John Mattingly.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I sure hope you do, PreachingFun.com is where you can go.
PreachingFun.com.
Head over there, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
And now, a show.
Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Oh, man, it's so exciting.
We have the stars of Showgirls, the unauthorized musical here.
Yes.
With us, talking about all kinds of showgirls.
It's pretty exciting.
I made an appearance right here.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting over there in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, that's Paul Mattingly.
And in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob, the audio guy.
We're PreachingFun.
I forgot Pittsburgh for a half second there.
It's easy to do.
Somewhere in Pennsylvania.
Philadelphia?
No, that's not right.
No, we're still covered in snow.
It's so cold here.
It's disgusting.
It's in the single digits, and it's going to be that way for a long time.
We're going to get hit with a lot of snow later this week.
It's going to be awful, but yeah.
I walked outside with no shoes on today and just took the dogs outside,
went and fed the fish and thought, boy, this sure is a nice January day.
Man, it's getting crazy everywhere.
Mike.
Fighting with my kid to take a sweatshirt with him every day.
He's like, I don't need one.
I was like, you might.
It might suddenly become January for real.
You don't know.
If you're out after it gets dark, you'll need one.
I leave the house every day.
If I have a backpack with me or something, I have a sweatshirt inside the backpack
because I know once it gets dark, I'll need it.
Jacob and Paul, what was your opinion of Showgirls the movie when it came out,
and what is it now?
I love it unapologetically.
We have a friend, SJ, and I have a friend who was in the Showgirls movie.
She was one of the dancers in the Showgirls movie.
So we've had multiple movie watching parties with her over the years with
different friends, and she would talk about some of her experience putting
Showgirls the movie together and all that kind of stuff.
And boy, I was the right age for Saved by the Bell, so Elizabeth Berkley coming
in to doing an NC-17 movie.
When I was in junior high, maybe a freshman in high school, was a big fucking deal.
Let me explain that to you very clearly.
It was big.
It really was like took Tiffany Amber Thiessen's Maxim photo shoot and put it on blast.
Yeah, it did.
If you think that's enough, it is not.
Hold my beer, Maxim photo shoot.
I, uh...
It took me a little while to get into that flick.
I didn't watch it during its original theatrical run.
I believe I owned it on DVD at some point.
Maybe.
I'm not sure.
But I have seen it a couple times.
It's hilarious to me.
And I am Facebook friends with Patrick Bristow, who is the catty choreographer
from the show.
Great.
He is actually good friends with my pal, Sarah McKenzie.
And Patrick Chesney, who has worked with Henson in the past.
She's a puppeteer.
And Patrick has gone on.
He is the host of Puppet Up for most of the time that that show has done, which is the
improvised Muppets thing.
Yeah, the Henson improv puppet show.
I think I know where this is going, Paul.
And no, we're not making an all-puppet version of Showgirls.
We're not doing it.
We're not going to do it.
Not yet.
And also, Matt.
It's not an all-puppet version.
It's an all-puppet version except for one human character.
That's how it goes.
That's how these movies are produced.
That's right.
Who would the one human character in Showgirls be, Paul?
Oh, it had to be Kyle MacLachlan coming back to reprise his role at this age.
He's the only one with the gravitas to pull it off.
And with a straight face.
He could do it with a straight face.
You're right.
I know.
I haven't not.
I haven't thought about this.
So, but yeah, I'm desperate that maybe one day I'll get involved with Puppet Up a little
more, too, because I've got a lot of satellite pals within that orbit.
Paul, the question wasn't about you and puppets at all, as a matter of fact.
It was, what did you think about the movie?
But what I'm saying is, what I'm saying is, Showgirls has always been rife for parody
and puppetry.
Well, I believe you do get both in this unauthorized parody.
I'm going to see it tomorrow night.
It's a press opening, so I'm going to see it tomorrow night.
Oh, nice.
I'm very excited.
I have tickets to see it, I think, on March 1st.
Okay.
Very cool.
Yeah, a group of us are going to go on March 1st and go see it.
Elaine, when this first came on your radar, what made you decide to hop in and give it
a go to be in the Showgirls parody musical?
I've always been a huge fan, and particularly a huge fan of Nomi Malone, which is the character
I'm playing.
I mean, she's just a savage.
Like, when else, as a woman, do you get to, you know, basically, like, tactically stab
people, push them down the stairs, play all of the emotions, but you're just a girl with
a dream, and you just have to do, you know, she's just dealing with the obstacles in front
of her.
I'm putting them on one by one.
Go ahead.
And, yeah, so I've always loved her, and it's a joy to play her.
A Rosie the Riveter type, if you will.
A pioneer.
Sure.
The feminist icon, writer, and director, Joe Esterhaus, named Nomi Malone, because it would
be, basically, also mean, Nomi, I am alone, and he wanted that to be.
I am alone.
very significant
about that character.
I want to see a list of
the top ten things that he wanted to be
significant in Showgirls.
Oh my god, me too.
It's quite, yeah, like the license plate.
He made all the choices
thinking he was making a very significant
movie. Good, good.
That's what I want.
Well, and he was.
Yeah, and he was right.
And touchdown, success.
Yeah. Remind
people who Naomi is.
It's Nomi, actually.
Nomi, excuse me.
Start there, start there.
I will see
myself out.
She's the main, you know,
main character, one of the main characters
in Showgirls, and
we catch up with her kind of
hitchhiking to Las Vegas.
She decides she's
going to go to Vegas and dance.
We don't know that much
about her past at the beginning.
You know, that kind of is
revealed later on, but
she's a dancer, she's
ambitious, and she
sees one of the big
production shows in Las Vegas starring
Crystal Connors, my co-star
here, Katie, and
she's kind of like,
I could do that.
And from there
ensues like the path
of ascension,
you know, taking out obstacles
as they come, whether
that be her fellow
Showgirls or like Kyle
McLaughlin, like who's the
entertainment director, wooing him,
just kind of,
you know, all the steps that
I'm sure real Showgirls
go through to make it to the top.
Well, that's what I was going to ask you. I wanted
to hear about the parallels
between Nomi and
your own showbiz career, of course.
Right.
What are the
positives and
negatives?
Well, you know, if
a man's trying to sexually harass you,
sexually harass you, you've got to pull a knife on
him, obviously.
Especially, you know, post-2016,
they really, you know, that is encouraged.
That's option one. Go right to that.
You know,
if
someone's in your way, you've got to push
them down the stairs, either literally
or figuratively, but I
do like the literal approach
personally. It is.
It works. It works.
Yeah.
Yeah. It does. And you just have to, you know,
try and make sure you don't get caught.
Because
that's the key to it all, you know.
We actually did have a guest on the show.
It was
a peep show.
And they
did have shenanigans.
Do you remember someone put pins
in her boots?
Someone was trying to sabotage her
and put thumbtacks
in her boots.
Oh, I do vaguely remember this.
That sounds familiar. There was so much
shit that went on with that show.
Tara. Yeah. Someone tried to put pins
in Tara Palsha's boots.
That makes sense.
To be fair, I did apologize.
Well, you know, this was
the path, the career path
chosen by Elvira, Mistress
of the Dark. She came up as a
Vegas showgirl. That was
how she cut her teeth. And then, speaking
of cutting their teeth, Matt, you might want to
close your ears for this. I've mentioned this before,
but it's been a minute. So, you remember
the
Jenna Jameson,
the porn star.
Who? That name's familiar.
Sorry, I was trying to... She also
went through a
dancer slash
showgirl moment
at a very early age. And at
a certain point, she went
so far. In her ambition,
she had braces
on at the time, and it would
belie her young age.
She had her brother take
pliers to her head and pull
the braces off.
Yes. Oh my gosh. In order to
pass as older.
Yeah. So,
if you've ever read her biography,
that's a hell of a showgirl
biography, too. That's pretty wild.
I'm going to do that. My son has braces right now.
I'll make sure to remove them myself with pliers.
All right. You don't own
pliers. Daddy needs smokes.
Jacob,
take my son's braces off his face.
Jacob, come over and bring some pliers.
There's got to be some silver in these things.
Melt them down.
Now, Katie,
every time I watch this movie...
Oh, sorry. I'm just going to jump right into the next question.
We both are doing the same thing. We both are transitioning to Katie.
Go ahead, Jacob. The floor is yours.
Katie, every time
I watch showgirls, I...
I am struck by
the 90s
Vegas and
all of the kind of entertainment landscape
that was 90s Vegas.
I moved here in
2007.
And you and I have been old... We're old friends.
We've known each other for a couple
of years, for a year or two.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
This is my training from SJ. I just say I've known people
for a year or two.
That's smart.
Yeah, so we've known
each other for a year or two.
How much does
that kind of old Vegas and old
showbiz casting
in Vegas and kind of that old
showbiz energy in Vegas...
How does that make you feel?
Compare that a little bit to
your old days in Vegas, if you would.
Oh, well, I mean...
I remember...
So when I moved here in 2008,
the Riviera, which is very
prominent in the backdrop of
that movie, was still up.
Some of those old
neons that you see in the movie
were still here.
And so, yeah, it just... When I watch
it now, parts
of it feel still very
like today Vegas, but
most of it feels really,
really old and
not dated, but like, oh,
that was so beautiful. Why did we
get rid of that?
Yeah.
Yeah, Vegas has gone
so mainstream now that you see old portraits
of when it was still like this cool kind of like
escape place and you're like,
oh, man, badass, right?
Yeah.
Kids from Iowa hitchhiking
on the side of the road.
Different places.
Did you always love this movie, Katie?
Did you always have a love affair with this movie?
No, I didn't really see...
It's weird the way I saw it.
Upside down.
When I grew up, both of my parents...
Yeah, right. My parents were ministers,
so I definitely didn't see
showgirls.
Until I was moving
out here, like literally the night before
I moved out here to be in Jubilee,
I watched two movies. I'm not even making
this up. I watched showgirls
and I watched Alive
because it was on TV when I was about to get on a
plane. And I don't know
what's wrong with me.
If you had given me a million
guesses for the second movie, I would have not
gotten to Alive.
Were you simply trying to scare yourself out of making
this life move? Were you trying to like,
don't do it?
I...
Yeah, I don't know. But you know, the weird thing
is that showgirls didn't make me afraid to come
out here and be in a big showgirl show. It actually
like made me even more excited.
Oh, really?
Because it was so... That movie's so pretty. The
costumes and the makeup. Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Will you give people a little inside behind the
curtain look? The audition process. We see a little
bit of like the big lineup audition for the big
Vegas showgirl show in Showgirls. Will you talk a
little bit about those big kind of...
Lineup auditions where, you know, a hundred people,
200 people, 300 people would show up and they just
have to basically go through them factory style?
Yeah. Well, the first thing that Jubilee would do,
which I totally appreciated, was they held like a
stick up. And before you even stepped on the stage,
if your head did not pass that stick, it was, thank
you so much. Goodbye. Because you're not tall
enough to be in the show then.
SJ is familiar with the stick.
Oh, no. Oh, I'm sorry.
And you're like, I know, but I still want to get my
tits out today. And now I can't even do that.
Oh, she would show up with like tall hair and
everything. And they just, they'd smush it right down
with the stick. It would be so hurt.
Oh, that's a bummer.
That stick was the director. That's the weird part.
That stick was named Fluff.
Right.
That was Fluff the stick.
Yeah. And then the next thing they would do is you
had to do PK turns across the stage because you can tell
in one PK turn, if that person has had any dance
training at all.
Oh, fascinating.
Yeah. So then they would make a cut from there and
then you'd start learning combos and stuff.
And so before the combos, what, what percentage of
people are cut before the combos?
Oh, 50.
Wow.
Yeah. Yeah. Cause a lot of girls would show up just
like, well, I'm pretty, well, I dance at this strip
club. I could be in this show kind of know me
style actually.
Yeah.
You know,
that's what I tell myself.
Where do you think they got the idea?
I leave the house.
I tell myself I'm pretty.
And then I, I, I go about my day with a lot
of confidence.
I'm pretty enough to do this.
Uh, and in this show you play, uh, uh, the, the
villain, uh, Gina Gershon's part.
Um, was that something you were looking forward to
playing and something you wanted to play?
I had played know me the last time we did this
show, which was like, Oh my God.
Almost a decade ago.
Okay.
And when Troy said he was doing it again, I said,
cool, I'll be one of the dancers.
I don't want to be, know me.
Um, cause that part's really hard.
I don't leave the stage.
It's exhausting.
And then they just pointed to her head, like
mental, no, sorry, sorry.
This is up there with pins saying, don't write
yourself running in scenes.
Very smart.
Yup.
Uh, and so then, uh, when I.
When it was getting closer to auditions, I kind
of said to him, you know, I feel like if no one
shows up for crystal that you're interested in, I
feel like I could play crystal.
I've been a show girl now for 17 years and I'm
tired and I'm jaded, you know, I get this woman
between the last iteration and this one, you felt
like you have earned the role.
Uh, 100, 100%.
Yup.
I want the role that I identify the most with, and
that is.
This person over here, go fuck yourself.
And now, uh, you and Elaine, uh, uh, have been
friends for a long time.
You guys have been accused of being twins.
Uh, uh, you've done a lot of gigs together.
Uh, was not knowing if you guys didn't realize the
audition that you'd be working with each other in
the two lead roles, right?
Well, it, so Elaine had kind of talked to me
about maybe auditioning for show girls, uh, before the
audition popped up and then she just wasn't at
auditions and fucking boss boss way to get one more.
And then like when they were looking for a Nomi, I
was like, look, there is one girl I know of in
this city that is beautiful.
That is great to work with.
And that is absolutely not afraid to be crazy ugly.
That's the requirement.
Yeah, absolutely.
Uh, and that girl was busy.
She was, she was too busy making some kind of giant
Hormel, uh, chili dip on her.
Yeah.
Elaine, as you have this entire other life as a, uh, uh, is it,
would you say bizarre cooking influencer?
How do you, how do you phrase your, your, okay.
So I, I say like.
Content creator or like internet chef, but, um, yeah, I kind
of have an alter ego that's, uh, especially on my Instagram,
like a Midwestern housewife who is well-meaning and just trying
to make, you know, semi homemade, like Sandra Lee in the largest
quantities possible.
Most of the gigantic grill that you always just pile tons of stuff on.
Yeah.
To create these amazing ornate, uh, delicious looking, but crazy huge meals.
Well, thank you for the delicious looking that's, um, such a, quite a compliment.
Yeah.
Uh, this summer, like I really, I just had this idea.
I really wanted to do Blackstone stuff.
So we got one of those big Blackstones.
I think ours is like three feet and anything that you could cook on a Blackstone or could
not cook on a Blackstone.
I tried it.
So what's your, what's your favorite, what's your least favorite?
Um, well, one of my favorites was, you know, I saw this recipe for twice baked apple and
cherry pie.
And so I went to Costco and bought three large versions of those and I, um, turned flipped
them face down on the Blackstone one after another, you know, jizzle drizzled them with
some sweetened condensed milk.
Added some other ingredients.
Just, you know, you need a, if you need like a big pie to feed a group of like 60 to a hundred,
like I definitely recommend doing it this way.
All right.
So it was like, I became friends with Elaine through just like mutual friends in town.
And so I became friends on a regular Instagram account.
And then someone's like, well, obviously she's busy being an influencer.
And I was like, wait, what?
And I was just only friends with your personal, your personal account.
Wow.
I was like, whatever.
And then I went over to your, your big page and you're making a, like a punch for like,
if you're having a backyard, you know, get together, make a punch.
And then I was like, and I was, I was, I was like duped.
You're like, show like a little thing of fruit punch and all of a sudden there's like a kiddie
pool and the kiddie pool is being filled, just filled with, with booze and liquids and
all kinds of chopped fruit and all kinds of stuff.
And I was like, what's happening?
And then I looked at your page.
I was like, it's all this.
It's all this crap.
It's all this crazy stuff.
Yeah.
You know, like lots of, uh, themed party foods.
I love it.
Sometimes it's in a fish tank.
Sometimes it's in a kiddie pool.
You gotta make the people happy.
Give them what they want.
You do.
Uh, you do.
You did one, like a pumpkin pie one near the holidays with on that big grill, like a pumpkin
thing.
And I was like, I like this.
I like weird videos.
Cause you go like, yes.
And then all of a sudden something happens.
You go, no.
And then something else happens.
You go, yes.
And then you're like, oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh.
I was like, oh my gosh.
Yeah.
when you get the call from katie was it oops i forgot or was it like were you on the fence about
committing the time like what happened there no you know what i was on the fence about getting
my boobs out ah ah sure yeah um i mean i wasn't on the i guess like i'm i haven't been in a show
like jubilee i haven't ever been i don't even do burlesque or anything like that so um you know
it was a it was a not sure slash deal breaker for me with um with that and so i had talked to her
about it but then um yeah when they didn't have a know me well i was like okay this is my uh dream
role and um i figured maybe there was a little more wiggle room for negotiation with that you
know holly berry negotiated like five hundred thousand dollars a tit in that one uh movie she
did monster i think
monster i think
monster's ball that's it wow well my rate is similar
there's also a five in it no it wasn't monster's ball monster's ball yeah it was artsy there's a
movie where she basically like like someone goes like hello and she just puts the thing like it
was like a big action movie oh yeah that's right puts a something down she's just topless on a
chair for like a split second and apparently it was like a million dollars just to do that scene
uh otherwise yeah
yeah yeah uh and then she did monster's ball just because i think just because she wanted
to hook up with billy bob thornton i think there was nothing else to it oh i get it
i mean he's dreaming now uh katie you're also very shy about nudity is that right
i was gonna say elaine you probably talked to the
one worst person to talk to if you're nervous about nudity on stage that's true
swordfish by the way swordfish swordfish that's it yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh i bet it was much
more negotiable i bet katie was probably the hardest person to negotiate with well yeah she
she was pro well katie katie takes the term wiggle room personally she's like no no if there
is room to wiggle we shall wiggle the funny thing is when
oh sorry go ahead elaine no you when when they figured out how to do the topless
not but not topless i was the only one like so i can't get my tits out now because no one else is
all right so you hit your own deal breaker katie you were then yeah yeah yeah well i was gonna say
in the parking lot post like coming in and reading with everyone i was like she only she like had me
very close to her and i was like oh my god i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so
convinced i was like well maybe like jacob by march 1st who knows buddy who knows pal that's
right that's right we'll see you've been doing uh previews um how's it been going
good really good we've had great audiences um you know some areas get like way bigger laughs
than you expected and then other areas you're like okay like this needs to be tweaked a little
because it's not getting a reaction so they've been they've been helpful and they've been
supportive and good yeah i think parodies are hard that way parodies are on the broad strokes of
course it's like it's it's it's very much a layup to obviously celebrate showgirls uh musically and
everything is super fun um but yeah parodies get really tricky because it's hard to figure out what
fits in the box like theatrically like and but you are you're poking at the fourth wall the whole time
you're dealing with an audience that has a knowledge base of the material paul and i did
50 shades the parody together so that's why um you know we're talking about that is that it was
always strange to figure out like what your relationship with the audience is with the
material um well and also it's a similar vibe with 50 shades the parody because we always joked it's
not really 50 shades the parody it's just 50 shades and look how ridiculous this is and i
think there's probably a not a similar effect all the craziness came from the source material yeah
right not not to
similar effect probably coming from showgirls because there are moments that it's just
beyond it is beyond parody some of that film yeah right i mean like direct from the script
you know what's al's line word for word it's like it must be strange not having anybody come on you
yes this is what i'm talking about yeah yes exactly
exactly and paul you relate to that line a lot yeah i was
i thought i mean talking about source material yeah i mean exactly
yeah um playing uh gina gershon's part katie are uh are was is it as fun as you thought it would be
more fun is it crazy is it hard what what what was it like taking on this role 10 years after
not playing it um there there are parts of it that feel very very natural uh i will say like
some of the things that i have to say about it are the things that i have to say about it are the
say to know me elaine are are difficult for me because elaine is so so goddamn funny um it it is
difficult at times uh well just not to laugh out loud on stage like my very first scene with her
i say something and then she screams in my face and she runs over to a wall and slams herself
into the wall and it's just like i it's that that's probably the hardest part of being crystal
everything else is natural is it was it a total head trip because you basically went from maria
to baroness von schrapp you know so what what's that shift like uh what's mentally do you find
yourself are you ever at times in opposition to the character you're playing in a way uh what's
what's the game there no never because as i've gotten older in the the tidy space that is the
classic showgirl world i see all these young green girls coming in thinking they know everything
and so i have slowly just grown into crystal i think i think that's just what happens right like
you just grow up in the entertainment industry and you go like yeah that's just that's just what
people are now i don't know what you want yeah yep yeah so you've made us into this no i was
actually that's exactly that's exactly how i feel this city and and show business in this city made
me into this
i was uh you know just just visiting with my mother-in-law and she of course uh um was in
no no net with ruby keeler when ruby keeler made her big triumphant return um or whatever and
someone brought up i'm trying to remember the the name of the other it was another movie star
and ruby keeler putting on her makeup quietly goes like yes but can she still do a thousand
taps blah blah and just talked shit about this other movie star and i was like
based on my health she's still an amazing tap shape at her age in her 60s and basically could
still out tap any any other movie star and i was like man this is the one who left show business
and still like kept her receipts oh yeah i left this whole thing i came back also fuck you
and elaine uh yeah you know my wife is working on the show as well and speaks so much so highly
of your comedic background do you have a formal comedic background or you're just a funny person
um you know i started in
theater and musical theater like when i was a kid like nine i was like nine i went to perform
arts high school and then um i went to amda in new york for two years and i started working when i
was 20 and in 2007 and actually like 2008 because i think i started taking at the people's improv
theater in new york and both um nate starkey and ashley ward were teachers of mine love those two
and then
yeah i know me too me too and then when i moved to la i was kind of at the ground lanes like on
and off because sometimes i would take breaks between levels but between 2012 and 2016 that's
a lot that's not a small background that's a background and actually what groundlings training
specifically what katie's describing your grounding training must be coming in very handy
right now with these these big choices i mean i'm
i love exactly i love like brownling style and like just characters and you know exactly
our listeners like groundlings is always about like taking your choice making you distinct and
then take it to a 10 like that's basically what they're known for is take take your smallest choice
and then make it eat everything else uh and and the character um which is why so many of them are
iconic from our old mad tv days to the ones that have the training that stuck out on senate live
and stuff it's like those are the the that kind of era of comedy where we're all all sketch comedy
was so character distinct was definitely because of groundlings yeah yeah yeah um so oh so you're
you're a heavy hitter you're you're you i didn't i didn't realize you stuck with the uh all the
training in the uh post pit so that's that's exciting um yeah it was great like i think that's
my favorite thing in life is just you know like laughter of reflection right because like it's the
best way to connect with other people i think yeah yeah i think so sometimes you do it on stage
and sometimes you do it on the internet through food but but through uh uh you are pushed you
know through pushing the envelope through through tension spots and you know and messing with people
like you do figure out through filling a kiddie pool with punch
yeah like no i think when you surprise people their re-feelings their real feelings burst
right that's that's what stand-ups do and everything else is like when you when you
surprise people their real feelings burst before they can rationalize and so suddenly that's where
you get like a real temperature a real take of what's happening in the room and when you're in
a comedic environment when we all get to laugh at that time it's a relief we're like oh good we're
all we're all flawed we're all laughing at this thing which means we're all secretly maybe hiding
our terribleness all the time yeah some of us doing a better job than others speak for yourself
hiding it
well people who want to be decent are trying
the time for that game is past my friend
uh well i'm so excited to see this show tomorrow night uh how long is it running it's running the
majestic theater we should tell people it's at the majestic theater downtown downtown arts district
beautiful beautiful downtown arts district uh so much new stuff in that downtown arts district
do yourself a favor and subscribe to our channel and we'll see you next time
uh go see the show get your tickets get there like two hours early uh walk around find yourself
something to eat uh do a little shopping in the area hang out after there are a ton of bars right
there again and walking distance from the majestic theater uh yeah it's really great the whole area
downtown there in the arts district has just been blossoming it's a vibe and and frankly the majestic
is uh right there at the forefront of that blossoming so uh so good job to them as always
i love that theater we know it's our favorite theater
theater because we oh yes we begged we begged troy to perform there all the time and so uh
he won't do it i love that uh crazy environment uh and how long is it running
through march 8th through march 8th all right we've got yeah we've got every thursday through
sunday from now until march 8th and of course special performance tomorrow night so so cool
so fantastic all right
all right anything early yeah jacob wants everyone to come up with shopping bags for some reason but
uh we'll figure that out it's fine it's fine uh your favorite scene to do elaine and then the
same question to katie um well i really love when katie and i see each other kind of for the first
time outside of the dance-off i just think like that's so much fun and and you know i think it's
so much fun and and you know i think it's so much fun and and you know i think it's so much fun and
god there's i i love the whole thing honestly beginning to end i love watching her song
constant pain i'm on stage for that and i kind of um get to just like oh that would have been a
better question much easier to answer okay elaine what's your favorite katie scene and katie what's
your favorite elaine scene much better you're a better podcaster than i am go ahead oh well
definitely like i said uh crystals big solo ballad constant pain just so much fun i think there's
so many layers to what has been added in that song and there's just things that crack me up
i mean starting with the lyrics and and what katie's put on top of it being a dancer being a
real show girl i just think that's a blast and the audience is having so much fun at that moment
yeah katie i uh for me it's definitely when elaine comes out to do a song called lap dancing um
the
the first time that she was just rehearsing it i had to excuse myself uh because i was crying
laughing so hard that i was disruptive um because i'm not going to give it away but the pole is it
plays a big part of course you know she's got to lick the pole but it plays a big part in that
number and she just goes so full out and it's so goddamn funny uh well that's it i just want to
point out yeah like much like paul and i were when we did for chase the parody what we what was
particularly great about it was original music uh you're not you're not using typical parody songs
which is a lot of parodies use typical mainstream songs just to kind of make fun of certain elements
or whatever but this is all originally scored right yeah which is that's pretty cool so yeah
a lot of great songs in it i can't wait to check it out um well thank you guys for coming by uh and
checking out ice cream social and we'll put all the links and all that into our our bio and stuff
and uh people have plenty of opportunities to go see the show downtown vegas hope you guys have an
amazing run yes thank you so much thanks for having us break all the legs y'all come see us
thank you everybody i'll tell you who else is gonna go see showgirls the musical parody at
the downtown majestic theater and that is the following sponsor today's show matt and madeline's
ice cream social is brought to you by yo-yo ma's yo-yo mart that's right from 2021
this is from one of the wills yo-yo ma's yo-yo mart
hello it is i yo-yo ma
master of the cello
what i'd like you to do is shut off your brain for a moment and hear the sound of a cello
as it's played by one of yo-yo ma's specialty yo-yos this is a duncan wonderball
um
wrong
boom boom
boom
i bang it into the into the instrument that's all i can do with it now yo-yo ma will walk the dog
and now i will do baby in the cradle
yo-yo ma's yo-yos from yo-yo ma's yo-yo mart
are coated with
a special resin that give them a resonance but when you spin that yo-yo when you go around the
world you really go around the world musically with yo-yo ma's yo-yo mart yo-yos
enter his groups to checkout
i don't know where i expected that to go but um yeah i'm just a better person having listened to
it doesn't matter i'm just a more sure where else is it gonna go this is it uh oh gee scoop in the
chat matt is pointing out uh didn't your wife do something with the uh with the showgirls my wife
is the choreographer but i didn't i didn't want to like you know flex my uh my family's involvement
with the with the show i just uh no we're just we're just we're wanting people to go see the
thing yeah yeah i think sarah sarah and troy have talked about working different projects for a while
now and uh as you know uh disco closed sarah had free time and uh nature abhors a vacuum so sure
uh she wanted to nature and sarah abhor a vacuum and so uh sarah filled that time immediately with
showgirls and working on showgirls didn't she agree to do it before disco show closed though
yes i think she agreed to do showgirls before she had the time to do it
that's how you get things done i suppose i guess so i guess so yeah so the timing worked out time
worked out but yeah yeah so it's the
we can't wait uh there we go so yeah um yeah i'm so excited i mean i mean i i love that show
i've seen uh i saw a parody of it in new york back in the day that wasn't a musical
uh that was just hysterical too and i just uh nice i well i will tell you that no one actually
loves that show more than my friend maybe i won't name him for the story but he was um
he was uh he was dating a stripper and they wanted to watch it together
and uh he took ecstasy uh uh to when he was rolling when he watched it
and then he was watching it and he thought it was so beautiful and significant and then he
was looking at his girlfriend not react that way and so he was like like leaning over to his side
and secretly texting and calling his friends to express like how amazing and important showgirls
was well i've watched actually because that was paul verhoeven
who directed that that's right yeah yeah that's the man behind the writer
the man behind robocop yes yeah like and if you look at like i've watched some really interesting
uh commentaries online yeah where they kind of deconstruct what's going on it's ah nuts the the
the stuff that he was the messages he was putting in there that didn't necessarily translate for
i mean that's that's that's that that is what's
fascinating about if you if you want to look into it at all it is like these i forget what kind of
filmmaking it was but like it used to be when you watch student filmmaking you watch uh whatever
films from another country where like if they showed like uh you know a wine bottle it was
supposed to mean something every little image is actually supposed to be the significant meaning
and it never translates to the watcher unless you know it ahead of time unless you have also
studied that filmmaking method right this film is filled with it it is filled trying to make this
such a significant story
um and it just is known for it's like crazy uh backstage antics and then of course
bizarre sex scenes but let me let me let me posit this to you guys let me let me just say like if
the three of us were tasked with making showgirls the year is 1990 whatever it was and somebody
comes to the three of us and says okay you guys are going to make this showgirls pick uh we got
the girl from saved by the bell she's going to be in it we got all these other people they're going
to be in it it's vegas showgirls blah blah blah
we'd go great we're going to start looking into this world and as soon as you start looking into
that world there is so much interesting stuff there's genuinely all of this incredibly
interesting stuff in in you know exotic dancing in in the showgirl world and and uh in las vegas
entertainment oh like then you want to try to communicate all of that interesting material to
the audience it's just not a thing that's really communicable
unlike most things in the movie showgirls which are very communicable i think like yeah i think i
think that like if this comes out years later it's more fascinating as a prestige television show
yeah i mean it's a it's a it's a history document yeah yeah i think you really see the world through
the life of the actual occupation of a showgirl obviously the movie came out last showgirl people
are taylor swift just nailed her named her album showgirl like there's still a fascination with
this and i think oh and i think largely right now because it's going away largely right now because
of that kind of idea of putting together some kind of really big production show with pageantry and
that being something that attracts modern audiences is going away now it needs celebrity
and ip and all this other stuff to make people uh want to see something i think you know like
the largest driver of tourism right now is the fucking wizard of oz right like uh for for las
vegas right so it's like um like i think like we have this fascination of this era that is
is closing out right even even dita von teese opened up her show over at bally's and the big
discovery was that all of those um is it mac was that what's the name of the famous uh costumer
bob mackie yeah mackie mackie bob mackie yeah all this is because you uh dita's dita show was in the
jubilee showroom at uh bally's right and they were using all of the old a lot of the old jubilee
costumes i'm just filling people in on what you're saying
no i'm sorry i'm trying to let you i'm trying to let you also i didn't mean to be like yeah i knew
that yeah but no they they were in the jubilee showroom where jubilee had been since the 60s i
want to say 60s or 70s uh and clothes like i have i've got pictures on my phone somewhere of them
taking the jubilee sign down outside of bally's right uh just because it was it was right across
the street like and so we just watch this happen every night and uh and jubilee was a show that
i mean i saw i i don't even know how many people have seen it i don't even know how many people have
seen it how many dozens of times i saw jubilee and so like dita's show going in there with all
of the costumes and katie mentioned a little bit like with the height stick and i think i'd even
talked about this seeing dita's show when when they were doing it it was so neat with jubilee
because it was it was this this beautiful exhibition of you know here here are all these
these people and we have gotten a group of people that we can get to look as identical as we can
still have a hundred people on stage but we're getting them to look as identical as they as we
can with that with the height and the build and everything else and then we're just going to
display these costumes on them yeah and so to see that and so to see dita then take that and say
we're we're going to get people who look as different as everyone just truly looks we're
not going to do any of that nonsense of of trying and not nonsense it's not fair different time uh
but like we're not going to do any of that stuff where we're just displaying the costume
we're going to display the people as well and so dita having people that were of kind of every
shape and size up there wearing these costumes that for decades and for my whole experience had
been like no you have to look like this to wear these costumes it was a neat thing to to watch
history kind of get turned on its head a little bit with uh with dita's stuff but then yeah i think
you're i think you're onto something though i don't know how interesting that was to the layperson
was i think i think i i think that it through its efforts became iconic stamp of like what to go see
in vegas right when you were there like and i think part of it was the toplessness and then that kind
of stuff but i think i think these that era where you try to meet in the middle right it was like
sure you're going to stop us but we're actually going to show you production anyway we're going
to we're going to value and you're not it's not going to be lurid it's not going to be sexual i
mean that's that scene in rocky four when apollo creed is coming out and and the huge the huge
production thing with the bull that collapses and all that stuff that's just a scene out of
jubilee it is they did they do that shot that's in the jubilee theater where they do that shot
and they just did a scene from jubilee and and put uh apollo creed in front of and put a boxing
ring in front of it but i mean that's what they did every night yeah it was crazy no he's talking
about like
you know they basically had those costumes just locked up there's no one in charge of preserving
them and so basically that production company was like good lord and tried to like preserve as much
of it as they could and and do whatever and we we don't we still right now don't have like a museum
or a preservation space for these iconic costumes of this was the same kind of difficulties and
travesty that happened when they closed down the experience there were so many pieces of memorabilia
uh the jimmy hendrix experience so there were so many pieces of
memorabilia and actual legit costumes and you know right not to mention all the replica stuff
that just a lot of it went in the fucking trash oh i mean i was i was working at the tropicana
uh after folly's brager closed which was the kind of the sister show to to jubilee it was the other
big showgirl show in town and i mean i found a room one day maybe a year after follies had closed
that just had basically all the costumes that had been worn on the final night
they had just taken all those costumes as soon as people got off stage and thrown them into boxes
and closed them up they hadn't washed them they hadn't laundered them they hadn't dry cleaned them
they hadn't even dried them out yeah and so like they were all sweaty they had mildewed like they
just they just rotted like it was it was horrible well it's it's you know we'll save the day there's
a silver bullet we own it we own the silver bullet guys what's the silver bullet chapeau
chapeau would chapeau was a production show chapeau could do it i mean we've got the first
number would do it we've got the first number seduction escalated there yeah seduction escalated
we're right there it's halfway we are it's halfway i'll tell you who else is halfway up that escalator
to success and they're gonna slap on those butt cheeks to show their appreciation and that's the
following sponsor today's show matt madley's ice cream social is brought to you by rfk junior
throat worm-based lozenges that's from scoop of monte cristo in 2025 this is rfk junior's
throat worm-based lozenges
it's a cold and flu season
it's cold and flu season and
ladies and gentlemen it has been determined that rfk junior is in fact job of the hut being
choked to death by princess leia from return of the jedi his death scene on the sailing barge
is a literal translation of verbiage from the future from our department of health and
services
come and don't enter hey scoops at checkout
i didn't know an ad was gonna get us sued by jfk and disney all at the same time
um so i got some firewood delivered to my house the other day firewood delivery uh firewood
delivery so what i usually do because we have a fireplace in the house we use that to keep the
house warm during the during the winter time uh so we don't have to run the heat so much oh yeah
that bitter that bitter vegas cold it'll get you that's right that's right you know it'll get down
into the 50s sometimes paul we are in show business we put on productions fire is an element that we
have as like part of our hosting abilities while we all come over in our short sleeve shirts for
our winter barbecues in the backyard the barbecue exactly hey i believe me i fucking miss it this
year it's already been just shit we drove yesterday to go visit with my in-laws to go have
dinner at this uh 80s diner it was kind of cool it was all 80s vibe you know like they had ghost
busters and shit on the wall and like an 80s diner like an 80s thing so uh really like in which
decade like the one right before like 94 95 i mean it really but it is right like the the 80s retro
stuff is all the 90s idealing idealization of the 80s it's not what the 80s the 80s was really
70s couches in a basement with a big ass tv and a nintendo hooked up to it that's what that's what
the 80s was um it wasn't all fucking day glow triangle what's your story paul listen
telling you paul telling us what the 80s wasn't we're getting ready to we're getting ready to go
you know what else the 80s wasn't
and uh the phone alert system goes hey snow squall warning ah no squall yeah so and it's like let's
pump the brakes on the snow squall warning let's let's not leave until the snow the snow squall
warning is done so it finishes about 10 minutes after we were going to leave so she texts she
texts our relatives and hey we're heading up there now we get in the car we get on the highway
we're on the highway about three minutes and snow squalls are coming it just so many snow squalls it
just did not stop and i was like this is i mean it was literally like i don't know
70 feet visibility maybe maybe 60 okay it was pretty intense maybe 65
uh i'm gonna give it 30 how about that 30 feet visibility great it was bad this is really bad
and then the sun would kind of travel and i was like oh my god i'm gonna give it 30 how about that
trying to peek out and make it even more of like a whitewashing i can't see oh yeah
anyway we finally get to the restaurant and about a minute before we get to the restaurant it stops
like literally on the road to the restaurant the squall stopped and i get out and i look at my phone
all we're just trying to eat in the squall we were i look at my fucking phone and i was like
oh look and they issued a squall warning again about 40 minutes ago
during our trip to the restaurant and i was like oh my god we're just trying to eat in the squall
we were i look at my fucking phone and i was like oh look and they issued a squall warning again about 40 minutes ago
during our trip to the restaurant and i was like oh look and they issued a squall warning again about 40 minutes ago
during our drive she said can you text them fuck you
can you reply to that i would like nothing like to do nothing more i got i got this in my kids
school where they always issue if any bus is late the entire school gets a late bus alert
and i go like at this point we should just get alerts for when the buses are on time
right hey everything's going to plan right every other day you know that
shit's happening so yeah um i like that maybe there was a guy at the weather service who was
hard of hearing and every time anyone said anything he's like what squall board oh i'll
send it out sure hit the squall button squall button the fact that they cut off the squall
warning and then issued it again like five minutes later as soon as we got on the road
they started it up again like fuck you so yeah the only i'm not a fan of this winter bullshit
i uh because uh you know i i travel a lot and so sometimes planes are delayed the only airline i
know that will delay a plane and then go never mind actually we're leaving early is southwest
everyone everyone else if you're playing delayed then it's just delayed but with southwest your
place late you're like don't go anywhere because they might just turn around be like never mind
it's all here we're going they do they do they do that again yeah they will do that shit spoiled
on the fucking southwest man i love my southwest
so i so most years i go i take the truck and i go pick up firewood yeah and they there are these
services in town that's what i thought jacob i thought you were a man you know that's the thing
so every year i've done this every year i've done this this year i couldn't find anywhere that would
let me do it wouldn't let you pick up firewood they wouldn't let me pick up firewood everywhere
is doing deliveries and i asked one guy i was like what's going on with this and he goes oh
some people are they'll come pick it up and then they'll drive it somewhere and resell it
like on their own oh this is the economy we're living in guys so what
you're still selling them a truckload of firewood i agree like so why can't i buy a truckload of
firewood oh my god that's funny wood people will be like look ticket master couldn't figure this
out you can't either pokemon can't pokemon can't figure it out that's there's a whole economy based
around reselling pokemon shit you can't help it half of the half of our current economy is just
reselling pokemon cards so i have this area in my in my shop in my in my garage uh that is the the
firewood pile and it's you know big area there and we pile all the firewood up there every year
and and it's there it's it's indoors a little bit like we don't have to go outside to go get
it during the winter time it's nice and uh so he he pulls up in his truck and he takes one look
at where the firewood is going to go and he goes oh that's not going to fit
and i go and i say very confidently don't worry i do this every year and i point at my truck
which is the same size as the truck that he just pulled up in so i'm feeling good i say i i go load
that truck up every year with firewood i stack it all right here we'll stack it up and we'll and
we'll put it in front of each other and it it doesn't look like it'll fit but trust me it'll
fit and he goes oh okay great and we start unloading the firewood and we're like oh my god
wouldn't we start stacking it up he was correct
i was gonna say the fact that he was like all right was basically like you know
let's go then you just did the equivalent of someone who works at a restaurant
uh every day yep and the and the customer going like i eat here all the time
yeah you're like no i work here all the time and you don't you just don't yep
he is a he is a professional wood stacker as you are a a biannual stacker yes yes an amateur at
best yes and uh so we got um kind of the main space of a firewood storage area filled up
yeah and i looked at his truck i turned to look because he was kind of like bringing wood to me
while i was stacking he had more to come really paying attention to the truck
and so i turned and looked at the truck and keep in mind the area that i usually fill up
with firewood is now about halfway filled up at this point i have filled up about half of the
normal load that i bring into this oh so you you were wrong by like a a a great deal you're you're
wrong by a significant percent a great but you said that the same size truck turns out when you
guys throwing pieces of firewood into your truck willy-nilly and just stacking them a lot less
firewood fits in it than when when one guy very carefully goes through and stacks all the firewood
into the truck getting as much firewood into the truck as possible oh okay so this is do you think
you have more than a year's worth of firewood here then oh yes not only do i have more than a
year's worth of firewood currently at my house i have more firewood that i've already paid for
at this guy's establishment that now that he knows me i can just go pull up in the truck and he will
load it he was like we we stacked as much as we could i was like i'm gonna call it there was still
maybe a third you gotta if you don't have an account on truth social right no no okay you
should get one because what happens is they're gonna eventually need to start paying some people
to host book burning parties and so like you should make sure that you're on the forefront of
that jesus christ get on the cutting edge you can get on the any any book that mentions the word gay
or trans or whatever or a black person or or facts our country had slavery at one point
that's all gonna get burned that's all gonna get burned and they're you know what they're
gonna need for that firewood exactly i'm not i mean it's it's strange for me to tell you to be
profiting in these strange times and i'm not gonna tell you to be profiting in these strange times
but i'm just looking out for you man it's you know we gotta pivot sometimes we just have to pivot
you gotta pivot we gotta jeremy pivot jeremy pivot so okay okay wait so where are you where
are you loading up when you when you're realizing this failure of loading your truck properly is
happening where are you where is this this is at the house is that your house so he so he brings
the truck because he because they won't let me come pick it up so he brings a truck load to the
back to the truck in such a way that he can he is fit he has filled every space in the truck every
nook and cranny what he did is firewooded when the guys fill my truck up when i go pick it up i i
basically pull up hand them like 60 and they just like four dudes just start throwing pieces of
firewood into the bed of the truck yeah i'm always a little worried that my truck is going to get
damaged when they're loading it get out of here really that's how they're loading it that's the
way in which they're loading this
this guy had like carefully packed all this firewood into the bed of his truck
and i mean it had to have been three times as much as i usually get into into mine same price easily
a little more expensive but definitely worth the worth the extra cost wow but you're at your house
i'm at my house so we're stacking it up in my house okay and we got there was maybe a quarter
or so of his truck bed left and i called it i was like i can't
like i'm gonna have to start moving shit around to find places for firewood now and i knew that he
was close by because we had already talked about it i was like you're gonna do more deliveries with
this truck tomorrow right he said yeah so i said if i leave firewood in your truck that doesn't that
doesn't screw you up on your on your later deliveries that you're doing tomorrow he said
nope i'm already partway loaded then that's just that's all that means it's a great said can i just
come pick up about this much firewood later on from from your place which is right down the road
from my house yeah
and he goes yes you can and he looks at he goes that's about two and a half wheelbarrow loads of
a firewood that i owe you uh you should argue with right there you'd be like no
this sounds like he was very gracious i've got a wheelbarrow in the back we'll load it up and
test this out this guy was very gracious in victory he was yeah he certainly was he was
very gracious like he had a second opportunity to misjudge his call again i mean you did miss
runner but uh still i mean if you two are the only ones that are getting it and he's just like
i mean at that at that point i'm like whatever you say man yeah i'm not i'm not disagreeing
with a single word you have to say if you tell me that i should be using a different type of wood
great load all this up take it away bring me whatever you think i just agree with you
holy amazing amazing oh i i was i went back in the house and uh later on sj gets home and i was
like you see that uh giant pile of firewood she goes yeah said we have uh more coming
that chunk that because like i basically made my two big piles of firewood that i always make
and then i made two big two more big piles of firewood in front of that and i was like as soon
as we burn this like ancillary pile we're going to get enough to make another ancillary pile
the only thing you should have done is gotten out chat gpt and be like chat gpt how much wood
will the fit and
here and then like put it in his face like no i did my research i did my research this wood
should fit it'll be fine no we're stacking it wrong we're the problem
you and i are equally the problem here sir equally uh so you load it from his truck to
your truck at your house no no his truck to the end of the house my truck was not involved got it
okay okay that's where i keep getting confused okay yeah we were loading it into like the wood
storage area in in my house and he was like it's not going to fit in that storage area yeah yeah
and he was like absolutely not and he was just and you took the rest of the wood and built a
second storage area you built a second just put that wood together yep that's right that's right
this is the you know what this means you have too much wood we should host some kind of mini
burning man we should build some kind of figure that we can that we can torch an effigy uh to
celebrate something i can't think of any uh public figures that you'd want to burn an effigy right now
i don't really i don't think we have we need to wait for a more uh aggressive political climate
so we can just just just a just a a know-it-all norwegian is what we'd build
god damn it
oh fuck oh people are asking why i didn't want to stack it outside i i just didn't want to it was
more of a pain this is this is easier it can rain in vegas it can rain in vegas also like i've got
kind of an outdoor fire pit and there's already a wood pile outside that kind of runs that fire pit
and that that one's also full jacob is neat he doesn't want sloppy wood about his yard he needs
things tidy yeah plus this guy is like a mile down the road from me this was just easier yeah
this was just much easier as a guy a little jock versus
as a guy who gets firewood a bag at a time from the grocery store
it is easier it is easier
ladies and gentlemen
it is
Explosion!
Of wood.
We got a scooper from the OG Scoop today.
I think he said this was an AI scooper.
So I don't know what that means, but we'll find out together.
The categories are Matt, Paul, Jacob, and Ice Cream.
Paul, you're up.
I'll try me.
Oh, Lemur Screamer, they are local trees.
Thank you for asking, Lemur Screamer Creamer.
They are indeed local trees.
It's a wood, like a tree service.
This is the other half of the tree service.
So they cut down trees in town and around here and everything,
and then chop them up and let them sit and season for a couple of years,
and then sell the firewood.
So Andy had AI just generate all of the questions and answers for this quiz.
Okay.
Oh, all right.
This is scary.
We'll see how this goes.
All right, I'll take me for 200.
Let's see.
The state where Paul was born, its official name is a Commonwealth.
That would be Kentucky.
The KY itself.
My old Kentucky home.
Let's see.
I'll try.
Well, I'll try Jacob for 200.
Andy, I'm asking, when you put this into AI, did you put any facts in with it,
or did you simply want AI to use whatever knowledge it already had of this podcast?
I'm curious about, like, the actual input for this quiz.
Oh, yeah, that's interesting.
Yeah, yeah.
I gave it just some, like, one-word things, like Springsteen, Louisiana,
bourbon, et cetera.
Okay.
Yeah, and then they kind of just went crazy, and some of the questions are really odd.
I'll bet.
I'll bet they are.
All right.
Thank you, Andy.
We'll find out together.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
The only U.S. state that isn't divided into parishes instead of counties, a legacy of
its French and Spanish colonial days, it's Jacob's home state.
That, of course, is Mississippi.
It's Louisiana.
Come on.
If you read the $800 question, it's like, Matt last sent a dick pic in this decade.
I feel like we'd all get that right.
Matt, you're up.
I guess we're on a roll here.
I'm going to go with, no, you know what?
I'm going to do Paul 400.
I'm going to try this.
Mixing it up.
Paul's favorite Star Trek series, the one with captains Janeway and formerly Sisko overlapping
in the same era.
What?
No, I'm on board.
I like this a lot.
Oh, man.
I wish I knew this just because it'd be funny to take this question, but I don't.
I don't think AI knows this.
Are you passing?
What are we?
What's happening?
I'm passing.
Oh, yeah.
Paul, I guess.
I mean, I guess it's next gen.
All right.
Star Trek, Deep Space Nine or Voyager.
Paul loves both.
He quotes DS9 more.
No, that's not.
There you go.
That's blatantly not true.
No, that's just.
Paul, you just saw it on the screen.
It's very true.
This is why we've got to burn down these goddamn AI power.
No, this is great.
Every AI facility must be burned to the ground because this is the kind of bullshit.
Oh, my God.
I know, right?
Oh, fuck, fuck.
I'll keep digging into my own grave.
600.
For 600.
The Simpsons episode where Homer goes to space.
Paul can quote the entire rake scene on command.
Oh, God.
I hope this is just an episode.
I know it's got to be Deep Space Homer.
Oh, okay.
But that's Deep Space Homer.
See, now you're friends with AI again.
Look at you go.
No, I'm not.
You love AI.
You love it, man.
I'm not convinced.
Does the rake thing, does Sideshow Bob's rakes happen in Deep Space Homer?
I don't know.
I'm going Paul for 800.
Paul's go-to improv comedy rule slash theorem that states,
there are no mistakes, only blank.
Opportunities.
We'll see what they say here.
There's happy accidents.
I mean, I'll say opportunities.
That is what he says.
Gifts.
I am so on board with this.
Matt, you're up.
Ice cream.
200, please.
The top-selling ice cream flavor in the United States year after year.
Well, according to AI, it's going to be like strained peas.
Strained peas, Neapolitan.
Strained peas.
I'll go with vanilla.
Let's try it.
No, I'm sorry.
It's strained peas.
Holy shit.
It is vanilla.
Paul.
I'll try Matt for 800.
Let's go crazy.
All right.
Daily double.
Yeah.
Here's where I win.
How well do you know me, Paul?
I'll be so upset.
If you get this wrong.
In what decade did Matt last send a dick?
In 2013, Matt absolutely lost his mind watching Penn and Teller debut their jaw-dropping new
version of this classic stage illusion, one they had spent over a decade perfecting, involving
a live stick of dynamite and a bullet catch gone terrifyingly real.
What?
This is just slop.
This is just nothing.
I mean, this is, this is, I'm going to say bullet catch.
Let's try it.
It's the bullet catch.
Well, that bullet catch is in the question and it's absolutely wrong.
There's no dynamite.
Gone terrifyingly real.
What the fuck?
The bullet catch was definitely not debuted in 2013.
Oh my God.
That's great.
Good Lord.
It's me.
I'll try Jacob for 800.
Jacob's favorite style of bullet catch.
It's the style of knife for everyday carry originally designed by Bob Loveless in the
1960s.
What?
Who is Bob Loveless?
You know, your favorite style of knife.
There's got to be a Leatherman, right?
Did he indeed make knives?
Is this a Leatherman?
Like it could be like a Leatherman.
It could be like a switch blade.
I bet it's a Leatherman because it could be.
Well, who the fuck knows?
Who the fuck knows?
Oh, no, no.
60s.
I'm going to say butterfly knife.
Oh, there you go.
I'm going to go butterfly knife.
A drop point or a hunter knife.
You don't even know your own favorite knife?
Come on, Jacob.
Apparently not.
It's a bunch of shit.
Ice cream, 400.
400.
This ancient civilization around 2000 BC.
Is credited with the earliest known ice desserts made from fruit and snow.
The Ice Maniacs.
The ice.
Show me the Ice Maniacs.
I'll pass.
Paul.
Pass.
It's me.
This is the Chinese.
Chinese did a lot of things.
I'll pass, though.
Fuck.
It was the Chinese.
It's just the Chinese.
I didn't believe in myself, everyone.
Believe in yourself.
That's the message from today's show.
Paul.
I'll take Matt for 600.
Daily Double.
Both the Daily Doubles.
They were the bottom two questions for Matt.
Bruce Springsteen's debut 1973 album that gave us Blinded by the Light and Spirit in the Night.
Oh, gee.
Jesus.
Was this.
Well, unfortunately, Paul, unlike the last question, the answer is not in the question.
No, it's not.
Okay.
I was going to go with Bruce Springsteen, but.
No, no.
Paul, if I was to say hello to you, that's a form of.
Greeting.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Greetings from.
Yes.
Yep.
Ah.
All right.
New Jersey City, where he famously started his career.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
This could be the tripping spot.
Asbury Park.
Oh.
Is that what the album is called?
Greetings from Asbury Park.
Greetings from.
I'm sorry, Paul.
It's greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
I'm sorry you got that incorrect.
I'm sorry, Paul.
Oh, boy.
It's me.
I'll try ice cream for 800.
Oh, you really dinged him on New Jersey?
He didn't get New Jersey.
The AI said it was wrong.
Is it just greetings from Asbury Park or is it Asbury Park, New Jersey?
It is greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
Okay.
Everyone calls it the greetings from Asbury Park or greetings for shorts.
Yes.
While we're here, famously, it's because Springsteen, his whole band left after the riots and started making money with Southside Johnny in North Carolina.
So Springsteen started making money going to the New York Village and doing the Dylan route.
They wanted to be the next Dylan, but he got his band back together for it, and they were still pressuring him to be like a New York Village.
He was a musician, so he insisted the title of the first album be called Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey as a fuck you to the record company.
Okay.
Oh, I like that.
Yeah.
I also like that Southside Johnny got a little.
Anytime we can bring in Southside Johnny.
We are by far the number one Southside Johnny podcast.
Easily.
Easily the number one Southside Johnny.
And we can probably easily get him for next to confess.
So those things are also true.
I don't know.
I mean, honestly, the fact that we haven't called him up for a turnout at a tyrannies.
That's that's that's the move.
Yeah.
He might have just my God.
You'd pack the whole place.
Oh, absolutely.
He might have been there anyway.
The record holding number of scoops balanced on a single cone.
Guinness of 2023 within five.
Uh, 37.
Good guess.
125.
My left.
What are these?
It's like little pancakes of fucking ice cream.
Little pancake ice cream.
Bullshit.
Matt.
Oh, let's do.
Don't worry, Matt.
There aren't any daily doubles.
Left.
Jacob.
600.
The NFL team.
Jacob bleeds black and gold for their home.
Dome is now called the Caesar Superdome.
That would be the Falcons.
Atlanta.
The Falcons.
Of course.
The Saints.
I'm sorry, Matt.
That's the New Orleans Saints.
The New Orleans Saints.
Is that actually the correct answer?
You are.
Oh,
yeah.
, you are ruthless today, Jacob.
I'm sorry, Matt, it's the AI.
It's not me.
It's the AI.
I'll do Matt for 400.
Matt's home state.
Whose nickname is the Garden State.
Despite what you might think from the turnpike.
New Jersey.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
It's brand New Jersey.
Sparkling New Jersey.
New Jersey smell.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's brand New Jersey.
Sparkling New Jersey.
It still has that New Jersey smell.
Yeah.
It's me.
I'll try ice cream.
600.
The ice cream chain founded in Burlington, Vermont in 1978, whose flavors include cherry
Garcia and fish food.
It's fish with a PH.
Fish.
I believe that would be Ben and or Jerry's.
Ben and Jerry's.
I'm sorry.
There's no and or there.
There's no or.
It's just and.
Matt.
You got Matt or Jacob.
I guess I'll go with Jacob for it or just so I can break even.
The brand of bourbon Jacob keeps on his bar cart that's distilled in Kentucky, but named
after a Louisiana parish.
What?
Do you know the answer to this, Jacob?
I don't own a bar cart.
Is there an answer to this?
I don't even have a bar cart.
I can't even think of a parish name to name.
I mean, there's like a bar cart.
I don't even have a bar cart.
I can't even think of a parish name to name.
I mean, there's like Orleans.
Treme.
Rapids.
I'll pass.
Paul.
This has to be a Kentucky.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
Not Ocean, but they've got other Jeffersons.
Yeah, yeah.
I do have some Jeffersons in the bar.
Cart?
Well, there you go.
I don't have a bar cart.
I just have a bar.
We've got to build you a bar cart before next game.
I do need a bar cart.
Paul closing out the category and the game.
Matt for 200.
This duo has performed together at the Rio All Suite Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas since 2001.
Penn and Teller.
Siegfried and Roy.
I really like that Ben and Jerry's, the answer for Ben and Jerry's earlier, had the ampersand in it,
but the Penn and Teller answer has the word and spelled out.
Good old AI coming through.
That's right.
That is the game Paul wins with 600 because he loves AI the most.
Matt's in second with negative 400.
I'm in third with negative 1600.
That's from OG Scoop.
Thank you, OG Scoop.
Yes, thank you.
That AI Scoopity worked out just fine.
Oh, my goodness.
I'll say this is a fine.
It's an experiment.
I don't know if it's worth replicating.
We're going to do it all the time.
No, let's not do it anymore.
Let's leave AI alone.
Let's stop fucking with AI.
Hey, Matt, how is Penn doing, by the way?
He hurt his ankle, yeah?
He did.
He broke his ankle.
He had to cancel all the shows this weekend.
And then, of course, he canceled the podcast.
So I only know from a couple of text exchanges that he's doing okay.
He's on the mend.
Okay.
I remember distinctly.
It really hit me again yesterday when I read this news,
and they had to cancel shows.
I remember distinctly on, I believe it was March 12th of 2020,
right before the shit hit the fan.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I was talking with one of the bartenders at Absinthe,
and we were talking because, you know,
there were rumors of things having to go on pause for a moment.
Yeah.
We didn't know it was up.
And I said, well, I'll tell you this.
I just found out that Penn and Teller have put their show,
it was on hiatus.
And there has to be some real shit for that to happen.
So I think things are coming down.
And sure enough, the next, like, day and a half later, kaboom.
Yeah.
They were a little bit ahead of the curve.
But then it all turned out to be fine.
Yeah, no, everything was great.
Everything was great.
Paul, as usual, was incorrect about that.
Everything's just been up, up, up, up, up since then.
That's right.
Turned out it was a hoax.
Yep.
And we're not still dealing with it.
Yeah, me and my negative Nancy thinking, well, I mean.
That's right.
I am a little concerned that I could explode at any minute,
having had many vaccines and updates.
But whatever.
But the government's following your every move now that it has,
you know, microscopic robots.
That's true.
I do have lots of tracers in here.
I'm basically a walking air tag.
So.
I've said that about you for years.
We're getting a shout out here.
Hey, Paul, Nick's son is playing basketball in Madison County
tonight.
Go Eagles beat the Indians.
Let's go.
Go for it.
Yeah.
Beat the Indians.
Of course, they're still the Indians.
We're not going to change that.
Of course, my fucking alma mater, Madison Central Indians are still
the Indians.
Good Lord.
I will say it did give me that one wonderful moment when and
John has told the story before, I think, too.
But, you know, I had I was able to during a homecoming parade,
the Latin club, I chained up my brother to a giant.
That paper mache rock and because we were the Latin club and we did the
the myth of who is it that brought fire to the to the.
Yeah.
Prometheus.
That's it.
So and he was cursed to have a vulture liver out or an eagle eat his liver
every night.
So we dressed John up as the opposing team chained to a rock and us with a
hatchet like an Indian hatchet.
I got to drive my brother getting his liver chopped by another football
player down the main street of Madison County, Richmond, Kentucky.
That was a fucking highlight.
Yeah.
John says he's not in show business.
That's a starring role.
That goes on the resume.
That better be on his resume somewhere.
It should be.
Yeah.
Opposing team Prometheus.
I have another list here.
Another modest list here, Jacob.
Are we we're figuring out what's going on with with the with the list thing.
But yeah.
OK.
We're going to keep on thanking people.
All right.
Well, I want to thank the bottom of everything.
I want to thank Ben Jeffery in this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
Get well soon.
Yeah.
I want to thank Elaine Hayhurst and Katie Hurd for stopping by.
Talk about this parody.
Fantastic to have them there.
I do.
I love it when we do.
Stay nice and contemporary with Vegas Entertainment News.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I want to thank the following people who have all been paraded by Paul Mattingly through
the town to create the Prometheus myth.
They had their livers pecked out with with axes and birds.
Danny Olwein.
Dark Shift.
Dave Serial.
Dave Hanson.
Dave Peterson.
Dave Slusher.
David A. Small.
David Grassi.
David K.
David M.
Rikov.
Risho.
I don't know how you pronounce that.
R-I-C-H-O-U-X.
David Smith.
David Sorensen.
Deb Title.
Dennis Hand.
Derek Dozier.
Dippin' Dots Jack.
Dimitri Stepinjoff.
Yeah, I got that one right, too.
Yeah.
Doc Scoop.
Don Donnie.
Dr. Tobias Scoopay.
And Ed Rosen.
Thank you so much.
These people, just like Jacob, have tried everything on a blackstone, including sucking
his dick for magic tricks.
Emily Ralph, Emma and Tonka, Truck the Pony, Emma Gregston, Unos Raccoon, Finn Stephenson,
Freeze Dried Scoop, Dave Enright, Gage Saucedo, Galen Diggs, Gavin Bristow, Gazpacho Scoop,
Gene Zink, Genetic Scoop, Gerardo Garcia, Greg Recton, H.S. Floatwater.
A.K.A.
With a Scoop Ball.
Who's your Scoop?
E.N.A.
Chapman.
J-Rock.
Jake Schneider and James Fox.
And I want to thank the following Scoops who all put thumbtacks in Tara Palsch's boots.
That's James Hubble, James McPhee, Janine Lankard, Jason Horcastas, Jason Specklin, Jason
Street, Jason Vasquez, Jeff Ackerman, Jeff Bizarre, Jennifer Reyes-Carraro, Jenny Ebarb,
Jeremy Hudson, Jesse Miller, Jesse Rain, Jim Inmanu, Jimmy Slonina, Joe.
Joe Magistralio, John Carter, John Jacob Schupenheimer-Schmidt, Johnny Parker, and
Jordan Smith.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do appreciate you.
We do.
Mastrangelo.
We should have switched lists, Jacob.
I had that one down.
We should have.
Mastrangelo.
That's it.
I hear these names and know them, but then you see them and you just have no idea how
to say them.
You're on the spot.
Oh, this is the Wednesday episode, yeah?
So this goes out Thursday, is that right?
Or Wednesday?
That's right.
All right.
So I want to.
So to give a heads up to Scoops, we're aiming for a Friday night Zoom hang, 9.30 EST, my
time.
So it'll be 7.30 on the West Coast, but then we'll go for a couple hours of playing some
games and hanging out and chatting.
You said that'll be Friday, Paul?
That'll be Friday night.
Friday, January 23rd.
That is correct.
Friday, January 23rd, this coming week.
And I will send out the invites through Patreon shortly after our second recording here.
And try and get that all squared away.
Leon is coming aboard.
Thank you, Leon, to help lead us through some games.
It's going to be a real fun night.
Yeah, we're all going to have a good time.
These hangouts have been exceptionally fun.
So I'm looking forward to it.
And please hop on board and join us on Friday night.
And I don't have to.
I'm on vacation right now.
So I don't have to work.
I don't have to worry about getting up early.
So I'll be well rested and feeling bright-eyed and bushy-tailed.
Who knows?
I might go for a while playing games.
And hopefully.
Hopefully Matt and Jacob can drop by at some point in the evening, even just to say hi.
Yeah.
When is it?
It's going to be Friday night, 7.30 your time starting.
I will be performing a show in Cincinnati, I believe.
There you go.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's why we're doing a double today is because Matt can't do it on Friday.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So January 23rd, I'm in Lexington.
January 24th, Cincinnati.
January 25th, Bloomington, Indiana.
Then August 15th, I'm in Lexington.
Then August 15th, I'm off to Chicago.
And January 27th, I'm playing at a comedy club there.
28th, Green Bay, Wisconsin.
29th, Madison, Wisconsin.
And January 30th, Milwaukee.
And January 31st, Wabash, Indiana.
I'll also give a shout-out to the 31st.
That's Saturday the 31st.
Myself and my friend Sarah are going to be teaching my free improv workshop that night.
Oh, nice.
And I've already put the stuff up on Scoop Group and whatnot.
Appreciate everybody retweeting and sending out the word to people you might know.
If you're in the area or you might even find yourself traveling to the area,
it's out there near Pittsburgh in, oh, what's the place called?
I can't remember the name of the crazy little town.
But, yeah, look it up online.
It's right there.
It's on Scoop Group and whatnot.
But it's free class, two hours of fun with me and Sarah teaching some improv.
Come check us out.
Hang out.
Come see me.
It'll be great times.
Remember, there are no bad things that happen in improv.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Lonely gifts.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
I am hoping the weather holds for these next couple of weeks.
It's going to be kind of crazy out here.