Oh hello there, I am so glad you are here because I want to thank you the ice cream
truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Bearded Scoop 3, Blue Line Scoop, Chasing the Dragon Scoop,
Christine Elsesser, Christy Salinas, Darren Cunningham, Darth Scooper, David Walker, Ted
Laszlo, Dirty Old Scoop and Dr. Scoop Little.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to preachingfun.com.
Preachingfun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who
knows, maybe the life you save, wait, the life you save may be your own, nailed it.
Here's a show.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great.
Let's go.
A man was arrested in New Jersey recently for a road rage incident where he shot a woman
in the face.
She's fine, but he shot her in the face.
She's fine.
Yep.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting over there with a confused look on his face, that's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting over there with an understanding look on his face, that's Matt Mattingly.
We're preachingfun.
I'm taking him to Las Vegas.
I just saw this.
Apparently he's a Sopranos guy, a couple other.
He's a bit actor.
His role on The Sopranos, his character name on The Sopranos was Thief.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
He's a Sopranos actor the same way that the guy who walked in the back of the scene is
a Sopranos actor.
Right, but to say she got shot in the face and is okay, that's not right either.
Right.
It apparently raised her nose, hit her in the nose, but it went across her nose.
She went to the hospital and everything, but she was not in any-
Full recovery?
I believe so.
I don't believe there was any life-threatening injury.
It was a flesh wound, as they say.
Yeah, but he is facing 31 counts in connection with the violent rampage, including first
degree attempted murder and aggravated assault with a deadly weapon.
Apparently they were both trying to get into the same lane at the same time.
She absolutely had the right of way.
Yeah, right.
And he got just enraged and shot a gun out of the window of his car.
Which just goes to show you how advanced Matt Donnelly is for a New Jersey driver.
Just calm, mellow.
The amount of people that'd be surprised if my death or someone else's death involved
my road rage would be zero people.
Zero.
It would be sad.
Just not surprised.
Not surprised.
I'd say it's the one benefit probably, I don't know if it's even a benefit, of the surveillance
state that we live in, is that they're going to have plenty of footage of this from the
cameras everywhere.
Oh yeah.
I got into an Uber the other day and the Uber driver pointed out the inside and outside
cameras to me as I got in and he definitely did it.
Oh, he was letting you know.
Yeah, he definitely was doing it in a way to be like, "I've had trouble in here before,
here are the cameras, please don't be an asshole."
Yeah.
Oh God.
I'm a Las Vegas local, I'm just going to my house and he was like, "Oh thank God."
Please ignore the hair.
Yeah.
Oh boy, what a hassle.
Well, I'll pile on the bad, sad, I don't know if you guys heard about this, noted YouTube
vlogger Adam the Woo passed away.
Oh goodness.
I did not.
What was he known for?
He was known for Disney parks reviews and haunted attraction reviews and he did a daily
blog, daily vlog and he was good friends with a lot of other creators that I'm interested
in like Jacob the Carpetbagger and a couple other people and yeah, he went to all kinds
of theme parks and stuff.
He even did Paris Disney recently.
He was very prolific with his work and just apparently natural causes, almost exact same
age as me, bit the dust.
Probably a heartbreaker, yeah, everybody's really sad about it.
It's one of those deaths that makes me look at it.
You look at the breadth of his creative output and you look at the reactions from the creator
community as well as the fans and you see a person who lived their life well.
You see nice results from their life.
And if anything, lots of positive things, fan interactions, people, you know, he treated
everyone very kindly, remembered people, like he would go to many of these fan events over
and over again, these horror nights and horror conventions and he would see people who go
to the horror conventions regularly and he could recognize them in costume and stuff
like that.
Oh, that's great.
You know, just seems to be, seems to have been a general all around good guy.
Good news though, Paul, I've looked him up here, he's actually going to be now haunting
the Disney parks so people will be able to do his style of show now about him.
So it's the circle of life.
There you go.
Well, there are suggesting that he be buried or at least have the funeral ceremony somewhere
near the Disney parks as that was his favoritest thing.
So who knows?
You know, Disney, Disney don't get into that shit.
Well, Disney is, Disney's like, if you want to do that somewhere on private property and
say that it's close to our place, that's fine.
If you want to do that shit on our property, you can go fuck yourself.
You know how many people that, how many times they've had to clean up human remains out
of the haunted mansion?
Oh yeah.
Because I think that's the entire reason that they don't want to fuck with their cremated
loved ones and dump them in the, in the dune buggies.
Yeah.
So don't do that, it's a public service announcement for the 19 year old that has to clean up your
loved one's remains.
Please don't dump their ashes on the haunted mansion ride.
It's a ride.
We are advocates of the Throshen option.
Throshen.
Throshen is the best.
Throshen is out there.
It's the most environmentally clean option if you're not a fish.
People keep suggesting that Throshen be the best option for the current resident of the
White House as otherwise talk about cleanup services being required.
No, I'm sure it's all fine.
Well, regardless, uh, yeah, just tragic.
You know, the other, the other side too, uh, when I would go to Kings Island as a kid,
this was still rural Ohio back in the day.
It's been somewhat more developed as it goes along, but it was still, you know, country
ish and there was a, there was a tiny graveyard just outside of Kings Island.
As you were walking towards the front gates and even in the parking area, you could see
a small graveyard.
These were the people that died on the beast.
I don't, I don't know who, who exactly, well, I should look it up.
It's a known thing.
It's a bunch of gravestones and grave markers right outside of Kings Island and, um, I always
thought what a great place to be buried because I loved Kings Island so much as a kid and
even as we know, Annie is a listener of the podcast, so take some notes here.
Yeah.
Um, I mean, I, you know, I, maybe it's a little arrogant to assume that Annie will outlive
you, but I don't know if it's very arrogant to assume Annie will outlive you.
I would just have to, oh no, Ann's already got us grave plots secured.
Does she have one for both of you or just you?
No, both, two of us.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, she's not going to bury you at Kings Island then?
She's not going to bury me at Kings Island, but I've told her I don't want to burial.
I'm going to get cremated and then, you know, whatever.
I don't know why I was calling her Annie.
I was calling her Annie because we're waiting on an email from our Annie.
We're thinking about Annie.
Yeah.
Thank you, Ann.
I think Ann should take note that you want to be buried at Kings Island.
She knows.
The cemetery outside of Kings Island known as the Dog Street Cemetery is a historic but
forgotten burial ground.
Not forgotten.
We're talking about it right now.
Well, the people who are in it.
No, people don't know, I guess, the people who are in it.
Yeah.
I think it's the dead people who have been forgotten about that.
Oh, got it.
Got it.
So are the graves unmarked in that way?
At least hard to read the name.
They're marked, but they're marked with things like Missouri Jane.
Ah.
Okay.
Yeah.
And it still sits quietly within the park's property near the main entrance.
Yep.
No.
You'd walk by it every time.
And apparently it was, the cemetery itself was forgotten about and was rediscovered in
the 1890s.
Okay.
Yeah.
You can't miss it.
So they found an overgrown cemetery that had been reclaimed by the woods and everything
in the 1890s.
Yeah.
You can't miss it when you're going into Kings Island.
It's kind of a nice little memento mori, you know, it's like, because not everybody survives
the bat.
Not everybody makes it off Top Gun.
Yeah.
Lindsay and Chad says, go ahead and dump me in the Haunted Mansion.
Don't cremate me.
Just, we can have Bernie's meat through the park and dump me there.
Just remains.
Not cremated remains.
What would be the legality?
And what would be?
It's not.
It's not legal.
No.
Hear me out now.
Hear me out.
I believe it falls under an illegal dumping statute.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm not talking Disney anymore.
Let's get away from the Disney affiliation.
How much would it take?
What kind of legal red tape, given that we are in the Wild West again, as far as you
got the money, you can do the thing.
This has probably been done.
Now that I'm saying it, this has probably been done.
But you could have people who are horror fans volunteer to have their corpses utilized in
a haunted attraction and you could just go through on a little scooter and see rotting
dead people, maybe put some animatronics in them, maybe make them jiggle around a little
bit.
This next body is actually Zach Baggins.
He founded this museum back in the 2000s.
Right.
I mean, if Epstein-
Scoop Jesus is talking about how bad it would stink.
Yes, Scoop Jesus.
Yes.
It would stink.
If Epstein was as enthusiastic about haunted houses as he was about child rape, then it
would have already happened.
It would have already been happening.
It would have been already a feature of his island.
I'm thinking-
To be fair, we don't know for sure that it's not, unless, oh, Matt, have you been to the
island, Matt?
Are you at the island right now?
I'm glad we're recording on a Tuesday because you do not want to record with me on Thursday.
I'll tell you that much right now.
Those files come out.
Just one very small haunted hole on Jeffrey Island.
Just a small haunted hole.
Calls it his boo cave, he does.
Don't go to the boo cave.
That's worse than the Tickle House, y'all.
Stay the fuck out of the boo cave on Epstein Island, the haunted hole.
I figured out how to get Trump's name off of the Kennedy Center.
Have I told you about this?
Oh, no.
How you do it?
All you have to do is show up with an even larger Donald J. Trump sign, and so when you
go to take the one off, they'll go, "Hey, you're not supposed to take that off."
You go, "No, no, no.
The president said his name wasn't big enough," and then that'll allow you to get it off because
everyone will believe you that he wants a bigger name.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
That's true.
If Vandals showed up with a giant Donald J. Trump sign, no, no, we're going to put this
one on after we take this one off.
That's it.
And then you're going to clear it.
Everybody would leave you alone.
This is the ultimate wearing blacks and carrying a ladder.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Right?
And then, boom.
I look forward to seeing this new, enormous Donald Trump sign tomorrow when I do my rounds.
Oh, that security guard is going to be embarrassed.
But he'll say, "They said they're going to put a bigger sign up."
And everybody's like, "Ah, makes sense, Terry.
So sorry, buddy."
Oh, I would have fallen for it, too, Terry.
That would have gotten me.
That really sucks.
And they were in like coveralls, huh?
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, they were wearing coveralls.
In hindsight, they definitely got those at Walmart, but they were, they looked really
official.
They had a wagon, a big wagon, a ladder.
He said he was a big fan of that, that Kirk guy.
I figured that just means he was okay.
Paul wasn't our friend, Missoula pointed out that the Arizona Cardinals haven't won a game
there since they did the Charlie Kirk Memorial.
Yeah, that's, I mean...
They've won away games, but not any home games.
It's a unique way to look at it.
The Cardinals aren't very good at football, so it's not the hardest thing to stretch the
truth on.
That's it.
Yeah.
But, Jacob, I saw that you had an actual vacation.
I mean, in the sense that we went places out of town, it was a vacation.
Oh, heavens, what happened?
In the sense that it was relaxing in any way at all, it was not.
Oh, no!
It wasn't bad.
It was just so fast paced.
We went down south.
We went all over the place.
We flew into Austin, Texas.
We saw some of Estre's family.
There's your first mistake.
Yeah, exactly.
Saw some of Estre's family outside of Austin, went farther east in Texas and saw some more
of her family and then drove to Louisiana and saw some of my family.
And then we flew out of Jackson, Mississippi.
So we did Texas, Louisiana, and Mississippi.
Oh, goodness sakes, that's a lot.
And I think we did it in four nights, five days.
No, no, no.
That's okay.
But we saw the whole family, we had Christmas every day in a new location with the kids
and the family members in that location.
So it was really nice.
It was a really nice trip.
We were just fucking exhausted.
One of the more embarrassing things that I've had to do happened on the flight back as well.
Oh, no.
Are we going to get into situational awareness territory?
No, no, no, no.
Thank goodness.
That is not where I'm going.
All of my pants are fine.
All of my clothing is not in the garbage.
It's just folded up.
So we had a layover in Nashville and the Nashville airport, if you've never been through that
in Nashville airport, it's really cool.
They have a bunch of live music stations set up all over the place.
Like in the gates and everything, they'll just have little stages ready for somebody
with a guitar to sit there and sing some stuff into the microphone there.
It's really nice.
And so we were hanging out.
They have an Ole Red, an Ole Red bar in the Nashville airport there.
So we said, oh, we'll go get some dinner in Ole Red.
We'll sit there and we'll listen to some music before we get on the flight back to old hometown
Vegas.
And so we're sitting there at the bar in the restaurant and we're listening to the live
music.
It's really good.
It's really tender.
Everybody's really nice.
And this fella comes and sits down at the bar stool next to me, you know, asks if anybody's
sitting there.
I say, nope.
And that is the extent of our interaction.
I said, no, no, it's all you.
I had a bag that was kind of in the way.
So I moved from a bag.
I said, no problem.
You enjoy it.
And then we sat there and we did not interact anymore for about an hour.
And then he turned to me and he goes, so you're a podcaster, huh?
And I went, yeah, yeah, I am.
Yeah, that's right.
And now we, I'm sitting there racking my brain, did SJ and I say anything?
Like have we been talking about the podcast?
I don't think we have.
I don't think we've mentioned anything about any of it.
Turns out he thought I was a different podcaster and just asked me if I was a podcaster and
I said, yes.
And then he realized that he was talking about a different person entirely that he thought
that I was.
There's a couple of us now.
He thought that I was, uh, Theo Vaughn.
Get the fuck out of here.
I mean, I can see it.
This man believed that I was a podcaster, Theo Vaughn, hilarious.
At which point I had to explain to him that I was not Theo Vaughn, just a different middle
aged white guy with a podcast.
Right.
Yeah.
Did you give him a chip?
Is that solves it all?
Jacob.
I didn't have a chip.
I didn't have any bags with me.
So I did not have a chip.
But, uh, I believe that he is, I believe that he is a new scoop now.
We did chat.
We had a real nice chat.
I hope so.
Well, I keep, I think he said his name was Dave.
So shout out Dave from old red at the, at the Nashville airport.
I keep two chips in my wallet at all times.
As last year, I don't carry a wallet.
What the fuck is going on?
I have like the little card holder that I keep in my front pocket.
And that's it.
Well, you wear jeans, right?
With the little front Lippity upper to pocket.
All right.
Suppose I wear pants.
Well, like a little Lippity up in a pocket, a chip fits perfectly in the Lippity up in
her pocket.
Two is great too.
So I would just suggest tuck one in between cheek and gum for emergency situations.
But, uh, well, good.
I hope we did get a, uh, an obelisk off of that.
I think I, I think I'm over the course of an hour, obelished one person.
Great.
We're not an efficient system that we're not.
We're not an efficient system.
I'll tell you who else does not have a very efficient system that they run on.
Uh, and somehow they also base their entire business model off of it as well.
And that is the following sponsor today's show.
Man Manley's ice cream social is brought to you by the wearable blanket, a blanket with
sleeves so you can nap better on your couch.
That's from Smitty scoop in 2025.
Hey everybody.
It's me.
What's up?
I'm crunch.
I'm here to advertise a wearable blanket.
I don't know what I would like.
I like a blanket with sleeves.
It lets me eat my cereal and warmth and contentment and keeps me away from the soggies.
Those motherfuckers.
They're always ruining my fucking cereal.
God damn it.
Eat my own asshole all the way you soggy fucks.
Now you can't get to me because I've got a wearable blanket on and if I drop my milk
on me, it doesn't matter.
Soggies can't get me.
You know, the horrible thing about my existence is I can't live without the soggies and I
need my milk on my cereal, but I hate them and they try to destroy me on my product at
every turn.
But they're a necessary evil if I want to have my cereal eaten.
Oh boy.
Look, catch 22.
Fuck these bastards.
I hate them all.
If I catch them on the open seas, it's on International waters.
I got love to see on my side, bitches.
And that was how Captain Crunch became a pirate.
Look at me, soggies.
I'm a captain now.
That's captain with an apostrophe in.
S.J. had a show at the Silverton the other day.
We had a fun Taylor Swift show the other night and a big free show.
They did it as part of the rodeo and boy, was it fun watching all these little kids
up there dancing around.
It was so good.
I was exhausted by the end of it, just running around talking to people, just kind of socially
exhausted by the end of it.
Sure.
Walk through Silverton.
There was a Johnny Rockets.
Oh, yeah.
Motherfucker.
Did you want a chocolate shake?
I was like, Johnny Rockets got the shakes.
A Johnny Rockets shake.
I'm going to go get me a Johnny Rockets shake.
So I go up to the Johnny Rockets counter and say, I would like one chocolate shake to go
please.
Because everybody else was going over to a restaurant to go meet up after and I said,
I'm going to go.
I'm going to show up with a chocolate shake.
I'm not eating anything.
I'll have some beverages and my chocolate shake.
This is going to be great.
And the guy at the counter told me how much the shake was.
And he said it was $13.22.
What?
$13.22.
Where was this?
The Johnny Rockets.
Yes.
In the Silverton casino.
Oh my god damn.
I mean McDonald's shakes are $5 now.
I exclaimed for a moment and said, that is a very expensive chocolate shake.
And then he handed it to me and I took a sip of it and that is very good.
I don't know if it's $13 good though.
And he said, well, he goes, it doesn't matter.
You already paid for it.
Oh Jesus.
And I said, what?
And you instantly tapped your phone on the thing because I was standing there thinking
that I hadn't paid for it yet.
And I had just completely spaced and without meaning to had just like just did my phone
on the little card reader and be like, yep, there we go.
You had a very, I was still complaining about the price having already paid for it.
Yeah.
Very pulp fiction moment there.
And that was the $5 milkshake where everybody's like, what the fuck, $5 back then it was five
at Jack rabbit slims.
Holy shit.
$5.
That's outrageous.
Yeah.
Well, you know, the, uh, you know, being able to like bring, uh, uh, the dairy cows in Montana
down cause of drought now and stuff like that, you know, milkshakes have gotten very expensive.
Well, that's the fucked up thing within our lifetime and ain't getting cheaper for a milkshake.
So drink them up now, boys, enjoy them, enjoy them now and chocolate cows are harder to move
to.
I did a corporate show in, uh, Sexton, Missouri.
Oh, this is the, this is the one, right?
Two hours outside of, uh, St. Louis.
This was the, you had to jump away from your regular gig.
Yeah.
Got it all cleared.
I had a load into Chicago.
Do my first show in Chicago, pack up, go to the airport, fly to Missouri to show Missouri
pack up, fly back to Chicago, load in again and finish up my run in Chicago.
This was pound of flesh.
This was not, uh, not going to be easy as per your management.
Yes.
Possibly this was for drunken businessman was the pitch.
It was, and it was not that I, that it was, it was mispitched that way.
Okay.
Cause they, the guy that booked you told you this was going to be blood money.
Yes.
This was going to be a real pain in the ass.
Um, it was, it was, it was a Christmas party for, uh, a company that specializes in like,
um, uh, basically like a gas tank, uh, compatibility.
So whether you have like ethanol or butane or whatever, like, uh, it basically is like
a, a tank company, like different types of gas tank company.
There was a family Christmas party, so it was all the workers and their husbands and
wives, uh, and it was held inside that paintball, uh, place, uh, like kind of like amusement
park area.
This town, this town was small, like it drove through town, no, no lights, no traffic lights,
you know, no sidewalks, you know, uh, literally had one gas pump or like the gas station had
one pump.
Oh shit.
So, uh, it was, uh, you know, like that's a small town.
The firehouse had like a little Christmas tree outside of it decorated, you know, that's,
that's the little activity scene.
That's the, that's it's Christmas time and, uh, inside it did, it had, it had, you know,
uh, you know, everything's for a dollar else.
The freshmen stand at the, at the, uh, it wasn't open.
I was there for a closed event, but you know, like I was like, oh, they still sell sodas
and water for a dollar and snacks for a dollar in places.
That's cute.
It was very nice.
Yeah.
Um, but no, uh, they, uh, they just don't go to shows often.
Right.
So the idea of like putting on a show was just something that was kind of like, okay.
Now the funny thing that happened was the woman who was supposed to do my intro, like
she went over all the intro with me and I was like, yep, that's the intro.
And then, uh, they had to show a video and then break down the screen and take everything
off stage to make room for me, uh, after the intro, well, this is it.
So I thought my intro would be after the breakdown of the screen.
Oh no.
The video finishes and she just calls from the, from the audience, not from stage, from
the audience.
Just turn to the microphone.
It goes, uh, the man of the hour, Matt Donnelly.
Just like that.
Yeah.
Man of the hour, the man of the, the, the event was there to honor you.
You didn't know this.
That's what I mean.
Like man of the honor, as you're like, Oh, uh, I don't know, a man of the honor, like
man of the hour.
I mean, like what, like we're not there for me, his retirement from magic.
This is his last show.
Everyone.
Mr. Matt Donnelly, the mind noodler, that's the, that's the comedian coming up and go,
you guys ready to laugh?
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
Oh my, what a great prank.
How about some fantastic jokes, everybody.
It's giggle time.
If we gathered everyone, Matt, take your ear, take your earphones out.
Okay.
All right.
So here's what we're going to do.
We're going to, we're going to gather everyone that has been important in Matt's life and
in his professional career.
And we're just going to put together a last retirement show for Matt, but he's not going
to know about it.
We're just going to hire him.
He's going to come in, it's going to be billed as Matt Donnelly, the mind noodlers last show.
That's the way to go.
People are going to get speeches.
It's going to be great.
Lonnie Hammelgren out in Vegas, the brain surgeon.
Oh yeah.
He had a crazy house that you could tour for a while.
I got to go one time just, you know, no, nothing even remotely close to an HOA.
He had crazy shit in there and he planned and held his own funeral and you want to hear
what people said about it.
Fuck yeah.
And I think he's still kicking.
He did this several years ago and he's still alive.
So I believe so.
Yeah.
So good for him.
Uh, I guess that's what Matt's going to do to Matt, but it's good, but he's not going
to know about it.
It'd be great if Richard was a, ladies and gentlemen, the man who will do about an hour,
Matt Donnelly.
Yeah.
That's what you needed.
The man who promised to do an hour comfortable for an hour ish.
It's Matt.
It's that uncomfortable intro.
How did things pick up during the show?
Well, I had to wait for them to break down the stage.
Oh, they weren't done.
No.
So the video finishes, she introduces me.
This is great.
Three or four minutes of total silence as they break down the screen and move everything
off of the stage.
Well, you can't start your final show while they're still breaking down, right?
This is the way you do it, man.
You ice them.
Yeah.
Ice them cold.
And I literally just went over to the side of the stage where she had moved to and said,
"Are you going to introduce me now?"
Again?
Yeah.
She goes, "Oh, no, just no."
Just go.
Just do it.
And I go, "But that's it."
So I go, "So then I go out on stage right now and just start."
She goes, "Ah."
You just want me to do it.
Yeah.
Yep.
Perfect.
One gas tank, everybody.
I went out and I started the show, and honestly, people weren't heckling me.
A lot of people were like, "No, I don't want to go on stage," which is annoying.
Sure.
Okay.
And it wasn't like a lot of people were clapping.
A lot of people were laughing.
I was getting to my stuff.
It just felt like I was doing one magic trick after another.
It didn't feel like a show.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
I got you.
I was like, "I'm just going to keep going."
And I got another one.
There was another Diddy.
How many were in the room?
Yeah.
I hate that your last show was that bad.
About 150.
Okay.
Yeah.
But I went out doing what I loved, and I had to call Chicago Magic Lounge and say, "Sorry,
this is it.
This is it."
How did the trip out to the random gig went well and everything?
There were no hiccups in the travel?
Funny.
You should ask.
I get there, and I take my little shuttle to ... Okay.
So do you have any ... What is your tactics for renting a car when you travel, Jacob?
I usually pre-book before we get there.
If I can check in before getting to the rental car place, if I'm able to check in before
getting to the desk, then I will.
And hopefully there is just a key pickup spot somewhere, or the keys are in the car, and
we load up, get in the car, and head right out.
This is where I need to get more savvy.
I'm not good at figuring out how to be one of the guys that walks past the counter directly
to where the cars are.
The only tactics I have been using, and this used to be very successful, and now it's not,
and I'll tell you why.
I used to book the third or fourth cheapest option, because it's usually a difference
of $5.
So I would choose that because basically sometimes there's a rush at one rental car counter
when you get there and the line's out the door.
And so I always book the third or fourth cheapest rental car, because usually that means I won't
be on that same line.
And this used to be a successful tactic until now ... This happened with Paul and I when
we went to Jersey, and this happened now when I came here, all these rental car companies
are now just run by the same people.
When you get to the counter, everybody works for all three rental car places at that counter.
Right.
Like Budget, Thrifty, and Avis, I think are all the same company.
They're all just ... No, there's no merger.
They're just running the ... Yeah, it's just like the guy at the desk at Thrifty, if there's
nobody at the desk at Budget and he doesn't have anybody in line at Thrifty, he just stands
up and moves over to the desk at Budget.
It's budget cuts.
So he's only getting paid one salary and working three jobs.
That's right.
Fuck man.
I don't know how that guy is being paid, but yes, he's definitely working three jobs.
He might be making $700,000 a year.
I don't know.
I'm guessing not.
Probably not.
If I made $700,000 in one year working for a rental car company, you would never see
me at the rental car company again.
Yeah.
That would be it.
I'd be there until they figured it out.
Are you kidding me?
This guy.
This guy's been working here for 28 years.
He is a rivaling Elon Musk and his billionaire status.
Jacob has a higher threshold for pain than I ever will.
If I saw $700,000 in my bank account today, I would disappear.
Disappear.
Poof.
Gone.
Without a trace.
I'd keep doing this show.
This is where we find out that Paul and I are different people.
Fair enough.
So I get there and the line is out the door.
I am the 40th person in line and there's two people working there.
One guy's wearing a Santa Claus hat to be festive because it's a Christmas weekend.
I was like, "Yeah, it's a freaking Christmas weekend.
Maybe I have more than two people at the rental car counter, huh?"
For sure.
No.
He's like, "Absolutely not."
So I am nervous because I'm supposed to be there at four, and I didn't account for an
hour of waiting for the car.
No.
I sarcastically brought up Netflix on my phone and started watching the new Knives Out movie
being like, "I'll never get through this."
Because it's 240.
That's a long...
And I was like...
Because I basically was like...
So I was timing each person.
I was really getting myself really angry and anxious, and I was like, "I need to check
out.
I need to be gone, and podcasts are not doing it because I'm still looking around."
So I started watching Knives Out.
It took me an hour and 15 minutes to get my car.
That's a bit of a wait.
Holy shit.
It took me an hour and 15 minutes to get my car.
That's a wait, baby.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
It was maddening.
It was really maddening.
And what airport was this?
St. Louis.
It's a major airport.
Not the smallest little podunk airport that you've ever seen in your life, yeah.
No.
And like...
It's because it's run by those St. Lunatics.
That's right.
And, you know, they had enough desks for eight people to work.
Well, that's it, Matt.
They spent all their money on desks.
They can't get desks and employees.
I got through an hour.
Someone's asked me if I finished the film.
I haven't finished it yet.
It seems to be the better one of the Knives Out movies.
It seems to be like the best one.
Really?
Oh!
We should watch it at Scoop Fest.
For people who don't remember, we tried that at a Scoop Fest one time.
Didn't work well.
No.
We did a different...
We had Murder on the Orient Express.
It was my call and it was the wrong call.
It was your call, but we were all excited about it.
You had the idea, but all three of us were very excited about it.
Yeah.
And it was a bad idea.
Anyways, I ended up getting late to the gig, which is not great, but it ended up being
fine.
We had rental car trouble in Austin as well, but different type of rental car trouble.
We breezed through the line.
That wasn't an issue.
We got in the car and went to drive away, and SJ was driving, and she goes, "Oh, there's
a tire pressure warning light on."
And sure enough, the passenger front tire, according to the car, was supposed to be 38
pounds per square inch, 38 PSI, and it was at 16 or 17.
It was quite low.
Whoa.
So we went back into the office, and we're like, "Hey, the car has a low tire light on
it.
You all want to do something about that?"
And she said, "Shit, you not."
She goes, "Oh, well, you can feel free to fill that up at like a gas station or something
after you get the car out, but if the tire has a leak in it, then I'm in more trouble
than I am now."
She was like, "Oh, it's just the cold weather."
I was like, "No, no, no, the cold weather knocks it down like five or six or seven PSI.
This is like 20."
The possible flat.
Yeah, like it might just be going flat.
If you're telling me it's fine and just need some air in it, then put some air in it and
I'll take it out and I guess we'll deal with it, but we were going out into the country
to visit my in-laws.
I'm not trying to have a flat tire out in the fucking woods somewhere.
No.
So finally, they go, "Well, you can do a ..." Because we had paid for it with points.
So we had gotten the premium level car or whatever.
And so she goes, "Oh, well, you can take this other, basically just the low level, the budget
car."
We were like, "Oh, well, okay.
That's fine, but do we get a refund on ..." No, no, there's no refunds.
And so that just went back and forth for a while.
And finally, I was like, "Just ..." Because she goes, "Oh, well, you can cancel the reservation
as well."
Oh, boy.
What do you mean we're here?
We have to have a car.
I'm waiting here to see where you can get me a car with all four tires.
That's all.
I was like, "You guys don't have an air compressor?
You don't have just somebody that can come out and put air in the tire and check the
tires?"
You would think someone does a check, right?
Don't they do a check on the cars as they're cleaning them up and whatnot?
Yes.
And then she goes, "Oh, well, we can get you a different car, but it's going to be a big
car."
And they finally give us a nice ... A big car?
Like a Tahoe.
Oh, that's a big car.
Something that if the three of us were going somewhere and I had rented a car and I rented
this, at least one of the two of you would be like, "Jacob, why did you rent such a big
fucking car just for the three of us?"
Yeah, we'd be laughing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
This was like eight people could fit in this thing plus luggage, and yeah, it was stupid.
It was very nice though.
Or you can have whatever's in this box and just put this box up on there, give it a tap.
Or you're going to ride on this goat.
Ride this goat all the way through the country, it knows the way.
Ride this goat!
Ride that goat!
And when you open the box, there's just a dildo inside that said, "Go fuck yourself."
Woo!
Oh, boy.
It was such a pain.
It was so weird, and we were both on no sleep at all.
I think I had slept for maybe an hour and a half the night before, and SJ was on literally
no sleep.
What a load of baloney.
I'm just standing there in this car rental office with that sleep-deprived confusion.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'm like, "No, I don't understand why we don't have a car and why we aren't leaving
already.
We have so many cars here, and the one you gave us has a flat tire."
So dumb.
What?
And then when she goes, "Oh, you can take this Tahoe," and I go, "Great," and they
tell us the parking spot, and we go out to it, and there is a large Tahoe-type SUV in
the parking spot, but it says Denali on it.
And so I was like, "Well, is that a Tahoe?
I don't know if Denali is a Tahoe."
And so I go back in, and I was like, "Hey, the thing in the spot there, it looks like
a Tahoe, but it says Denali on it."
And she goes, "Yeah, that's the type of Tahoe it is.
It's a Denali.
It's a nice one."
Oh, okay.
I was like, "Okay."
I was just asking.
I was making sure we were taking the right fucking car.
Don't yell at me.
She went back to blowing up your other tire by my mouth, like a clown with a balloon animal,
just like ...
I will tell you-
That's a living.
I will tell you one of the things that I do really love about living out here in old Western
PA.
I can drive to the Sheetz gas station.
I can pull up next to an air compressor machine.
I can push that baby to where I want it to go pressure-wise.
I can stick that tube on my tire and go and then be done, all for fucking free.
Done.
None of this charging bullshit.
My God.
I had-
Then Paul pulls out his dick and pisses all over it so that no one else will be able to
enjoy it.
I had to have three different locations in Vegas because either someone would rip the
fucking nozzle off and steal the copper-
Gas uses are a disaster here.
They really are.
Yeah.
Or they would tear up the e-reader so you couldn't use the machine or it was only quarters.
The only place you ever still had to use quarters was that fucking air compressing machine.
Of course, as I always said when you did live here, I said, "Paul, when you're at my house,
just tell me.
I own an air compressor and we can put air in your tires."
Never did that though.
We never did.
Just carried around quarters.
I just kept carrying around quarters because it doesn't happen when I-
When he goes to the Sheetz, he finishes off with a happy ending.
He suitcases it at the very end.
There's a little- right at the keister.
Just wakes it up.
Yeah.
Just wakes it up a little bit.
I offered that.
He didn't take me up on it.
My happy ending at the Sheetz is a fountain drink for Anne.
That's what that is.
She loves a Sheetz fountain drink.
I can't blame her.
They're quite good.
I got to take a Sheetz fountain drink to Anne McFeeters.
You better have a poncho on.
I got some diet Pepsi fountain drink for her the other day.
It was primo, top notch.
Sheetz is pretty good.
I got to give a shout out to Anne.
Poor thing.
She's trying to get home.
She's supposed to be off today.
She worked a 14 hour day yesterday.
She's been at work since six o'clock.
It's a nightmare.
People just keep calling off and she's too good to not just let the place burn in hell.
It's not something terrible happening, it's just people calling out and just calling a
schedule type stuff.
Yeah, it's bullshit.
It's bullshit.
Yeah.
But she's supposed to be off.
But anyway.
It's not like the milk frothing machine is raging out of control or anything like that.
Nothing like that.
Nothing terrible.
But she's been putting out fires for weeks now and it's just a bunch of bullshit and
I hope things clear up soon.
I'm going to give a shout out to the people of Chicago.
I had a blast at Chicago Magic Lounge this weekend.
I had really fun shows.
It was really great.
I love Chicago audiences.
I always have.
It was before Magic, it just took improv in Chicago.
I just have always loved doing shows in Chicago.
Good theater town.
And good entertainment town.
They know how to behave in a show.
I went to a show where a guy was just messing up and I was starting to get frustrated in
a way that everyone thought was funny.
He was on a really hard time giving me straight answers and then finally I did the whole think
of any animal and he said, I want to go see that.
He goes, what is he?
He goes, seven.
What was it?
Was he on something?
Was he just playing?
Was he just pulling your leg?
He was not sober.
Okay.
But this is when I love Chicago audiences where I go like, what is happening?
What world are we living in?
Did I enter a vortex?
You know, whatever.
And I just turned and I was like, I got to find somebody else and I was like, you, what's
your name?
He's like, Dan.
I was like, Dan, are you an asshole?
And everyone laughs, including the guy.
Yeah.
The guy goes, I don't think so.
And I go, good.
Name any animal.
And he's like, squirrel.
Good.
I did boom.
Pulled out a fish as a squirrel.
And I said, just see how hard that is.
It's so good though, when the, when the drunk guy laughs along, he goes like, I'm sorry.
And I was trying to explain this as I got through the whole weekend with Mike Mills
and Mike Mills.
I'm about to go out with jokers of magic.
And as I explained to him, I was like, you know, my clips that do best on my Instagram
feed and stuff like that and tick tock and all that stuff are ones where I am frustrated.
And the problem is the comments in the thing are some of them are like, boy, this guy's
an asshole.
Right?
Right.
And it's hard to explain.
It's like, no, no, no.
Like from your family.
And I was like, you know, the firehouse could still use volunteers and
like everybody was laughing.
I was frustrated, but jokingly frustrated.
Like I was playing it up.
Right.
And the whole audience was laughing, including the guy who I was messing with the whole time.
You know, right.
Oh, it's the best.
And I was like, but, but if that clip on social media, like they just be like this magicians
being a dickhead.
And so it's really hard.
Even the one that's the most famous for the more is really busting the guy's ball and
threatening to leave and that kind of stuff.
We hung out after that show and talked for 20 minutes.
We, we, we, he was happy, he was happy, you know, he was happy with his show experience.
Yeah.
And so it's just hard.
It's just hard.
But I had a blast in Chicago.
It is always weird.
I see, I see people doing this, not just on your social media, but on many of my friends,
me and my performer friends, social media, people will critique the, you know, eight
seconds of performance that they saw on this slip.
I'm like, guys, this is not, I know it's hard.
This is not what this is.
And on the other hand, I'm going to put it out, right?
Like it's really, it's really hard.
It's difficult.
I can't pitch too much because I scoop is making the announcement.
That guy is Matt's apprentice now.
I do the bit, uh, scooping over glass.
If I do a six, seven joke, I had it in my show briefly because I always say what's our
connection on the scale of one to 10.
I pull a number out of my pocket and I can pull it out and it's six, seven.
It's a really polarizing, polarizing joke.
It's a polarizing joke.
Some people really love it.
And some people go like, Oh God.
And then I hate that.
It's the devil makes my children say that.
And the risk is that I look like an old guy trying to look hip.
That's why I do it.
I was about to ask if you like that joke.
I could give a shit.
Cause I don't.
Cause yeah, exactly.
I mean, you don't care about that joke.
No, look, I got soccer jerseys made for my kid and for this Christmas tournament.
And uh, uh, uh, boy, we didn't talk about that.
Did we end up, no, we didn't talk about your kids, Christmas soccer tournament, the three
on three.
Oh, I feel bad.
Cause I'm one.
I don't know if everyone listens here.
This is a Penn Sunday school, but I have this conversation at Penn Sunday school, but you
guys react quickly.
Then Penn does everything.
So it's, it's fine by me.
Uh, but I got shirts made up for it, you know, my brother designed a logo for the jingle
ballers and uh, I had everyone's Jersey number six, seven, uh, and uh, every kid was loving
as we walked by in our shirts with a six, seven, because I was amongst children and
that's what the joke is for.
Yes.
Um, but uh, uh, yeah, so in the show, I don't do it cause it just looks like I could look
like an old guy trying to look hip and that that's dumb.
And it also slows things down.
It's a, it eats the cause it's the number joke is a quick bit that leads to the fish
reveal.
So it kind of really clunks it up rhythm wise if it takes up to say, cause then you have
to get back and do the actual joke and then yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it, it reads as a recovery and that's not funny.
But uh, yeah, guys, hey, uh, uh, you are talking to a now retired soccer coach, uh, just in
and out.
I, uh, you know, I, I gotta, I gotta go out on top, you know, you're going out on top,
huh?
Uh, look, let's just say mistakes were made, uh, for the three on three.
Yes.
Did, did the, uh, did the athletes on the field not follow your instructions to, uh,
the point that they should have, uh, thus losing the game, uh, via no fault of yours
coach?
No, it's not even, we're not even like, we're not even, it's not even, I wish, I wish that
was the problem.
Oh no.
The mistake I made was you could check a box, you either be recreational team or competitive
team.
Oh, okay.
You check competitive.
Correct.
Cause my kids have been playing together for seven years and they had a really good coach
and they're going on.
And so we go off our first game and we crushed the other team, five, nothing like really,
really great.
Like great.
We're riding high.
We're feeling good.
Sounds like Donnelly's on the sideline.
You're guys.
I checked the competitive box.
How come you're not bringing me competitive teams and even the old coach whose kid is
on our team showed up and he was like, Hey, maybe we'll do a barbecue at my house when
this is all over.
Like we're feeling good.
All right.
It's an all day event.
So we've got to wait like an hour and change between each game and the next game we go
up against the games.
The games are really quick games are like 12, 12 minute halves.
Uh, the whole thing's over an hour.
Yeah.
Oh, that's fun.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
And so you do first thing first batch around Robbins and then you do a semi-final and
final of the best teams from the round Robin.
Okay.
So then we go up against, uh, a team that is the, uh, yeah, it's, it's, it's the split
team of the traveling team in town, like the main traveling team in town split into different
teams and we're playing one of the, one of the very Brazilian national team.
They beat us eight nothing and, uh, and it was hard.
They scored fast.
They're, they're up for nothing like very fast and same age as, as your team.
Right?
Yeah.
Same ages, same ages, but just, you know, these are guys are practicing year round three
times a week.
They're going at it.
Yeah.
Playing well or playing dirty.
Uh, oh, uh, so good point, Paul.
So it turns out we play in the rec league when you play club team, it turns out a physical
contact is not a refereed as closely as recreation rec, a lot of shoving and a competitive, uh,
uh, uh, travel teams.
They allows, they allow a lot more contact.
So yes, indeed.
My kids are actually getting pushed around and then it's hard to watch.
That's what I figured.
And they want to complain.
And I'm saying like, he got to just play through it.
Right.
Now here's the problem.
This whole thing, you can't do that in, you can't do that mid game.
You can't, you can't shift that, that thought process.
No, no, no.
And that's why I know this like my only thing is I just try to like not raise my voice and
just like, we got to keep playing.
We got to keep going.
All you can do is be the calm example at that point.
This whole thing was because my youngest kid had a nightmare soccer season because what
happens when you play rec is that the, the, whatever core group you have will stay together,
but you always don't have, you know, it's rare to have like 12 core group people.
And so you get five or six new kids each season and this particular season, my kid got a bunch
of kids who didn't show up one kid like broke his arm and like, uh, and we just lost.
So we were playing luckily at soccer.
So you don't need your arm.
We were playing short handed the entire season.
My son had to play the entire game of every game.
That's right.
Yeah.
He was just out there all the time.
And sometimes one kid short.
So they're getting their butts kicked by, by, by playing, you know, seven on six or
whatever.
Right.
Yeah.
And so I just want to one last fun event for these kids to like not have it so hard and
then I've marched them into a buzz saw.
Yeah.
You should have gone home after the first game.
Exactly.
We should just, well, we won.
We should have a barbecue.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Barbecue sounds great.
That's the plan.
So because we beat that other shitty team, five, nothing, we get extra points higher.
Yes.
Extra points for a shutout.
So you're going against the gods.
Yep.
That's why for the finals and it's three of the travel team teams and our team.
So you played a third game?
Yes.
Because we're the number four seed round Robin.
So it goes into a quarterfinal.
It's one versus four.
So we have to play an even better team than the team that just kicked our ass ate nothing.
You had to keep playing with this Paul again.
You think you're just bringing up a philosophical point and you're reading the story.
So this next team just destroys us.
I mean, just like it is 16, nothing in the first 12 minutes.
And it literally like a minute into the second half, like this, you know, 14 year old kid
walks over to me.
He's the ref, you know, no, this is going to hurt down.
We'll just be the usually he's like, he's like, there's a mercy rule.
You can just call it, you know, and I was like, and no, I'm not calling.
I'm not calling.
Oh no, Matt.
You've got to call it.
Did you ask the kids?
Did you, did you propose it to the kids at all or no, no, cause they were, they would
just confirm it.
Like, like that's, that to me is more demoralizing.
You think, okay.
All right.
I mean, you're having the option for the mercy rule is a demoralizing moment.
It is a demoralizing moment, but if the ref is telling you, Hey, we can, we can put a
gun to this horse's head.
Yes.
I take that option, but I mean, that's me, but you're not out there playing a rec league
soccer game in the first place.
I just wanted my kids to score.
I want to see it.
I want to see if my kids could score another goal or something.
I just want to see if they could just find something, some fun moment or whatever.
And they weren't getting shut out in the, in the, no, no, we scored a couple of times.
We scored nice, we scored on them.
We actually scored first, which got things way too exciting.
We were, we were, we were briefly up one, nothing.
And then down a lot to one, uh, which is a terrible, cause it even gave a moment of false
hope.
Sure.
Right.
Like, Oh, maybe we are good enough.
We're not.
It's more self-examination that you don't want now, as you know, this, this, uh, this,
this show is familiar with the term Italian air show.
Sure.
Yeah.
So worst to worst.
So the Italian national team showed up.
This is where, this is where we, this is where, this is where we take my Italian soccer team
to Romstein and, uh, so I, I look on my app, like there's a giant thing that's taking place
all over the field with all these different age groups and everything else.
And so every time you go to the desk for help, they're like, look at the app, look at the
app, look at the app and the refs just record the scores and the, and the, and the app naturally
populate your next matchup.
And I see on the tournament thing that after underneath the finals, it says consolation
game.
So I assume that that means that the loser of the two finals teams play a consolation
That's the way it looks like on the app.
Okay.
Yeah.
Like a third place game or something.
So after we lost, I don't know a million to two, I'd be like, Hey, this is where I do
offer the mercy rule.
I'm like, Hey, according to the app, we can play one more game, but it's against the team
that we, you know, we two games that we lost two, two games ago or whoever lost to them,
but it's another club team.
My son is out.
He's like, no, yeah, he's like, no, I'm done.
And I was like, yeah.
And I'm, I have like, I hear you, I hear you and the other four kids say, yes, no.
And then I'm looking at the thing and it says, did you give your son an opportunity to talk
the other kids out of it?
Did you squeeze into the tightest Jersey fit you've ever done?
I'm a jingle baller.
If that were the end of this story, it'd be if you, if you shaved and put on like a beanie
and did a dwarf, did a dwarf on your knees out to the field thing and been fucking hilarious.
No, my kid and I have a very emotional conversation where he's mad because he doesn't want to
play, but he can't quit.
He won't quit.
And so if his kids are in, he's in, but he has to play.
And I'm saying you can go home if you want, don't worry about it.
And he's interpreting that as like me, like admonishing him.
And I'm like, no, no, this is not like a sarcastic or teachable dad moment.
For real, if you want to go home, it's fine.
Dad agrees.
This sucks.
If you want to go, go.
I'm only finishing my obligation as coach to these other kids.
And we don't have this obligation.
I do.
You can leave, but he doesn't have much of a choice there.
He can't leave.
No, it sucks.
It definitely sucks.
It just sucks.
And in my head, I'm like, I want to be like, buddy, I already failed.
Like no matter what this day is a fucking failure for what I wanted to have happen today.
It's already gone.
I don't even have a silver lining for what today is.
Not a single part of this went according to my plan.
I was trying to put an extra little pep in the step of your five core players that you
committed with for seven seasons.
And all I did was make you just put an exclamation point on the shit that was this season.
That's all I did was facilitate an extra hundred kicks to the balls, right?
Like what the hell?
I'm just feeling like a terrible person.
I would also like my day to end.
I sure would like to go home to these other kids want to keep playing though.
So I have to stick around, right?
I misread the app.
The constellation game is for the winners of the losers.
So all the losers that didn't make the final tournament went to their own bracket, a bracket
I'm sure we would have loved to have been in.
Sure.
And so the what they called the fun bracket, the two winners of the losers got one last
game on another field and I had to then turn around after all of that fighting.
I just did with my son and all of the, all the pep talks, all the Paris escape to their
other kids and go, just kidding.
I misread the app.
There's no game.
Go home.
Uh, what a headache on the text thread like, are we still doing a picnic?
Right.
So barbecue, barbecue motherfucker, let's rain check on this one and we'll do it some other
day.
Yeah.
It's been a day trying is the first step to failure.
Oh, that's awful, dude, I'm sorry, sorry, but kids into the holiday spirit though.
Maybe a good lesson in sports bullshitness.
Um, well I found myself like going through all these things in my head, right?
And then I've, I was reminded of America's got talent where like, uh, when I crashed
up on America's got talent, I kept being like, oh, if I ever do this next time, and then
my brain kept going like, there is no next time.
And then I would still swim and swirl and beat myself up and stuff.
And my brain would go like, you're never going back.
And so that's what's happening here.
I keep like, oh, if I next time we'll do the recreation league, there's no next time.
We're not rallying this back together again, we're not getting the old gang back together
next year.
I'm like, I'm not going to call these parents again.
That tournament we played last year, you want to do that again?
But when you put your trust in me to march your kids to an awesome afternoon of soccer
and I just got there, it was more of a death march.
I was like, I saw, yeah, all these adjustments in my head, gave me your kids and I got up
these really cute jerseys.
They said six, seven, the jingle ballers was a whole thing.
And then the other team made them dig their own graves before shooting them execution
style.
Yeah.
We'll call them all next year in December and be like, are your kids feeling a little
too arrogant or cocky?
Could they use another lesson in humility?
How are your kids doing?
They need to get knocked down a peg?
Send the link for the three on three.
Boom.
Let's go.
Get on board the humility train, get on board the humility train.
It's the opposite of like a ropes course where they build kids' confidence up over, you know,
whatever.
It's like, you call me like your kids are arrogant.
Don't worry.
I will sign them up for a three on three soccer team.
No, no, no.
You're not so great.
12 year old.
Oh man.
Like, you know, we're sitting around before the games.
So this kids are just playing soccer with other random kids and just, you know, playing
on random, you know, just, just fucking around, right?
And playing.
Yeah.
And so I guess other kids that were on that team that, that beat us, eight, nothing.
We're like playing around with them and literally like was like, Oh, we're playing you guys
next.
And then one kid was like, Oh, we're going to beat them.
Like, and they, and so like, you want to be like, Oh, we'll show them.
And then they did.
And then just as like, Oh, it's like everything from a terrible movie and there's no, there's
no second act.
It's just, it's just the first act of the terrible movie.
It's a more realistic movie where the, where the rich, tough team comes in and just beats
the shit out of the upstart team.
But you're done coaching now.
That's cool.
That's great.
That's what I said.
I said, if you want to, I said, if you guys want to start an improv group or play basketball,
you let me know.
There you go.
You're done until then leave me alone.
Are you done walking yet?
What you like in general?
The milers shit, an intervention from Paul, any kind of physical activity, bail on everything.
It doesn't lead to anything positive.
It just doesn't give him one hip replacement.
He's like, quit walking, knock it off.
This is my strutting around cock of the block.
Here I am.
Ambulatory as fuck.
Look at me, dude, to do, to do the castle, both legs are workings.
Both legs have worked.
Oh, are you guys talking about Matt Donnelly?
You talking about the guy that walks?
Yeah.
Fucking walking guy.
The ambulatory flex is annoying, right?
He can't even get to a thousand miles.
Dip shit.
He can't count.
He can.
He can walk.
We can't fucking count.
Yes.
Kids can count.
They can do well, but that one, it was my failure.
Not theirs.
They achieved their goals.
Right.
And so it was like a joke in the family for my kids to make fun of me failing.
So I got to really lean into that and own that.
And that was kind of fun.
You just kind of had to eat shit.
You don't feel like you're going to lean into this one in the future that's going to come
up on new years as a big funny joke.
That's what I mean.
Jacob is like everywhere I look at, I'm like, no, it's just an L. It's just a total fucking
loss.
It's just a total.
I just, I failed and it's over.
Like there's nothing, there's no way to poke at it.
There's a silver lining.
Here's the silver lining.
Oh, okay.
Those jerseys.
You got them.
Yeah.
With the six, seven gang.
Every time they hear the six, seven shit, now it's going to be like, Oh, fuck that.
So you may have started a kind of a underground rid of the six, seven, six, seven, at least
for them, at least for your kids are not going to enjoy it.
We have neighbors who are more religious.
They really do think it's some kind of devil practice.
And they did.
They said this.
I wasn't joking when I said it's a devil ritual.
That's what these fucking people think they're crazy as fuck.
Their kids have said to our kids, like, can you not make six, seven jokes around us?
My parents say it's satanic.
So fucking stupid.
This country is getting what it deserves.
And I am like, do they really believe that or do they just hate that joke so much?
They want it to stop.
They believe it.
If it's the second, then I'm with them.
This is one of those things I'm all for.
I'm all for lying to children.
If it accomplishes getting rid of a joke, that's really annoying.
No, this is, this is the dumbest thing it is.
It is the same as rock and roll.
It is the same as underground comedy.
It is the same as anything that the younger generation has ownership of and understanding
of that the older generation can't comprehend fully.
And nothing makes the older generation go crazier than when their kids are doing something
that they don't understand.
And I've told you that K-pop, K-pop in general makes me feel old and out of touch.
And I love it.
Anytime I see.
No, I love it.
It's great.
But like every time I see or hear anything related to K-pop, I just feel old.
Well, I feel old and out of touch.
And you should.
We are.
I think it's just correct.
I think it doesn't mean the devil made it to poison and kill your children.
It's the dumbest shit.
It's all, it's all just, and it's all just, I don't think K-pop is of the devil.
It's all control.
I do believe that six, seven is.
It's all misogyny.
It's all racism.
It's all tied together in this bullshit that this now constantly now probably fine countries
have to be fine.
It's good.
Sure.
It's nailed it.
I'll tell you what else is brought to you by racism and massage.
No, no.
And that.
The United States of America.
Today's show is brought to you by Yeti brand ice creams, sitting cones, Yeti brand, Yeti
brand ice cream, sitting cones.
This is a, this is a real thing.
Who's this from?
This is from the micro scoop in 24.
Micro scoop.
So this is from an, a classic episode of the electric company.
Oh.
Have you seen this?
So it's a Spider-Man episode where there's this Yeti running loose in New York and Spidey
has to trap him.
So what he does is he buys ice cream cones cause of course the Yeti is attracted to cold
and he makes this trail of ice cream cones and the Yeti incredibly suggestively sits
on every ice cream cone as he follows the trail of ice cream cones to the trap that
Spider-Man has set for the Yeti.
So I don't even know micro scoop what commercial I can do here that comes close to just telling
people to go on YouTube and look up the Yeti episode of Spider-Man from the electric company
and watch the Yeti suggestively keister a ton of ice cream cones up its ass.
It's, it's beyond disturbing.
And when it does it, it makes like a, a hiss sound, you know, like when you, when you throw
a hot, hot liquor, a little bit of water on a hot griddle as that's the Yeti hot griddles
all these fucking ice cream cones and just psst, psst.
And like-
And her hay scoops to check out.
Really loves it.
Like the Yeti, the Yeti really loves it.
Yeah.
So go watch the Yeti get off on sitting on a bunch of ice cream cones.
Oh God, there it is.
Speaking of getting off, you're about to be getting off with some jock versus nerd.
Oh no.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time, time for jock versus nerd.
Explosion of sexually gratified Yetis.
It's live action.
You're like scooper Nova girl.
Thought I was animated.
No, it's live action.
And the live, the guy who played the live action, Spider-Man just passed away, uh, like
a week ago.
Toby McGuire?
No, this was technically the, he was a Henson guy, I think.
I don't remember, but he, uh, he was the technically the first live action Spider-Man and it's
really, yeah.
Kind of sad.
I wanted one more quick little announcement of what I did last week.
Uh, Matt and Malia are, are my dear Pennsylvania scoop friends were kind enough to invite me
out to Christmas vacations put on by the bricolage, uh, production company.
They did a midnight radio kind of thing.
They do a radio play version of national Lampoon's Christmas vacation with tons of Pittsburgh
references in it.
Oh, that's fun.
It was kind of cute.
So lots of Foley work going on through the whole thing and them just, and so you just
sit and you watch performers standing and reading through the script, but doing all
kinds of Foley work at the same time.
It was really funny.
Uh, a couple of things went over my head cause I haven't been out here long enough to know
all the, uh, the ins and outs.
Oh boy, I got it.
But um, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, we've got a scooper to come and ask today from rune scoop, uh, who sent a nice
email to about, uh, seeing Matt at the Chicago magic lounge.
So, uh, the room scoop really enjoyed Matt's performance at the Chicago magic lounge.
Uh, so you got that going for you, which is nice.
Yay.
My last shows, the retirement shows, it was great.
The categories are every breath you take, un-camouflaged animals, 50 50 and run it back.
Oh, and let's see, uh, team sling here.
I hear your fresh stats.
Matt has 2,800 all time.
Jacob has 2000 all time.
Paul is in the rear with negative 2000.
I'm always in the rear.
So that's, that's on the rune scoop games here.
Every breath you take is a category all about the police's every breath you take.
Uh, I loved the concept from Eric Dittleman's, uh, of, uh, camouflage animals.
So I present that to you with my own twist.
Un-camouflaged animals, uh, find the animal 50 50 where the odds are forever in your favor
and run it back questions from my last scooper D. Uh, Paul, you're up first.
What do you want?
Okay.
Uh, I'll try un-camouflaged animals.
One for 200, three, two, elephant blast off.
Un-camouflaged animals.
Right?
Uh-huh.
Three, two, elephant blast off.
There's a number three, a number two, the word elephant and blast off.
Three, two, one?
I mean, goodness, my dog is over here just going crazy about something.
I'll be right back.
Talk amongst yourselves.
The dog is like, it's obvious.
The answer is obvious.
Right.
Well, what one as like the answer as a, I don't know.
What do you think, Matt?
Three, two, elephant blast off.
What's the category?
Un-camouflaged animals.
I wonder if it's just elephant.
Trunk?
Oh, you might be right.
There you go.
I think it's a give me, it's a give me a thing.
I think he's making fun of the Dittleman category instead of, you know what I mean, where like
all the names.
Now I get it.
You're right.
That's exactly what it is.
Yeah.
Elephant is the answer.
Oh, shit.
It'd be weird if this was the time where Jacob's dogs decided to take over and eat him.
I don't know if anybody saw the follow-up that Dittleman posted on our Insta, but he
would have given me credit for Rue.
And it would have not given me credit for Holy Cross.
So I should, you should have won and I should have lost.
I should have won, but hey, water under the bridge.
All right.
Jacob's back with a pupper.
Now our views are going to go up.
Views are going to go through the moon.
So it's elephant, Jacob.
It's elephant.
That's, we figured it out.
It's a, it's a play on, on Dittleman's game of hiding the, the names.
There's no hiding.
So it's elephant.
Yeah.
So you think the answer is elephant?
They think so.
Yeah.
There we go.
It is elephant.
Matt.
I'll do un-camouflaged animals for 800, please.
Let's try it.
Your left shoe is plotting a coup against reality.
Oh, he did it.
It wasn't, it wasn't going to be that fun.
Okay.
I got, I got Dittle.
Let's see here.
Oh, or left, uh, left, shh, shh, shh, shh, yes, but.
Your left shoe is plotting a coup against reality.
Damn it.
I don't see it.
I'll pass.
Passes to me.
I don't, I don't understand what's happening in this category.
What's the category?
This is the, the Dittleman one, the un-camouflaged animals.
I had a delivery come to my house and my dog is furious about it.
I get a, huh.
What do you think?
I, I feel like pigeon, but I'm going to pass because I don't know.
All right.
There is no animal.
It's just a sneaky, sneaky, uh, he promised me it would be unhinged and he is delivering.
All right.
There you go.
I'll do un-camouflaged animals for 600.
The chef told us that we wanted to be average to work elsewhere.
It's B average.
The answer is Beaver.
B average together.
It's Beaver guys.
Beaver is what I'm going with.
Beaver.
Boy.
I'm glad I got that one right.
Paul.
Every breath you take for 800, I'm going to shoot the moon.
Ooh.
It's all about the police.
This is where I next saw you a venue.
Oh my goodness.
This is where I next saw you.
See now this is clearly one that I needed to do in order.
Paul.
I'll pass.
Clearly.
Uh, Matt.
Pass.
The Turner hall ballroom jokers tour.
Okay.
That's who's going to see me next.
See, see if I'm sitting near you, go to jokersofmagic.com, uh, un-camouflaged animals, 400.
Daily double.
I bet it all.
I have zero points.
Hey kids, quit monkey in a round monkey.
Ooh, it is monkey.
It's in monkeying.
You probably couldn't see it.
The word monkey is hidden cleverly inside of the word monkeying.
Pretty fucking sneaky.
It's me.
I'll try 50, 50 for 200.
The odds you get this question right are 50, 50 true.
So now wait, that's, I'd say the odds are a hundred percent.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I, if I picked false, they wouldn't have been.
This is that riddle of the twins at the window like that.
Yeah, exactly.
Everything I say is a lie and you can't believe anything I say or something.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Uh, I only tell the truth.
I only tell lies.
Right.
Uh, run it back for 200.
What is my favorite word?
Hint.
It's six letters, three of which are Y definition, a conjunction or opposition, especially of
the moon with the sun.
What is my favorite word?
Six letters, three wise.
Wow.
Why?
Yeah.
Conjunction.
Uh, conjunction or opposition of the moon.
Uh, yeah.
Moon.
No, what's that called?
It's not an eclipse, not an eclipse, not a ellipse.
I'll pass.
I don't know.
Matt pass.
Pass.
Uh, Y Z Y G Y.
Sidgey.
Um, uh, I'll do 50, 50, 400.
The odds you get this question right are one in 25.
False.
It is false.
Well done.
Knock that math out of the park.
I'm going 50, 50 for 800.
I'll take the burn this time.
Whoa.
The odds you get this question right or one in 100.
All right.
Let's see.
I'm going to say false.
Oh, it's true.
It's either right or it's wrong.
Oh man.
What?
Wait.
The odds you get this question right are one in 100 true.
It's right or it's wrong.
I don't get that at all.
Somebody explained that to me.
I got it wrong, but somebody explained it to me.
Yeah.
Paul.
Uh, run it back for 400.
Free square.
Yay.
Uh, reaction or response must feature a reference to bingo to get points.
Oh no.
Oh wow.
I said yay.
I thought yay might be enough.
It wasn't.
I'm sorry, Paul.
You got that wrong.
That's fair enough.
Matt.
Oh man.
Now I'm trying not to step in a landmine.
This is a sneaky, this is a sneaky fucking scooperty.
Every breath you take for 200.
All right.
Uh, this is where I first saw you on platform.
Um, uh, uh, also this is just a police style.
Every breath you take category just to Matt.
Stalking you.
Yeah.
It's got to be fool us.
Right, Matt?
No, no, no.
He came and saw me live and he told me when I saw him and I'm trying to remember, I think
it was when I was opening for PIF in Chicago, I think it was in Chicago when I opened for
PIF.
Do I need to know the name of the club?
I, I thought this was going to be like, I thought the platform meant like Twitch.
Oh, I'm just wrong on all of this.
I think.
I don't know.
Okay.
Let's see.
Yes.
There you go.
That's the solve.
That's all right.
Let's see.
Where did Rune scoop first see Matt Donnelly?
Um, fuck it.
Twitch.
YouTuber Twitch.
Look at that.
Yes.
Good job.
Jacob.
You got it right.
Good.
Yeah, I got it.
It's me.
I'll try.
Um, uh, run it back 600 to protect his new wealth.
A young, uh, oh, the Greek freak Janice.
Uh, I'm not going to try and say his last name.
That's it.
Captain kept in the NBA, kept in the NBA, kept his money at the FDIC limit in this mini
banks.
Hint plus or minus, uh, plus or minus two.
It's the first year of his rookie contract.
Oh, wow.
So he just owed money insured up to the FDIC amount in every many banks.
Wow.
Oh, I see.
So how many, how many, I mean, well, first, how, how much is FDIC insured?
Well, I believe that is the, uh, half of this entire question.
Okay.
I don't know that.
And I don't know his rookie contract.
I'm telling you that there are two halves of this question.
I don't know either.
Well, educated guesses.
How much do you think banks insured 25 K?
I think it goes higher than that.
I think.
No, it's going to be, I would think it's million, no, at least a million.
Would you pass your Jacob that passes to Paul?
Okay.
I'll guess, uh, I'll guess four.
Nope.
I'll guess 25 banks, 25 banks.
Let's see.
Seven.
Seven is the answer and does it make more sense?
This time, Paul, did it make more sense?
This time?
Nope.
All right then.
Paul, you're wrong.
Run it back for eight Hondo.
Expand the window.
As you read from the category, see here, hold on.
Can I do this?
What do I have to do here?
Uh, from the category, this expand this window, the thing.
This is truly outside the box.
The category spaces category, spaceless potpourri.
Oh, it keeps going.
Oh, here we go.
Although owned by the Mars corporation, M&Ms were co-invented by the son of the president
of this chocolate company and filled with their chocolate owned by the Mars corporation.
M&Ms were co-invented by the son of the president of this chocolate company and filled with
their chocolate.
Uh, gotta be Hershey.
Let's try Hershey.
Oh, man, this is off the rails.
I love it.
Man, it is Hershey.
Hey, I'm back to zero.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Uh, Matt, you're up.
Back on the board.
Oh, I can't see it anymore.
I can't see the board.
No, uh, I will take, uh, every breath you take for 600.
Daily double.
Now it's for 800.
This is where I third saw you.
The venue.
Chicago Magic Lounge.
It's the Chicago Magic Lounge.
Nice one.
Was that this time?
This was the third?
That's correct.
All right.
Uh, score check with two questions left.
Matt now has the lead with 1600.
I'm in second with 200.
Paul's in third with zero.
There's no more daily doubles left.
There's an every breath you take for 400 and a 50/50 for 600.
I'm going to do that 50/50 instead of trying to figure out where Rune Scoop saw Matt Donnelly
at different times.
That is game Paul.
Is that squirrel in your background?
Is that the squirrel in your background?
No, Paul.
No, thank God.
I'm going to say yes.
Okay.
Points of Paul looked.
Did you look Paul?
Nope.
Did you see me?
I didn't see you look.
That's why I asked.
No.
Jacob got that one wrong.
Paul closing out the category.
Every breath you take for 400.
This is the game.
This is where I second saw you.
What venue did Rune Scoop see Matt at the second time he saw Matt?
I will pass.
I don't know.
Oh, interesting.
Matt, that passes to you.
I am trying to remember.
He told me when I say opening for PIF, though, I don't think that's right.
Okay.
I think maybe he came and saw a foolers tour show.
I forget though, pass all that passes to me.
That would be Matt's house through the second story window at Matt's house that Rune Scoop
was looking through.
Oh no.
It's the Paps.
Yeah.
The fooler store.
There you go.
I got that one wrong.
And that is the game.
Matt wins with 1600.
Paul is in second with zero and I am in third with negative 800.
That's from Rune Scoop.
Thank you so much.
Rune Scoop.
If you want to send us a scooper to your price, a scryte jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock
versus nerd, head over to preachingfund.com.
Nope.
That's wrong.
Head over to heyscoops.com.
Heyscoops.com right there on the homepage.
You can make us any of those jock versus nerds.
You can send us some email that will get read on the show.
All those things happen right over there at heyscoops.com.
Go there now.
Well, not right now.
Finish the show first and then go.
Yeah.
I want to thank the people who support us over on Patreon.
Absolutely.
These people all scored a goal against my son's team in the three on three.
Angela Chan.
Peter McDougall.
Gelato Steve.
Rodimus Scoop.
Nikki Benoit.
Scoop Chang.
The Beijing Bugle.
Scoop of Root Canel.
All-Star Scoop.
Coach Rat Bastard.
Coconut Time Travel.
Cream City Scoop.
Doc Scoop.
Edla Scoop.
Erotic Scrape Scoop.
Freeze Dried Scoop.
Gelato Problems.
Genetic Scoop.
Greater Sunday Scoop.
House Dad Scoop.
Mississippi Churning Scoop.
One Fell Scoop.
P.E.
Scoop.
Petty Officer Scoop.
Quiet Quiet Scoop.
Salt Lake Scoop.
Scoop Bucky.
Scoop Emily.
Scoop Skywalker.
Scoop Mids.
Scoop Nick.
And Scoopy Bartfast.
The following people think a flat tire on a rental car is not that big of a deal.
Evil Monkey.
Gerardo Garcia.
Jacob Dinklelaker.
Jason Horcastis.
Jason Speckland.
Jeff Bizarre.
John Carter.
Johnny Parker.
Judy Schneider.
Kurt Hendrickson.
Larry Goodale.
Leon Cox.
Logren C. Mario Rosa.
Matt Glowacki.
Michael Calder.
Mike Wenz.
Paula.
Roger Edge.
Sanja Petrovic.
Scoop La Quesa.
Scoop La Quesa rather.
Shonathan P. Stab and Dash Scoop.
Stephanie Young.
Stephen Biggs.
Thomas Beach.
Tom Krieger.
Tom Stott.
Tony Cowley.
Frozen Cusser.
Pete Romano.
Sugar Rush Socio.
The Famous Ball.
Jenny Ebarb.
Macho Scoop.
Randy Sprinkles.
- The following people all got all the Pittsburgh jokes at the holiday show.
Ian's knows what I'm talking about.
Scoopy, Scoopy, Jess, Jess, Six Foot Scoop, Slightly Sleddy Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Solar
Powered Scoop, Sweetest Scoop, Take it Easy Podcast Scoop, The Last Thing in the Attic,
That Thing in the Attic, The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, Water Ice Scoop, Adam Stickney,
Adam Jernberg, Brian Richard, Brooks Lyle, Cali Ghost, Carolyn Albert, Court Myers, David
Sorensen and Derek Dozier.
- The following individuals, all Ian's went down the house and moved my pork and chair.
The Micro Scoop, Unbanned Scoop, A Ranch Slunk, Ameriscot Scoop, Apple Scoop, AWOL Scoop,
Bad Pirate Scoop, Bear Scoop, Belgian Triple Scoop, Bencher Man Scoop, Big Load of Scoop,
Big Sexy, The Digital Nomad, Bike Scoop, Bosen Scoop, Canadian Scoop, Crystal and Captain
James T. Scoop.
- And of course, the following scoops were all accidentally shot in the face while executing
the New Jersey Merge.
It's Parker Van Tiller, Coffee Bean Scoop, Cone Photo-Scoop, Photo-Rescoopter, Counselor
Matt, Country Scoop, Dave Serial, Dole Whip Scoop, Dippin Dot Jack, Distiller Scoop, Don't
Say Scoop Name, Fade Out Scoop, Freehold Scoop, Frozen 49th Scoop, Fudgy the Whale, Galoosha
Scoop, Gas Man Scoop, Gaspacho Scoop, Gravel Scoop, Green Wolf Scoop, Grill Sergeant Scoops,
Hatchet Scoops, Hylian Scoop, J-Rock Scoop, Keith Robert Corning Scoop, Kiwi Fruit Scoop,
LAJ Latter-Day Scoop, Lemur Screamer Creamer, Excuse Me, Lil Red, Mama Ninja Scoop, Matcha
Ice Cream Sunday, Matt Scoop-A-Fail, Max the Ginger Scoop, McTits, Milkleg Scoop, Mitzula,
Motor City Smitty, Mr. Head Scoop, Neapolitan, Nice Private Parts, I'll get back to the
list now, Okie Scoop, Polygon, Pebeck Scoop, Phil Tomlinson, Radioactive Scoop, Refrigerator
Perry Scoop, Remember the Alamoad, Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti
Monster, I think is what the rest of that says.
Maybe Scoop Eddie Monster?
I don't know.
Maybe Robots Ahoy and Scabby the Rat Scoop?
Thank you all so much.
We sure do love you.
Thank you so much.
If you want your name read on air, if you want a myriad of other rewards, then get yourself
over to PreachingFun.com and find a tier that you can afford today.
So if you're listening to this while you're on the field at your three on three soccer
tournament, get back to work, you're losing.
It's FartsInABag.biz.
That's FartsInABag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as three dollars a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
This show is dependent on our Patreon supporters, so if you have it in your hearts and you think
this show is worth more than $0, PreachingFun.com, FartsInABag.biz, those are the places you
can go.
And then there's all kinds of cool things that happen after you do that.
You hang out with us on Zoom.
There's all kinds.
You get to see like Paul's basement.
He gives full tours of his basement.
He introduces you to all of the rodents that are down there.
It's a very sweet thing.
It's a super nice, super sweet thing.
No more rodents.
Head on over there.
FartsInABag.biz, PreachingFun.com.
Do it now.
It's great.
All right.
Thanks, folks, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
Happy holidays and Merry Crisposh, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
This is our friend's house down south.
See you.