[MUSIC]
Hello there, it is my favorite part of the show.
This is the time when we get to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Well, I will tell you.
The ice cream truck drivers are the folks who deliver this fucking ice cream
straight into your fucking ear holes.
Sorry, I just got distracted by Matt's son signing on to the Zoom chat.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these five folks,
head over to preachingfun.com.
Preachingfun.com is where you want to go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver,
and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
Oh, we don't have a new list yet.
It's a new month, and we'll get to all that later.
Here's the show.
Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
And we have a murderous role as old school students in today's Zoom.
Yeah, we do.
Wendy Baumgartner, Delano Speeds, Aliyah.
People have been around for a while.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream socials sitting in Pittsburgh.
That's Paul Mattingly sitting in California, I think.
That's Matt Mattingly.
I'm Jacob in Las Vegas.
We're preachingfun.
Yes, indeed, my son has entered the chat.
We're recording in my hotel room, so they might as well hear.
Basically, I have to behave.
Might as well put him in here so you guys have to behave.
It's basically--
No behavior.
That'll probably--
The gloves are off.
I've given your son a copy of Powers.
It's over.
He's fully corrupted at this point.
That's true.
We can actually check in with him about that.
Okay, yeah.
Circles on circles.
Oh, I guess if you unmute yourself, it'll mess up everything.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You have to come over here if you want to talk.
You can highlight your screen, but you have to come over here to talk into my microphone.
Let's see.
Hi.
So did Paul corrupt you?
Are you going to bring that dirty magazine to school and show all the kids?
Are you going to--
There's no wrong answer here.
I actually haven't read the comic yet.
Oh.
You haven't read the articles?
It's that tantalizing, man.
Just look at the pictures.
I know.
That's right.
That's not what I mean.
I haven't read it.
I haven't looked at the pictures.
In fact, in the car when I was scrolling, I went from back to front.
So when Paul picked it up, I was like, uh-oh, wait.
Did he think I was looking at that?
No.
And instead, Paul was like, look at that.
Honestly, I didn't even remember.
I was like, oh, crap.
Yeah, sometimes there's boobs and powers, but it's nothing.
Whatever.
Paul stands by his decision.
I do stand by my decision.
It's a fantastic comic book.
It's by one of the ultimate comic book creators, Brian Michael Bendis.
And yeah, I stand by it.
You know what Brian Michael Bendis can't do?
Convince young boys to actually read the thing and not just look at the pictures.
That's not true.
I think he's inspired a generation.
Again, he's the guy behind Miles Morales.
He's had more than his share of successes.
So yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, we're in Arizona.
We're in Mesa.
Just Phoenix, Phoenix adjacent Mesa, Arizona.
Mesa, Arizona.
So I took my -- basically, we looked at the cost of the -- my wife is about to help relaunch Disco.
And so me being away figured whether we would, you know, hire a bunch of baby --
Do all the child care stuff.
-- hire a bunch of babysitters or I just take them with me.
And so, you know, I did what any dad would do.
I would be like, boys, this is the difference between the Las Vegas strip club
and a Phoenix strip club.
And I took them out to show them the different ways.
But --
More hands on.
So yeah, we road tripped it.
And we came out here to -- it is the -- Paul is holding up his phone that says the comic book
that we mentioned earlier.
Well, people were asking in the chat.
I'm just -- yeah.
Just showing people powers.
All right.
This is what -- this is the bonus content you get when you tune into the stream.
This is --
And this is the regular not bonus content that everybody else gets when they don't tune into the stream.
What do you mean?
This is incentivizing more subscriptions.
It's cheap.
Two bucks.
You can see my phone.
It's three now.
It's three.
Okay.
Three bucks.
Good God.
Inflation.
Never stops.
Three bucks.
You can see my phone.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So we road tripped it out here.
You know, all the times we would bitch about the Vegas heat and then our listeners from
Arizona would go like, "Ugh.
Whatever, dude.
Check it out.
Check out our neighborhood."
I used to be like, "It can't be that different."
It is.
Oh, no.
They're right.
It's so much --
Yeah, they're right.
It is that much more --
Arizona --
It's hotter here.
I understand people moving to Las Vegas.
There is stuff in Las Vegas.
There are things to do.
There's work.
There's jobs.
There's fun.
There's all these things.
Arizona doesn't have any of those things.
They're just hotter.
It's less fun and hotter.
Yeah.
We got to -- as my youngest said, it's a free sauna.
Free sauna here.
Yeah.
One of the most miserable times that I've ever experienced was when we did a Star Trek
promotion at a Diamondbacks game.
It was 108 degrees, and we were all wearing our full costumes.
We're walking around --
This was like a fan thing happening at the baseball game?
It was a promotional event for the experience.
It was like wearing your Star Trek stuff to the baseball game?
Yes, and one of our Klingons threw out the first pitch and didn't attach his gauntlet
properly and threw his gauntlet as well.
Part of his costume fell off.
I was like, "Ah, amateur hour."
How embarrassing.
Come on.
Get it together, Kermash.
Come on, Kermit.
That's where the expression is toss his gauntlet with his fastball came from, right?
That's right.
Yeah.
It's similar to throw out the baby with the bath water.
It's the same family of sayings.
But it was crazy.
After that day of walking around, we were just drenched.
Someone's not muting themselves.
Oh, we got them.
They're back.
We were funky.
It was gross.
In Vegas, there's the whole, "Oh, you could cook an egg on the sidewalk."
But out in Phoenix, it's like, "Oh, yeah.
I can look out the window and see shit melting."
The traffic lights are drooping.
Have you seen stuff like that, Matt?
Oh, yeah.
They figured it out.
They know how hot it is here, so nothing's drooping.
Nothing's drooping?
They know how to build their things.
Just Matt.
It was drooping 20 years ago.
Matt's the only thing that's drooping.
I was not informed that I was drooping.
In fact, we finished up the show last night.
I basically want to finish in time to make sure the kids go swimming at night.
Oh, yeah.
We got a hotel pool.
Nice.
Did you explain that to the audience as you were rushing through all the tricks?
Just pick at the card already.
All right?
We got to go.
We're going swimming.
Tick tock.
We're going swimming, guys.
Come on.
Panth or no panth?
Yeah, so we were swimming.
Even at night, 10 o'clock at night, the pool was still wicked warm from the days of fun
out here.
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes it's nice.
Sometimes it's just ...
Huh?
Nice, gooey, warm pool for you.
It just feels ... It just feels like pee.
Gooey warm.
It feels like pee.
It does.
It is like you're in pee.
That's why I like it.
Let me get that pee pool.
But then you don't get that fun thing of when you pee in the pool.
I don't know.
I just want to add to it.
I just want to feel like I'm contributing.
You're worried about not feeling the contrast of your own pee in a warm pool?
That's right.
Swim for contrast.
I like my pool to be 98.6 so that when I pee, I just have to feel the difference in buoyancy.
That's the only way I can tell.
Would that feel really, really hot?
It would, right?
Yes.
Yeah, 98.6 is nice and ... It's real warm.
It's not hot tub hot.
Yeah.
My hot tub is at 104.
We keep the hot tub at 104.
96, though.
It's pretty hot.
We actually dared ourselves to go into the hot tub so the pool would feel cool.
Oh, smart.
Even though it was hot out, we went into the hot tub and then went into the pool and then
the pool felt refreshing.
They had the hot tub on.
They did.
Wow.
That is surprising.
I agree.
August in Arizona.
It seems like a waste.
Well, it's 110.
Let's fire her up.
Hey, some people still have bad backs.
All right.
You do you.
I do sit in my hot tub because of my bad back.
I do get it a little bit.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
I did see a fellow trying to beat the heat on the Las Vegas Strip the other day during
my walk.
I don't remember if I told you guys about this guy.
I don't think I did, though.
He was wearing no shoes.
I started at the bottom with him and worked my way up just just observing this person.
He was wearing no shoes and mismatched ankle socks.
And he was wearing a pair of Super Mario Brothers boxer briefs in lieu of pants.
I haven't told you guys about this guy, right?
No, but so far all Paul heard was Super Mario Brothers.
And he was like, yay, I'm wearing this shirt.
Paul is currently matching this person.
I got my crocs on.
Well, you're already beating him then because he did not have shoes.
Okay.
He was wearing he's wearing socks.
He was not wearing pants.
He was wearing a pair of Super Mario Brothers boxer briefs.
He was wearing a tank top with one arm.
He had one of his arms through the head hole of the tank top.
So he's wearing a tank top, but it was like an off the shoulder number.
It was kind of kind of nice.
Don't think he was having a day.
He was just he was punching bricks left and right, hoping a mushroom would pop out of the top of it.
You have no idea how right you are, Matt Donnelly, because on his left hand, he was wearing one blue boxing glove.
Stop it.
Hundred percent socks, no shoes, no pants.
Super Mario Brothers underwear tank top with his hand through the arm or through the through the head hole and then a boxing glove.
Scullywalt says, so a 10 p.m.
Walmart shopper.
Yeah.
Basically, that's this was this was at about six p.m.
Walking down the Las Vegas strip.
And I'll tell you what.
Six p.m.
And you know how when you are walking near a person who is let's say has different sensibilities than than the average average people.
I mean, they're high.
Maybe they're high.
Maybe they're homeless.
Maybe they're a little off kilter.
Maybe all of these things like you see these people walking and you kind of you kind of clock them.
And because they they have kind of a manner about them that suggests even without the clothing, it suggests that they are a little a little off.
Maybe maybe they're not entirely based in reality.
Yeah.
Beating their own drum.
There you go.
That one of the most disconcerting things about this man is he was walking along seemingly just fine.
If it weren't for his appearance, the manner that he was walking, he was walking as though he had somewhere to be.
He wasn't in a terrible hurry, but he was walking with some purpose just heading down the street.
I think I know what happened.
Is it possible he was a refugee from a Mr. Beast contest?
Oh, that's possible, Matt.
Matt, what's your theory?
That is possible.
I was going to say I think what he happened was he found that invincible star where he would do it.
And he just went all over the place.
And then the star ran out.
And that's what he looked like when the star finished.
And he was like, oh, he didn't realize how much damage he was doing to himself with the invincibility.
Exactly.
Even though he was invincible.
So he was invincible, but his clothes weren't.
His clothes were.
His clothes took a beating.
He was fine, but his clothes really took a beating.
I think there's a new Mr. Beast coming out tomorrow, so I'll see it.
Oh, there is a new Mr. Beast episode coming out.
All right.
Hot drop.
We can find out if Paul's take is correct.
Look into his sweet dead eyes and obey.
That guy's a fucking monster.
Our pal Neil Fisher just wrote a book on that monster.
Just put out a book.
I can't wait.
Oh, nice.
I can only imagine.
He sent it to me.
I should send him an email properly, but why not use the podcast to thank him?
My kids were very happy.
It is fascinating.
Yeah.
Mr. Book.
Oh, by the way, we talked about this book on the show several weeks ago.
If you haven't started reading Cults Like Us by our friend Jane Borden, it is so fucking good.
I'm on the audiobook.
Jane reads it.
It is so good.
It is so interesting.
It's so good.
I was watching the news Superman and going like, oh, my gosh.
This is the thing that she talks about in her book.
I did the same thing.
From the Puritans, they demonized intelligence, right?
Yes.
And people who are smarter, freer thinkers.
I'm so glad we're over that shit.
No, she's saying it.
You think of yourself as whatever your politics are, but you think of yourself more as the open-minded politics.
You don't think you're bought into this.
But yet, when she breaks down that we just love a rebel, a rule breaker, right?
Yeah.
Oh, that part hits home really hard.
And so you're like, oh, every character I like in every movie and TV is the same thing that I'm hating about the current political climate, right?
Right.
And everything that we do in movies and TV about taking brainiacs and saying they're terrible people that should be ostracized and made fun of and taken care of, you know?
And it's like, and then freethinkers are not being respected.
We've lost our complete respect for expertise.
It adds a layer in that it makes you not care about kind of the current problems.
Yeah.
Because a strong man, you know, a hero is coming.
Yeah, yeah.
We've been conditioned to just not even believe, just conditioned to understand that a hero is going to come along and they're going to use some kind of physical violence and they're going to take care of us.
So I do that. Yeah. So Jane's book's been with me every time I watch TV or movies or book or whatever.
It is legitimately changed the way that I look at things.
I put a book last because that's the last thing I'm going to do. Watch TV, movies, then maybe read a book.
Right, right.
But yeah, and also it's helped me be a better parent as one of my children listens on.
But like the idea that we teach moralistic storytelling.
Not much better, just better.
Her point that we teach moralistic storytelling and therefore good things happen to good people and bad things happen to bad people.
So if things go wrong, you turn in and start hating yourself and blaming yourself versus other cultures that teach, you know, fortune, right?
Like fortune swings both ways. Things go good, things go bad.
You know, you're not in control of that.
Life isn't fair, but it is consistent.
Right. And that it's just going to swing both ways, no matter who you are, no matter where you are, it's just going to go. You're going to you're going to live a roller coaster.
And like that's so much better when my kids experience something bad and then want to beat themselves up.
Like it's really important. So, yeah, her book's incredible. Cults Like Us. Pick it up. It's great.
It's very good. And it's a very good read.
And she does her own reading for books on tape. So you get to hear her, her lovely, her lovely, her lovely dulcet tones.
And I tell you what, I tell you one of the most fun parts about listening to her read the book is all of the little asides because she loves to put the little little comments in on what she's commenting about.
So she there's there's little like almost kind of the office moments where she turns the camera and goes like, ah, see, but it's all her talking. It's kind of great.
And so listening to her do the asides on the audio book is pretty fantastic. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And like I said, we she's funny. We did improv back in the day. She was a powerhouse improviser at the old UCB.
So, yeah, awesome stuff. She's great. So we we drove down here to to to so this is Mystique Dining, but not a traditional location.
This is a this is a collab with a fever up productions. OK. And they do kind of pop up stuff.
And so when I got the address of where we were going, I pulled into like this Vegas has a Phoenix and Vegas have a very similar architecture. So if you're into this kind of like sprawling kind of almost like a warehouse feeling thing or like it's just a bunch of little pods of buildings where you have suites one through 50 and then the other one suites 50 through 80, you know, whatever.
Right. That kind of thing. And so pulling I go like there can't there can't be a magic show in here.
Like it's not it wasn't like a storefront. There was no kind of whatever. This is where the props for the magic show gets stored.
And then we finally my my my son pointed out they found the logo on the door. Like, no, it's there. And I was like, what? Oh, and we pull up and I would find out later.
They're like, oh, yeah, well, it used to be a church. And I was like, that still doesn't explain it. Like that still doesn't make it. It's a weird spot for a church, too. Exactly. It's just it doesn't it doesn't mean.
But you know, these are pop ups, right? So they're not looking for these, like, you know, they're going to take over a giant theater space or they're not going to take anything big up. And so makes it kind of cool.
And so when you do walk in, it is like a crazy its own magic trick. It is an instant transformation. You walk in and it is this ornate, beautiful, kind of like dragon themed bar and lounge with this with this parlor in the back.
And it's really nice. Yeah, really nice. That's fine. Performing magic parlor. So, yeah, so that part was super cool. The only problem is we couldn't get in when we got there.
And, oh, you weren't you weren't cool enough. And it was so hot. The guy, Frank, this great guy, Frank, was the easy opener. He's the close up magician and, you know, helper out or person, whatever.
Helper out or person. Well, he he's normally just the close up magician helps work the bar. Yeah.
And it turns out our house manager, his car broke down. And so he couldn't get to the space. His car melted. So Frank's trying to get things open.
And I thought Frank worked there and also couldn't get the couldn't get the place open. And I was kind of like, that's weird. But he would never been in this role before.
But again, it was so hot. I went to talk to him. He goes, no, no, no. He weighs me off. And he goes back into his car, turns on his air conditioning and he points to his phone. He's like, I'm not standing and eat.
We're going to talk air conditioned car to air conditioned car right next to each other.
That's that Arizona shit right there. I thought you were going to say that Frank invited you to sit in his air conditioned car with him and you can chat. I know he's not letting some hot man come in and take his air.
You crazy. He's on this giant thermal force. Enter that. He's not. He's no idiot. He knows. I'm happy to talk to you as long as you sit in your car. Your carbon footprint is far too large for the occupancy of my vehicle.
Get the fuck out. Stay the fuck out. So he, uh, uh, so he's having trouble with the door code, but I actually was like, oh, I, I did the San Diego location. I'm well aware of the weird key pad, uh, logistics of going inside.
You know, uh, you knew the lock. Yeah. So I was like, oh, let me give it a shot. So I get it open and we go inside and, and, and it really took me a minute, um, to figure out that Frank was not, uh, uh, a true staff person, but just a magician.
Is he is, he is like, he's getting, he's putting my kids to work right away. He's handing them remotes. He's like, I'll see if this works and see if you can get this works. And I think he's being cute and like taking care of my kids while I set up my show.
And after this, after it was all over, he's like, no, no, I needed their help. I didn't know how to open this place. And so I was handing out stuff to be like, go figure this out.
I wasn't babysitting your kids. I needed their help.
You know, who else needs Matt's children to get things done? That's the following sponsor today's show. Matt Madley's ice cream. Social are brought to you by the fine purveyors makers, outfitters and sources. Uh, a horse is a horse. Of course. Of course.
Hello. It's me, Michael Crawford from phantom of the opera. And I'd like to talk to you about, Oh, hello. It is me, Dracula. I have killed Michael Crawford to tell you.
He was low on vitamin C and easy to kill.
Drink your orange juice.
Now here's the thing. I really, I mean it for me, you know, I'm selling this stuff because I do, I want you to get your vitamin C, but more importantly, I want your blood to be sweet and full of Valencia. Goodness.
Pulp or no pulp.
Hey guys, I just needed a good clean drop of Paul yelling pulp.
Like a vampire. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Now you've got that classic drop of the vampire yelling pulp.
I don't know what that is. That's going to be, that's going to get that thing. You're going to wear a, wear a hole in that button. Companion piece to cults like us. I would recommend and has been reading this and telling me all about it.
It is the hot shit right now. Murderland. You guys know about this one. I've heard of this. Yeah. So Murderland is the hot business right now.
So this is the book. This is all about how in the sixties and seventies, the oil corporations put additives in the gas that they knew were poisoning us and lead and all that kind of thing.
Mostly lead and the smelting places that were processing lead were poisoning everyone around the smelting area and how basically you can trace like people like Ted Bundy and other serial killers to a certain radius of where these places were.
Seriously? Seriously. And also, and just in general, how a generation got poisoned by these gasoline additives that they knew were poisoning people.
Because I've heard, because I never understood unleaded gas growing up as a kid. Right. It's gasoline. Right. I was, I forget what podcast I was listening to, but I never heard the correlation, perhaps not causation, perhaps causation who knows of violence to lead.
Because basically we hear stories of our generation of men older than us, right? Who would, tales of just getting into fistfights, right? Like it became a trope in every movie we see. You go into a bar, somebody just pokes your chest and boom, you get into a fistfight.
And I just remember growing up being like, that happens so little as a bartender. So little. And then I didn't know that people, some people think that the lead in gas was actually why we were so violent.
Yes. Right. And, and it was- Well, Galatia President Superstar McScoops a lot in the chat is pointing out paint as well.
Yeah. It was in a lot of stuff. All the paint everywhere was all lead paint.
It was so dumb because the reason they put it in the gas- There was a decrease in violence with the unleading of gas.
Oh yeah. Well, and there was also an increase in IQ just in general. Like it just dumbed a whole generation down. And here's the worst thing.
Our generation actually got secondhand damage because folks like us who were born in the seventies, our mothers had been exposed to this stuff.
And it turns out that babies in the womb absorb calcium. They look for calcium from the mother, right? And in the taking of the calcium to- Not me, I look for booze. To build those baby bones.
You got any booze in here, lady? You look for the booze and the calcium. Those are the two main things. So you're looking for alcohol and you're looking for calcium.
Thank you. I feel seen. The booze and the calcium, the glory are yours now and forever. Amen.
Amen. But that baby is building its body up from lead-infused calcium deposits and it's basically fucking up the fetus.
And it's like, you know, I don't have to wonder too hard about my hip, you know, basically turning into mush after a couple of years, you know?
And I don't know if you guys- Your mom was a huge paint drinker, right?
Well, no, but I think I've mentioned to you guys before. I had, back when I was a kid, I had straight up Forrest Gump leg braces for a long time when I was a little kid.
Yes. Yeah. I was very pigeon-toed in my leg. Just recently, my brother found some old home videos of me walking around as a baby.
I am the gimpiest motherfucker you've ever seen. I mean, I had really deformed ass legs and hips and shit. I'm like, fuck man. No wonder my stuff is broken down. No wonder I was in such terrible pain.
Also, no wonder that they gave you those braces and kind of fixed you. Like, the hip thing didn't happen until later in life and we didn't know you as a gimp-y person.
So we have to also give some credit where credit is due that they addressed it.
There was some addressing, but also, but clearly one leg was longer than the other and that's part of what the hip thing was all about and a bunch of stuff.
But yeah, and that just makes me sad knowing that it's quite likely that some of that was due to environmental, lack of environmental protections on that little baby.
The demonizing of breastfeeding and moving up into formula. Right, that kind of thing too. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Flow back and then all of a sudden formula's evil and all that other stuff. Yep. Whatever.
I mean, people don't remember, when I was a baby, my mom was actually encouraged. They said, breastfeed, breastfeed your baby and everything. So she breastfed me.
But she would smoke leaded cigarettes while breastfeeding me because that's simply what her doctor recommended that she do.
She would add lead to unfiltered barbara cigarettes and she would just smoke those.
If anyone's stink guy at her for breastfeeding, she'd go punch him right in the face. She didn't care.
Of course, our system of whether we do or don't care of healthy products and how that affects our physical health, I get.
It is strange to me, the idea, like I think of getting in fights, fisty cuffs, as an emotional thing, not a physical thing.
Do you know what I mean? Like, I think it's weird. Oh, I do. Yeah, I see what you mean.
That's the distinction I find strange is that like I'm pumping gas and suddenly I go like, what'd you say? What'd you say, man?
This is what I find strange is that like, like we were getting into fisty cuffs more.
That's why we got an electric car. So I wouldn't have to get in as many fights.
I just my body just can't take it anymore. I'm getting older, Matt. I just can't fight twice a week every week.
I need recovery time. You need me to fight once every two weeks.
I'm there, but this is the frequency at least for another 10 years.
I've got I've got to fight a week in me. Yeah, I find it. I find it strange.
Well, I will say on the positive side of nature is healing, perhaps somewhat.
Anne and I last week went to a flower festival, the Freedom Farms Flower Festival.
This is the hippiest bullshit I've ever heard of in my life. Well, I don't know how hippie.
I guess it's kind of hippie. No, no, no, Jacob. You get in one Autobahn society and you have to go to these events.
Is that what it is? They're keeping score, right? Oh, you didn't go to that flower festival.
I thought you were a member of the Autobahn Society. I was a little trepidatious because it was Freedom Farms.
And any time anything comes with the moniker of freedom or liberty or anything like that, my alarm bells just go off.
Because as we all know, whenever a bill is passed in this country, that's something like the Child Protection and Free Cotton Candy Act.
It explicitly somewhere in the bill states all children under 13 should be executed and cotton candy should be banned.
Right. It's like it's always the opposite of what they're saying.
After this recording, I'm taking my kids to Cracker Barrel for breakfast. Good, good.
I just found out they just put legislation to rename it America Barrel. America Barrel.
Yeah. OK. I just thought they were going to rename it to a white people barrel. Just barrel. Just barrel.
It's always just been a barrel. Why do we have to qualify for who eats there?
I mean, Honky Barrel kind of rolls off the tongue, right? We can work with Honky Barrel.
It's definitely a self-selecting sample already. Oh, it's so. I mean, I do love that food.
Honky Barrel was my college band. We were Honky Barrel.
Did you open for Hootie? Yeah, yeah, yeah. After we won the Battle of the Bands, we got to open for Hootie.
You know, Honky Barrel is what Bozo the Clown used to call those little cups that you throw the ping pong ball into.
And if you get up to 13, you win the prize. The big prize.
Yeah. So you went you went to OK, it's a flower festival.
Freedom Farms Flower Festival. Yes. Oh, the classic FFF. Yep.
The Quad FFF. Fantastic Four.
Whose idea was this? You or Anson? I'll give you three guesses and the first two do not count.
So it was Paul's idea. It was Ant's, but Paul's and Target on Instagram.
Honey. Look at this. Put your shoes on quick.
It's a flower festival. Holy shit. In the middle in the dead middle of summer.
summer, one of the hottest days. Let's fucking go. Calm down.
Anyway, it was cute. It was kind of cool. You drive up. It was
adorable. It was adorable. It was pretty adorable. So we went
on the first day. So we got good pickings because this is the
thing. They have rows and rows of flowers just growing out
there. And you can just go and pick flowers. As many as you
want. 20 bucks. Get all the flowers you want. All the
flowers you can eat within reason all the flowers you can
eat. There were sunflowers. So I suppose you could eat some of
that. They say this is one of the last all you can pick flower
festivals. Most of our retro, you know, going retro and
they're becoming flower halls. They're really the flower halls.
That was a really clumsily constructed joke about Las Vegas.
Getting rid of all the buffets and replacing them with food
halls. Oh, I was spelling it h a u l. That's what I was thinking
too. Flower hall. I'm gonna I'm gonna go to Cracker Barrel. I'll
see you guys.
All right, Matt's gone. So you get on a little tractor. And
it's got they've got it. It's fancy like the tractors pull in
these fancy people wagons. It would be a really cool little
hayride kind of thing. So we do to do to do up to the up to the
place. And up top they've got like I said, rows and rows of
flowers that you can just go through and pick. And then they
had some live music playing. They had farm animals you could
go and check out. They had some food places that really good
barbecue, pardon me, barbecue, and like crafts.
We have a barbecue place who's trying to figure out who's got
the friendship where they figured out how to like, you
know, this, you know, this flower festival needs some
barbecue. It was called F and good barbecue. Oh, good. The F
also they stuck with the F F dash F and good barbecue. And
their mascot is a like looks looks basically like a wild
boar as the grim reaper. So by way of my understanding, this
that a reaper more this pig reaper God is slaughtering his
brethren to provide us with with hog meat for eating, which
I'm cool with. I think there's something there's something
interesting in there with like, oh, wow, this shit must be real
good. This guy knows his pig. He is a pig. You know, even the
pigs eat it. Like you go to a cannibal restaurant, you want a
guy who actually eats there. Yeah. You know, I mean, you
don't want to just go, you know, you enjoy those flowers. Can I
interest you in some human ribs?
Well, I don't know. Are you are you eating them? I am. Oh,
then yeah, if you're if they're good enough for you, I want
their damn good falling off the bone. Oh,
again, we are we're we're making fun of the almost conflictive
nature of this barbecue place being at this flower festival. I
just want to know how that friendship was made. Like, I
don't know. I think I think it's a combination of proximity
thing. How does Darren from effing barbecue kind of meet
Cynthia from the flower festival and go like, right, I'll bring
my brisket. It names are Frederick and Francine. It's a
proximity thing. I think it's mostly proximity thing because
you had that you had like this really great kettle corn that I
got. Okay, I do like a good kettle corn. Holy fuck the best
kettle corn I've ever had. And then to top it off, how much
are you eating kettle corn? Do you want like the big the big
package of it? Because I want like a handful of it. And I'm
really happy with about a handful of kettle corn. No, no,
no, no, no, but the two bucks, you're just worried about what
kettle waste? Is that what your concern is? I bought the medium
back. There it is that ranch slunk has got it there. Pig
grilling out for Richard scary. The has an awesome image. The I
bought the $8 medium bag. And after I was after I was home
eating this freshly popped stuff, I was like, I should have
bought the giant bag. Because this is it wasn't enough. This
is the best. And and I was saving half for Anne. So I was
just like, I'm tearing through this stuff. So oh, I'm seeing
Malia saying she she asked her husband to go to the flower
festival last weekend. This is Pennsylvania. Interesting.
Surprise, surprise. Interesting. Can you believe it? Can you
believe it? Anyway, it's probably it's probably fairly
well picked over at this point, as they say. But no, the big
topper, the big topper. Her husband said no, by the way.
Matt has more willpower than I what can I say? Malia's husband
and I would get along just fine to tell her about the
barbecue. What happened? Well, there's that and the big topper
Amish doughnuts on site. Real deal Amish doughnuts to the point
where there were little Amish kids running around Rumspringer
style chasing building little barn chasing the tractor. Just
giggling, talking in whatever language they speak. What do
they say? Yeah, Pennsylvania Dutch, right? Yeah, I was gonna
say it's a Dutch lot of Dutch. I'm just just like, they're just
running around giggling in Dutch. Well, I don't think it's
Dutch. I think the people who speak Dutch can't understand
them. I sure as fuck. Yeah. And you don't even speak that. I
don't even speak Dutch. Yeah, so I don't know, which is really
German. Yeah, exactly. Turn the page. Turn the page says it's
German. Yeah. It was it was fantastic. Just seeing all this.
Germans. It's a version of older German. Yeah, it's like ancient
German. The language of the Druids. So I am, I am more
excited for the sequel to spinal tap than I want to be. What are
we talking about here? Cinnamon sugar? What are we doing? What
are we doing on these doughnuts? Name, name your desire. Boston
cream. Done. Everything under the sun, man. They had so many
donuts. Yes, I was shocked. Shocked at the variety made to
order. Or were they were they? They were well, they were making
them fresh on site. And then you could just pick up. But I mean,
you're you're standing three feet from the the donut boiling
vat. They're doing it. Yeah, they're just making it, man.
They're just cranking out the cranking out the fucking
donuts. And it was so good. It was so good. I'm just picking
myself like laid out after a belly full of brisket and like
11 donuts and be like, I'm so glad we came to the flower
festival. This flower festival was so worth it. This is what
country fairs are like, man. That's what that's what ham
days is like you go and you get the pancake breakfast in the
morning, then you get the ham in the afternoon, and you get the
barbecue at night. It's just, it's just all food. How many
people are here? It was just like, is this is I'm gonna say
there were probably Well, there was Paul, there was an
Malia wasn't there. So that's still just two boys speaking
gibberish. I'm gonna guess there were three to 500 people bopping
around. So you're part of some big grass lot, big, big lot of
parking a parking lot, big parking lot, and then they had
some overflow parking and then everybody just walks up to the
tractor and then zips back. They had two tractors and all
these people like roller coasters and shit. They're
trying too hard. Flower festival. Yeah. I mean, there's a
field, there's some flowers, there's some barbecue and some
donuts. What else do you want? It's it was really easy. Oh,
there's a somebody's magic shells tell me about a long
Johns. Oh, in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. It's worth the
five hour one way drive. Okay. All right. I mean, they're up in
the chat there. They were talking about the Pennsylvania
Dutch. And I never I never knew this turn the page was saying in
the chat and og scoop was was chiming in as well, that it's
misheard. So the the Dutch is apparently a bastardization of
like Deutsch. So it's it's speaking Dutch or something.
It's all German. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know. While we're putting
out things in the chat, I'll just point out a scoop bearded
on says, it always amazes me that Matt and Jacob look like
their bodies match their voice. And then there's Paul, it always
shocks me. Wonderful people. I don't know what that means. My
body doesn't match my voice.
Wait, do you want to describe? I guess I'm curious. Well, I'm
describe who you expect. I sound like a thinner man. Yeah, do you
sound like a nerdy? I sound like a thinner guy. I have to put on
my full Ludmilla to to get people to understand my girth.
Are you? I was confused by that post as well. But not because of
any of that. Because they called me Jake.
I sometimes still call you that once in a while. And I don't know
why. I don't know what creates the Jake comes out every now and
then. Yeah. Before to type it, you need to type it.
Scoop beer. Now. Are you able to unmute yourself? Or no? Are you
at work or something?
No, no.
Oh, well, you sound so different than I expected. What did you
think Paul would look like by his voice?
Well, it took a while before I saw him in pictures. I heard him
bunch of times before I started looking up how you guys looked.
And I thought he was more fit. Yeah, more fit. He sounds like
a more fit person.
Well, I mean, you sound like a really fit guy trapped in the
not so fit guy's body.
That's essentially what I am. That's what I am. Yeah, no, no,
honestly, look, look, look, seriously, I've been working at
the target. I got some serious definition happening suddenly.
Guns. I got them guns, man. I got these traps, these traps.
Ain't no joke. You will get caught in these traps and you will
not escape.
Okay, go for the pen diet and keep it for like four or five
months.
No, they don't lose the traps.
I know. I wouldn't lose the traps. No, it's always a trap.
I'll just say this. Scoop beer nun just turned on his camera and
he does look how he sounds.
Yeah. Oh, no, I'm not surprised by how he looks at all.
I can see myself. So, but where are you?
Almost eight o'clock in Sweden, Gothenburg, uh, the barbecue
going.
Oh man, that looks amazing.
Ah, it just looks like perfect weather for it too.
Living better than I am. I can tell you that.
The only thing that would make it better is if you pushed out
your Amish donut kit and roll that up next to that.
I see the barbecue. I don't see the flower festival.
Well, beer nun, I appreciate that you think I sounded
healthier. I think I, I don't know. I think that's true.
I think I'm just a fairly healthy guy with a little too
much weight on me.
You don't eat vegetables.
I don't eat vegetables. I hate them and I am an emotional
eater. I'm an emotional eater, have been since I was a kid.
That's kind of the thing, you know, I don't eat cause I'm
hungry. I eat cause I want, you know, I eat cause it makes me
feel, uh, less nervous and upset. I don't do drugs. I don't
drink. So I guess that's kind of the thing. Uh, I don't know.
All I know is scoop beer nun's wife or girlfriend or someone
came out and I turned it off like that.
I don't want you to, uh, show off our house, uh, for some
fun or something.
We got to keep it safe. We got to keep it safe.
All of our listeners that can easily stalk Sweden for its
different locations.
Yeah, but beer nuns right. Our show is infamous. Our show is
infamous for people casing houses to rob in Sweden.
We have a lot of geo, what's it called? Geo sluts or whatever
it's called.
If anyone comes here, if they can chase that.
What are you making? What are you making on your grill?
Uh, well, uh, some sausages and a club steak that's not unwrapped
yet, but, uh, some carrots, uh, some, uh, what it's called, uh,
well, don't sleep on it, Paul. Don't sleep on a carrot.
Sounds like a solid, beautiful.
Well, you guys have a nice little feast going on out there.
I'm trying to do the last, uh, day of vacation.
Oh, I hope it's a good back to work, huh? Oh, sorry.
What do you do out in Sweden?
Uh, I am an electrical engineer, a consultant working for an oil
refinery.
Working for a while refinery, an oil refinery.
All right. All right.
Wow. That's, that's important.
Yeah.
People like gas and diesel and stuff. And, uh, we just, uh, did,
uh, expansion for bio, uh, fuel. So,
bio, uh,
biofuel, like, uh, like liquid, like fats, uh, from, uh,
uh, uh, uh, what do you call it? Uh, plants and, uh, animals.
Oh, really? Ah, great.
And make, uh, jet fuel, uh, diesel, uh, regular gas and, uh, well,
does ethanol fit in that?
Is that, oh, propane.
Uh, no, no, no. They, they had, uh, an, uh, ethanol plant, but, uh, it wasn't,
uh, didn't make money.
Is ethanol is mainly a U S thing, right?
Does anyone else really do ethanol?
Did any other countries really do a lot of ethanol?
We have our, uh, first primaries in Iowa just to make sure that we keep ethanol
as a subsidized thing in America.
So, yeah.
Yeah, for some reason we love ethanol here.
That's what they failed to do in Sweden.
They failed to leverage it politically to make it to that's what it was.
Well, everything's political, but, um, still.
Yeah, I understand that I was also going to start being the first primary for
Sweden. I think that'll be a nice change.
I'm not sure they're welcome.
The Swedes famously hate Iowa.
No, no, we can visit.
How long, how long have you been there?
That's a company.
Oh, well, I started my company five and a half years ago.
Okay.
Uh, has a lot changed in that industry over the last five years?
Um, well, there was a lot of more money made in, uh, the.
In, uh, carbon, uh, or fossil fuel, uh, businesses, uh, starting from around.
Yeah.
Corona and, uh, going through, uh, the Ukraine, uh, thing.
That makes sense.
Sure.
So it's, uh, pretty much the same through Corona.
Uh, when I started, I got in there in 2019.
Okay.
And, uh, then, uh, they started the big, uh, bio refining thing and, uh, well,
putting got a bit too, uh, grabby and changed the whole world.
And, uh, then, uh, the, the crude oil markets, uh, and, uh, the
fuel market, uh, bumped a lot.
So it was like, uh, a good, uh, a good margin was, uh, around four or
five dollars per barrel, and then it swooped up to 30.
So they made, uh, the, the, the refinery made, uh, around, uh.
So I know, I know there's a language, I know there's a language barrier, but, uh,
so, but, but I think it's fair to say you're a fan of Putin and what he's
done politically, it's helped you out.
That's what I'm here.
Well, uh, in the same way that you hate, uh, your home states and everything
around you and, uh, children, your wife and, uh, parents, and you don't have
any difficulties, uh, coping with your mother.
That's how they say yes in Sweden.
So in that way, yes.
Thank you for coming on and I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Thank you guys.
I will try to live up to my, the sound of my voice.
I will, I will endeavor to, uh, to, to, to lose, to lose some
foundage who you sound like.
There was a time, there was a time way back in the aughts that I wasn't, uh, I
got really focused on my health and I dropped to write it like 205 and that was
the skinniest I've been in a long time.
That was good, took a lot of effort.
I could do it again, I suppose, uh, probably should, maybe I will.
How do you go?
It's a firm, maybe let's take it from here.
Uh, I won't be thinned by scoop fest though.
You're going to see big old scoop fast.
Whenever I talk to other podcasters, I always say the mistake that I've made over
like the, whatever we've been doing this for like 12 years or whatever, that's
on the school 13 years, 14 years, whatever is like, uh, basically you, you tend to
only hear from the people who complain about little things.
You don't know when, no one ever just takes time to write, like enjoy
today's pod signing off.
In fact, one of the cool benefits of doing these new zoom episodes is seeing
people laugh and enjoy it in the chat and that kind of stuff.
But it's, it's very helpful to it.
And I always say, what happens is you end up podcasting to those voices.
You end up talking like you're trying to avoid the nitpicking little things that
come your way, that kind of just bother you throughout the day.
Right.
Um, and then when I go out and do magic shows, I get to run into listeners.
And I always find that refreshing because then I picture those are the people I'm
talking to when we're doing our podcast.
Right.
I never been picturing a fit Swedish dude over a grill
with sausages and carrots.
That's not something I'm thinking about.
Right.
You think he's outside our demographic.
That is clearly our demo, man.
That is a very different things.
That's all I've been picturing the whole time.
I would be, it would be good if we did.
Right.
I feel like I find it so reassuring that we have listeners like beer, none.
Uh, he can't be the only one.
So that's great.
Anytime we have listeners in other countries, you know, you know, Wendy's
up in Australia the whole time.
Like we're so awesome.
Yeah.
But yeah, did a guy listen to us at his grill in Sweden.
It's pretty cool to think about as a podcaster.
It's what I love about our international listeners is that we get to have them
tell us how bad it looks from the outside and get to empathize with what we're
going through as a country, which is nice.
Uh, and, and, and they still listen to us and they realize that we are
stuck here with this bullshit game that's being played.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Uh, thank you, Bassie.
We support you.
Uh, yeah, no, it's, uh, it's reassuring to have, uh, outside, uh, of
the state's, uh, listeners as well.
I'll tell you who only pictures fit Swedish men grilling.
Oh, and that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by the prequel to the famous Paul's guide to
being a dead horse series, Jacob's guide to murdering horses.
Hey, I'm Jacob.
You want to kill a horse?
Here's what you do.
Just go ahead and build yourself a cliff.
You build a cliff, build a big old tall cliff, maybe about 30 feet high.
And then what you do, you go ahead and whip that horse, whip it, whip it, whip
him and ride him right to the edge of that cliff.
Then jump off the horse right as he's going over the cliff.
You tell him Jake, get him Jake.
That's right.
I'm Jacob.
Take him, take that horse off the cliff.
Whoa.
There you go.
Dog food.
Oh, well 100%.
100%.
Oh, 100%.
Oh, for sure.
When was the last time you and SJ went, uh, picking flowers together?
Oh, all the time.
We go in our backyard here with our fake grass.
I got to say, you know, Anne has made a list of things for us to do around PA.
And she does come up with these things like the flower festival and that kind
of thing, and I can be a little bit of a curmudgeon from time to time, but I'm
trying to break myself for that a little bit more and just go for these things
and do it and I almost always enjoy myself.
And I really, I did enjoy myself at the flower festival.
No lie.
So your wife takes you to flower festivals.
Uh, my wife proposes that I do things, uh, at the house.
My wife adds on honey do lists.
So, uh, we, yeah, we had a guy coming out the other day, uh, yesterday
as we're recording, uh, had a guy coming yesterday to, uh, to look at part
of the backyard to put some new fake grass in, uh, some additional
fake grass in to, to our yard.
And right before he gets here, SJ announces that she has a new
idea for part of the backyard.
And it affects part of the grass, but it affects part of the fake grass
because, uh, where she's talking about, uh, it's kind of takes up the same space.
And I want to know if, uh, if your spouses have, uh, ever asked you
for something like this, my wife looked at our backyard and said, do you know
what we need in our backyard?
And I think we can put it right in this area, right over here.
She motioned towards, uh, towards an area.
Uh, she said, I think that we need a stage.
A stage.
My wife is proposing that I build us a stage in my backyard.
Wow.
And I'm kind of along for it.
So can I make an added suggestion?
Go ahead.
You might as well.
I've already built in a fucking stage in my backyard.
Can I recommend that the stage double as a gazebo?
You can recommend that.
Sure.
And the guy goes to one flower festival and he's suggesting you
add a gazebo to your backyard.
He learned the word gazebo.
Make the gazebo the stage, you know, have a, have a pergola roof on the
gazebo so that it's some, some shade.
You can maybe string lights up there at night.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could do that.
I could just see a band playing inside the gazebo.
Let me ask you this, have you ever been asked to perform inside
a gazebo as a stage?
Uh, yeah.
So have I, it sucks.
It sucks at the stage because you, those are terrible stages.
Yeah, yeah.
We're not going to it's theater in the realm, but it's not really
watching everyone to watch you through a fence.
It's like every show's a neighbor across, across the way.
I'm not saying the gazebo has to be a traditionally built gazebo.
You could just make the roof connected by like five main tiles.
Oh, a non-traditional gazebo.
Yeah.
More like a, more like a traditional, a non-traditional
gazebo, more stagey.
This is not, this is not your mother's gazebo.
This is not your mother's gazebo.
No, no, that gazebo would be a terrible stage.
Paul's non-traditional gazebo.
However, Paul, you do have a very elite barbecue every so often in your
backyard, so a stage makes sense for your backyard.
Uh, no, a stage is not the dumbest idea that has ever been
proposed for my backyard.
I think we're going to do it.
Where are you going to do it?
Well, I, that's part of it.
I think that last night I was, I was taking a stroll last night.
SJ was in California on a gig.
So I was at home last night by myself.
Uh, so I took a little stroll and I think I, I think I've given an A plus note to
where, uh, SJ was talking about having it.
Oh, cause she was talking about having kind of in the back of the backyard.
And I think we're kind of going to kind of move it over to the side a little bit.
And, uh, you know, the rock river, I think it's going to cover part of the rock river.
I think it's going to be over the top of that rock river.
So when water flows through it, it'll flow out from
underneath the bottom of this stage.
That's pretty cool.
Give it more of a gazebo vibe.
Yeah, I'll give it more of a gazebo vibe vibe.
Sure.
A non-traditional, a non-traditional gazebo.
A river doesn't run through a traditional gazebo already.
Either of you, have either of you ever really wanted something for your backyard?
I'm like, what?
I'm laughing because literally my wife and I were in the middle of it, having
like a very serious, not a serious discussion, like we were just having a
deep conversation and she just looked at the backyard and immediately changed the
subject to something she wanted to change in the backyard.
And I was like, we're really just switching gears.
All my wife does is want us to, we've actually already, we actually have.
You've done a lot of work on that backyard.
I was going to say, Jay, you haven't been over in a while, but if you would,
you wouldn't, you actually would be surprised in our backyard right now.
We've had so much work done back there.
Oh, nice.
Uh, so Matt, can I ask?
Two full-time jobs.
She decides to get them some things changed in the backyard.
Can I ask you Matt about your, uh, your backyard?
Is this too sensitive a topic from the 4th of July?
I know there was a fake grass incident.
What's the, what's the status?
Uh, I, I, so this is a sensitive topic.
I know.
Keeler's weighing in.
We had everybody over the 4th of July, you know, all the things that we were
buying for our kit, uh, for our, for our backyard, we bought a new fire pit.
Cause the, the, the chimney that Jacob delightfully lent us so many years ago,
uh, has been destroyed by, by the sun and weather and, and, and, and became
an, an, a non-functioning chimney.
Yeah.
Can I get that back?
You get it back from whatever neighbor term is over, whatever neighbor took it.
We put it out for bulk trash day.
You get it back from them.
Good, good.
I'll go, I'll go get it.
And, uh, so I bought, we bought like a new little, like, you know, quick put
together a fire pit type of thing we can put in the backyard and then the kids
wanted s'mores on 4th of July.
So I quickly built the fire pit.
I put it together.
Right.
This is after I put together all the new furniture in the backyard in 40 hours
before the cookout as well.
We had, we put brand new furniture outside.
Everything was my bite.
When I bought this one kid, it was all Allen key.
The entire thing was Allen key.
And I like my hands hurt for days, but they built so much
furniture on those, on those.
The days before 4th of July, when I came over to Matt's entire, the entire
living room was covered in these, uh, seating, uh, pillows that were expanding.
He'd left them out to expanding.
But also Matt had all brand new wood flooring throughout the house.
Yes.
So I came in and the first thing I said is, Oh, this looks really nice.
And he's like, fuck you.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
I was just making fun of my pillows all over the front cover.
I'm trying to make a nice backyard.
I don't care about your messy thing.
I'm talking about your nice new floors.
So, uh, I built a gym and they, uh, uh, both a fire pit.
Um, and you're saying build it.
You're talking about like one of those fire dish things and it's on a little
stand and yeah, giant black bowl with a screen, with a screen on top of it.
And so we built it.
So the kids made s'mores in the front yard and then, and then the party's over.
So we're trying to wrap it up.
And so, uh, Keeler got a water gun.
We started spraying out the fire.
They started smoking like crazy.
And then I'm trying to put everything away.
And then I have all these neighbors that come by and the user, uh, with
their dogs and use our front yard as a toilet.
Uh huh.
And so, uh, I was walking around cleaning stuff up and someone,
so be clear the dogs are using your yard as a toilet, not the neighbors.
I don't want to be that clear.
I don't know.
Okay.
So I, uh, the woman is, oh good.
I'm glad you're out here.
I saw that smoke.
And I was like, oh, people are making a big deal about this smoking fire thing.
So I move it into the backyard, but I don't want to put it too close to the house.
So I don't want the smoke going up the side of the stucco on the side yard.
Our side yard is fake grass.
Right.
And even though we put the fire out, the bottom of the fire pit was
still a very hot, uh, instrument.
And even though it has little pegs holding it off the ground, it wasn't high
enough off the ground that didn't melt a square foot patch of fake grass, uh, to,
to, to hard plastic ruin.
And, uh, my wife was not happy with me about my decision to move the fake fire pit.
So all, again, all I was trying to do is keep everyone happy.
And what happens bites me in the ass.
Yeah, that's right.
That's why more interesting.
And that's it.
It basically was like, can these guys play on a barefoot or is that a hazard?
Basically I just needed to figure that out.
And so I sent the children out to play like play.
And if you don't come back bleeding, I don't have to fix that little patch.
But if you come back to grinding, I do, I think you can fix this.
I think this is, I think you, you take a, uh, an exacto knife or a, you know,
a box cutter, cut a, kind of big square out of this, go get you some new fake
grass, just get some cheap fake grass from like home Depot or something like that.
You nail it down in there.
Bob's your uncle.
So this is a good, good talk, Jacob.
And this is what I looked up and I said that and I said, oh, maybe we can fix it.
And Sarah said you can't, you can't fix fake grass like that.
I said, well, I just looked up on the internet and the internet says you can,
but the internet says all kinds of things.
Yeah, I bet you can do it.
I bet Jacob's right.
And that was my first, the internet says that step-siblings are
fucking each other left and right.
I mean, there's no evidence to the contrary evidence for none against.
So, uh, we hope that I also really, I could see Matt's son on camera right now.
I, I'm uncomfortable with how quickly he got that joke very quickly.
Yeah, I don't like that at all.
I feel old now.
The internet is not a mystery to 11 years old, to 11 year old.
I don't like it.
So, um, so the question is the, the burnt thing, which you can only
see when you go up close, you can't really like when you look across the
earth, will it looks fine from a distance?
Will the exacto patch stick out more to my wife's gaze?
That's the issue.
Yeah, no, you gotta, you gotta do some serious color matching here.
That's the hard part because possibly because it's been weathered.
It's been the sun for years.
Yeah, exactly.
So there's no, there's no way we're going to find an actual matching patch.
I have to wait, have done the right thing.
Maybe just buy some spray paint.
Is the, when, when they, did you put the fake grass down?
This is a silly question.
Did you put the fake grass down or did you hire somebody to put the fake grass?
Uh, uh, go ahead.
I'll give you three guesses on the first, you don't count Jacob.
Okay.
So Matt hired people to put the fake grass down.
If they did the ground prep under the fake grass, it might be easy to pull that grass
up and just put new grass down and redo the whole thing.
That's what I was.
That is actually what I was thinking.
It might be, it might be pretty easy to do the whole thing.
If they did the ground, the ground prep.
Yeah, they did.
They did.
They did the big sand, big sand, man, all that stuff.
Yeah.
So yeah, I basically thinking like down the road, it's probably like a new patch
of grass is probably like a five to $700 expense for that space.
Maybe not even that much.
You might be able to just buy some, buy some roles of the whole thing.
Well, Matt has kids now.
His kids are going to do sure.
They can open up a, a weird hole in the wall factory magic place.
They can, they can, they can roll out the grass.
But yeah, I just call the company.
It was funny because when we got that installed right before the pandemic, right.
And it was like, foolish was where we're right in the middle of foolish.
Right.
And I bought a basketball net, a recliner and those fake grass.
And then all of a sudden we're like, oh wait, we don't have jobs anymore.
And I was like, wait, I can't afford to hit this stuff.
We tried to cancel all of it.
And for the grass company, they're like, well, we already cut the thing.
We just haven't installed it.
So the only thing you save on is labor.
Like you're still going to get charged for the creating of the entire thing.
Right.
Yeah.
So you just had to go for it.
You know, the sand was piled up, uh, not, not, not put down with bags of sand.
And I just was like, yeah, we just have to eat it.
We have to be even more, we're just doing it now, but we have to finish it out.
Yeah.
We have already done this now.
It's, it's past tense.
Might as well keep going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
We did that with the, uh, with our windows.
We bought new windows for the whole house.
10 scoops is just put a garbage can over it.
Oh, terrible idea.
Or just put a fire pit over it.
Make that the fire pits.
Well, I will make this suggestion, Matt.
Yeah.
I was asking you guys if you ever wanted anything in your backyard, because
I want something in my backyard very much.
I've always wanted, and I keep.
Oh, before Paul says that, I'll tell you out of the Twitch chat that, uh, uh, fifth,
fifth, Leah, maybe, uh, suggesting you just put a gazebo over it.
There you go.
So you have your nice little bird to spot.
Gazebo, not a traditional gazebo.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I think we're past traditional gazebo at this point.
An 18 inch hexagon with lattice work in a roof.
And then you can be like, look, we put a stage in too.
It would look like an 1800s phone booth.
You could put it in a phone booth.
You could just set a phone booth right there at your side yard.
Canadian scoop.
Crystal suggested a wishing well.
That's not a bad idea.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Which reminds me of that hilarious Mr.
Show sketch about the wishing well, which is if you haven't seen it, scams and flams.
Uh, no, I have always wanted, I keep giving Anne the guff.
I want a Chinese bridge in our backyard.
The kind that has a really big arc, you know?
Okay.
Yeah.
That's what I want.
And she's always given me guff.
Sorry, Colton, Colton, Samurai either either went through AI or their do
sell children's gazebos, but it just put a photo up of a mini children's
gazebo that's very funny looking.
Oh, it's a sandbox, a gazebo sandbox.
Yeah.
That is what you would call not your traditional gazebo.
And Jay's box was my wrestling name.
I would say, uh, Matt, if you didn't have cats, that might be a good idea, but
that's going to just become a big old poo poo hole.
We used to have said in our backyard and we had to get rid of it because
it did become a cat poo poo hole.
Yep.
That's the cats like to poop in sand.
It turns out.
Oh, where would you put your bridge in your backyard?
Well, so again, like it opens up the Pandora's box of needing a water
feature kind of thing, which we don't have, and that would be a lot.
Not impossible.
How would this affect Anne's ranking in the Autobot society?
Would it probably take it up?
It would take it up a little notch because, uh, a bigger water
feature is something that she could add.
Honestly though, she's knocking it out of the park.
The only thing that they had against her was it wasn't quite big enough.
She needed 800 more square feet of habitat, which she could do if we
just trick out the front yard with bushes and shit.
You should trick out the front yard with troubled water.
And that way you can make a Chinese bridge over troubled water.
Like a Chinese bridge over troubled water.
Oh, that's so much better than what I was afraid.
I was afraid that he was going to do it in a Chinese accent and just do it in
bridge over troubled water in the Chinese accent.
I said dim sum.
Yeah.
I didn't do the Chinese accent.
I'm thrilled.
We've progressed as a, as a podcast, right?
I mean, we're growing.
I like you just put the bridge over a flower field.
That's exactly right.
That's flowers over there.
No, instead of water, donuts next to them, instead of water, you put flowers and
make the flowers look like a flowing water, uh, water thing, kind of.
Yeah.
So that's, thank you, Keeler.
That is exactly what we were considering.
And we still might at some point, uh, we'll see, but yeah, that's the,
that's my dream is to have a Chinese bridge.
And Anne's just like, we don't need a fucking Chinese bridge.
But I'm like, I want one.
Is she okay with other nationalities of bridge?
Oddly, oddly, she got really angry when I suggested a Spanish bridge.
Like she got mad.
I have always suspected that Anne is racist towards the people of Spain.
What is going on?
Uh, no, no, not at all.
Uh, who knows, um, you know, she's got some cool water features.
She's got some really nice little fountains and stuff.
We might do a bigger one.
We'll see.
All right.
Well, good luck with your Spanish tile Chinese bridge over, over
Veroma's waters of her troubled flowers.
Like a bridge over troubled flowers.
Let's do a little jock versus nerd.
And he's right.
Your wife is a Bridges.
It's simply a bridge too far for her.
Oh, hey, I have a revelation that came straight from Anne that you and
the scoops may be interested in a revelation to Paul.
She listens to the podcast religiously.
She listens to every episode.
She just informed me that sometimes she has to fast forward my
commercials if they're gross jokes.
Sometimes she has to fast forward it cause it makes her gross out.
So checks out.
Well, you couldn't, you couldn't pay my wife to listen to the show.
So still, no, I know.
I mean, I, I, I'm so, I, I thanked her again.
I was, I, I, I don't mind.
I get it.
As they say, you know who you married and you know, the jokes, the kind
of jokes and the sense of humor.
She's like, I know, but sometimes you get really gross on those, those
commercials and I just have to fast forward a little bit and I'm like, okay.
Every now and then my wife will listen to the show.
It is, it is rare.
I mean, it's, she's in the same boat as Matt's wife.
And, uh, and I mean, when she does, it is so surprising to me.
Every time it just shocks me.
She showed up to scoop fest last year in a, in a costume.
It was like, what?
How did you do this?
Oh my gosh.
Yeah.
And he's right.
Think of the sponsors.
What about the sponsors?
Paul, think about them.
Do they happy with their gross portrayal?
Of course they are.
They paid for the gross stuff.
They pay for that foul stuff.
That's what they come.
We got a scooper to come in as the day from silver fist scoop.
The categories are Oprah Chopra, Oprah, Ikea, Crimea, gonorrhea,
Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, or which Prince.
All right.
It's me first.
I'll try which Prince for 400.
Fascinating topics.
This man was born in 1958.
Is it Prince Andrew Prince William or Prince?
Huh?
Okay.
So I think Prince Williams out Prince Williams.
One of the, like the princes now, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
So he's right.
He's right out.
Prince Andrew.
I think 58 is too young to be Prince Andrew.
I'm going to just say Prince.
I think the purple one.
It is Prince.
Good job.
Did my math out loud and everything, Matt.
Well, he died right at 50, right?
It was something.
It was right around there.
Yeah.
Oh, you die in '09.
I'll do which Prince please.
Which Prince for 800 made an honorary fellow of the society of light and
lighting in 2016, Prince Andrew Prince William or Prince.
I'll go with Prince William.
Okay.
It's Prince Andrew.
Really?
They're still giving that guy awards in 2016, huh?
I don't know what the society of light and lighting is.
So, uh, who knows it's give him awards or give him children.
One or the other.
He, you know, you gotta, you gotta pick your poison there.
I think he accepted from Epstein Island.
I will go with, uh, Ikea, Crimea, gonorrhea for 400.
You can find, uh, cor, cornea here.
Is it Ikea, Crimea or gonorrhea?
I'll go with Crimea.
I mean, that's, it seems like a proper noun.
It is.
Oh, it's the cornea river.
Cry me a river.
That's me.
I'll try, um, let's try Jupiter, Saturn or Uranus for 400.
You would.
This is the fifth planet from the sun.
Jupiter, Saturn or Uranus.
Jupiter.
Yes.
I had to count on my fingers.
Jupiter.
Matt.
Uh, I'll take, uh, Ikea, Crimea, gonorrhea, please.
Daily double.
All of it, Jacob.
All of my negative one, negative 800 points.
This was featured in a song by little Wayne and Drake in 2010.
Is it Ikea, Crimea or gonorrhea?
I really hope it's Crimea.
Honestly.
I really hope that little Wayne and Drake did a song about Crimea.
I don't even, I, let's see.
Um, my guess was gonorrhea.
Um, all right.
I'll go Crimea.
Oh, it's gonorrhea, gonorrhea, cha cha cha, gonorrhea, cha cha cha.
A Prince died at 57.
Thank you.
Ted scoop for that information.
I thought it was just 50.
That was MJ the data 50.
Uh, so he died in 17.
Right.
Or 19 or whatever.
16, 16, I think.
Okay.
Or 15 anyway.
Uh, but, but, but, but, but I'll do Ikea, Crimea, gonorrhea.
All right.
Again, you can find Clippin here.
K I K L I P P A N is that Ikea, Crimea or gonorrhea?
I'm going to go with Ikea.
Yeah.
Let's try Ikea.
It's a sofa.
Ah, Clippin our vice president's favorite item at Ikea.
I'll close that Ikea for 2000 sold the Russia based mega family shopping center
chain to Gazprom bank in 2023.
Is it Ikea, Crimea or gonorrhea?
All right.
I'm just going to do the math here.
Did gonorrhea sell the Russian based mega family shopping center chain in 2023.
You don't know gonorrhea is life.
I don't.
All right.
I'm going to say that it's not gonorrhea.
Uh, I don't know enough about the political socioeconomic structure of
Crimea to be really sure about this.
Does the country of Crimea own things like, like a shopping center
chain that they can then just turn around and sell, or is this a
subsidiary of a subsidiary of Ikea?
Yeah.
I'm going to say Crimea.
All right.
Shit.
It's Ikea.
Scuba.
Flip the coin.
Got it wrong.
Matt.
You, I just, cause I was the only one who got anything wrong.
And I was really get my butt kicked.
Um, let's see here.
I have 1600.
Uh, let's see.
I'll go with negative 1600.
I go with Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus for 2000.
All right.
In mythology, this God was both the son and the husband kinky of Gaia.
Is it Jupiter, Saturn or Uranus?
Oh, I don't think it was Uranus.
You don't think so?
Wait, now that I, now that I pronounce it the right way, it might be that.
Jupiter is a, Jupiter is the God I know reference a lot in Shakespeare and stuff.
Okay.
Saturn.
Jupiter is the Roman counterpart of Zeus.
Yeah.
Jupiter, of course, famously where girls go to get more stupider.
Um, right.
And Saturn sets the pattern.
Yeah.
Uh, my gut was going Uranus is inflamed.
I'm going to go with Jupiter.
Okay.
Let's see.
It is often it's Uranus.
Oh, it was always Uranus, Matt.
Paul, you put Uranus on the line.
Uh, I'll try Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus for 800.
Boy, we're all steering away from the Oprah category.
This planet has the second largest moon Titan in the solar system.
Is that Jupiter, Saturn or Uranus?
Uh,
this plan, I think that's Saturn moon Titan.
You think it's Saturn.
It is Saturn.
All right.
To me, I'll close out Uranus for 1200.
This God was the parent of Pluto.
Is that Jupiter, Saturn or Uranus?
Uh, let's see.
Pluto is Hades, right?
I thought Hades and Zeus were brothers.
Well, if that I thought hasten Jupiter, but I also, but isn't because Poseidon
is Saturn and Zeus and Jupiter Poseidon.
We're also brothers and Jupiter is Zeus, right?
And Jupiter is Zeus.
So I think I guess it's Uranus.
I'll say Uranus.
That's Jupiter.
Oh, man.
I don't fuck it.
Paul, Paul's running away with us and not in the usual way, not because we loaded up
on nerd questions and he's crushing it, but, uh, Jacob and I have buried
ourselves in this one.
Yeah.
Uh, Matt, you're up.
Fucking, uh, Oprah, excuse me.
I'm cursing for my kids.
That's how you know how much I'm enjoying this right now.
Let's do which Prince for 2000.
Which all right.
Has a BA in geography at the university of St.
Andrews is that Prince Andrew Prince William or Prince?
This is the first one where I've, I've sincerely felt like
it could be any of the three.
Yes, exactly.
It could be.
I mean, uh, St.
Andrews, of course, in Ireland.
I'll go with, uh, Prince William.
Good guess.
All right.
It's Prince William.
I'll try some Oprah Cobra Oprah.
All right.
This person was born in January, 1954.
Is it Oprah Winfrey deep pop Chopra or, or, uh, Oprah or an
Oprah Oprah born in 54, probably.
I don't know for sure though.
I'll pass.
Uh, let's see that passes to, uh, me.
Oh shit.
Uh, I have no idea, but I have to guess anyway.
I will say that that was, uh, Deepa Deepak Chopra.
It's Oprah.
It was Oprah.
Now I'm just getting more buried.
It's me.
I'll, uh, which Prince 1200 daily double.
Good.
That's what I need to get me in less negative points.
What I was quoted as saying the internet is completely over in 2010.
Was that Prince Andrew Prince William or Prince?
Oh, again, this two of these is very possible.
Yeah.
I'd be really surprised if it was Prince William.
Uh, boy, I kind of think it was Prince.
I'm going Prince.
Yeah.
It was Prince.
Uh, Matt, you got, uh, Oprah for eight, 12 or 2000.
The only way I can get into positive points is 2000.
Yes, that is true.
Okay.
All right.
Don't blow it.
This person launched Virgin comics in 2006 with Richard, with Richard Branson.
Is it Oprah Winfrey Deepak Chopra or an Oprah?
These all feel like the wrong answer, right?
I don't see a comp, a comics company.
I don't see Oprah doing that, but I certainly don't see deep.
Oh wait, Deepak Chopra comics might make sense.
Cause it's like a deep thing.
Uh, I'll go with, I'll go with Deepak Chopra.
Okay.
It is.
Yeah.
All right, Matt, listen to his son and didn't screw it up.
We got 800 or 1200 either way.
Paul's going to win.
Good.
Uh, I'll try the 1200 then.
Why not?
This person was sued for copyright infringement for a book they wrote in
1993.
Is that Oprah Deepak or an OPA?
Uh, who's an OPA?
I, you know, everything that I do.
I'll pass.
I don't know.
Uh, it's me.
I'll say, um, Deepak.
Yeah.
Sue him.
Get him lost.
Get him.
And I'm closing out the category and the game.
If I get this correct, I will be tied for second place with
Matt Donnelly.
This is a deeply kneeled, laterally compressed, discoid fish.
Deeply keeled, laterally compressed, discoid fish.
Stay down Oprah.
Is that Oprah Winfrey, Deepak Chopra or an OPA?
I love that.
That's just a straight up answer.
That's just great.
I'm going to, I'm going to say D, your mom.
Oh boy.
I believe that'd be an OPA.
It is an OPA and that is the game.
Paul wins with 2,400.
Matt and I are tied at 400 a piece.
And that's from silver fist scoop.
Thank you.
Silver fist scoop.
If you want to send us a scooperty or a price of Skryte jock versus nerd or an
obelisk jock versus nerd, head over to HeyScoops.com.
That's where you can go.
HeyScoops.com right there on the homepage.
Make us one of those jock versus nerds.
Send us some scoop mail, buy your tickets to scoop fest.
Do all the things right over there at HeyScoops.com.
I believe for scoop fest, we are now officially sold out of
the Jacobs whiskey barbecue.
Okay.
However, now with gazebo now with more gazebo.
However, I don't think we're going to have as many of our guests, uh, coming
to the barbecue this year, as we've had in years, I just don't think we have as
many guests, uh, that are going to be in town for it.
So, uh, if you are wanting to come to the whiskey barbecue as part of scoop
fest, hit me up, uh, hit any of it's up, honestly, uh, but yeah, we'll, we'll
figure out a way for you to come.
Uh, because I think that we can make it work.
So, uh, from, from here on out, uh, it's just a catch a sketch can on the whiskey
barbecue, but we can definitely squeeze some more people in limited exclusive
tickets still available through directly.
That's it.
Just, just hit us up and we'll, uh, we'll figure it out.
We'll get you on the list.
Tickets are still available either three day or two day passes, depending
on your budget, uh, for the regular scoop fest, go to scoopfest.com.
We are at that point where we can basically, we think we will be able to
accommodate everyone, uh, with the scoop fest bags because of sizes and stuff.
At this point, we can't guarantee your size, um, for the, that we're selling.
We'll have stuff, but, uh, you know, at this point, if you buy a ticket, we will,
we will do our best to accommodate sizes.
I can tell you right now, you're going to be so happy with the mystery item.
You won't care.
I'm going to tell you right now.
Oh, it's so great.
It's so good people.
I'm going to tell you right now, the first photos that are coming out
of the scoop fest, you're going to laugh.
All right.
Uh, really fun surprises on the way for that surprises galore.
In fact, get it over to scoopfest.com buyer tickets.
Now you can also get, call up the Orleans and get on that room discount block.
It's a sweet discount, man.
It is.
It's always, they always give us a fantastic discount.
S C F I two, three C two, five, two, five C.
Uh, there we go.
Um, check that out.
S C F I two, five C.
Let's get them on the phone and big scoop fest.
God damn it.
Okay.
Uh, thanks so much.
It's the beginning of the month.
So we don't have thank yous for it, but this podcast is possible because people
support us over on our patron and we really appreciate it.
So if you have it, uh, within your hearts and your budget for both a monthly or
yearly support, um, we really appreciate it each and every time.
So head on over to preaching fun.com.
Or if you have ever burned a hole in your fake grass that your
wife was super happy about, head on over to farts in a bag dot biz.
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun.com.
I take you to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you
can help keep this show on the air.
Head on over there, preaching fun.com farts in a bag dot biz.
If you think this show is worth more than $0, hit us up over there
right now, we can always use your support.
And, uh, right now we, we really could, uh, Matt son has just taken
his credit card and is signing up.
We got a really big, uh, Patriots bump right here.
Uh, this last donation came in all in Roblox bucks.
We'll take it.
Um, so the people have been love, uh, been so lovely to join us on our zoom.
If you have a minute to go over to the bucket show.com, if you get a free Amazon,
if you're an Amazon member, there's a free subscription button there.
Uh, and if you can give us the Amazon subscription that, that gives us a few
dollars, uh, that are at, not out of Amazon's pocket, not yours.
Um, so it's a huge help to us.
So if you take a second, just go over to the bucket show.com and check that out.
Um, and, uh, for everyone else, you know, uh, if you want to help us out without
money, but you want to help out our show, participate in our obelisk scheme,
choose one person and one person only, you think they might, might like our
podcast and turn them onto an episode today.
No, that's a really, really helpful.
Don't try to get five people do it and get those five people to do it.
That's a pyramid scheme.
That's a pyramid.
False promises.
Please just choose one person and one person only.
There is a very small pyramid on top of the obelisk.
We don't mention that we don't even talk about it.
Weird.
It's really even brought up now.
All right.
Uh, thanks for everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Oh, I recently guested on a podcast called creators cafe out of Los Angeles.
It's a podcast where the, uh, host Jessica Payne talks to different
creative people and, uh, and show business all over the place.
Really fun.
And, uh, I had a nice long conversation with Jessica over there.
Go check it out.
Creators cafe anywhere you have your fine podcasts on YouTube too.
We are preaching fun.
[BLANK_AUDIO]