oh hello there I'm so happy you're here this is the part of the show where we
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers I don't have a new list yet we might get one before this one goes out I
don't know so you may or may not hear this part of the show that I'm saying
right now you might hear names instead but in case you don't how you doing you
look right we are recording a couple days earlier it's true if you would like
to be an ice cream truck driver deliver that fucking ice cream shake everybody's
fucking ear holes head over to preaching fun calm preaching fun commas we're gonna
sign up to be a nice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save maybe
your own or it may be a program hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream
social yeah I'd love to great let's go
hazel honeysuckle in the house today
boldly straight.com is the website if you like movies and Star Trek go check it
out I like two of those it's not my first time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream
social sitting in Las Vegas that's Matt Notley sitting in Pittsburgh that's Paul
Mattingly I'm Jacob sitting in Las Vegas for preaching fun mm-hmm I do like two of those
three things I like Star Trek and the left one the left one only yeah this is
another great reason for patrons to get on the ball and put in that couple bucks
a month to join us on these live podcasts and zooms hazel is in full Trek
regalia you can that's right her in her I mean it's dangerous she's in a red
she's a red shirt but yes yes she might not last the whole podcast but she is
and she's sitting in front of the Sun on her video so I mean it's it could
happen any moment yeah yeah yeah yeah does any have any Star Trek characters
ever died by just being thrown into the Sun that's got to have happened in
Star Trek I'm sure oh that's a good point Paul you're telling just a star
plenty of people followed into stars I think but I don't know about our son yeah
oh I mean stars are other people's sons that's right let's not
disparage other people's sons people well the Sun of Vulcan one of Vulcan
Sun's exploded and Osmos the whole sure sure that was son of Vulcan Sun exploded
and the osmosis and the whatnot then we used the Sun our earth Sun's
gravitational forces to go back in time and save the whales using a Klingon bird
of prey so sure for now we should we should hashtag for now I don't think it
took I don't think it took I mean last like proper Star Trek invention you
attended oh god as an actual I don't I mean the last time was two years ago at
Rio when I was doing Fool Us and happened to be there at the same time I
didn't really get to go to the con proper though I got to just see people
walking around and well when was the last time you like went out of your way
and I'm gonna go to this Star Trek convention got yourself a ticket did the
whole nine and I have never I have never gotten a ticket for a Star Trek
convention that you never entered through the Stargate or wherever they
walked through to go I have never gone through as a civilian I've always been
there for work all right okay all right then what was last time you worked
convention when they still had them at the Hilton so it's been a minute it'd
been a minute it's been it's been probably a good solid 15 years since
I've been the Hilton at a very long time none of them have closed they're just on
hiatus right how long until the Star Trek experience comes back I have no
idea I have no idea well first turn back into the Hilton well here's the thing
hazel is on the ground floor out there she is amongst the peoples what scuttle
but have you heard about people trying to bring back the experience scuttle them
butts hazel I mean there's a whole chapter new book just about scuttling
butts the butts the butts are saying oh so much to do that oh I should bring
about it would be great they don't they don't understand is anyone saying oh I
should do that is anyone say oh I with the money that I currently have should
do that oh that's a shame here I am just stuffing them in my ears and wiping my
ass with them why don't I put them towards Star Trek it'll make the same
amount of what I tell you a bunch of people though were like hey you know
that you know that Empire strips back show you should do that you should do
one of those for Star Trek oh right that's that's that's it and and how's
that going well I think we're gonna need another Kickstarter for that one right
but I use the Empire back seems to be going well right I think so yeah yeah
it's a great show it is a great show I got to see that here in Pittsburgh oh
yeah yeah nice it seems to punch above its weight class it seems to deliver
more than what you're expecting mm-hmm oh I would agree with that yeah first
scene they come out strong in that in the first scene of that show they come
out just swinging they're real good yeah Jeff Loomis is saying that Empire
strips back touring show was close to a sellout for an entire month in Seattle
oh wow so that's you go on the ground reporting ticket sales we love it we
love it well and it's and it's it's doing decent business in Vegas it's got
it's found itself a residency of sorts right oh I hope they did well during the
Star Trek telling me right now I'm gonna put him on speaker oh jeez oh boy the
chaos yeah it seems like a lot of people were going to see that show well hi
Brian you're in yeah going beautiful this is the sound brian makes when he
was want to talk personal stuff himself in that situation where he's extroverted
with his friends where he gets to say no that's it you've reached a limit I mean
by virtue of her Asian race yes
there he goes there he goes big tribal chief Brian brushwood everybody I got to
take the moral stand there Andrew Eaton everyone Andrew that was heating that
was heating for sure mm-hmm so there is crossover than hazel between the Trek
and the Wars oh yeah yeah of course of course of course I mean I drive a
stormtrooper car and I was a Klingon so it's all good yeah right but that that
that hurts the idea of doing a Star Trek version of Empire Strips back you think
yeah well cuz it's already done you think it's cannibalizing its own
audience you're not gonna fly out to Vegas twice to see two different
burlesque shows I know I think there is a slight possibility that you could man
I really like your logic there you make the same person you could make the Trek
one way more tech forward I don't know I don't know you know what the key would
be I'm gonna shark tank here I'm out I'm out here's what was that is that a foot
that was coming in what in the hell was that what is that why I wanted to turn
off my background why was that is that a Horta oh it's a dick rock oh it's a big
old dick rock it's not a Horta all right but it might as well be say Horta one
more time ball Horta Horta got that you know the way to do it this here's the
successful thing they just closed Muppets 3d we almost had it with borg 4d at the
experience but what they didn't do they had stuff that would move your butt in
the seat they had water that would squirt in your face but they didn't have
things that would attach to your junk so if you get into a theater and you get
borgified in the crotch uh-huh and the show literally fucks you while you're
watching burlesque preach then you are going to go see that show a couple times
probably we got to go back because you slept through the second half for the
first time you gotta go back twice there's no intermission was just a
refractory period the smartest person handling the Star Trek IP is hazel
honeysuckle that's right the person doing the smartest thing is combining her
superpowers as a nerd and burlesque artist it's true hazel what's your
website it's boldly stripped calm boldly stripped calm and what will people find
when they go to boldly stripped calm oh people will find a very excellent
Kickstarter campaign where I'm where we are raising funds to create the second
version of boldly stripped I've noticed only stripped to a bit of electric
bugaloo a simplifying a bit of paring down of the options that was offered a
boldly stripped one like lessons were learned I think so I think so is that
when we can get the button put on it upside down or or to the left or to the
right depending on which box you click for delivery purposes like with all
kickstarters it's full of all kinds of options so that you try to keep some you
must have understood one it was the first one was so much more successful
than you imagined it was going to be why did you just go right away what took
you so long to come around to think about doing version 2 I had to wait long
enough until I forgot how much work it was that's a real thing yeah that's it
that makes a lot of sense so now you just launched you've already achieved
your your goal and your stretch goal yeah we made we've done three stretch
goals so far and you've nailed them all and nailed them all and you're gonna add
more stretch goals or you're done with stretch goals never done with stretch
goals yet because one should be a Star Trek convention watching Paul sit
through a show in his own taint tickling chairs one should be that should be one
stretch I want to know exactly what he wants attached to his joke during the
show no no you sort of device you think you want to know that but you don't I
thought I wanted to know that one time I found out I didn't want to know let's
just say the question implies that he's picky and he's not I'm imagining I'm
imagining a Borg's head comes up out of the chair in front of you and you just
take that Borg's head are you supposed to imagine the Borg says attached to a
sexy body on your own or are you supposed to be picturing skull fucking a
Borg that's what I'm the Borg's head yeah the Borg's head will be all on us a
skeletal spindle like the Queen like the you know is gesturing how the head would
go towards him and hazel yes it'll come out on a hanging spine and then and then
you pick the orifice this is the thing so either you can go choose your own
adventure you can go for an eye socket because it's a Borg yeah or you know if
you want to get wild you can go for just a straight-up mouth or you can have it
add on like it's got like a tongue attachment or something for the lady I'm
going for the ear because I wanted to hear I want to hear me coming okay yeah
you can go for the ear or it could be a or it could be a Borg's butt with the
words ass simulate on it that could be kind of cute as simulate that's what it
is Borg for board 5d plus ass simulation that's it simulation we got there
everybody who we've arrived who's gonna work there that's what I want to know
who wants to clean up after the audience and they all your remnants is mopper
resistance is futile and your remnants are pure aisle that's how it's going
space just mopper space just mopper someone's got to do it it can't be any
worse than the shit that was going down during chicken jockey during the
Minecraft movie so upset about us disparaging you're right fuck plastic
sci-fi things in an open theater that you're taking random shots of the
Minecraft movie look this is just the next step in the popcorn buckets tell me
I'm wrong I'm wrong that's just one more month until a popcorn bucket fucks you
they already sold a big old Galactus head and he had big old ears you could
hold on exactly the dune worm no the dune worm was just a fit that was the
shot across the bow and people did not answer the call and I'm disappointed
but was just a pocket pussy but it was also one of those like unattainable goals
I mean that was it that was like a eight-inch mall you'd have to be the
girthiest tuna can motherfucker to even experience standard for everyone does
everyone not have that kind of girl there it is see now that that's the
popcorn bucket right there this is how I will always picture hazel oh where do you
think the butter goes that's a butter reservoir for the popcorn you need a
little butter refresher just give it a squeeze just dunk it yeah Hazel how many
characters did you play in volume one we did 14 different photo shoots okay so it
was 14 is it how many hard to come up with 14 more or is it easy in the
Star Trek universe have 14 more different characters um I haven't
decided on all of them yet because yeah you know we got we've got all of the
most obvious ones in the first book yeah you can revisit them right because
people do multiple oh yeah yeah I might might redo some of them you know
different situations or or eras who was your most popular what was your most
popular creature from volume one oh yeah what most popular species oh the green
one the Orion woman okay that's the one that everybody likes by far um when you
sell those I mean you sell these at the conventions and stuff yeah yes yes a
galaxy con and do you start right do they just start thumbing through it right
in front of you right there at the table did they just start going through them
all well I asked people to I say look at the book then they're like oh wow look
at all these girls and I say that's me and they're like that's you yes so way
the way the opposite of what I thought where I thought it was going that's
really funny Matt thought it was gonna be awkward but in the other direction
yes no plenty of people make it awkward too what's the most awkward somebody's
made it um gosh I don't know what do they touch the picture in front of you
do they put their finger on like a body part I like some sometimes people pick
up the book and look at every single page and then just put it down and walk
away data committed to spank bank mission recently I was at magic live and
Mike gave me was selling these really awesome books what was the history of
song a woman in half and the other was just kind of like a history of magic but
I knew they were like $200 books so I didn't even pretend to thumb through it
I just I was I dared to read the back of one of them and then I was like I'm
gonna stop touching these books all together because I'm not spending but
yeah so but that guy had no problem that guy just thumbed right through it left
his oily residue on every page yeah this is why I have you know the table book
which has been thumbed through many times have you considered going kind of
a pat the bunny route where like you have a patch of some kind of real
tactile stuff in the middle of the book that continues throughout that you know
I don't know what it could be Star Trek wise could be like a moon rock kind of
thing or something I don't know I don't know I thought for sure you're going
barking like a silicone that could be that could be yeah I'll just keep
moving towards fuckable objects today that's really not fuckable I mean oh come
what the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by the fine makers of
this following product have you heard of the product not yet oh a new film by
Gwyneth Paltrow the gloops the gloops that's from the microscope in 2025 the
groups I'm Gwyneth Paltrow I used to be married to Coldplay now I make movies
again because I got left behind from that guy in jail now I'm doing what I
want to do with my life instead of making Oscar bait I'm making a movie
called the gloops what's the gloops you might ask well it's that passion project
about my website called goop right that's my website goop but the gloops is
the poops you get when you're living the gloop lifestyle if your poops are gloops
then you are gooped up you get it that's how it works me Gwyneth Paltrow teaching
you what to put in and out of your body that's how it works don't let others
fool you this is my real voice not manipulated anymore by the Weinstein
company then what I really sound like I'm basically a walking talking Grover
lady but that's me Gwyneth Paltrow go see my new movie gloops in theaters only in
theaters equipped with Borg 5d fuckable technology and her a scoops to check out
yeah yeah okay I think I heard you all like skincare products are you all like
some what some gloop I got it Oh Lord she's an alien Oh Lordy Oh Gwyneth Oh
speaking of a little guy of aliens speaking of aliens guys they're aliens
two nights ago I wake up to go to work I'm up at almost 3 a.m. I'm letting my
dogs out and straight out my back door up in the sky I'm seeing UFOs now I say
UFO because to me they were UFOs they were unidentified unidentifiable they
were flying it was a straight line of about five just dots of light okay and
then occasionally lights were blinking in to the left and right of the column
and zipping in towards the column then disappearing blink in zipping toward the
column disappear and then the column was going up and then disappearing and then
another one would start at the bottom and disappearing strange were you
watching an elevator no okay but here's the fucked up thing I would say that
modern life has accomplished its goal I didn't have time to just stay in there
and keep watching this shit I had to go to work so like I'm broken I can no
longer three rocks off the ground shove one in your butt fuck the other two went
to work I can no longer stand there he raptured at the majesty of the mysteries
of space I have to go I can work so I'm just I feel like we're just broken it's
over like I don't even know what that shit was I can't I don't know but I can
even have time to watch it all the way I'm out of here this is just thanks
whatever you are just so frustrating thanks that's fine I hope you're from
space yeah I'm going to work now did you think to get your phone and film it no I
did not I did not I should have but I didn't in the moment which is weird seems
unlike you I know again think that he's just over it I mean do you think he's
just like yeah yeah they're aliens yeah that's kind of where I'm at like it's of
course there's some weird shit going on who knows what it is but if aliens showed
up tomorrow would you react with with surprise joy or just kind of kind of a
board like of course you're here I'd be like hmm I'd be surprised yes I'd be
surprised and I'd be like wait we didn't get ready hold on we gotta fix open up
open up a flap and get some of this heat out of here what somebody open a flap
wait we're not ready but open a flap if I saw we didn't clean up the alien land
in front of me I'd be like oh man this is gonna be the worst Paul is right
email I've ever gotten so terrible so your first concern hazel is a tidy house
when aliens come you know like like the like the Federation they always they
always wait till like the society is ready they have to achieve warp
capability they have to achieve more capability yeah yeah but they can't join
the Federation until they've like got their shit together right you know which
blows my fucking mind that the earth was ever even let in like even if you look
at the if you look at first contact and you're like wait a minute they came to
earth they saw that from Cochran go warp and then they went oh yeah this planet
just recently got decimated by full-scale nuclear assault I think
they're good to go come on join us guys but then they got their shit together
for like you know I don't know 50 years or something oh boy oh boy we were we
should never have been allowed in the UFP it's all there is to it that's it
preach yeah you know me preach if I was on a walk and the aliens landed it would
be so sad as I'd be concerned about my family and then I would like awkwardly
not be able to run full speed back to my house like I'd have to like jog for a
minute and like keep walking fast then like jog for another minute and the
aliens would just be standing behind you with their arms crossed just looking at
you in judgment like don't get me wrong I'm one of them making fun of Tom Cruise
running in movies right like oh there he goes ha ha ha meanwhile I can't do it I
couldn't even do a Tom Cruise movie if you paid me it'd be really tough no it's
to be fair though I would I'd love to give it a shot so if anybody would like
to pay me Tom Cruise is going great to make a movie I will happily attempt to
make that movie absent of money I'm just doing the Tom Cruise fitness challenge
and that's where I will try to become a better runner and also strap my thing
strap myself onto various dangerous objects and see if I can pull off a
classy stunt at my age so that's those are the two things I thought you were
gonna say strap myself to various objects and fuck them like Canada RMS
Nicole Kidman shot myself to those objects meanwhile the Penelope Cruz
longing for a nice piece of cod the whole time you know what I could really
go for right now some cod did this isn't that possible come out or it hasn't
come out yet and nobody cares that's right yeah yeah nobody cares anymore
nobody gives a rat fuck that first the first one the first one that he had the
audacity of that last one to be like oh it's a two-parter and it's also 18 hours
long like eat my butt sir no one has time for your garbage bullshit but the
other but the bad guys might get an AI thing Paul you're not totally wrapped up
in that that apparently was the whole thing like the the the MacGuffin they
were having like all these discussions about what's the MacGuffin what's the
MacGuffin and Tom Chris finally like just nuclear bombs just make it nuclear
bombs and that's what they did it's like bad guys have nukes good guys need to
stop them done this is so dumb I don't think it was I thought it was like an AI
thing like a computer that could that could control nuclear bombs oh got it
okay oh that's what sunk that submarine that submarines full of nuclear bombs
that's the whole beginning of the movie which is all I watched how many mission
impossible movies has Tom Cruise made everybody no price is right rules just
how many how many hazel's hazel's correct she just yawned while you asked
that yeah yeah that's correct that's the right answer that's exactly it it's
boring cuz it's cuz nothing's gonna happen the answer is fine the answer is
eight and I had no idea you know just three you know what I think um Fast and
Furious was benefited from the tragic passing of Paul Walker in so much as
something could actually happen to a main character but I guess in the in the
fictional world he's not really dead is that right are they gonna AI him back
into the new movie is that what I'm hearing now Wow wait Paul what's his
name Walker Paul Walker they're gonna AI Paul Walker into a Fast and Furious
movie I think so let's see here the new one seems like a mistake I think you're
right Matt I think it's a terrible mistake and a terrible precedent to set
to bring back dead people into movies yeah but if it goes I'm totally making
Ben Hur two and I'm bringing everyone back Ben Hur two remember they did a
Ben Hur remake today like who the fuck had a ball it was it was remarkably bad
right but who even has the balls to even go you know what we should make again
Ben Hur yeah what epic the fuck could you even add to that oh my god I love
remaking things they do the upcoming the upcoming Fast and Furious movie the
upcoming final Fast and Furious movie rumored to be titled fast 11 fine Jesus
Christ set for release in April of 27 is planning to feature Paul Walker's
character Brian O'Connor will likely use CGI and potentially AI to recreate his
likeness Oh not his corpse then I gotta string him up like a fucking puppet
they're not gonna weaken it Bernie's them glad I'm glad they told us how I'm back
family did you miss me that's all about family not some child he didn't know he
had dressing up like him and trying to look like him in the movie because it's
been that long it has been that long his his kids are alive I think he really is
like supposed to be like on vacation kind of thing in the storyline he's on
hiatus I don't know or maybe he's dead in the story and then they're gonna
bring it back but everybody dies in that thing now too and they bring him back
same thing with what's your head hey whatever Paul he's family all right we
take care of family family never dies family never dies here's Paul fucking
Walker family never dies take a look you think I'm joking motherfucker look
family never dies this one literally never dies they could do a crossover
could call it Paul walking dead I've literally never been more interested in
the Fast and Furious franchise I bet Kirkman could get on board he's a
magician he could write some great shit for that he could make it work
get all those Atlanta tax credits they helped make it happen no the Paul
walking dead hazel any thoughts for putting video content as part of your
attached to your your your magazine with with animated Paul Walker driving you
around funny you say that because no except for the Paul Walker part yeah we
okay so one of the shoots we're gonna do is a Ferengi mm-hmm oh whichever you
know I know everyone was clamoring yes well the thing is tell tell everyone the
thing about the Ferengi ladies the thing about the Ferengi ladies and they're not
they're not a very you know progressive progressive civilization not at all but
their women their women all are just naked all the time
ah and they're not allowed to do business profit it which is like their
whole society is about earning profit right so the women are naked and they
can't work and like the kinkiest thing is for woman to wear clothes and this is
this is how they they got the the main characters like the main Ferengi
character to put it on would land them in jail is that what was that what
happened ah it's like oh the main character like goes home and his mom's
like wearing clothes and he's like oh gross gross mom and then she takes her
clothes off and he puts his head in her lap oh boy it's weird no what you said
sounds great yeah yeah now I gotta do the rest of this show like this so to do
a risque Ferengi female boudoir shoot as it were yeah you're gonna have to put
some stuff on she's gonna put it on yeah yeah it's gonna be the only clothes character
in the entire book I mean that could be funny to have it go in reverse to start
off really would go oh it's it's definitely going in reverse completely
starkers and then yeah full clothes by the end of it that's fun actually that
would be a really funny burlesque routine like a bad camp act you know
where you just keep putting on clothes and so you're like giant like a snowman
you know that guy wore all the t-shirts how many t-shirts did he get to didn't
hurt himself real bad doing that one guy who's famous for wearing t-shirts Paul
just asked three questions if none of us have any idea what he's talking about I
just remember this guy wearing so many t-shirts and it got really bad and I
don't I think it was I think it hurt him Jacob what are you even searching for
what did you type into the search bar I pulled up a search bar and have yet to
type anything very curious what words I don't know what did a guy hurt himself
here it is too many shirts to death calm here we go I don't think he died did a
guy hurt himself by putting on too many shirts let's see here Google is shrugging
at me Google has no idea I'm just picturing hazel wearing like a thousand
outfits so it looks like it looks like almost like Jabba the Hutt with a tiny
head out of a bunch of clothes and then a bunch of Ferengi dudes just like
totally on the ground just like wasted from the eroticism they've experienced
just just just yeah just lounge opium den like napping just throwing bars of
Latin America like like like you know those those machines that throw a bunch
of money yeah but they make it rain guns yeah yeah yeah which is like which are
like metal yeah go press latinum would bean somebody in the noggin it's like
a strip club in Canada man they make it hail loonies into is right in your hand
you got all the loonies going up there oh man I got another loony Brewers above
my eye yeah no your honor it's from a loony it's from a loony yeah yeah
galactic presidents worship star mcscoops a lot talking about ear rubbing
equals Ferengi grooming or gooning rather yes yeah it is it's a umox yeah
umox get this umox my buddy the so you're sitting down in the writers
meeting for one of the Star Trek's right and you know I had no no no I got the
world guys Ferengi right there a little backwards all right everyone's naked
everyone's like I'm listening like and then you know what everybody else is all
of this project Donnelly you're handling the Ferengi's by yourself go on and you
goon by tugging your ears I regret my decisions fuck film this yesterday get
to the lot this was a scooper Nova girls saying I'll explain the DS 9
documentary and there is a story that Armand Shimmerman tells because he was
one of the original Ferengi in deep space not or in the original or in next
generation right they were originally gonna be the new big bads they were
gonna be like the Klingons of next generation ah that was the start told us
about this before I think I have and and there was a there's a scene where
they're on this planet and they've got you know the Frank you have these
fucking laser whips and you know they're coming hard for the fed yeah man Marauder
Moe type yeah look out their energy whips yeah but they ended up being really
goofy that's it they they they use the sonic weapon against them and the
directors like oh yeah grab your heads and like writhe around in pain and Armand
was like you know if we do this we're gonna look stupid as fuck nobody's gonna
think nobody's gonna think that these guys are scary at all ever again and he
was dead right and they became these very clownish aliens from that point on
but they wanted they wanted to set them up as like the big bad alien species for
the for the whole series and no one bought it no no one's like those those
goofballs grabbing their big Dumbo ears and screaming no I don't give a shit
about it yeah laser it's energy whips energy whip I have myself an energy whip
sir I do declare if you wish to get more forceful let us adjourn to the next
parlor and we shall settle this like gentlemen with our energy whip sir
does been fits me my sonic gun this this ragamuffin has a laser whip do not
bring a sonic disruptor to a laser whip fights I hope you enjoy the tanky zip of
my energy whip and that was a make a sandwich of your innards that was of
course the episode that Tennessee Williams wrote for Star Trek Hazel
Leon Kasab just asked you about what was there a something in the first boldly
stripped what what is that and is it an axion a till axion that's how you say
that okay and is there a till axion in the second boldly stripped and what is
it not so far come on come on what's it till axion it's a Neelix it'd be a whole
cooking see it's a Neelix come on Jacob it's a deal moving on again this is that
this is what you you would lose your mind Jacob and Matt if you were ever in
these writers rooms because Neelix that's correct
Neelix was supposed to be the Voyager breakout character they're like
oh this whole thing this is gonna be such a great thing this Neelix character
and they fucked it up six ways to Sunday they had him dating a 12 year old it's
like nice no no no she was like yeah yeah yeah yeah it's awful I was trying
to make it sound a little more this looks like she Tara's ugly step-cousin oh
they nearly wait there was a female the problem is female till axion Ethan
Phillips they don't allow female till axions on the internet I bet you anything
Ethan Phillips is a chill guy from what I've seen of him he seems like a nice
dude the actor who portrayed Neelix that character is so fucking annoying and
stupid I don't think it's Ethan Phillips's fault I think he's great
exactly that's what I'm saying but he is like let's get this character and he's
kind of like oh he loves to like sell stuff to people and he's the cook yeah so
he's always cooking weird alien thing yeah let's make a hairy farting cheetah
clown that makes food no one likes let's do that let's put that in the chin hair
he's everything and then they bring this they bring this like hot girl onto the
show but they're like oh yeah her race only lives to like 10 so she's full
grown at like two years old and so she's dating the weird cheetah guy yeah I
think we know who a secret executive producer was on this
just a bevy a bevy of bad ideas Neelix or flocks who is better ask scooper nova
girl flocks by leaps and bounds leaps and Bayes awesome yeah HLO X spells
flocks huh yeah dr. flocks he can inflate his face he's all I care from a
planet of swingers yeah go on every every denobulant marriage is at least
like several different people they all have they all like have you know kids
with that one kids with this one his wife comes on to the ship at one point
it starts flirting with with the with the engineer and he's like really
uncomfortable and that's fun yeah I mean that's from enterprise just do it mm-hmm
chicken things separate commercial come on trip yeah let's just do it let's do
any other commercial hey you know who else is super turned on Star Trek talk
I don't know somebody probably is somewhere the following sponsor today
shows brought to you by half a glass of water from Pommy bastard scoop in 2021
today shows brought to you by half a glass of water hey there everybody it's
me Tim the otter I'm here to tell you about half a glass of water that up but
up up up if you're thirsty don't you wait make sure that you do hydrate have
a drink before it's too late have half a glass of water you know kids a lot of
the times we don't want to drink everything that's in our cup but we need
to get a little more h2o in the old body flow to make sure our days go smooth and
we're feeling ready to roll if your tongue is dry and you need a drip well
go on over to the sink don't slip and pour yourself half half a glass of water
drink it on down it's a big old gulp have some it's delicious and it's gonna
help you if you don't get enough h2o your cells can't repair themselves in
the proper way do you understand what I'm talking about that's the way to do
it hazel get yourself half a glass of water a day at least 8 to 12 ounces and
as much as you can after that and I think you're gonna find that after you
have that first half a glass you're gonna want to go back for the other half
that's right yeah so if you're tired worn down and you just can't go there
might be something you need to know a little bit of that h2o have half a glass
of water yeah make sure you keep drinking you motherfuckers wait hey
scoops to check out I think Jacob wrote the end got your attention doesn't it
ugly bags of mostly water says galactic president scooper star makes scoops a
lot wait I felt like Leon popped out for a second to say something and I missed
it what he say Leon were you talking to us or were you just talking we just did
sorry get the button in my pocket great he's got a button in his pocket are you
just happy to see it it could be the nukes get him Tom Cruise no oh Greg just
bought himself a ticket to scoop fest and you should too yeah Greg just got an
email from Greg saying that he bought himself a ticket to scoop fest scoop fest
dot-com head over there we're doing it in September hazel's gonna be there
she'll be selling books of boldly stripped I bet she'll do an act at some
point you know the whole thing the variety show again hazel yes great have
plans oh yeah very guys seriously our variety show when that shit hits you
leave they're like god damn I saw the best thing in Vegas and you really did
you've seen probably one of the best shows in Vegas after you've seen our
variety show mm-hmm if you combined all the ticket prices for all the people
that we pull favors from to get good Lord play our variety show it would be one
very expensive ticket it'd be incredibly expensive yeah yeah we're like a best of
Broadway thanks if that doesn't make you brawl race to the internet to buy your
ticket to scoop fest we're like the best of Broadway our state fair is a great
state fair all right well hazel so what what what what should you already are
you most looking forward to already from a book yeah yeah no just in general you
got some coming up just in life nothing what's what's an alien species that
you're really looking forward to uh to getting dressed up as okay so we're
gonna do a duo shoot with a friend of mine a model named Ashley diet and we're
gonna we're gonna cross streams and do a star wars oh snap see same audience told
you yeah yeah you're right we won't do the Star Trek show fine we're gonna do
we're gonna do the Twi Licks that have the tentacly things
yeah okay yeah I'm showing the zoom what Twi Licks are because I didn't know what
they were it was the the one that was the exotic dancer in Jabba's Palace yeah
yeah gotcha gotcha yeah yeah yeah you have two big floppy horns why are their
horns so floppy why are they such a floppy horned people they're they're not
horns they're they're called leku actually the leka zoom type and they're
bred that way because they've gotten more docile as they reproduce because
no one to keep the aggressive ones as pets so slowly but surely they've
gotten dangly they just got floopy they got drippy over time the same horns that
happen to basset hound ears no did I did I do the beholder and scoop fest yes yes
I did yeah was that last year or the last one we did right that was what you
did yeah that was the D&D thing yeah yeah yeah that was great I've been I've
watched Sandman I finished up Sandman on Netflix okay you watch the second
season I did I started to watch that that animated kind of wrap-up of the
final first season that they just put out uh-huh and I and I and I couldn't
even get through it I was too depressed I had to stop it was it I was like oh
where where where's the population at with Neil Gaiman are we allowed to say
we watch Sandman or like salmon are we not allowed to say we like the Sandman I
was Neil I mean he's he's problematic as hell at this point yeah he's been
accused of being a dirty bird that's right at home yeah yeah I mean and what
stinks I don't know I thought Netflix actually did a really good job of
creating the comic to the series I didn't watch the animated thing I just
watched the actual episodes smart this is because I had to nope out after I
watched the first five minutes I was like oh god I can't take this this is and I
basically was like breaking my heart true to the comic look at it go and I
think it's a fascinating world that was created that I really liked when I read
it because I was like yeah it doesn't really advance it doesn't like it's not
driven by like a plot plot more like you just keep exploring worlds and the rules
that go with the world's similar what we've been just doing here today and so
I thought like it was really neat compelling it's also great to watch
before going to bed because it's not it's not a compelling plot point with
cliffhangers so you can just watch one weird dreamy scene and go right to bed no
problem and then I was like I don't think I can talk terrified about
sleeping at all I've worried about whatever happens once I fall asleep can
be completely leveraged against me and generations of my family no problem and
oddly enough as you're watching it though the character dream which
obviously is influenced by Neil Gaiman himself and the whole fashion trend that
came out of that and it's all about guy regretting his past and moving around
see if he can go about possibly changing who he is and I was like man I'm trying
to keep my mind off of things and this thing is just poking the bear of what's
happening in real life and it's really strange oh I have a hard time with those
shows he does not the character does not have a good relationship with any of his
exes I'll tell you that much right now so wouldn't it be great to see a show one
time where everybody's like oh yeah that's my ex we get along fine but
there are actors in it that are amazing I enjoyed the first season very much she
is really fantastic yeah I watched a few episodes of the first season it was good
I don't know why I stopped watching it I might have just forgotten about it
maybe I went to sleep you might have seen the whole thing it was only like
eight episodes Jacob oh maybe I saw all of it though no because they weren't
long right no yeah an hour okay yeah but let's see you guys want to do a little
scoop mail here oh my gosh more than anything on earth let's do a little
scoop mail we are one from dirty rotten cone artist dearest Paul your gnome
repair operation from episode 1194 would make an excellent YouTube channel you
could film your gnome repairs and put them up as fun videos you could then
parlay that and then selling the gnomes from the videos people could send their
gnomes in for restorations and you could film those at charge for it the money
prints itself I look forward to the meteoric rise of Paul and am and gnome
dome fucking with the face that's the dirty rotten cone artist Paul have you
thought about opening up a gnome hospital we thought about it we actually
did talk about it a little bit and was like maybe we could just do this and I
was like no oh no I'd love to get internet today so Paul might might be
having problems here I said you know and said maybe we could just do this and I
thought yeah that'd be great but I don't I don't think so oh I gotta work out
it's over guys it turns out gnome repair does not provide health care so but gnome
repair content does provide extra money that is true I'm not ruling it out in
the future fixing up stuffed animals I'm not ruling it out in the future I'll
tell you one problem though with some of that repair video shit I don't know if
you guys are how much how deep do you guys go and repair videos cuz I watch
quite a bit oh all I'm doing I used to watch a lot of them like fixing old game
systems and whatnot but it turns out like a lot of those channels just fuck
up the product and then pretend to repair it you know what I mean like
they'll intentionally they're filthy liars yeah yeah yeah yeah Jeff Loomis
do this on your video you could you could like carry a gnome up to the roof
and then parachute it off and then you'd have to fix the gnome they go oh no my
gnome you could you know you gotta be what if you took the gnomes and you know
just you turn them into something you can fuck I'm glitching out sure now
you're glitching out your honor he's too busy fucking that gnome glory gnomes
is a great name for you know there we go I'm back Paul has terrible internet
today all right recording his own end but uh but he has real bad internet hey
Cindy or flindy Cindy flindy uh flindy put up a post about how they're going
camping in a forest in New Hampshire last weekend of October the post and
scoop group about it they must see some scoops up there oh nice I've actually
been at a campground with flindy because I did the porcupine festival as as a
magician and what's a porcupine festival it is a honestly it was it was
probably still is a very libertarian themed outing for people go camping and
a bunch of people in New Hampshire who are trying to start like a government
list state free state try to try to hold some lectures there's a lot of crypto
lectures and then I went and I just I did like two magic tricks and talked
about Penn and Teller for like an hour and they offered to pay me in crypto and
I said no and lessons learned lessons learned yeah yeah but yeah go camping
with Flynn they make the best food they make good camping food I went by by
their campsite we had we ate lunch oh nice I still have there from Keene New
Hampshire I still have the bag I put all my podcast up in this bag it says
fucking great from a faux restaurant in Keene oh great that's uh it's one of my
favorite bags let's do a little speaking of favorite bags you're my favorite bag
let's do a little jock vs. nerd all right
explosion of gnomes everywhere we got a scooper to come in as today from pony
scoop it's Emma the categories are pop culture ponies hoof and glory scoop
stable and horse sense ooh Matt you're up first horse sense 400 if a stallion
loses the family jewels he becomes a hmm it's not stud okay shoot I know this I
know it oh I'll go to hazel for my lifeline please
gelding gelding gelding I'm sorry it's a stud a stud was the correct no it's
gelding for the people this thing Paul you're up yo also side note my dad we
might have had a solution for not for long the podcast as a viable thing
because we talked about trying to use a patreon that like own a horse and then
it turned out that all right like that was like crazy money silly even with a
discount my dad found a site called racehorse.com where you can buy like
small shares in horses for like 119 dollars my dad bought a share in this
horse and I was like oh well that's patreon money we can probably do and so
we can we can we can we can buy steaks and young horses and small steak and
follow their travails yes okay yes could we buy like a frozen package of horse
steaks with that money we can instead of buying steaks in a horse we'll buy
steaks from a horse yeah two different websites but we could totally do it okay
okay Paul you're up I will try pop culture things to make Paul go that's
made of plastic that's plastic it's put your wiener in some plastic that's not
eaten a horsey oh man the sexiest kind of hole is plastic holes everybody knows
that there's only one type of plastic small enough for me to fuck it that's
microplastics yeah some people have microplastics inside of them I like to
be inside of microplastic I need a microplastic popcorn bucket please Paul
you're up I'll take pop culture ponies pop culture ponies the palomino that only
talks to Wilbur Post in a 1960 sitcom of course of course that would be the
famous mr. ed the famous mr. ed it's me I'll try a hoof and glory for 400 the
final jewel of the u.s. triple crown that would be the you have the Derby of the
Kentucky Derby then you have I think the Belmont is second so I think the
pretendness is third I think you're right you switch to no you fool I did
switch you fool I'm that Paul Jamie just disqualified us from hosting a force
podcast I will take I knew all three of them I will take horse sense for 800
please long in the tooth comes from the fact that a horse's teeth keep doing
this as it ages growing getting sexier yeah there you go growing or erupting oh
yeah let's go with erupting yeah oh I'll continue with pop culture ponies please
I'm just gonna say it would have been really funny if Matt's answer to that
last question had been erupting oh it's easy but it'd be like oh they're
erupting Matt Damon narrates the life of a wild
Mustang in this 2002 DreamWorks adventure I was here every night an
audio just listen to him spirit it was spirit spirit the stallion of the
Cimarron oh I thought it was cinnamon I am gonna stop listening to it whoever's
reading the audiobook is doing a terrible job spirit the stallion of the
cinnamon this cinnamon it's me I'll try I'll try pop culture ponies 1200 and the
Simpsons episode saddle horse saddle sore Galactica Bart rebrands the family's
gentle racehorse with this tough guy name I don't fucking know you know this
one Jacob yeah I don't I'm passing it to Matt I refuse to answer I will pass but
Matt is pleading the fifth and Paul has signaled to me silently that he also
doesn't know the answer to this question I really don't be moving on oh you
really don't I really don't this is this has got to be like season 20 or
something I don't know oh okay let's see furious D oh Jesus I didn't know that
one I have not I have not seen saddle store Galactica excuse me like that name
though excuse me sir my furious D is caught in this plastic head I seem to
have some beans on my furious D I don't think hazel knows about the beans but
hazel doesn't know what the beans tell her some other time let's move on yeah
no I'll do horse sense for 1200 please that has never moved on faster in the
breeding shed a stallion can drop roughly how many inches of equipment plus
or minus two inches how big is a horse's cock that's exactly what this question
is asking yes hmm trying to think I'm just well so it goes past there don't
forget you can use hazel as a lifeline guys remember that early ass fucking
video from hazel tape measure handy can you measure your arm real quick you're
going with hazel arm as a competent comparison yes boy pass it to you good
old hazel horse dick arms honeysuckle they used to call her the delicate flower
now they call her horse dick arms I'm going well danger is not her middle name
I'm gonna go post to it math 38 inches 38 inches is just over 20 20s like 38
right if you've got horse eyes that is baby is 38 38 believe me pop culture
ponies for 2000 please oh yeah with my no money now boo with your no money and
Bob's burgers the adult super fans of the equestria knots proudly call
themselves the equestria what hmm I don't know I have to pass you can't
that's a it's a day I can't pass equestria knots equestria the equestria
knots so the equestria knots I take it are a band probably
equestria terrians I'll go a quest to terrians let's try a quest to Terrians
quest there it is a questicles that's me I'll try what was hoof and glory about
I'll try hoof and glory for 800 the indoor arena that fills with 1.4 million
pounds of dirt each December sits on the campus of this Nevada University
oh it's just a university I'm you and LV yeah you and LV all right good stuff
all right Matt I just got that right I don't know I don't know what tell you so
my instinct is to keep clearing out the horse it's kind of already set that I
actually only used one answer I got from hazel then I passed the other two so I'm
gonna actually switch to scoop stable please for 400 Matt's gonna make a
change let's see listeners listener letters become scoop mail but if a horse
delivered them the segment would share its name with the 1860s all equine
postal service that galloped across the West that would be the pink pony club
the pink pony club it's the pony you deliver letters pony express the pony
express of course it's the pony express I've read that they did not actually
gallop the very far they would it was apparently a what do you call like a
publicity stunt they would gallop into and out of town to make it look like
they were just galloping the whole time but you couldn't gallop a horse that
long so they know gallop in and out of town and then just walk the horse that
makes it apparently like a publicity thing that they did on purpose yeah those
man the whole world is bullshit man yeah Paul hoof and glory hoof and glory for
1200 and the 1973 Belmont this chestnut won by a record 31 lengths secretariat
secretariat is correct huzzah it's the only one you know Belmont being a third race
it's the third race rubbing it in yep I know that I don't know who wouldn't know
that I'll see I'll try horse sense for 2000
daily double boy you died the bullet there man you did did and I jumped in
front of it a horse can't perform this normal mammal function which is why
choking or stomach upset is a medical emergency done done done done done they
can't regurgitate something right they can't like like like cough something up
and and like vomit or vomit regurgitate cough it up I don't know if they swallow
something basically they can't like vomit it back out okay okay
vomit yeah yeah show me vomit vomit there man I was you not I was not like if you
gave yourself points for regurgitate because those are different things no
they're not are they no they're not rotating vomit is not regurgitation um I
believe it just from an attention standpoint no but I mean you can say
that birds regurgitate baby birds really funny the thing that took down our
podcast with this vomit versus vomit like I went to counter I was like I don't
want to have this I don't want to have this argument at all I shouldn't have
even said what I said I suppose there I mean like it's probably the bird
probably is regurgitating food that hasn't gone all the way past it's uh now
there has to be a difference I think Matt's right there has to be a
difference I just don't know what the difference is yeah Matt you're up scoop
stable place for 800 what is the name of the official pony of pod therapy oh it's
Emma's pony if that helps Jim's dad is a horse oh you had one too many letters on
that I don't know is the answer let's see if you were going to buy your son's
maybe when they were a little younger you might buy them some some toys like
some trucks or something to to drive around on the living room floor to talk
about what oh what was that to Tonka oh oh maybe maybe a little less stutter
is Tonka Tonka Tonka aka Tonka truck the ponies I don't know why you're
putting an extra T on this mat all of my kids trucks are buffaloes is what it
says my horses after buffaloes I'll try hoof and glory please hoof and glory for
2000 at Paris 2024 Snoop Dog rolled up to Versailles and full breeches and
tailcoat along this homemaking icon his longtime TV bestie that'd be Martha
Stewart the shore that's Martha Stewart yeah I don't know what the fuck she has
to do with horses she owns horses oh great maybe they're implying that she is
in fact a horse ah that's Snoop rides her like a horse
hey look out she's horny let's do this who rider wait that's a pony that's
genuine no yeah that's genuine we're like well like ecu wine oh my god nobody's
happy with that joke score check I liked it I liked it nobody didn't say that no
everybody agrees with that that is the best joke you made the whole show good
joke just nobody likes it Matt and I are both died at 2400 Matt Paul has 1200 we
got scoop stable for 12 and 2000 I guess okay I guess I'll get the big one and
try and win the game 2000 how dare you big one Nick's transport rant mentioned
that crossing the US border with racehorses triggers USDA Coggins
paperwork testing for this blood-borne disease named for the bacterial agent
EIA objection your honor this yes this is scoop stable scoop implies ice cream
social there have been two pot therapy questions in this category I'd like it
banned I'd like it stricken sustained sustained this will be stricken from the
record hey information on the blood-borne bacterial agent EIA there was
no horse who got a disease yeah I mean I I just don't think there's any way that I
would possibly know this pass Matt I'm just reading through it to make sure I
actually understand the question because I really didn't the first time I was to
be distracted by why am I answering pot therapy questions but I'm assuming this
is a bit that we did on pot therapy at some point that I don't remember yeah
it's gonna be a pass for me Jacob Paul could it be hoof and mouth disease
that's something horses get I think I've got hooves and mouths they do I got
hoof and mouth disease from my nieces right yeah I should get in your hooves I
didn't I didn't make your hands get like like Oh Shetty yeah just turn turn them
into hoops their whole guys it makes your eyes get really big I was in mouth
that's why I was doing horse sense categories waiting for the horse eye
question it never came equine infectious anemia that'll just nice otherwise known
as hoof and mouth of course and Matt close it out the category and the game
scoop stable for 1200 in the show pod therapy which therapist on the show pod
therapy does the most pod there pies Matt that's Jim if Jacob if Jacob names
a full after the show's tagline it's jockey club approved name 18 characters
max would read like this
or preaching fun no different different tagline preaching fun is really more of
our tagline but but maybe something else that could be confused as a tagline oh
what what in the but farts in the bag dot biz keep going I'll just pass Paul I
don't know I was going with preaching preaching f you but it's I don't know
pass I don't know I mean I wouldn't it be the FYI TF oh fuck you in the face you
dick and tit farmers you dick and tit farmers of which are you dick and tit
farms of which I am the farmer right that's yeah that's my answer
oh no just preaching fun it's preaching fight would have been the whole thing of
preaching fun okay I was right I was right the whole time why doesn't matter
because I was wrong and so either way Matt wins yeah Matt wins with 2400 I'm
insane 1200 Paul is in third with negative 800 and that's me go and my
latest pony scoop six times bigger than I than you think it is because I have
horse eyes too much change in my pocket it's horse sense I want to thank the
inspirational hazel honeysuckle for stopping by yes thank you hazel would
not have come up with the clearly award-winning theater piece of the Star
Wars fuckable seat franchise that we're we launched because of this episode
without you I can't wait to start development I'm picturing a Borg head
and we just we somehow mount a fleshlight inside of it that's the
prototype BYOFL boldly strip comm is where you can go to support hazel's
Kickstarter for volume 2 of her piece go go there support it right now yeah I did
I got I set up for both versions again Wow thanks Matt you got it and it's a
really fun project and then we'll see hazel at scoop fest hazel we will yeah
boldly ship commas where people go to support your Kickstarter where else do
people go to support what you do well you can you can come to Galaxy con in
San Jose next weekend when you can come to scoop fest yeah you can also go and
see absent at Caesar's Palace yeah there you go there you go I'm a little fairy
short and stout I will be at the Magic Castle August 20th to 24th good luck
getting in there and then I'll be in the magic saloon in San Antonio very
accessible magic saloon San Antonio September 1st is the number 8th come
there I don't know anyone there so come hang out I'm hoping it won't be as hot
as it was last time I was there where I basically hid inside during the day and
only went out at night like some kind of vampire but yeah and I want to thank
people support us over here on our patreon page we don't have a list just
yet and that's it's my fault I moved the recording to Monday instead of Wednesday
fucked up the whole system guys but just know if you support us at patreon we love
you and we thank you and we really appreciate it and if you have it within
your heart and within your wallet please throw a little jingle our way at
preaching fun.com
or if you also don't really know the difference between Star Trek and Star
Wars like you get them all kind of confused in your head maybe like one of
the hosts on this show head on over to fartsinabag.biz
that's fartsinabag.biz that along with preaching fun.com it takes you to our patreon page
where for as little as three dollars a month you can upkeep this show on the
air if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars head on over to
preaching fun.com and fartsinabag.biz today and of course head on over to
boldlystripped.com nudistartrekbooks who wouldn't like a nudistartrekbook for
the holidays my mother keeps one on her coffee table at home right now it is a
conversation starter it's great she loves it all of her friends love it get
yourself a nudistartrekbook over at boldlystrip.com or as I like to call it
sci-fi smut oh man if you get that first book you may even read a passage or two
influenced by my filthy innuendo give it a read guys give it a read looking at
that makes my teeth erupt this is what they need to put in the seats horse
mouths that keep erupting they bite harder as the film progresses in
sexuality oh and with that lovely notion we'll see you soon
secretariat 5d off to the races yeah
saddle up indeed
the cone says pro yard yeah