Oh
Hello there I am so happy you're here because this is the part of the show where we thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers
We are actually having trouble with patreon right now to get all of the lists out
But we will thank all of you patreon's out there each and every one of you before this month is over in the meantime
I want to thank each and every ice cream truck driver out there for delivering that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver help support this show head over to preaching fun calm preaching fun commas
We're gonna go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows
The life you say
May be your own it be
Or someone might call you on a phone
Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
I think we brought this up before
Stands on cool
I actually have something
Okay
We're preaching fun I had a friend's mom
Buy my kid cologne for his birthday. Oh, oh
oh
And your kid is 11 12. I
Mean that's the age
Cologne that is that is dracon war age
That is I went through a brute phrase not dracon war
Jacquard noir
was definitely the cologne of choice when I was in high school I
Grew up thinking that cologne was an old-fashioned notion like when I hear the word cologne
I picture like, you know
We don't use cologne. I've never used cologne. You don't use a scent
No, no, neither of you. No
so I went to Walmart yesterday with my lovely wife and
Your anniversary trip our anniversary trip. No, we're going and getting our stuff, you know, and every time I'm in Walmart
I make a point to go over to the perfume aisle and there is generic CK one. It's called you and
I always grab a bottle of you because that is the scent I've been using for damn near 30 years and
I use it every day and it's just been my scent of choice and it's cheap ish
I always like CK one because I started with CK one and it's just what I chose and it's been my thing
But I I don't go without it and I'm out as soon as I step out the shower. I hit a little something
spritzle on the clothes
rub the old
Hands together boom boom boom freshen up you said hands and you showed wrists, which one is it wrists wrists wrists wrists? Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just putting colognes in your hands is really weird. That's gross. Yeah
Right on my hand
Fridge everything just like everything you grab just what I like that Paul's coffee cup just reeks of cow
No, no, here's the thing you two have spent an inordinate amount of time with me
And you've never noticed some overpowering odor coming from me. That's correct. I've never what I've noticed
I don't have the greatest sense of smell but that's not to disqualify you not being a stinker room
But but but on the other but I mean not all not me be a stinker room
But not even me like I'm not sent forward like you don't go
Oh
Because there's people that wear cologne and you're like they were here five minutes ago, or maybe they're on their fucking way like you can
Famously we called, you know a Wayne Newton had a crazy Lord had a crazy billowing
Yes, pink pin style
It's like a choo-choo the Wayne train came through
And that's it when I hear cologne I think of like old-fashioned parties. I was dragged to in Monmouth County, New Jersey
Where all the men put on dinner jackets and and had very their own stinks on them while they drank a lot of alcohol
And I got well, that's it. It's a it's a disguise for stinks and I don't have to use much because I don't stink
And I don't drink and I don't smoke. That's the other thing too
If I drank and smoked it'd be I'd need something more powerful than CK one because that does not hide shit
Right, but I'm curious like I just I just personally never thought to
Ever where my wife never mentioned it. She doesn't do a lot of perfumes either. She might get a little bit of something
She just nice lotions and things like that. Sure, like we and then I use like
a pleasing natural musk
Always say about your wife. That's what she says. That's all that people talk about to her. It's just her must
Pleasing natural much. Yeah, she's like it when I tried when I tried talking about her must she's like get in line
So many people just talking about my musk all day
If you send me an email is she selling her urine for hunters boots, is that what's going on now? Yes
Attracting attracting dancers in the wild that they can yes the bow and arrow. No, it's hunter Biden
She's she's putting her piss on hunter Biden's boots go to hunt hunting boots piss Vegas and you'll see my wife's website right there
Or
But I'm curious if like what I'm curious about the people if if you know, I'm in my late 40s, right?
So we do late 40s early 40s late 30s
It is more or more people wearing cologne in general
Like or am I like am I wrong and thinking that was an old-fashioned notion because to see it come back with younger kids
Is interesting to me, but maybe I'm just wrong and a lot of people were column
I want to know in the chat. We have enough people here. I wear cologne
Paul's a cologne guy
Jacob even you you get spritzed up when you go out to you don't never thought you never think to go cologne
No, I never do cologne. I'll do like maybe a little aftershave or something
Okay, but even even that like I don't want I don't want an aftershave that smells. Yeah, I don't like having a scent. Yeah
Like in high school there were times that I had cologne like there were there. I definitely put cologne on in high school and stuff
I think by the time I was in college though, I was done with cologne
So sounds like there are some three guys have chimed in they all wear a little cologne like a very like they're talking about Paul style
Oh very little a little amount of all right a little dabble. Do you?
Do you do the clown you walk through the cloud?
I use it. It's honestly it's kind of like aftershave
So, you know cuz you know, I dry shave
Yeah, I'm not dry dry by use a little bit of water
I use a little bit of water and all razors now have a little lube strip on them
So it's not really dry shaving but nobody likes a lube strip more than me
Yeah, so, you know a little bit of that and I basically after out after the shower. It's almost like
aftershave, you know
Something keeps the bumps chill and whatnot. And yeah, and I spray it right on. I don't I don't do the cloudy walkthrough thing
Okay, according to to this Gen Z is big into cologne. Yeah, well, that's what I'm saying
It's definitely the young people it's back in for sure. So it's just a generation perhaps. That's it. That's it. I'm wondering
And also this is talking about having a fragrance wardrobe, which is apparently a popular thing
Which is multiple fragrance fragrances in your collection and you select the fragrance that you feel is most appropriate for that that day
Well, I was like something that but that feels like something that happened to me. I never get one of anything
I definitely feel like maybe you could do a little laughter what I was like I have like eight beard oils
I don't use in my house different places
Cuz I like go get the go get the purple bottle off of daddy's smell shell
You haven't gotten into the beard oil habit yet. My wife didn't like it
I kissed her once with beard oil on and she was like pissed off and I was like, all right
Well, it was it too much. Yeah, it's easier to have beard dandruff than it is to to put accidental beard stink on my wife
So I like doing the beard oil when my beard is a little longer
I don't like when I've got I've got my beard trimmed very short right now
I like it when it's when I've got it a little fluffy and then I like the beard oil
That's part of my daily regimen to
Sebastian Menescalco. Am I saying the name right? The special medicine. I'll go I think is that stand-up comedian? Oh
He did a live episode on Amy Poehler's podcast. It's really great highly recommend
and
he wears
Two colognes one on the front and one on the back
Sebastian come on
So this is what I want to talk about like this is coming and going I can't imagine
I mean, that's a lot of work to build up a cologne
wardrobe because
Wardrobe because everybody's body chemistry reacts differently to sense
So you got to find the one that that hits home and for me one just doesn't
Doesn't rock the boat like whatever I oh whatever I got going on
Jives with ck1, but there have been times when I've tried a little like Burberry and whatnot
And it just it's like the vibe is off kid. Yeah, I
Think I'm gonna start just taking tiger snake whiskey and using it as aftershave and just letting that be my my musk
That's not wrong. Do is take a drink of it, and then it will just ooze out of your pores
Fucking how much that fucking Duke Cannon shit that I stock on the target shelves every day
Yeah, it's all bourbon barrel infused shit. So you might as well
It's all bourbon. This is another another cologne. It's it soaps. It's it's aftershaves
It's a shame. I was gonna say same with a beard oil as well. Yeah, all of it all of it is
oakwood bourbon
Barrel infused shit. Yeah, everything smells like a basement in, Kentucky
Kind of does it kind of does you know?
Yeah, well, that's interesting. So do you are you are you encouraged by your son getting into scents now?
Or no, I was way too early fucking 12 fuck off. No, I
Too much you hate it because it's your kids growing up mice exactly. My son was starting to look so adults
Yeah, and then he had to get braces and I literally picked him up from the orthodontist and I was like, oh, thank God. Oh
He looks like a kid. Oh, thank goodness. He was literally just starting to just look like just a
Just a man. Yeah, it was yeah, really really that had me up. I know it's inevitable insurance the other day
Well, he's been doing that since eight
I guess first he convinced me that my current insurance was not was not good enough
Healer is there he is unlicensed and and that is not FDIC insured just so you know, but
Like the FDIC is gonna be existing in like your son will pay out though
Automobile accident. I feel like your son's gonna take care of that's true. That's true
Gear a scoop has said braces the puberty and virginity extender
Certainly helped in my situation. Oh boy
It does not seem to be a deterrent
Socially at all not anymore. Yeah, I don't think so. No, that's everybody like all kids now have braces
No, yeah, they do most kids do and I feel like it's a much more common thing now
It wasn't completely outrageous for me. You know a lot of people still had braids. Oh, they're also doing them younger
Yes, that's for sure. Yes
It's very rare that a kid in high school has braces now. They do them all in the middle school years
Yeah, they do that because younger gums it works faster. Yeah
Yeah, Oh
Garry scoop is saying our braces
smaller than they used to be
Maybe you're scooping the chat is saying that braces are super tiny and minor now. I think they're asking
The things that they're able to stick to the teeth
That day yeah, they seem smaller to me. I just got a big gold grill
It's just a big it just holds those teeth and just move it. I have you seen those people that wear their grills too long
And it fucks up their teeth forever
It's the nastiest thing they just keep they keep them in it's like months and it's because it's a visible version of Invisalign
Oh, no, but it's not even no not invisible. It's like just not they're not
No, that's what I'm saying is the grill is acting like just a visible
Invisalign, but it's just not even helping anything
Gross doing what braces do but in the wrong direction
Galactic president scooper star McScoops a lot has a great question in the chat
Did the boys convince you or did the HOA convince you to do anything about the giant skeleton in your front yard?
Giant skeleton is still up in my front yard
And that's the way on the with we keep joking that we're gonna put a Santa Claus hat on it
I've been HOA will not approve of that
Most of the problems can't ask permission you can't ask permission. Oh, no, we're not gonna ask permission, but I just
I think we just still get fine. That's what I mean
The skeletons head is bigger than mine, so I have some big Santa Claus hats, but not big enough for the skeleton
So I got I got I gotta go out. I'm sure it's just a quick search on
The internet will get me a giant Santa hat for the for the head
But plus I think a little saccharine is on this back there
But the problem is simply that it's a two-person operation and my wife and I first I was away and then my wife's so busy
That like we literally we literally just huddled up right now for like just to finally have an hour to play out the next two weeks
I have no idea what we're gonna
Right. Oh good news
Home Depot sells a Santa hat to go with that skeleton. Yeah, there's no doubt. There's no doubt
What about putting in the pool? I did a Google search for giant skeleton hat and and that popped right up
Could he just live in the pool?
That's pretty great, yeah, that's pretty great
Yeah, those bones will probably dissolve in the glory. You think maybe I don't know. It's probably not
It's probably not good for the or it'll activate the spell that lies within the skeleton and he will simply grow magic
An animated one way or another something's going down. Yeah, it's not one way or another. It's not gonna be safe
It's gonna be unfortunate. Well, I got through yet another round of eyeball testing. Oh
And it was kind of crazy
Went in. Yep. This is an eyeball. And yeah, I'm certified eyeball and
We've done every test that we can except for the dye test
So he was like you wanna just do the dye test and get it done
I'm like great so they could detect any possible swelling or whatever. I'm like sure
Yeah
So they had to put dye in me and then quickly get a bunch of pictures of my eyes and then we looked and no
There's no swelling. Okay, so everything's everything's written off except I have
Crummy veins and there's really nothing I can do about that
Until things go take catastrophically wrong. So I'm going back in in seven weeks to see if things are better or worse the yellow dye
Yes, it was very low
So as you know as they're doing it and everything they're like so you're gonna notice discoloration in your urine and stool
That's gonna last a day or two. I'm like, okay cool
but then I'm getting ready to go back to my car and I might well better hit the head before I go and
Swear to god. It was the secret of the ooze
So it was fluorescent fluorescent that's what it's supposed to be it was fluorescent I was like
Cooler shoot now your urethra
Yeah, yeah that well and I'm afraid of no ghost it was well, okay
Actually, I share this is this this is too much. Wait a minute. Hold on the things that you shared without this question is been
Paramount to this podcast. I can't believe whatever you're about to say
seems
I've been peeing for a day basically and it was still pretty bright and I was like
Well, this is this is throughout. Yeah, this is this is corrupting everything
so in the in the in the
interest of science I
Had to bust one out and see what was going on
And I'm here to tell you that permeated
I literally fired off some straight up
My no-no-no-no video my no nut November was done done a while back
But but I also thought I also thought not only in the interest of science
But also I thought probably good to get this out of every part of my system that it could be lingering. Yeah time to flush, right?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so that's what you know, just general maintenance
What's going on?
There's a thing as I'm doing this as I'm thinking about it how many times
Have because guys are the worst
How many times have guys had a die?
situation and
Then had a romantic interlude not long after and what does that do to the possible children conceived?
let alone
the kind of
Intimate moment you're having like oh, I thought you I didn't realize that's where you're going with this
I thought you were concerned about the fluorescent pearl necklace that I was giving
After getting my I died
I thought I thought you were worried about your gym socks glowing in the dark when you try to go to sleep or something
Here's the thing
Yes, so this is this is the other thing too. It's like
is this dangerous and
If it's not that dangerous
Then I think we've found a weird
Porn subculture thing here, maybe a kink. Yeah, right people who fire
Upside down spider-man
I'll tell you who else has fluorescent semen
This commercial break after this commercial break, I have a bunch of new tour dates coming up in 2026 for the jokers of magic
It's all officially on the jokers of magic website. Yeah, all the cities
I'm going to when we come up after the break, okay
Every single city on the jokers of magic tour will be jizzed on and fluorescent semen. That's that's the
Guarantee, that's right
Also, here's a sponsor
Today shows brought to you by Oh Matt Donnelly. There we go from Kevin Chamberlain in 2022
It's brought to you by me. So yeah, I'm gonna be going on the road. Go to jokers of magic calm
Okay, next commercial today shows also brought to you by leftover lobster. That's right from LAJ in 2022
This product is leftover lobster
You see Ariel sometimes people can't finish their entire meal and they need to take a basket home
Don't forget to have an extra cheddar biscuit. Why not? Ah
Under the tin foil
Under the tin foil. I will be waiting down on the shelf under the tin foil
You'll put me deep back in the fridge and you'll forgot. They ever lived. I was alive once now
I am free frozen under the tin foil
You leave me there for a week and then I start to reek
You remember only far too late that it was something you were going to eat under the tin foil
tin foil
I'm a stinky mess. The germs have coalesced and it's mold all over me
You spent on to me
$25 on the plate you weren't going to let that go to waste
But you should have left me cuz now I'm just scrudsy. I'm covered in mold here. You don't want this dear
Leave me. I'm rotten all kinds of nasty under the tin foil
Scoops to check out
Yes, oh my god, I we found a at work the other day we found
Just somebody's coffee cup that they had put somewhere and then it apparently had gotten hidden like other people got put in other things
I put in front of this coffee cup and the coffee cup got hidden and then
Long story short several months later. A coffee cup was found. Oh
What was it like a fancy cup?
No, like a paper coffee cup. Oh shit. Okay good an at work an at work coffee cup just right into the garbage
But it was it was disgusting. Sure. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Disgusting Matt speaking disgusting life finds a way
I'm gonna be in
Chicago is actually a preview jokers of magic at Chicago Magic Lounge
Is gonna be Mike Mills and I so it's two of the jokers of magic or we're playing together in December 18th 19th 20th and 21st
That's Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday. Oh, happy birthday
How about a show in Chicago just for you?
Thank you. I won't be there. I think we'll be doing six or seven shows
So check out check out Chicago Magic Lounge for for that
But yeah, no 2026 starting January 23rd, Lexington, Kentucky, baby
Lexington Opera House, I'm so excited
And then we're going to Cincinnati, Ohio January 24th
And January 25th, we're going to Bloomington, Indiana
January 28th, Green Bay, Wisconsin January 29th, Madison, Wisconsin January 31st
Wabash, Indiana January 31st still waterbush in the end and then in March March 19th
We're putting Saratoga Springs March 20th, Newark, New Jersey, baby, and JPEG
Yeah, and then
Fishing up in Easton, Pennsylvania March 21st. So yeah, go to jokers of magic get some tickets there
Come out and see the show get your purple chips. I'm so excited to be doing this show. Yeah, this is great
I just saw this on a Dittleman's
Instagram last night. Yeah, I believe I'm doing all of them at Dittleman and then and then there's gonna be a rotation
Mike Mills will be doing all of them and then we'll be rotating between Derek Hughes
Who I'm so excited to be doing a show with Derek is Matt King's number one filling guy had an awesome run on America's got
talent if you're watching our stuff, he he's just killer everywhere and
We're also gonna Nick the fats coming back for one of the legs of the tour also
Ruben Morland who a lot of people don't know he's actually been killing it in fringe festivals. One of the nicest guys
It's the big goofy redhead. I love Ruben. I'll find out with him a bunch of times
I'm so excited to be sharing my first shows with him. He's so pretty super funny
So yeah, very very excited each shows a four magician lineup
Of comedy magicians and it's gonna be super fun. That sounds wonderful. Yeah
magicians I watched the most recent fool us the other day and
that cat with the with the fucking card trick who
Who was it close talk to him like the day before something like that to get him on Paco a crowd though a guard. Yes
Wasn't even gonna try to remember his name. He was amazing. So I was
This is a abracadabra spoiler. So I but I guess you know, we're here
That is the reason why you don't see me on this season of
I was in the chamber as an emergency guy
we lost a couple of people to do for different reasons and
I was being
Primed up to do some kind of version of my card stab or ring trick routine for fool us and then all of a sudden
It was like no, never mind. We got this guy and of course, I was like
You know and I think he came out and he was he just killed he just killed so yeah, he was there just as a friend
Helping out John Carlos Scalia
Who's who aired an earlier episode this season and they used to have done a two-person show with each other in Spain
And so it was another thing. It's like the same way they got
Danny D or tease on they simply said like you're here. Like you're right here. What are you? Why are we not doing something?
Just do it. And so he showed him a couple stuff. And yeah, he went on there and fooled the shit out of him. So yeah
And so did John Carlo. So and I've worked with John Carlo a bunch on the Princess cruise ships
he's the nicest guy and
As someone said on abracadabra, maybe the only person who can just totally successfully use charm as misdirection
Just just totally can just be so
Charmingly goofy and whatever that you just you just take your eyes off of everything he's doing. Yeah with his hands
It's it's really they're they're both just killer killer guys. Yeah, they're great
Yeah, he was amazing. Yeah, this is a good the episodes. I've seen a fool us this season, man
They it is it is a good season to fool us. It is we don't know what the future holds
You know, we they took the season and split it in half, right?
So the air 10 episodes and gave like a big four-month gap and then now they're airing the other 10 episodes
The reruns get the same exact ratings as the new episodes, which is usually a bad sign for TV things
We've done over 140 episodes
so there's certainly enough to syndicate to the end of time and that includes getting rid of three seasons of
The kovat seasons, which they don't seem to rear as much
Studio audience. Yeah, I think those episodes are now covered with the last two seasons
And so I don't know and also what is CW in this modern media landscape?
Is anything it's it's a really weird is not been gobbled up by any of the major streamers. It's still its own app
It's still a network television show which means it still airs on rabbit ears
and
So I don't I don't we don't we don't know so we so it's all it's all up in the air
I I just don't I don't know what anything in TV means anymore
No that point now. We're like all of our experience in in television entertainment
Doesn't mean anything at all. The models certainly aren't there anymore that we now came up with. It's so strange
It really is a very strange time specifically for television and and yeah, it is it is weird. And so yeah
You know
Would Penn and Teller wants to do another season would would they want to maybe try a new show somewhere else?
I don't know, you know that kind of stuff. So I mean we did
11 seasons and secretly like 13 and a half seasons if you do it by a regular episode count
And so that's just a whole lot of TV and a whole lot of cool stuff. So I I don't know and how
It's that many seasons over how many years now?
gosh
It's over a decade. Yes, it's definitely over a decade. Yeah. Yeah, I'm trying to think when I started well
Yeah, so my kid was born
Yeah, it's been a decade. It's been a decade. Oh, there you go
Yeah, yeah, so my kid was born my second kid was born during the first season. So oh, yeah
They're a supernova girl season one was 2011. Yeah
There you go
Yeah, so I mean it's that's
That's a run. Yeah. Yeah, he's coming over
I'll talk about the original season of air in England too. So season two is where I kind of start the American
Season all right, it's been ten years since it was refired up in season two and goes on. Yeah. Yeah
Are they thinking about a new show man?
There always are they always are they always are
Yeah, the new show that they're talking about doing it. It's not gonna be as difficult to get a trophy
It's just fool Matt Donnelly. Yeah. Yeah, it's just just gonna be like if you don't get one
It's gonna be like what's wrong with you
Injured piff, yeah
No, it's strange it's strange to be busy enough that I don't need it, you know
I think I think that was always like the weird thing of like all right any time full scale. I was like, oh good
That was always a nice nice thing
and I think also like
I've really gotten like it like I heard I
Heard me something about another magician. They're gonna put they're putting together TV special for a magic
Okay, and I'm not necessarily on this magician's radar, but like people around him are and I am actually like I
Think because we're gonna show like I have I understand magic for TV versus magic for magic sake pretty well
And it's like probably true and I was like I should be at least get a phone call from one of these people, you know
It's like and so I am a little bit like oh wait if this shows over I need to figure out how to put
Myself out there more as a possible right like, you know
Lower level producer. Yeah. Yeah, cuz of like I really do I did learn so much
Sure show and I think I could help a lot for something like that. But yeah, yeah, we'll see
I bet you could buy the CW
It's on the block
Yeah, my improv classes are going great. I just got done with my first
level one
four-week class and nice
I had a couple students who were so jazzed that they wanted me to keep teaching and go on to level two and
I was like, well, I don't have a level two class scheduled right now, maybe next year and they were like nope
Let's get this going and so they contacted
and and made a made a
thing and and and got
got things moving forward and
holy shit
Justin was up for it and
They've got five students registered so far out of my class and they're gonna get a couple more hopefully and oh good
By the this next month. I'll be teaching two classes a week. So whoa
Yeah, I'll be doing a level one. I'm still doing on my level one again and a level two. So it's great
So we are doing what I was hoping to do which is build out
Improv community in Pittsburgh. It's gonna take some time, but it's gonna happen. I believe we'll see. Oh nice
Yeah, so that's going really well
Thank You bossy. Yeah, it's uh
it's just a you know, it's what I've been hoping for and I'm still teaching the occasional free class over there at the
Pduty network, so that's gonna happen. So I'm gonna go do that next Tuesday
Then the Tuesday after that provided everything's lined up will be rocking and rolling with the Tuesday classes, too. So
very encouraged with that
Let's go. Yeah making some more headway with getting getting further away from retail gigs and more and more into
this thing, although
today
today we went and bought some stuff for Anne's garden and in the
Complex where we ship in no, we did I know the complex where we went. What do you know?
There's a brand new bricks and minifigs store opening up and I'm like, oh shit
So for those of you who aren't familiar, this is a chain a franchise that actually deals in used Legos and repurposed leg
so
Uh-huh. So I think they're not gonna open till summer next year
It says or or spring at least so I'm gonna work like I'm gonna try I think
Might as well right if the if the compensation is comparable
What the fuck? Yeah, I could spend all day fucking around with Legos and hosting kids Lego parties rather than
Shoveling coal, you know, this is gonna be like Ellsroth at the weed place
You're just gonna rise up there without trying and you're just a king, right? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, man
Did you hear about the weed stuff though? That's that was if my first thought was Ellsroth today. What happened?
No, they have our Congress has decided to outlaw weed again
Nationally what? Yes
Couldn't possibly be a distraction from other things. But yeah, that's what they put in that fucking
Open the government back up bill that weeds gonna be illegal nationally in 26 again
I know right. Yeah, why?
Why indeed it's almost as though they're trying to sabotage the country
It's almost as though they're trying to just bring it to the brink of no, I mean, I mean like, okay
Sure, because I can't I've
It's a weird time and Paul's more right than wrong about this crazy shit, but
Like
Like okay, why isn't the government bill is what I mean?
So in other words, why was it allowed to be part of the opening up of the government again?
Like is it helping prisons? Is it helping? Yes. Do you know what I mean? That's exactly it. It's helping private prisons getting private
Yeah, getting more people because private prisons are complaining that they're not getting enough people so they need something else criminalized again and
the liquor industry wants their
Liquor money back from the people who are have found out that weed doesn't make you want to kill your family as much as
alcohol does
Feel like I still want to kill my family as much I don't know man
But you're like, oh the knife's all the way over there and my family's all the way over there
I'll do it tomorrow either of them next to chips
Oh my god, Mike or my family
Totally calling me out said I can't work at the bricks and minifigs place because I kept saying Legos when it's just Lego. Oh
No, it is true. They are they are pedantic about that. Although bricks and minifigs
So I don't have to say fucking Lego at all. I just bring your bricks and minifigs. How about that?
Figs is a weird. I've never heard that term
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
Yeah, bricks and minifigs many figures. Yeah, many figs. Yeah bricks and minifigs is a like I said, it's a it's a franchise
So yeah, that's what they call the minifigs
Any Lego figures? Oh minifigures figs is for figures. Yeah. Yeah minifigs. Yeah
Not when you said bricks and minifigs at first I was picturing some like tawny like upper middle class place for like bricks
Like brick brick like masonry. Oh how funny trees and like beautiful things like that
Nope, I'm talking about tiny lot of cologne a lot of tiny tiny little Lego men
That's all it is teensy little Lego men. These are looking at this stuff here
I don't know if this is about weed as much as it's about hemp
Well, it's saying THC products. So it's no products that contain a certain amount of THC
or
or what's the other active thing that's going on to the
Any of it, but anyway last night the Senate passed a continuous CBD CBD. That's it along with oh, there you go
Yeah along with three appropriation bills one of which an agricultural appropriation bill effectively shut down the US hemp industry
well
That's one way to put it
Growers use the the plant cannabis sativa to produce both hemp and marijuana blah blah blah. I
Don't know this weird. It's fucking weird like I'm looking through it now
I can't really read through the whole thing on the air right now, but like I'm looking through it right now and good
That's true. I guess
We are nothing if not a marijuana forward
Thing like I I am the least smoky of all of us as in I have never I have never imbibed and even a gummy
You know, I'm just not a drug dude
But I I am very much an advocate of of all of it because you know
I've seen the good effects it can have on people and it can make people feel good and
mitigate pain I
first of all that once lived in the Virgin Islands, so we're going to go over my partaking of weed, but
What in the Virgin Islands?
You know, you know, you don't live in a tree house in the Caribbean and not smoke weed
Residents you lived in was constructed of help
Was just weed just weed. Yeah, just lived in weed. Yes
It like literally like in a movie like washed up we went I'm at a giant garbage bag of a wash up on shore
Everybody was it just like Christmas we made oh that ended up leading because it wasn't good weed
So then leading to my friend Colin making what I called instead of weed cookies
He made weed briquettes is what I call them. They came out green. It was like it was like your it was like your gym
Sock Paul. It was neon green
And they were so strong people accused him of lacing them with other illicit substances
Which is hilarious just because he was Rosseferian and like really just believed in like just it was just skunk weed
He's like no, it's such a density cooked into the cookie. It was like sugar. Yeah
We were there was more weed than sugar. You're just feeling the power of jaw. It was weeks of the craziest behavior
Pandemic
Company but I bet nobody nobody got hurt nobody gotten a brawl
People got people got paranoid and I'm stuck on like a little island key like a story island
Like for like hours because they were afraid to go back in the water
They were worried about their ability to swim to shore so there was an incident there was an incident of survival nobody was hurt
It's it's you know, and like you said, I hate that I'm the diet of exposure on that island
Injured before dying. I hate that I'm more right than wrong on this stuff
but I think you know weed is such as such a good calming effect on a lot of people and just chills folks out and
Alcohol just get some amped and people are gonna turn to whatever substance they need to
Day, I actually thought like I thought I thought
Legalizing weed in Nevada wouldn't be that big of a deal wouldn't change things and it right was I wrong?
Like it changed things everything you can't walk down the street without smelling it exactly
I don't enjoy the effect that weed has had on Vegas
But my answer to that is not jail my answer to that is not and let's get also nice involves
But also the it's capital punishment. That's that's a kill people
Yeah, the fact that you can't walk down a Las Vegas Street without smelling weed
Tells you if you're not brain dead that oh fuck
They are selling tons of this shit
This is an industry the stereotype of old cab drivers as they would take
Whatever
Yeah, but they would you know, not the one you asked for but the one that paid the cabbies the most
Yeah, right and that has now changed to weed dispensary. Yeah
Yeah, well remember how we were talking even before like we there's before I moved there was still a real
Possibility that we could have been really fun
dispensary
Entertainment right? Yeah, there's gonna be the easiest job in the world
exactly
A couple of places here have tried the the cannabis lounges and nobody has figured it out yet
Yeah, how to do the lounge? Yeah, what's the time?
I'm just like hanging around and getting high somewhere else. It isn't that appealing to people. It's not it's not it's not working with stand-up lineups
That's for sure. Well, I suppose if if one of the major side effects is paranoia, you don't want to be in a strange place
well, this is that they have all these different strands now that one can you know, the
Paranoid man, this is just gonna give you a real mellow trip. Yeah
Yeah, and it tastes like ice cream. So let's go. I just saw a video
Some cannabis celebration and somebody had rigged up an apparatus where they had a giant
Stack of weed inside what amounted to a stovepipe and that stovepipe was directly
built on top of and Jerry rigged to and taped up to a leaf blower and
So somebody lit all the weed with a blowtorch in the top. Oh, yeah, the stovepipe they turned on a leaf blower and it just
For like two minutes straight just billowed weed smoke
It just looked like a haunted house
We call that the dandy isn't that dandy? It's the dandy is that it was
Crazy, it was crazy
It was wild to see and just people just getting face full of weed smoke from a blower
From a leaf blower. The whole room was just coated. Yeah. Yeah
So but yeah that real that really bummed me out this morning and my first thought was Ellsroth because he has found something
He's exceptionally good at he's enjoying the shit out of it. He's trying to entrepreneurialize with it
All right, he's become a true character man. Right and this is the machine, right? This is exactly why I'm like that's America
That's fucking capitalism true. That's that's get it done and they're just putting a kibosh on it
Then I guess I guess we should fuck. I'd be curious. He's probably working which why he's not here, but be curious
But that's what they're saying what Ellsroth saying what they're saying at his work. I'd be good. Well, we've got a day here
Maybe we can try and get him on tomorrow because we're doing it again tomorrow
Yeah, maybe we could get him in to chime in cuz yeah
I would love to hear the initial cuz and I'll give it a day to stew cuz it just hit today
So, uh, yeah, let's let's hear it. Let's hear it
Speaking of hitting today
So the the new federal funding legislation moving through Congress is expected to impact the sale the sale of hemp driven THC products
But not state regulated sales of recreational metal medical marijuana
Medical yes, it's CBD
It looks like though from this from this other article that I'm looking at over here from the cannabis business times comm
Oh, you can't sounds that they sound very CBT. Let's not let's right you can a business. It's right there
Can a business times it should be candid times and it's definitely looking at it again. I was wrong
No, it's cannabis business times. It's right there. You got a guy got to make some calls
Yeah
Can a bit later?
No, I only take my news from this time. This is Hannah the times of cannabis business weekly
Times of cannabis business weekly is out of the that's out of the realm. You know, I'm pretty leftist
So I do this the Sativa Tribune. So I do this
Yeah, would you pinko?
What about high times? Oh
Hi times that'll rank
I'm all about kind of business right now people's front
That's exactly what I was going for Jacob, I knew you'd catch it
Yeah, this looks like it might be
according to the what should be the cannabis miss times
Would prevent the unregulated cell of intoxicating hemp based or hemp derived products
Including Delta 8 from being sold online in gas stations and corner stores while preserving non
Intoxicating CBT and industrial hemp products according to the summary me. Well now me while kratom runs rampant, right?
Oh, it's stupid that they're involving themselves in it at all, right? Absolutely
That's the thing. Is it just stupid? We've gotten to this point. We've gotten this we don't we've had nothing but wild success
Let's fuck everything. Yeah. Yeah, let's mess with it doesn't make it
I'll tell you who else wants to mess with stuff just for the sake of messing with it and that's the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by
Where'd you go? Where did you go? I brought the jokers of magic and now we're screwed
I'm doing a commercial
From the makers of permanently wet socks permanently crunchy socks, that's right
Oh scoopa troopa in 2025
permanently crunchy socks
Hey everybody, it's me
Applejack from Applejacks the mascot that never existed. Hi, are you interested?
Shit in your socks. You should try Applejacks
Applejacks is combining with Doritos to create a brand new sock
Full of Applejacks and Doritos. That's right. It's gonna be crunchy sticky cheesy and sharp
Just like you like it. It's the walking sensation that's sweeping the nation crunchy cheesy sticky sharp. That's our guarantee
chit
Crunchy cheesy that is crunchy cheesy is two C's
And a T CCST
Kissed you'll be kissed your feet will be kissed with the delicious taste of Doritos
Applejacks and the mixture of the two with your sweat
Nothing like foot sweat to get a Dorito to that perfect flavor taste place
Mmm, and combine it with the sweet sweet stickiness of Applejack cereal, which also have a certain crunch
Ah, you can't beat it
So go out and get yourself some Doritos and Applejacks filled socks from me Applejack
the
Mascot that never was
Enter hey scoops a checkout
That's a cologne that I would wear Applejacks
Applejacks and feet
I mean you wear any sweet enough cologne near your socks long enough and you got it. Yeah
By the way, Matt, it looks like next our media group already owns the CW. Oh
Okay, we already owned
They they own the biggest chunk of it and then like paramount and a couple of other
Groups like that own like 12 percent stakes here and there. Oh, no. No, I think I understood that they're yeah
I mean, I knew they had some organization behind them and next are I didn't know was next are but yeah
They're already the big dog, but but doesn't but it's sure that they're there's still an independent
Independent. Yeah, there's still an independent streamers. It's really important was on pointing out and right
I'm just I'm confused now now that I know that why they're still an independent streamer, right?
yeah, it seems like they would already have been looped into other things that their
Owners own right and they're not that's weird and they're not which like the facts
They're not already part of the paramount plus or peacock or something like that makes it kind of weird
Yeah, and they yeah, all right. Yeah. That's fine. Oh, let's do a little scoop mail. Let's do
Scoop
Dear Neapolitan since this podcast is one of the reasons why I met the love of my life
I wanted to share more happy news about our little family. You're welcome. This is this is a Manu
Hi, Manu Manu. Mrs. Cincy scoop a couple weeks ago at the end of October. Mr. Cincy scoop
And I welcomed our Dippin dot
Little boy who was at 99 who was at the 99 percentile of size during most of the pregnancy
Turns out to be great because he arrived three weeks early. We were both fine and healthy after the birth
I had my first hospital stay and do not recommend for anyone who needs to rest baby is growing getting nice and fat
He likes to sleep so much that we need to pester him every few hours to feed him
Then he feeds for about an hour straight until he falls asleep in the cycle repeats
That's a baby after my own my days off exactly that is my life
Most days are good, but the little one is getting the hang of being a human
So other days are a little more challenging overall
We are very happy the experience as a first-time parent is interesting to say the least
Honestly, the broken sleep is not the worst part for me dealing with other people's bullshit comments and opinions are the real test on my nerves
Since your advice is always impeccable. I come to you for solutions on how to deal with the worst offenders
I love these questions. Oh boy starting strong with questions about the baby's circumcision status
I don't think it's appropriate to talk about my baby's gonna tell you at all, but I guess I'm the weird one
What do I even say to that?
Then how do I shut down the comments about the next baby?
There will be no next baby and it genuinely made me sad hearing these those remarks only one week postpartum. That's
Insane. That's the same you about the next baby while you're still healing from getting the first one out of you
Well for the first question you can tell them straight up say no Microsoft got rid of Clippy
They faced Clippy right out yeah Clippy is gone. So that's just not a not an option anymore. Yeah
Yeah, okay talk about their genitalia
I'm just gonna say the short clippy answer is you know, like why are you thinking about getting one?
The the the bold one is to say like are you asking me about my child's penis is that what we want to talk about
right now
right
Yeah, how about we just talk about other aspects of their genitalia instead of the tip of their feet?
Let's talk about the shaft. Oh, it doesn't have to be your child
Turns out they're gonna take any kid to the oil and they'll just don't just nip the tip
I remember once I'm having a guy, you know, whatever being like no, don't circumcise. I think I think it's circumcised
I end up having to get circumcised at 12 because of an issue or whatever and I regret you know
I wish I wish we didn't get it done or something like that and I turned to the person I said
You think it's you didn't stop fucking did you and then he laughed and I was like, it just seems to me like
People try to compare it to like the oppressive like
Circumcision of women that happens in like different countries that's a little sure. It's a it's a lot
It's a lot different than that. It's a lot different
Yeah, for the most part it is a sanitary thing but also like it's nobody's fucking business
Yeah, yeah mind your business. This is exactly this exactly goes right to this
marijuana stuff
mind your business and
Let business mind its business. It's outrageous the stuff the talking out of both sides are fucking heads with this
We want we want business to rock and roll and we're gonna fuck with business constant so stupid
I mean, yeah, though a nice response to it is
You know as much as I would love to talk about my baby's dick with you. Why don't we talk about anything else? I
I've
Say this, you know, this is the thing that this is like a life lesson from improv that I moved to real life
Which is don't get stuck having conversations. You don't want to have right?
So like if you're on stage in a scene and you and you see partner don't feel like you're enjoying the scene either one of you
Do anything to change the subject until you are talking about something you want to talk about and the audience will be relieved
right and so I
Had if you simply go like oh, I don't want to get into this at all
Yeah, if you just say that and then just beat silence
That person will not pester you about it. You they will change. They do
Get him out of there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but simply sound like oh, I don't want to get into this with you at all
Not right now. I don't feel like talking about it, you know anything along those lines
Just just shut the person up, you know
But you owe it to yourself to like do not have conversations
You don't want to have if you don't want to talk about your child's genitalia to somebody you do not talk about it
and if you're confident and calm and almost quiet about it that person will just freeze up and
Yeah, you one of you will move on
Right, right. Yeah, like somebody will continue the conversation or the conversation will end and either way I feel like that's fine
So also the people are asking about the next baby a week after the this baby they're asking about the next baby
Are you gonna pay for it? I have another baby. You're gonna you're gonna pay the bills for that, baby
Yeah, I don't know. I'm reading in chat. Are you worried about my kids? I'm reading in chat same
My brother's wedding was just two weeks after my son
Two weeks after I had my son and everyone had a comment about not circumcising him
and
My aunt kept saying well, my husband was so I'm like not gonna talk about my kids or husband's penis
Yeah, yeah, like I like it's really like they'll never be able to follow up on their hypothesis, right? Right?
No, they have no medical background
Idea for this for whatever they're bringing up. They have no
Factual basis for it at all. You know what can be really funny. Tell them you're having it added on to
Tell extending. Yeah, tell them you're adding four inches. My baby is gonna have a five skin
We're doing like a chip clip with like fishing weights on it and we're just
We're gonna stretch this thing out it's gonna be like the bungs of the rungs of the Notre Dame Bell up there
It's gonna be like being really really really they're not gonna be able to circumcise my kid because it would be a major
Surgery based on how much they'll be removing the tip of his cock is gonna look like the ladies lips at Mar-a-Lago
What I mean to say is like most people are concerned about it from the sake of like
sensitizing the children that the kids miss or that the person is gonna be made fun of or ostracized for not having it done, right, right, right and
Those people have that opinion of a child that young are not gonna remember to check in 15 to 18 years from now to be like
Hey
How's the fucking going with your kids like they're not?
Can't follow up you're never gonna get an answer to your hypothesis. You're only going off of your own personal shit
so it's just as like yeah, but
It's it's madness that people think, you know
Cuz they go to this with like C sections versus natural birth and stuff like that the amount of shaming that people do to each other's
Children and stuff like that. It's just and and it just comes what does it matter?
Well, it just comes from people not being confident in their own life decisions
that's what it comes down to people do not have the confidence to just live in their own decisions and they need validation and
They need conformity from others to make them feel like oh, I did the right thing
It's like fuck you you did the right thing for you
That doesn't mean it's the right thing period and it's not necessarily the right thing and you gotta learn to live with decisions, man
Also, how much happier would everyone be if they just didn't know all this shit about everybody else? Oh, god's sake
Like I feel like no about anybody else's kids genitals to live my life. I don't know
I think it's important that people realize I fired glowing jism out of my cock earlier this week
I think that's an important that is important. That's important. No, no, we mean car. We have carve-outs in these rules
That's it. You should go. Hey, I don't know if I want to talk about my kids peace through right now
But you know what I second them out most people have some form of herpes. What form do you have and how you deal with it?
It's true. It's true. It's universal, baby
The old pissing disease what other aspects of my kids genitals?
Are you gonna want to talk about later so we can just knock all these conversations out, right?
You should be like actually the truth is I'm teaching a class on circumcision
And I need you to give me a hundred dollars right now or I cannot talk to you about it
Yeah, I didn't get him circumcised, but I got him a Prince Albert
Make the choice a couple years later if he wants to keep it he's got it if he wants to get rid of it
He's got a pull tab. You can just
Misses since he scoop is saying that people then followed up asking about the birth
How do I convey that that's an incredibly personal moment? I probably don't want to talk about it. You just say that
We kept the foreskin, but we clipped his balls. So he's a
We were asked to choose we flipped a coin
Two-faced style like of like a Batman villain and just thought well either we're gonna give him a circumcision or no nuts
We were we were too busy debating how we're gonna handle the fact he was born with three buttholes to figure out
My son is essentially a boy worried about his tail my son is
Bowling ball with a tail so you tell me where to prioritize lady
Well the half-grown twin in his ass cheek that would like a word or two
Psychic conjoined twin he's got a he's got a guano in his left but saddle so yeah
You know prior I got around to the circumcision talk. Yeah, we're still we're exercising the the ass guano first
Lastly any tips on how to raise my baby gay
I think you just start engaging in all of these conversations about the their genitals
People it's conversed about their genitals as you can and that's how that works. We've been doing our best. We have a gay agenda
we're trying to raise our kids gay and
Believe it or not these ages. They just figure it out on their own. It's the weirdest thing. Yeah life finds a way
Gay porn around the house. We have nothing like our Christmas decorations are just like different dirty decks of cards with hot dudes
So we just hang the cards. So yeah, yeah this tree
They're really getting a full mouthful of it. We only serve phallic fruits and vegetables for dinner
You know, I heard this really interesting thing
And I may have said this before on the podcast table, but we're talking about you know, how a lot of your hardcore
Religious types want to talk about sexuality as a choice. Yes, right and
What this person said was for them
It is a choice because they've had to choose to repress their natural sexuality their whole life and they don't realize that it's not a choice
It's just interesting
But they've had to make the conscientious choice to say no to their instincts to their basic human nature
They have they have had to make a choice their whole life
So they see it as everyone has to make this choice, right?
Like I made this choice. Everyone must have made this choice somewhere along the lines like now man. It ain't a choice
It's just the cards you dealt with those people. They're in that zone. They don't understand that
I'm not going down to the fucking bath house. It's not a choice
It's because I'm choosing every day to not go down to the back out bath house. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, but it's just your name
But they don't understand that they can't see that and especially if they've been indoctrinated in a very small community that has the whole
You know, so I thought that was a really interesting look at it
It's like you would think it's a choice because you've had to choose to repress your own nature your entire life
Thank you for all the laughs and creating such an awesome community Murray is still a great name for a baby
It sure fuck yes on it because it doesn't work in Portuguese. Okay, fucking you in the face with a boob full of milk
That's Manu. Mrs. Cincy scoop. Thanks for the information
Congratulations. Yes. Congratulations Cincy scoop both of you. Yes, wonderful
It's time for a little jock versus a nerd it's all
Am I fuck yeah, I'm on the hunt for balls
On the hunt oh
Look, there's a picture on the on the zoom and the twitch of little baby dip and dot Manu baby. Oh
That's so baby. See scoop. There's another reason why you should sub up and support the patreon
For as little as baby pictures you can come hang out with us
Yeah, oh
We got a
scooperty here today for rum
Wait, wait is it from there's another note here? I want to bring up Rebecca and Chad say I oh, yeah
I had two kids one and disposable diapers formula fed hospital born
The second kid was born at home breastfed and diapered in cloth
You wouldn't know they both turned out fine and I'm sorry people sell all this dumb stuff to you
That's that's exactly what we're talking about. Is that like yes, we are the children you are you are worried about, right?
So look at all of us which ones are which was a formula fed which ones have circumcisions, which ones, you know
We did die. It's like you can't tell you can't tell babies survive, right? They find them in freaking
dumpsters crap and they all live babies are
Amazingly resilient. I put those babies in those dumpsters
Absolutely with the intention of them dying and they won't
No, and Jacob still walks free. Why prom night dumpster, baby
Prop that dumpster baby and I'm taking a stroll
Yeah
From scala wall scoop. Hey you face fucking tit farming socialists
I'm gearing up for a trip to New Zealand and thought I'd drive and I thought I'd dive into some Kiwi culture beforehand
In hopes to hear this New Zealand theme scooperty while on my trip
Apologies to the real New Zealand scoops for what is a tourist take on what?
I'm sure I'll discover to be a lovely country definitely less cunty than their neighboring land
Mass hole of a continent and a country across the water now that I've probably insulted two wonderful nations
Does that give me honorary American status?
See what the cone with that talk buddy, yeah
Let's see this scooperty is the categories are
Flight of the concourse. Oh, wow, New Zealand cities New Zealand actors New Zealand director. Oh great
Yeah
I'll try New Zealand doctors for 200. Okay
This leading man probably wishes that Jurassic Park spared a little more expense
Not sure why he went back to that island multiple times can't be the money. I
Don't know which one of those guys was in all the Jurassic Park movies
Who's from New Zealand? Yeah, I don't know
It's Jeff Goldblum from New Zealand. I don't think so. I guess I'll pass Paul
Shit I'm just trying to rack my brain for his name. He's in
Event Horizon I
Just can't I can't remember his name you remember his name Matt I have to pass
I was thinking of Richard Adams burrow, but I don't know if it's like could be Richard Attenborough, too
Oh, yeah, I guess could be I don't know nothing Richard Attenborough. All right
Sam that's it. That's
Paul yeah, yeah. Yep. That's it
Oh, I'm in the hole. I gotta start changing my tactics. I will go New Zealand director
It's correct correctly. I don't know. I'll go fly the concords
Fly the concords for 200 the boom king the Rhymos the the Rhyme nocerous
Yeah, the rhyme nocerous
Oscar-winning member of the band that is Germain. Ah
It was Brett Brett McKenzie also will accept Brit
I hung out with those guys every night at the Edinburgh French Festival in 2004 and it's so funny. That's amazing
Yeah, they were awesome. They were so funny and so oh, yeah
Wait wasn't oh, no, he's the hip-hop hippopotamus
Germain's the hip-hop hippopotamus not the Rhyme nocerous
Well, there you go. And go my face even cities for 200
New Zealand's largest city known as the city of sails. It's home to the Skytower
What's the capital of New Zealand
starts with an a
Is it isn't Queensland?
Hey, I don't think so a Queensland. That's a
Australia. Yeah
Oh
What the fuck is that city called?
I
Don't know I can't think of it. Oh
Wait, this is Matt's turn what how's this Matt's turn? I don't know. It says Matt's turn on top
Yeah, oh in that case pass. I
Passed to Paul. I'll pass
Auckland oh you knew you were right. You were on that is the city
I was trying to think of the Queensland of New Zealand, Auckland the Auckland
Auckland
Wait, that was my turn. Okay. All right. Oh
It was because of the passing I got it's my fault. I got confused because of the passing so yeah, that was man
I'm playing under protest. I quit. I'm leaving
Continuing the game under protest. I'll go to New Zealand cities for 400
Although I didn't get Auckland so I don't know why I'm going other New Zealand cities because that's the one that I knew
Located on the South Island. This city is nestled between Lake
Walk it
walkipoo, maybe walk and the snowy peaks of the
Remarkables with a name that hints to the country's British colonial history
T times Berg. Oh
This is gonna be like
Queensland or something like that. I don't know what it is though pass Paul
I'll go with
London all right
Queenstown shit the London of New Zealand, but you take me to Queenstown
I'll do
New Zealand director for 800 I got to get on the board. All right
Daily double Wow, this is where I get redemption. This is your opportunity
Sadly, we just lost this giant of directing talent to Parkinson's disease known for his great work on once
We are once were warriors the edge along came a spider and the James Bond film die another day. Oh
Dolly the sheep no
Shoot
I'd give you hints if I had any idea I have to pass. I'm sorry. You can't pass double. Oh, I I'll guess
Richard Attenborough
Richard Attenborough is correct. It's not
Lee Tomahawry. I knew it was gonna be gone too soon from the
Maori, but I didn't I didn't
Matt you're up. God. We are killing this. I'll look at us with our own New Zealand. Now. It's not gonna know Zealand
Currently I am winning with zero
I will do New Zealand actors for 400, please
This actress born in Winnipeg
But raised in New Zealand shared her Oscar-winning debut with fellow Kiwi
Cliff Curtis in the piano and went on to famously play women with powers a mutant and a telepath
Okay pass
Okay, that passes to me I
Watch the piano at least once a week
Once I actually know this one Jacob if you want to pass it to me. Oh, that's that's good because unfortunately
I've never paid attention to the actress from New Zealand in the piano
I purposely don't pay attention to her at all while watching the piano
So I will just watch Harvey Cattel's wiener and a pack one and a pack one
She went out when she was in a pack when she was a baby. That was a very young age to win an Oscar
Oh, it was very very young to get the Oscar then. Yeah. Oh that changes the score completely now
I am still in the lead with zero points Matt is still in second place with negative 200 points
But Paul is now still in third place with negative 1,000
Thousand good grief. I don't know because you lost points. I don't know how these games work
Do you do you lost the daily double on the New Zealand? Oh, that's right
But does it turn into 1600 what no and I guess wasn't no you would miss the other ones - okay
There you go. I'll go to New Zealand actors for 600 known for her TV success. This actor has starred on iZombie
Once upon a time and most recently ghosts an actor by any other name would smell as sweet. Okay
Rose McGowan
Rose MacGyver, oh look at that you all you had three-fourths of it. I did I had more of that name that I thought I was
I'll do a New Zealand director. What the hell for 800. Well, that's not New Zealand director
You said direct. I thought you said New Zealand actor. Sorry fine
this young actor
So much protest this young actor has made memorable turns and hunt for the
Wilder people Deadpool 2 and how to train your dragon
He shares a name with a famous son of a beetle not Dennis's son. Yeah
I don't know. I'll have to pass passes the map
Probably Julian somebody but I tell you it passes to me. Oh
I should have got I should have guessed can I guess still?
Sure, it's my turn. But you can guess I'm gonna guess juice. I'm gonna guess it's Julius Rodman
Just on context clues
Great, I'll guess Julius Rodman motherfucker
It's Julian Denison. Oh, there you go
I'll take Dennis Robbins relatives for 600, please
Give me a flight of the concourse for 400
This fan this fanatic co-star on the series went on to animated series fame as Mabel in Gravity Falls
Yeah, this is Kristen Shaw. Yeah
Okay, sure is it is nice job
Just a legit correct answer for one of these questions. It's so refreshing. It's a new day
It's me I'll try a New Zealand director 200
The most famous director to come out of New Zealand. He doesn't know when to quit when it comes to hobbits and beetles
What the fuck is that guy's name
Pass it to Paul. Yes, it's
Peter Peter
Pumpkin eater Jackson. Is it Jackson Peter Jackson? That sounds right Peter Jackson. That's right. Hey Peter Jackson
Questions for the only ones I was hunting for is the only ones I know I'd know if this category is looking for Kristen Shaw and Peter
Jackson
I
Will do fly to the concourse for eight. I
Got to get on the board
This musician is depicted by Jameen Clement who comes to Brett in several dream sequences
Representing different personas and eras of the artist even seeing your song named after the musician
It's me Brett David Bowie from the music video of ashes to ashes
It's David Bowie
David Bowie is
Right answers in a row. It's a great. What are we coming to great runner for that episode?
So, all right, Matt, let's see if we can make it for right answers in a row. You're up
Fly the Concord 600
He is the band's manager who later went on to play a gentleman turned pirate on our flag means death
Oh shoot. I know the guy but I don't know his name
He's great. Yep. Yes. Yes. He is. He's really funny. You know, really good. I don't
pass
Pass to me. I pass as well Reese Davis
Reese Davis. Oh fuck Reese Darby fuck my ass
Some that was some last-name revenge there. I was fucking sure
I'll go New Zealand cities for 600 Darby. It's the other Daily Double. Ah
And the game is mine
Now I just pass pass pass
The capital of New Zealand this city is nicknamed windy on account of the strong winds of the cook straight
Not sure if it's famous for its beef, too
hmm, I
Thought Auckland was the capital of New Zealand
Huh
Hmm Auckland Auckland doesn't lend itself to any beef related anything though
The instance it sounds like it's trying to say the name is Chicago, but I don't think that the capital city of New Zealand, Chicago
right
Capital is really funny if it was though, and we just didn't know it
I have beef experience
Yeah, if only I had a little more beef experience
I have no idea
Auckland, I don't know
Wellington beef Wellington
I don't know how the windy is part of that, but okay
Well, I guess it's just windy in Wellington. Oh, it is windy. Well, it's Nick. Okay, Wendy Wellington. I don't I dated Wendy Wellington
She was lovely
Director for why don't you marry her six hundred because she was disgusted by my uncircumcised penis and she ran away
Well, it was the chip clips on it, yeah, yeah
This two-time Oscar-winning director has directed the follow women in leading roles Kate Winslet Meg Ryan Nicole Kidman Holly Hunter and
Kirsten Dunst
Oh
I watched an outtake of the first spider-man movie with Kirsten Dunst in it the other day and
it was just over and over again this one crowd scene where she's in front of the crowd and
The the director is just trying to get this one extra to stop doing something
Yeah. Oh, that's every time like they'll cut the director over the speaker will be like great great great
You were doing this don't do that Kirsten is doing that. So don't do that thing that you're doing
Oh, man, let's go again. And then they'd go again and the extra would just do it again
Sam Raimi, right?
That was Sam Raimi. Oh, yeah
Exactly, I'm the same here
The original spider-man movie isn't on the on the category. Don't think Sam Raimi Nicole Kidman
Holly Hunter goodness sakes
About to pass passes the mat
Own Steven Spielberg sheep fucker
Pass oh you're using his full name Steven New Zealand Berg
Did Stanley Kubrick direct all of these people and is he New Zealand I don't think Kubrick directed Meg Ryan
Maybe I'm wrong or or Kate Winslet. Yeah, I don't know
pass
That's good, I was about to say it's a lady there you go Jane the
That's the you've got mail lady. I think maybe
Matt you got New Zealand cities or New Zealand director gosh, I won't know either
Let's do
You are submitted in first place. Yeah. Yeah, I'll do director for 400
This actor slash director has lent his talents to both TV and films notably
Reservation dogs the Mandalorian our flag means death and Marvel movies not to mention his turn as Adolf Hitler. Oh
Isn't this?
Take take Kiwa TT. That's it. Oh, yeah, that's right. Take away TD
Yes, I
Got a last name, right? I got a last name, right? It's a different. It's a different day tight tight TD wah kitties
Tight tight to the Wacky
Tight to the walkie-talkies bikini walkie-talkie. That's who it was. Yeah
And I'm closing out the category and the game New Zealand cities for 800
This is the oldest city in New Zealand and was sadly devastated by earthquakes in 2010 and 2011
I'm not sure if locals shouted out the town's name in frustration while it happened
Still water fucker. Yeah
still water
Our Nair
This is bad I come from our Nair
Our Nair, how times for let it
I guess I'll pass Paul. You seem to know this one
Shite shite, let's try shite a
Christ Church Christ Church
Damn it. That's the other city in New Zealand that I knew the name. Oh
Christ Church on a cracker Aaron there. That is the game
With 600 Paul is in second with a negative 1600 and I'm in third with a negative
1800 and that's from Scully walls scoop. Thank you Scully walls scoop
Yeah, if you want to send us a scooper to your price of sprite jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd. Oh
Hold on somebody just let me do it themselves. Got it
Anyway, if you want to send us any of those jock versus nerds up
You can hear us though, can't you?
I think I'm muted ten scoop and then he tried to unmute himself again or he tried to mute himself and unmuted himself
I don't know. I got it. What a mess. What a mess prices right obelisk scooper t
Scoop mail do all those things right over there at hey scoops comm go to hey scoops comm you can do all those things
We are still running low on those jock versus nerd
So head over there make us some jock versus nerds and send them on in you can see how much we crush the New Zealand
One, so, you know, just pick a topic and knock it out. Yeah, we basically know everything about New Zealand
Let's get another let's get another New Zealand quiz in here. Keep coming guys all New Zealand all the time
I know my knock them down BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
Now we can give me the deep cuts where we can really shine
Again, I feel like we'd get as many I think could be pretty close to the same. Yes. Yeah
Yeah, you're pretty close, but we do sincerely appreciate everyone right again with all their stuff. Thank you all so much for
Signing up for our patreon those of you have I did a test patreon hangout
Trying to learn the ropes on how to get the zoom thing going and I think I did it
I'll have to double check with Jacob to talk it out. But I think I got it, right
Joined my own meeting but it worked out. So I guess that's how it goes. I don't know. Is that how it works?
Yeah, okay join your own meeting and it pops in. Okay, great. Yeah, so yeah, I did it. I figured it out
I got the list from the from the
Thing and if yeah, so anyway, yeah, we got some more fun stuff coming up and
Please join in support us if you can if you can't support us financially currently understood
But please don't forget about the obelisk scheme
Just tell one person and one person only about the podcast someone you think would actually enjoy
Hearing about my glow-in-the-dark jizz and then see if they like this this podcast ever again ever
But you know, hey, but if the answer is maybe the answer is maybe have a scoop shot man, that's exactly
That's how we get our scoops for life. But anyway, we really appreciate all of your help both financial and emotional
It's wonderful to have all of you listening out there. And yeah, we're pleased you're listening
Oh lemur screamer creamer in the chat Lord
There were no Lord questions and lemur screamer creamer is sad that there were no Lord questions. I am too
I knew Lord was from New Zealand guys. I might have gotten a Lord time for another New Zealand quiz
Let's go get on it
Lord the answer to everyone
I want to thank everyone who supports over on our patreon page
Right now some folks have just simply gone from the chill our level to the three dollar level just to just to go with
The the rising costs we appreciate that other people sign up for the first time
We even got a new ice cream truck driver
Thank you guys
So thank you all for doing that so much
We really appreciate it if you want to support our
Podcast and you have within your budget to do so pick out a tier that fits your budget over at preaching fun com
Come visit preachingfun.com
It's better than hanging with your mom
Or if we didn't talk about Paul's jizz as much as you expected us to today head on over to fartsinabag.biz
Fartinabag.biz
Let's give them something to talk about
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com. It takes you over to our patreon page
We're for as little as three dollars a month. You can upkeep this show on the air
That's right if you think the show is worth more than three dollars a month
Don't go there or knowing to go there do go there if you think the show is worth more than three dollars a month
Yes, if you think the show is worth less than three dollars a month. Don't even bother
And also we get it
Yes, thanks, everybody. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
We're for as little as three dollars a month. We love you and we'll see you soon