Oh hello there I am so happy you're here it's time to thank you the ice cream truck
drivers thank you so much all you ice cream truck drivers out there who are
the ice cream truck drivers well these are the folks that deliver that freaking
ice cream straight to your freaking ear holes I don't have a new list of names
to thank yet but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver by name at
this part of a future episode this month but in the meantime thank you to each
and every one of you out there who does subscribe at that ice cream truck driver
level we couldn't deliver the ice cream without you who knows maybe the life you
say maybe you're oh now here's a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice
cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go I'll get on the unapologize right
Oh yeah scooping over girl was just mentioning YouTube doesn't care about
swearing anymore and that does seem to be the case they have you know arbitrarily
just changed up the whole thing you say fuckity fuck fuck fuck so much you want
right at the top doesn't hurt a damn thing well then they deliver that fucking
ice cream straight to your fucking ear hole yeah baby that's what I'll go back
in and I'll go back in and edit that thank you thank you yeah no problem no
problem yeah Paul how's your eyeball doing okay so eyeball update I'll play
the theme eyeball update eyeball update it's a ball in Paul's head that he sees
through hey so left eye I'm left I Lisa Lopez and I went into the so optometrist
is the one to get your glasses ophthalmologist is the one that actually
looks at your eyes right I'm sure yeah let's say yeah anyway I mean
optometrist also looks at your eyes I don't know but they think of this yeah
let's go do we really know the answer to this question like in our hearts
ophthalmologist is the one that knows how to really get in there and do the
thing yeah Larry in the chat is saying ophthalmology is surgery yeah so I went
to the ophthalmologist according to our juniors let's see a Shaman I don't think
you're gonna ever heal until you start having more you need to wear them in
your eye RFK jr. I wasn't gonna bring you in until later in the guest segment of
the show but it's good to have you
I have to say some of your information seems to be outdated from what I
understand medical accuracy how many blood leadings did you do today
I personally have 18 leeches on my scrotum right now yeah but not for health
reasons personal pleasure the Kennedy curse is ball leeches I have
misunderstood what the Kennedy curse was so how's your eye okay so it hadn't
gotten any worse which is good good good over two days or whatever the guy looked
at it very intently right eye is fine still the fact that it's only in the one
eye it is possible that I have some back and forth blood flow issues so just to
be on the safe side we're gonna get that my whole neck looked at for the veins
going back and forth there just see we've always had a great neck it's any
kind of occlusion anyway we'll see but he doesn't think that's it either he
seemed to be very very positive about it's just probably it's probably just
the stress of scoop fest the extra work the extra travel all the extra lack of
sleep all that shit and dehydration etc then yeah and then that's it so it's
probably just on its way to Wellsville it's healing up hopefully but at all the
blood work in the world done I don't have a they don't have syphilis and you
know and I'm not yet you don't have them yet I'm not diabetic well that's the
case with all those things I'm not diabetic yet I'm not syphilis yet I'm
not AIDS yet yeah we should start to go fun fun me for for Paul to get syphilis
oh yeah that doesn't cost that much couple hundred bucks right oh you're
paying a couple hundred bucks who's your syphilis guy I didn't get it for you for
you get it from a grizzly so fuck you and me yes you'll get
it there all right I'm gonna write a musical about this RFK junior getting
bare syphilis that's good I got the bear syphilis from carrying a bear carcass I
thought it would be funny as a joke what an asshole all right so yeah I go to get
my thing looked at in a couple weeks and then I go back to him in like five
weeks oh but the one thing that was kind of rough during the whole exam the
second exam the follow-up okay and was there with me the whole time again she's
great as far as even she got a little squeamish cuz at the very end he's like
okay I'm gonna press on your eye now it might be a little discomfort cuz you
don't you've never worn contacts or anything no no no so yeah I was like you
know just jamming on there and looking with the thing and so that that didn't
feel wonderful yeah and optometrist told me something when I was a young kid
first getting contact lenses and it is something that has stuck with me and
weirdly made me feel better for decades of my life yeah which is your eyeball
doesn't really feel pain so whatever you're doing like everything around it
like there are nerves around it that feel pain and everything right like yeah
yeah your eyeballs fine so mess with your eyeball like touch it do all the
stuff it's just weird and icky but it is doesn't hurt yeah so that's out but my
thighs thank you my eyes definitely not having stick your finger right in there
I'm good I'm good so I had him dilated what's the patreon level for Matt to
poke himself in the eye and I'm dilated on Friday
twice scooping guy and then I had him dilated again yesterday early in the morning so
dilating motherfucker I'm definitely like I'm feeling like oh geez so I think the
the the I don't know can your eyes just feel tired yeah I just feel tired I
slept as much as I could today and yeah look to do some more sleep as soon as I
can but otherwise rock and roll of Ayatollah everything seems to be okay so
that's good I appreciate everyone's concern and I'll keep you updated but so
far so good hopefully it's just a symptom of a lot of travel and what not
and I've got a little wheeze going on now I'm laying down reading my comic
books last night before I go to sleep and I and I hear this little squeak and
I'm like what is that squeak and it's me and it's coming from your eye that's my
life man that is my tiny little a tiny little squeak coming out of me every at
the end what the hell is going on just a little squeak at the end of my my
breathing is a small dog inside of you no at home I like sleep with my head
facing away so I don't let my like weird weird throat organ keep my keep my wife
awake it happens all the time I've never thought your throat organ was weird I
mean and I best throat organ in the business yeah so but yeah so there's
there's the update how's the boats treating you Matt oh man well the streak
had to come to an end sometime I got on board it was immediately demanded to
hand over my knife to security it did happen yeah holy shit this is one for
the books virgin nicer cabins stricter about not talking about your creeping
fascism and then that's what I said I thought this boat was about freedom I
yelled no it's not it's buffets this boat is about I mean anything for those
passion fruit meringue tarts here take my night areas yeah so what happened
that that's a that's a key part of your act no no they give it they give it to
me for my show so they keep it checked somewhere why before it when you're not
performing they keep it in the arms the arms safe but whatever they do they
really it up they lock it up yeah yeah and then some from security brings it to
my show and as soon as my show is over they come again I'm here to collect your
knife I said oh there you go is it possible that they are worried about
pirates and boarding parties and they're like we have to do this is just a
captain's general order like get all of the weapons in case we have to repel
border they actually said they said it's not a policy across the board said we
ran a background check on you specifically and we're taking the knife
away from you that's what they said stop it they did not
I was like wait this isn't this isn't as extreme this is too real it's too real
Roy it's too real yeah very good else right born in Jersey hand the knife over
pal yeah yeah that makes sense that's a yeah a cursory background check born in
Jersey get the first red flag right away first item first item on the on the
background check they didn't have to even have to read down the list no and I
had a other but we have other magicians here on board early foolish Kylan misty
night a little magic duo this guy time follow them on the insta this guy Tom
Crosby who fooled Penn and Teller with his Rubik's Cube routine nice he has a
he's one of those things we're like if you knew anything about him before he
went up he has a Rubik's Cube twitch channel that's very popular so in terms
of guessing whether it was a gimmicked cube or skill had you known about his
twitch channel you would have guessed skill but he fooled I remember that he
was he was one of the he went on and fooled them by just doing the ultra
violet yeah he had someone else makes of the cube it was ultraviolet he took a
flash ultraviolet flashlight to it and then stalled them behind his back yeah
and so with the with the cube they thought they guess that basically that a
cube can light up whichever way it wants you can lay it since since it's the UV
thing you can light it up therefore it's a right thing so yeah technically puzzle
cube good job scoot shooter Rubik's Cube is a brand name puzzle cube is the is
the term although most cube people still say Rubik's Cube even though almost none
of them use an actual Rubik's Cube right yeah actual Rubik's Cubes are a junky
clunky cube there are so many more well-made cubes by different companies
that people use yeah anytime you see somebody like holding it with one hand
and like spinning just a single plate of it or something like that with their
with their finger real fast that is not a Rubik's brand cube yeah I remember way
back in the day we got one from rice checks proofs of purchases did you ever
have a rice checks cube rice checks cube yeah no yeah what rice checks like the
rice checks did a rice check yeah the cereal that uh that we did a mail away
rice checks cube and it had like rice checks on the stickers and stuff yeah
was interesting huh rice checks really got into it man they even had a doom
clone towards the end of their I guess they're still out there but they did a
doom clone for cereal clone yeah you know you remember doom the hot the hot
hotness the game yes of the video game okay yeah yeah PC game yes yeah I
remember doom okay included a disc on there there it is oh yep it's in the
chat now there's the there's the checks the checks uh oh you beat me to it yep
and there was a doom clone that they came out with checks quest checks quest
and that came as like a CD on the packaging there it is there's checks
quest wait someone in chat saying my uncle made that game get out of here
what is happening James T scoop James T scoop is saying that get out is that for
real that your uncle worked on checks quest that's kind of James T scoop could
you unmute yourself hey sorry one second we gotta get out of my office oh if she
talks about her uncle in her office she gets she has to call the cops yeah they
put her right down um but yeah yeah he's uh well he's not my uncle anymore he
divorced my aunt um don't bring up his name at a family reunion I'll just say
that okay okay once he invented the checks game you know he all the power
and fame went to his head he went out fun that's right that's right the lander
he's a little nutty according to my dad but yeah no he's my my cousin's he's
their dad and his son is a big game developer now and yeah pretty cool that
always got me a lot of points with the boys in elementary school so you know
I'm sure well yeah because all those all those boys in elementary school they
were all just hard for rice checks all the time god damn it give me that rice
checks yeah James T scoop don't give away where you keep your private checks
memorabilia collection on air it might get robbed by those NFL players well
that's really cool what a small world huh how often have you ever bring up in
conversation with people I wish I could say not often but I have so little that
I can drive about also check I can say I brought it up last check quest was
monumental monumental I say yeah I mean yeah it's all in if people do that um
yeah when people aren't related to the guy that made you I mean like I said a
lot of people think that's pretty damn cool so yeah I'm fairly certain
I'm 90% sure that might have been the very first free video game ever given
with a product oh just saying certainly the first free video game given with a
cereal I gotta believe well apparently he wrote up he wrote a book his name's John
Romero and my aunt is not stop it wait a minute stop it stop it stop it I didn't
know who you were talking about John Romero is your uncle yeah former uncle
oh fucking look hold on oh my god Paul is leaving it'd be great like if like
Paul's care just backed up like into a wall and like through a wall like Kool-Aid
man and just kept going all keeps us there Paul it's coming Paul keeps another
room he also has a hidden Romero vault holy crap where it is you guys have any
idea John Romero is the number two guy it's John Carmack and John Romero the
rice checks you the price checks thing isn't even he that's not even that's not
even no okay this is this is the book Masters of Doom look so Masters of Doom
is all about the incredible success of Romero and Carmack motherfuckers fuck you
guys fuck you guys John Romero is a seminal he is a seminal character in
video game history at large yeah that's right he is he's incredibly important no
no no no no no no no no he's still yeah you know no he's one of the more
important video game guys I talked about ever so he finally left id he left it
kind of early and seems like he has a hand leaving am I right James T scoop
does seem to be well he started his own thing and he fucked up because his his
big game Daikatana was a massive failure they put tons of money into the into the
advertising and everything so the but the big advertising push in many of the
print ads was in you know in September whenever the game was coming out John
Romero is about to make you his bitch that was that was that was the tagline
because he had such cache among first-person shooter fans but then the
game the game tanked so were you around when Daikatana came out was that part of
why you left because the failure Daikatana everything went to shit in a
relationship after he lost all that money yeah yeah he well he oh gosh I
don't want to speak out of school here I don't get like on like fun speed or
something yeah I think yeah the first time he lost all his money is is about
the time they split so pretty early on yeah my dad always was he's just one of
those guys he'll lose his money but then he always finds a way to make it back
he's out living in Ireland right now with his new wife and yeah yeah yeah
he's still he's still very wealthy guy oh yeah oh you know he's doing all right
yeah he's but you're right he's gained and lost fortunes over the years oh yes
we got a I almost said email but we got a mail mail an invitation to a wedding in
Ireland from from some from Sarah Buren who has been a longtime listener and
apparently is getting married in Ireland so we should go get married and and see
Sarah in Ireland and and go visit with your previous uncle yeah that sounds
great yeah why not oh the wedding is in oh it's coming up it's at the end of
November okay to it's a rally at John Romero's house ridiculous yeah and so in
my my husband he's a software engineer and he you know works on the side makes
some games he's developing an app right now and so he and my cousin Michael
John's son you know they yeah they're talk about stuff and you know you know
anyway so they're pals so yeah yeah yeah that's wonderful but the same guy make
the game Quake yeah I don't know if I don't know if Romero I guess I think he
was yeah he was on with Quake yeah yeah yeah I just looked him up and it says it
says Quake yeah he was on with Quake yeah I mean yeah like I mean I don't
know John they're like really at all but mostly his sons you know but yeah yeah
it's fun yeah but that's funny though that you're that you're related to the
guy who made the the Chex cube yeah so even though he's not actually part of the
family anymore I assume that you're gonna get that sweet Chex cube money I
actually passed down to you when he dies I guess it's time to come clean I'm not
here as a cruise ship entertainer this is my cruise ship I'm on my own ship
which makes the knife think even weird
yeah I could oh Matt and I sound exactly the same no it's miserable here I'm in
st. John New Brunswick and it is just overcast dreary oh yeah the storm
cuz they're sitting right on top of everything and so it just makes my whole
head we had some they blow up oh oh Captain James T scoop thank you for
telling us about your previous family member thank you Captain that was
awesome next time I see you in person I can tell you some stories I don't want
to say while being reported fantastic awesome thank you I'll tell you who else
Captain James T scoop is gonna tell stories about next time she sees us in
person and that is the following spot they show Matt Madley's ice cream social
is brought to you by come on internet machine go go but you buy dirty Diana's
New Jersey diner that's right that's dirty Diana's New Jersey diner from
ranch ham in 2022 she wants some french fries with cheese but she ain't willing
to pay she's pretty hungry you know she ain't nothing today she's gonna step
right on in and get herself a plate she's really hungry you know this girl
she will not wait she says what pies do you have they say apple and peach she
says that will do give me one slice of each can I also get an order of fries
and cheese they say we don't serve that and she got on her knees dirty diner
Diana yuck this floor is gross this floor is disgusting gross why did I
kneel down yeah I'm not the end of that song when she realizes that even after
she did all that they don't have any other flavors of pie no that was it she
got her two flavors though she got one slice yeah that that was good that
turned out good dirty diner Diana that was good I made those rhymes it ended
well very happy very happy yeah good and you you killed it before I could ruin it
which is yeah because if I went further it would have gotten weird but it's
still good yeah speaking of throat organs Paul McCartney this week oh my
god I wouldn't saw a beetle perform this week it is a whole fucking thing how did
he do uh he is really good at that he's still really good at doing the whole
thing yeah the whole the whole putting on a show and singing and talking and
doing the whole thing he's had a minute it's like he has practiced and he's very
very good was did did you get graced with the double beetle shot did Ringo
pop in secret on this no Ringo Ringo wasn't in town he was in town the week
before and I was hoping that he would that he would stick around and make an
appearance but it didn't look like he did okay so yeah no no special guest but
holy fuck was the show good I bet they had they had audience cameras and
everything at one point the the camera stopped on somebody in the audience and
and Paul was talking to him and they had a sign that said that they had seen the
Beatles at Shea Stadium a while in 65 okay that's pretty and so he's like wait
you really thought you saw us in 1965 at Shea Stadium and she's like yeah if I
fucking well did it was it was so crazy the the number of people that were there
what it meant to everyone I took my mom my mom my mom came in town and and so
she came in town to see the Beatles and yeah I mean it it meant a lot to her it
meant a lot to me it meant a lot to everybody around us yeah it was it was
so fucking cool it'd be like John Romero showing up to my house I kept yelling it
out I kept yelling it out as a request of die Katana how you talk about a
seminal seminal creator there you go how big was your I have cancer sign will you
please say it was roughly the size of a sherry's berry it was a holy shit Paul
McCartney did because there were signs in the audience and he I thought did
something very smart which was he addressed the signs and they could put
them away put them down that's nice yeah yes I did like he did like five minutes
between two songs early on he was like oh we got some signs out here let's see
what they say it and you'd go through a couple of them and then when when he was
done with him then put him down there was one person towards the front that
they're holding up a large piece of cardboard yeah and all it said was Paul
McCartney saved my life can I have a hug oh my and that was one that he did not
acknowledge of course no cuz nobody sorry because the answer I'm sorry is
just probably not no no no no no no was there one song that he performed that
really put you over the moon or one that you were surprised that he was belting
out oh you know he's he's 80 what 383 move on I'm skeptical by the way okay I
don't think that Paul McCartney saved that guy's life at all I don't think he
did anything I mean I think he just was by coincidence this song maybe meant
something to the guy before he maybe it was gonna jump off a bridge or something
but I don't think Paul McCartney specifically you don't think that
renowned neurosurgeon Paul McCartney might have saved that guy's life you're
close you're close Paul actually the the guy in the audience I did I got to speak
to him he was confused I turned out John Lennon jumped in front of a bullet meant
for that guy he thought it he thought it was Paul McCartney this whole time and
I was like no I'm sorry that that actually killed John Lennon that the
bullet meant for you did kill John Lennon. It'd be really funny if he really did have a
doctor named Paul McCartney who helped his brain but then he's like
mistakenly thought it was the other guy so they're like like halfway through the
concert he maybe puts a sign I was like wait it can't be the same Paul McCartney
yeah this guy doesn't look anything like the guy that saved my life. This is a different guy. I should have known. I paid so much money for these tickets I don't think this is
the same guy at all. I feel foolish this piece of cardboard I feel foolish. I mean
this is a nice song and everything but this is not what I'm here for I was here
to give thanks to the person that saved my life. Cut a brain tumor out of my skull and I
wanted to give that person a hug so anybody doesn't want to hug me at all if
anybody has a chance to go see this McCartney tour now you would highly
recommend them? Oh yes oh yeah it's the got back tour there it was it was so much
there was so much going on. Is Sir Mix-A-Lot opening for him? Sir Mix-A-Lot is not opening for him.
Well that's a missed opportunity. That is I agree. Baby got back. You can do side bends or
sit-ups please do actually keep your body active as it gets older if you want
to keep that blood flow going. You are an octogenarian you should do side bends and sit-ups. I engage in a lot of Tai Chi I got an
afternoon over at the park. I got pool aerobics. It's pretty great. Keeps my ass in shape. I walk every day 4,000 steps a
day. I know that isn't 10,000 but it's still pretty good. Baby does bends. Baby's got steps. I'm in the bother slub. So I think I
mentioned to you guys that on on my greatest day ever last week I ended up
buying that Rock Band 360 controller that I've been looking for. Yes. So I
finally got it mentioned that I got a chance to test it and Jacob you'll be
happy to know my first game I wanted to test it with was Rock Band Beatles. Yeah
you talked about that last week. Because I loved that game and I loved the art
style of it and everything. So I get my old 360 going hadn't turned it on in
probably a year. Turned on my 360 opened it up put a disc in the tray closed it
up it goes meh meh meh and then it just says open tray and I'm like oh no. That
seems like a bad sign. It was a bad sign so I pressed it and opened it up and I
tried it again and meh meh meh nothing. So my 360 isn't reading discs and I'm
like fuck I got like 200 discs sitting here for my 360. That's the one system I've kept. I would like my
games to still be able to run. So I'm like oh shit. So I started getting really sad
because not only was I like well you know all my 360 games aren't working but
now I'm gonna have to go through all the hassle of returning this guitar. I don't
really know if it doesn't work or what but I I don't know how people existed
before the advent of YouTube honestly. So I go on YouTube and I look up this very
specific malady going on with my 360 and a short pops up and a guy does exactly
what I did gets that same error message open tray. He puts it back in as the disc
is going back in. He just reaches up on the top of the system goes bap bap bap
oh and then sure enough sure enough he just hit the top of the thing bap bap bap
on the top of the system and then sure enough it reads a disc and he plays the
game and I'm like well I don't know I don't want to be beaten on my system
necessarily but I but I do know like ps1s old ps1 models you had to flip them
over and run them upside down to actually get them to read after a while
and when they got old huh that was a fix so I was like all right well so I
looked again the next one that came up same error message same thing guy goes
bap bap bap it starts to read it I'm like alright fuck it what have I got to
lose I do the thing I put it in bap bap bap fires it right up my fucking
controller works with it I played a perfect round so the controller is very
responsive for a you know 15 year old piece of plastic hardware that could
easily get fucked up I'm like yeah this fucking works is great I was really
happy got to watch my you know the Beatles animation and all that which is
really really cool so I played a couple Beatles songs with my new Fender
Stratocaster and I was just I was just over the moon but yeah I had to fucking
Fonz my 360 just bap bap bap yeah got it going yeah yeah yeah no if your dog
starts feeling bad and you're gonna take it to the vet to have it put down try to
hit it on top of the head a few times I tried that with pirate maybe that was
what brought it no no no no no no no no dogs are doing really good thankfully
although I don't know what the fuck happened last night and gets up she has
to go in early every every fucking day it's something new with this place with
her she's getting called in early so she goes to let the dogs out at like four
in the morning it was and well no one had yet that was why she had to do it I
don't know what the fuck was in the yard but it ran over the fence she heard
crazy commotion it had knocked over and bent the bird feeder I think it was a
big fat raccoon but Anne thinks it might have been a bear who the fuck knows
bear a raccoon did not bend the bird feeder then it could have you have like
a metal pole on yeah the big metal pole big big metal raccoon didn't bend that
so yeah it might have been a bear is what I was thinking it might have been a
bear but the dogs went and chased the bear I love this yard yeah invited him
over he'd have been probably nice enough to give you this if you ask ask him you
know just say please can I have your bear syphilis they'll do it I want that
bear syphilis give me your bear syphilis
so anyway yeah who the fuck knows or could have been a deer maybe I don't
think a deer though because deer would have really had to jump over our big
fences as possible who knows but it was probably it could have been a bear but
yeah so a little little crazy we had some wildlife activity in the in the
yard on the housed drug addict who wanted to eat bird feed not completely out
of the realm but I don't think he would have bent it over like he did to get at
the bird food but I fixed it I fixed the the pole today so it wasn't that it
wasn't that strong I was able to straighten it out with my hands just kind
of you know so I think it could have just been a big fat possum big old fat
raccoon yeah I think it could have been or tiny raccoons in a raccoon costume it
might have been it might have been stranger things my god or a lot of tiny
raccoons in a bear costume you guys experiencing these full moons right now
there was a big one last night yeah these big harvest moons so as the moon
got fuller and fuller when I'd go into work in the morning good gravy are there
deer out at four in the morning they're everywhere I must have passed 16 deer
last time I was driving to work no three mile radius crazy do you think maybe
they're choosing you as a leader I hope so I usually drive with my window down
and I and I call out to them I say hey gorgeous hey beautiful just to make sure
they don't run into the road looking good out there I do I compliment you
look you don't run at you you look incredible I don't know what you're
doing but don't stop you're amazing I mean his whole life complementing women
has kept them away he figures it'll work for deer too I don't do it to women just
dear I get my this how I get my cat call fix I just can't call the tears I'm
driving hey that's at least a 10-point rack you're sporting you're amazing that
is fabulous oh yes girl you've had well he looks like you've got two little does
with you beautiful go mama do it work mama I'll tell you who else gets horny
watching Paul's deer and that's the following sponsor today's show is brought
to you by dog made doggie dentures for cats that's dog made doggie dentures for
cats that's from New Hampshire caveman in 2023
we're tired of the kiddies with their fangs so anybodies so we made dentures to
stop their shit hey it's me the dog dentist dent dentist D dog dentist I know
it's dad I'm working on the name dentist D dog dentist D dog dentist my last name
is D DEE my first name is Dennis I happen to be a dentist a DDS dentist D
dog dentist DDS don't let it get it to it don't get it twisted
dentist D dog dentist DDS has come up with a really great solution for kiddies
fangs fuck these cats trying to claw our eyes and bite our balls we I got these
special-made crowns that are very dull and thick and not only does it prevent
biting but it also impedes eating so the cats get thin and weak around us roof
roof roof so come see me Dennis D dog dentist DDS at your local earliest
convenience and I will fix your cat's mouth so it won't bite your dog anymore
a roof roof roof roof roof roof roof roof roof roof roof that's my dentist D dog
dentist DDS guarantee it's the hey scoops of check out the list that's simple
at the McCartney show they had a lot of you know there was video of old Beatles
performances and things like that and one of the things that was in there Matt
made me think of you and your kids okay and like specifically kids like more
specifically just kids in general today but but especially your kids you thought
you thought to call child protective services during the concert I think that
often I you know I probably probably popped into my head at some point
during the concert yeah how would you feel okay about things if your children
while while attending a concert or you know a big a big event for for somebody
that they liked if they were screaming in a way that seemed like they were in
pain just because the person was on stage you know what I mean yes yeah I
mean it it kind of struck me I don't have kids I don't think about things from
the point of view of having kids very often and for some reason it just struck
me at that concert that is a weird thing for you know fairly young children to
just be you screaming at someone because they are so overwhelmed with emotion
that was the children at the Paul McCartney concert screaming no no this
was this was videos of old Beatles footage when this was that's really hard
like there were children at the Paul McCartney concert several of the we saw
several of them with their parents and their parents were trying to keep them
awake because boy 13 year olds that have been brought by their parents to the Paul
McCartney concert not give a shit this is a thing of kids and their parents
going to concerts I never thought to go to a concert with my dad I don't think
my dad ever thought to go to a concert with me I guess we would go to like a
show or musical or something so maybe I don't know how different that is but it
is it is a thing that I'm hearing a lot more of which is like but he didn't take
you to something that he liked and just to be like you should like this is
Willie Nelson buckle up yeah well I mean they called it Beatlemania for a reason
it was straight up right that's what I mean mania yeah it was insanity it was
and I think you know it just goes to the repression of the society at that time
you know sure one of the few times people were allowed to really let their
emotions fly and I mean if you haven't been able to be free you know that's a
chance to really get it out it's it's not dissimilar from you know going to
like a church revival speaking in tongues and shit you know I yeah you're
probably right I also think like you know like it's really hard to relate in a
non-internet era where like there is no fix right like you like Paul McCartney
and he's not in this country that read this year right right and you can't go
on any internet outlet to do it you have to try to find a magazine or something
doing them do an article I'm just to kind of keep scratching that itch and
then finally you after you know however you probably only gonna see him was in
your life and you're there and you're gonna you're gonna scream your guts out I
definitely think that's a crazy thing I remember when pedmas filming apprentice
One Direction was staying at Trump Tower for their Madison Square Garden concert
and the amount of fans that were just sitting there all day just packed around
that building oh yeah member of One Direction to walk out of the apartment
was crazy we tennis with they were all waiting for Harry's time this was about
as famous as it gets right now yeah I think people go wild seeing her and
screaming for her definitely yeah but I think it's more yeah but it is yeah it
is rare yeah I don't know I was sitting there I was standing there during the
concert trying to like appreciate the gravity of what this was in the in the
60s and 70s and yeah I don't think I can do it I couldn't really wrap my head
around what that must have been I mean at scoop fest I don't think people even
moved to applaud at all right that's at least half on us do something to warrant
the applause I don't know is it is it kind of like a bell curve where the raw
sexual chemistry just gets too profound and then the applause dies down it's
like they're like they're just shocked into silence when they see us on the
stage are like dear God my libido is in a state of frenzy that I can't even
articulate I just have to I just have to sit here calmly or I may explode from
just observation yeah that's what that's what several scoops came up to me during
scoop fest and told me their libido is in a state of frenzy from observing
that's right sorry we're not applauding my libido is in a state of friends
never gonna clap never gonna give it up because of my libido that's in a state
of friends he said paralyzed by horniness that's exactly it no that's
crazy that hard to applaud with two hands full of cop how old scoops you
how old is McCarty 83 I believe it's crazy that he's still out there and
delivering oh yeah and putting on a good show putting on such a good show how
much stuff was new how much stuff was Beatles how much was wings oh that was
there was some wings there was a fair amount he made a joke at one point he
was like oh we're gonna play some of the new stuff right now well I guess it's 20
years old but it's still new ish and they went into it that's funny there
wasn't much that they played that I didn't know there were a couple of there
were a couple of wing songs that he played but he played for a long time too
he played for it was well over three hours that's crazy wow yeah oh Laurie
Ellsworth in the chat saying not not wings one of the best moments of the
night was a wing song when they played live and let die oh and oh the end the
whole place just explodes crazy it was so it's crazy how prolific he is right
because like we can bring up like four wing songs that are just gigantic smash
hits host Beatles really it's just crazy have you I mean Jacob yeah Del delved
into the simply having a wonderful Christmas time conspiracies I've heard
a little bit about these right what do you of course I haven't delved into these
I have I am vaguely familiar with what you're talking so apparently simply
having a wonderful Christmas time is actually about someone interrupting a
wiccan ceremony we're in there having like pagan rites I'm skeptical as you
should be as you should be it's really funny to have that song be a song of
interrupting is very funny like people see that's that's where it starts the
moon is up yeah so it's like it's the beginning of a pagan setup that's that's
there you know that you said it like it's a to B that's a to Z because I'm
just on the search for it is simply having a wonderful Christmas time about
witchcraft is the auto fill that's right when I said right of course and it says
no interestingly enough no oh oh did you ask Siri about that notoriously truthful that's Siri the moon is up wiccan
wiccan ceremony no other human would look up at the sky see the moon and
think that'd be good first line of the song nope see the moon I get wiccan oh
see the moon I get wiccan apparently this is all based on just a
misunderstood lyric all right okay sure so yeah the the the lyric that people
hear and thought was wiccan Paul such a staunch defender of this wiccan
ceremony conspiracy fine let's hit a lyric mr. smarty pass yeah so the lyric
that Paul is referring to is the moon is right that is what that is the the
lyric that people took to they glommed on to it that this is wiccan according to
Paul McCartney when it when interviewed about this I said no the lyric is about
the mood m.o.o.d. not m.o.o.n. the mood is right not the moon is right the mood
Paul I want you an rfk jr. say one side of the conspiracy theory and then say
which one the other side of the conspiracy theory is and see which one
seems more natural and rfk jr.'s throat well when you when you watch listen to
simply having a wonderful Christmas time well you'll find his own there are
moments when they're talking about sharing drinks and those could be tainted
with adrenochrome from babies you know simply having a wonderful Christmas time
that translates to I'm drinking adrenochrome from babies you play it backwards it's
uh we're drinking adrenochrome and now what's the other side that is just a
Christmas song yeah yeah for me and my family it's not Christmas until someone
brings a dead bear and I'm not dead yet you will be sorry that was the what do
you call that pole at Christmas not the Yule log
the Yule log yes someone bet that you're right the regular Christmas sounds more
believable the only way to win is to force you to agree with rfk jr. and then
I figured you would maybe that'll bring it back the moon is right fucking AI
character the moon is right the moon is left ah man there were so many good
moments in that concert completely full it was Allegiant Stadium Raider Stadium
in Vegas totally full but they so he did I'm looking at the set list now
they did band on the run from from wings they did get get back and then they had
a little moment and he would talk a couple of times between between some of
these little moments and then they went in to let it be and they started let it
be in a very interesting way and then they in that they filled out the song
and then they did the whole thing and by the end of it there were a couple of
times in the concert by the end of it you had about 50,000 people really
nicely singing along not singing at the top of their voices not screaming but
just like pleasantly singing along children that's right that's right now
this is an Allegiant was that was it where it was okay yeah there's an
Allegiant Stadium that makes and at the end of let it be three years old still
filling up Allegiant Stadium is crazy that's insane that was insane yeah and
seemingly just effortlessly just and also moving around playing a lot of
different instruments he played his bass is his you know famous he still had his
bass out yes famous violin style bass I played a couple of different guitars he
played two different pianos he played a mandolin and he played a ukulele that
had been given to him by George Harrison and he told a little story about how
George had given him this ukulele so he plays a lot of different instruments
like he's all over it but the end of let it be you asked if there was anything
that kind of hit me and the end of let it be definitely was was one of the two
times in the night that I teared up a little bit just just standing there and
and let it be yeah there will be an answer let it be and the whole audience
is singing that and at the end of it he did something that I thought was fucking
brilliant and perfect he just let that last note hit and as the audience
applauded they just stood there they just they just didn't say anything and
you could tell that everybody was definitely a little moved like the
energy in the room was a little moved and he just said you know there there
will be tomorrow just let it be I said man this guy fucking knows how to do
this yes like he knows how to do he knows how to tap in to the energy he
knows how to tap in to the room everybody in this room was was
seemingly listening to to this song and thinking about the the way the world is
right now and thinking about our brothers and sisters all over the place
that are having a hard time because of a great many things because of war in
different places of the world because of the the insane political climate that is
in the United States right now and lots around the world as well I know I know
it's an old guy thing you have to be 83 to really see the whole pattern and all
of the average age of MSNBC watcher yeah that's it and I mean man he you know he
hits the end of that and he knows what the whole room is thinking he knows what
the whole room is doing and he just lets him let's everybody sit in it and he
doesn't have to say it he doesn't even have to come out and and point an arrow
at it he just says like yeah this is this is a thing and it's shitty right
now and it's gonna be okay and then the the concert ended or that the the main
part of the concert ended before the encore and the last song of the main
concert was hey Jude which was another big of course sing-along moment I got a
good you know 360 video of the whole crowd exactly yeah and I finished that
and then they came out for the encore a couple of minutes later and here comes
Paul carrying an American flag and then the some members of the band are coming
out behind him one of them has the Union Jack they have the the English the
English flag there and one of them comes out with the Nevada flag because that's
where they were and then the fourth band member comes out with the oh I just
forgot the name of it the the pride flag with the with the newer extra stuff on
the on the one end of it yeah the name of that of that flag but you know it's
the inclusion flag pride progress flag there you go thank you latter-day scoop
and they just stood there and wave these flags around for a few seconds and let
everyone just kind of think about that and then they and they went into I've
got a feeling the Beatles I've got a feeling they played some of that they
played some sergeant peppers did Fergie come out did Fergie and will I am come
out for that one they did not they did not weirdly yeah weird yeah they also
did Helter Skelter live which was pretty great do see them do Helter Skelter was
pretty awesome that's pretty cool yeah man it was just it was good it was
touching it was entertaining fuck me Paul McCartney is good at what he
where were you in the stadium oh we were on the floor I my mom my mom had never
seen any of the Beatles before and so I wanted to do some some good tickets so
we were in the 16th row on the house right yeah they put the rain yes we were
we could we could see him they put the raider grass for you or they just they
put the tray away did you get to ride they put the tray away for some reason I
was the grass wasn't there yeah oh okay Pandora is absolutely listening to me
just right now it came up with a thing that says a notification just hit my
phone there's all of the Beatles every beatle song yeah I've been getting a lot
of Beatles recommendations oh no that's terrifying it's really exciting Jacob
and it's good to know that something successful can happen inside that
stadium so it's very nice that's right it can actually happen right something
that ends with everyone just feeling good and like they spent an evening out
doing something worthwhile that's good to know oh it was so fucking good
let's move in a little scoop mail here yes physical scoop mail physical scoop mail zippity
doo we got mail in a box I love it oh it's physical mail great for Jacob
bad for Paul and Matt cuz they're not here oh we got one from the coffee bean
scoop Matt we got we got some coffee from our friend the coffee bean scoop
gentlemen the stars did not align this year for me to make scoop fest but
hopeful I'll make it next year I hope everything is lining up well or that it
went well depending on when you get this that's Paul the coffee bean scoop he
also sent the second letter here the summer seems to be flying I hope it's
treating you all well I forgot to send you a package last month so I upped your
shipment this time that's right we got extra coffee this time nice I've also
included a little extra something for Jacob I like bourbon and Jacob likes
bourbon a big part of bourbon for me is sharing what you're enjoying with
friends I can't be there to share a bottle with Jacob so I'm sending you
some of what I'm enjoying this month this month's is Penelope estate 10-year
single barrel at 105 proof so we Paul also sent me a little a little tiny
bottle of bourbon here me to enjoy on my own so that'll be very nicely thank you
very much already mentioned Sarah and and mayor in a why oh you getting
married in Ireland here in November yes absolutely fantastic and then we got
something here from the OG scoop we got Andy the OG scoop who is in the chat
with us right now hey gang I have some small gifts sent by Amazon to the Vegas
address and also to Paul's place and I just want to send you this note they are
small tokens of my appreciation to you for all the laughs that you have given
me in the past and continue to do so thanks to all of our wonderful community
for all of the love that you have shown to each over other over the years thank
I love you all mentally and sexually fucking you in the face that's Andy the
OG and Andy Andy sent two books along with us here oh what you got there Paul
this is what Andy sent me he sent me a cool bird of prey would print out 3d
model that I can put together so moving forward we're gonna be specifically me
I'm gonna be hosting some extra zoom chats as a patreon reward and this is
gonna be one of the projects I'm gonna be working on during one of those zoom
chats for sure so thank you Andy yeah this will give me some more fun stuff
this and Lego type stuff will be some of the things I'll be engaged in while I'm
chatting to you guys during some of those meetups very well I might be
drinking some of the whiskey that I learned about in this book a field guide
to whiskey which is what Andy sent to me which is looks like a very informative
whiskey book here and Matt don't worry he sent you something as well and it is
fantastic he sent you a little golden book you
remember the little golden yes from from our childhood yes he sent you a little
golden book all about Bruce Springsteen it is a Bruce Springsteen biography
that's as a little golden book that's really cool I just got this are you
excited about the movie Matt I just got this note slipped under my door and it's
telling me I should check out some Beatles my music player oh my god uh no
no I'm not excited about the movie what do you what's the scuttlebutt is it is
it a Jared Leto and Skeletor kind of situation because that's got me in a
fucking tizzy Jared Leto is playing Skeletor in the new
Bruce Springsteen movie yeah oh well that way I would I would be out of it
too yeah it's got the dude from succession taking very big swings you
know the bear playing Bruce is like a really weird melancholy thing and I love
Bruce so much I've read I've read multiple biographies on him his
autobiography as well as other biographies I I love I will see that man
in concert as long as he's playing I'll see him when he's 83 playing playing oh
yeah uh he can't fill up a legion by the way that's the thing it's like that's
why I'm so impressed with Paul McCartney I don't think Bruce could fill up a
legion yeah I think Paul I think Paul plays less than Bruce though yeah I think
Paul gives audience less opportunity to say also he just does the big ones
arguably one of the most popular people in the last in the 20th century yeah I
think he's got a little more fame than Bruce yeah yeah anyhow I just don't I
just don't know what the I don't know what the story is just worried you're
just worried I don't know Matt has concerns about the Philips when Ray came
out I do like Ray oh yeah sure really great biopic and then they kept making
other ones that weren't as good afterwards right still about Ray Charles
just like then a bunch of others that came after it well we did get walk hard
from all that so that I was gonna say you have the John C Riley wall card came
out of that whole hard yeah we say like we I think one is very hard to make a
really good biopic and then - I don't think we have it like in our in our in
our in our you know artistic hearts taken a lot of biopics you know like I
think one comes around that we really just kind of like guess for what it is
right and so I this is coming right on the heels of that really well done
Dylan movie and yeah I just don't know if you'd get to do that twice that was
good that was a good movie and I agree let's cancel Bruce Springsteen
Jeremy Allen White's not singing right he's lip-syncing or doing whatever
oh that's that's rough - yeah because that was actually our boy doing the
songs right yeah Timothy Chalamet just straight-up became like a channel ever
ding-dong don't play man same with Jamie what's his last name we played right Fox
Jamie Fox Jamie Fox oh yeah you're right me Fox like what's a good straight up
went to like Ray Charles school just straight up oh yeah Charles I mean doing
Ray almost turned Jamie Foxx into a full-time musician yeah was Ray Charles
still alive at that time yes I think so I think so he had some he had some
actual direct firsthand - yeah yeah there's definitely yes there's definitely
footage of Jamie Foxx learning from Ray Charles that's cool in the in the
behind the scenes oh yeah Ray Charles died in 2004 so I hope I'm wrong but
everything about everything I'm seeing it makes me go like sure sure well I
mean at Tron Aries is getting in the 50s for scores right now oh no yes it's
also not a good Bruce Springsteen movie at all and not great but I get it he's
hardly it there's hardly any Bruce Springsteen in it you could barely call
it a Bruce Springsteen movie I don't get the Jared Leto thing the only thing I
think is honestly Jared Leto must have dirt on a lot of Hollywood place like
you know to place like an interplanetary you know neon motorcycle race based
solely on the ghost of Tom Joad album is a mistake it's just a mistake I was
really excited I'll be very honest with you I thought that was gonna be it yeah
just because they had so many of them first there were two that there were
three that there were four no it's all about soon I have to try to see it right
away because I think for the sake of this podcast I just have to I think as a
podcast yeah I have to but yeah we'll see how it goes
same thing with me and Tron Aries I really want to see those visuals with
that Nine Inch Nails music I want to go see it in IMAX because the soundtrack is
exquisite right it's it's some of the best Nine Inch Nails music in the last
ten years yeah so I don't know I watched it's really really good I watched F1
last night okay new Brad Pitt movie this is the Brad Pitt right yeah you did a
great job with a soundtrack on that it's really like felt like old school like it
was really a lot of scorpion songs very old school sports movie that like the
soundtrack was really pumping you up nice I liked it it was it was it was you
know I think we figured out so much with movies now it was it was a it's a sports
movie it's a it's a sports movie traditionally done well executed it was
really fun to watch and yeah I just I I'm looking forward to it it looks like
watch for me so last night did my first shows on the ship so it was like I was
staying I was a little wired so I just watched it to the end so then I went to
sleep it was fun how did the first shows on the ship go good good good good it
was it's a big enough room where I basically like couldn't get like I did I
did the show as written and so it went over well a lot of people laughed you
know me I like to get like something spontaneous happening in the show and I
want like another character to emerge that kind of stuff and I didn't get any
characters out of the show and so everyone else like you know could show
really funny I was like yeah yeah I was fine there's a fine show there's a solid
BB - this is good I mean even awesome crew here is also neat they have seven
movable giant LED screens that you can arrange or whatever order you want that's
a that's a nice plus it is yeah and so I created like a V with six LED screens
and put one all the way back nice and it was really nice to create intimacy with
the audience to kind of focus that V right there and so I got to perform kind
of center stage and not feel too small in the giant theater okay and it was and
so that part's super fun their crew is just unbelievable they just follow
every direction to a hill you tell everybody everything once everybody's
remarkably calm nobody's there's no crew that you want that's the juice right
there ship is next level it has no cruise director that they have different
people in different positions that handle things but no one's job is to
talk to our hosts to the audience so you just come out and do your show and your
show ends there's no extra hey this is what's happening tomorrow here's what's
going on later on tonight on deck seven blah blah blah blah that's that's cool
this whole ship is so different it's so it's like it's like it's honestly with
the cosmopolitan let's see it's it's a there's no fake opulence like there's no
like grand ballroom type feel to stuff like it's all very hip hotel nice little
niche nice things yeah yeah it's really it's designed from what I can see in
there it looks pretty cool it's oh it's the nicest room I've been put in as a
guest entertainer by far well that was the thing as soon as I as soon as I
asked you how the boat life's going I thought wait a minute is he just in a
regular hotel room oh yeah yeah yeah and then it has like different light
settings as an IP the whole thing so the whole room is controlled by an iPad I
guys different moods including get it all every room has its own iPad yeah
everyone was its own iPad I can turn on the TV open the curtains turn the lights
on and off everything temperature order room service it's all right here is
there a patreon level where we could give a scoop control of the lights in
your room on the ship we're just gonna keep hitting get it on get it on you get
it on and all the lights turn purple and then music comes on is it is there a
setting for real yeah that's amazing show us like he show us yeah let's see
man this is going to hit this is why we broadcast with this why you would oh my
god oh there is just a large button on the iPad that says get it on there he
goes Matt has hit the button oh my god yes oh my god it's just close just a love
machine and I won't wow nobody but you wow look at this it's like that moment
straight out of an 80s movie where somebody bumps into the record player yeah instant
sweat house I'll hit photo shoot and then that's gonna turn the lights super
bright yeah look at that wow it doesn't have a refractory period button where
just go to like a nice dark blue and some soft music starts playing you can't
read it because it's too bright says then is that close enough is pretty close
it's pretty good and goes to blue and the curtains do close again yeah that's
shit holy smokes all right go back to the get it on look real quick I don't
know what that means lights go up in this kind of purple and blue but okay you
want to get it on okay yeah give me give me that get it on look again I just need
to get a quick shot of something here do it there we go maybe damn it my screen
capture isn't working wow that is something else right there yeah that's
amazing I think I got it well technology is better every day clearly yeah oh yeah
this place just like it's really like about yeah there's not like excuse me
there's not like a pageant to the cruise ship do you know what I mean like
there's not like this kind of mark someone marching you along through the
cruise it's very you'd be your own thing kind of thing and even the showrooms are
all hold like 300 400 they don't there's not like a giant theater so like it's
just you're not gonna do the same thing as everyone do their own thing and it's
just totally it's the restaurants so they're crazy amazing restaurants yeah I
went to the test kitchen where they bring out all this experimental food to
you and courses they just bring it out and that was uh yeah it was just nuts
this has been a crazy crazy trip every I put a picture of me working Virgin and
like every every entertainer who hasn't worked is like seeding like I'm trying
to get there and everyone who has played Virgin is like oh so you're here now
like it's very like everybody everybody just wants to play here everybody just
wants to get the call all the time to play here like it's definitely like the
number one it is the spot yeah I get it I totally get it like I before I leave
I want to be like I will do anything to be here again I will leave my family for
any period of time I will come sit on your ship and your purple neon light in
my room let's do a little jock vs. nerd
I'm on the hunt for balls
on the hunt for balls
oh we got a scooper to come in as today from ML Kennedy the categories are that
was remade this time in English good remakes and confusion remakes always be
first I'll try I'll try that was remade for 200 this 1984 Ivan Reitman film was
remade by Paul Feig I think in 2016 but never mind that one we're trying again
with a soft reboot next March this is a this is an older scooper to here oh yes
I guess it is but thank you this is great what I have is this not next March
is this is this like a previous March that already happened yeah yeah this is
March 2017 or 2018 yeah oh well that's that explains why I don't know this I
pass Matt yes Paul Ghostbusters oh oh yeah dad dad dadada oh okay Matt uh this
time in English please for 200 based on a play 1978 Lacan's a folly was titled
this when it was remade with Robin Williams in 1996 the birdcage the bird
cage is correct let's see I'll try oh no it's Paul Paul you're up uh I will try
that was remade for 400 this 1987 Paul Verhoeven classic was remade in 2014 the
remake made 243 million dollars despite no one remembering it I guess crimes new
enemy didn't make an impression RoboCop RoboCop is correct ah boy I'm not doing
well on this one at all I'll try good remakes for 200 be afraid to be very
afraid this 1986 Cronenberg remake starring Jeff Goldblum and Gina Davis is
much better than the original 1958 version help me that would be Jurassic
Park Jurassic Park starring Gina Davis she was the t-rex she was the t-rex big
old lady that'd be the fly the fly yes she was the pilot Gina Davis Matt good
remakes 400 but the category number three there we go yes this film was
awesome in 1956 arguably better when remade in 1978 still pretty good when
remade in 1993 and pretty terrible when remade in 2007 as the film is about
duplicate replacement copies it makes sense that another remake is in the
works Oh I don't know pass that's Paul Paul would you know that is invasion of
the body snatchers invasion of the body snatchers is correct Paul is fucking
rolling with ML Kennedy's game today Paul you're up that was remade for 600
please this 1990 Paul Verhoeven film starring Arnold Schwarzenegger was not
based on a Stephen King work it was remade with Colin Farrell in 2012 you'd
probably need a perfect memory to recollect that that would be get your
ass to mouth total recall total recall is correct there we go I forgot that
Colin Farrell had made a total recall was that any good it couldn't have been
right I didn't see it let's see I'll try a good remake 600 this 1960 killer plant
film was made for about $28,000 and all its interior shots were done in two days
naturally the more popular 1986 version is a 25 million dollar musical I believe
oh wait does it oh it's a daily double I can say it all out loud I think it is a
little shop of horrors but it could be attack of the killer tomatoes in 1960
yeah I don't think it's yeah yeah yeah it's a little shop of horrors yeah yeah
there it is you got it Matt I will take good remakes for 800 Jeff
Bridges replaced John Wayne when the Coen brothers remade this 1969 film in
2010 true grit true grit is correct Paul I'll close out what that was remade for
8 Schwarzenegger was replaced by Jason Momoa when they tried to revive this
film franchise in 2011 the 2011 remake made less money than the 1982 film even
before adjusting for inflation tell me what is good in the box office that hurts
not this that hurts Conan Conan the barbarian I had no idea Jason Momoa did
a Conan remake oh yeah it's terrible and I love Conan I'm sitting here with the
whole classic run a Conan I got this I got these brand new ones this is the
brand show of hands anybody surprised that Paul has Conan toys at his
fingertips no hands no hands look they definitely didn't inspire each other
that's all I want you to know okay master's universe is not a ripoff of
Conan that's for sure good who yeah he should he's getting there well it's if
they do pull off that third Dune movie which I guess they are moving forward
with some production stuff he might that might be really interesting to see him
turn that because that's a crazy character arc for that character that
he's playing oh really oh yes yes yes yeah cuz he is good and the he's one of
the parts of the Dune movies that I like so far so do you know what happens to
his character no no I don't know anything about it so it's Duncan Idaho is
this okay character he plays and Paul Atreides love Duncan Idaho you saw how
you know they'd captured that relationship of how he idolized him and
everything is like that's what was that second name you said Paul Atreides the
main character oh okay that's oh the Timmy shit Timmy's channel have a ding
dong yeah okay so they were you know best buds well he ends up cloning him
over and over and over again and he gets Duncan Idaho gets real weird and
philosophical about shit being a clone it's interesting so yeah just like
Michael Keaton in multiplicity just like that exactly it's me I'll try this time
in English for 400 Spike Lee directed the 2013 version of this 2003 Korean
film the second installment of the Vengeance trilogy preceded by sympathy
for mr. Vengeance and followed by Lady Vengeance
what you heard it I I have I have no idea I I don't think I do I think I'm
gonna pass the mat
Matt do you have a go me no yes Paul I believe this is old boy all right let's
try it it's it's old boy yes that's just what it is yeah I didn't know he did a
score check yes yes the original version of old boys legendary yeah yeah the
Korean version that's fucking crazy yeah I never saw that that another one was
the what's his name yeah I didn't see that one Matt you're up I'll do with
confusion remakes 200 Rob Zombie remade this 1978 movie in 2007 then he made a
sequel then we ignored both those movies and all the other films in the
franchise to make a sequel to the original 1978 version in 2018 which
shares the same name as the 1978 and 2007 movies huh I don't know this but
that's very funny yes Paul Halloween Halloween is correct oh I
wasn't against Halloween but yeah you would have got it yeah if you had you
would have gotten more points Paul shit uh yeah confusion remakes before the
thing from another world was remade by John Carpenter in 1982 and called this
then in 2011 they made a prequel to the 1982 movie and gave it the same name
as the 1982 film of a thing the thing is correct this category specifically just
bread and butter to Paul here I mean this really is pretty much with four
questions left I have 800 points Matt has a thousand points Paul has 3,400
points guys and none of those are off a daily double there's still a daily
double out there could bring us could bring me to my knees real quick I'll try
confusion remakes for 600 in 1998 Gus van Santen made a shot-for-shot remake of
this 1960 Hitchcock film for reasons it had oh what's that guy's name that's in
a bunch of stuff it's fun I can't think his name it's fun yes yeah yeah this was
the remake of psycho yeah yeah Matt uh this time in English six hundred the
Austrian film funny games was made in 1997 by Michael Hankney Hankney Hankie I
think the 2007 American version was also directed by Michael Hankie and was
called this funny games I don't know is it the game I think it's the same title
Matt you think the same title I think I'll pass Paul how much does he think
it's the same title I'll go for it funny games what is funny games it was also
called funny games okay yep boy is this really is just made for Paul I've seen
the English you know I saw it and then didn't get the question right Paul yeah
oh no funny games is awful I mean it's great just watched it this morning funny
games is really good but it's horrific I never yes this time in English or
confusion remakes one of them is a daily double here we go here we go into zero
town I'll go confusion remakes oh if Paul loses now it's gonna be amazing
yeah here comes either I'm the king of all or crushed to nothing this 1988 film
series about murderer Charles Lee Ray comprised seven films the most recent of
which came out in 2017 then in 2019 it was remade without Charles Lee Ray but
now in 2020 the original version of the franchise is getting a 10 episode TV
series that is Chuckie is that your answer is correct you did not give me a
minute you did not give me a minute to ask what the thing was come on come on
you got it relax and I'm closing out the game and the category this time in
English 800 the American version of this film came out in 2010 despite the
original also being in English and coming out in 2007 Peter Dinklage plays
the main antagonist in both films huh American version of this film came out
in 2010 was this the station agent gotta be right I'll say the station agent now
it's death at a funeral no I think the station agents older than that yeah I
didn't remember when I saw the station agent oh well oh I got that wrong yes
and that is the game Paul eat down a victory 8,000 points Matt is in second
with 1,000 points and again thanks to Peter Dinklage I am in third with 600
points and that's from ML Kennedy thank you ML Kennedy if you want to send us a
scooper to your appraisal sprite Jack vs. nerd or an obelisk Jack vs. nerd head
on over to hey scoops calm hey scoops calm right there on the home page you
can send us any of those things go do it it's awesome all I was doing is trying
to find the category that blade runner and I thought Blade Runner was gonna be
in May an answer and I couldn't find it I just I just answered true grit and then
sat back and rested on my laurels thank you ML Kennedy I also want to thank
pendulum creating this podcast thanks Ben I just want to thank did you send a
list Jacob I didn't we don't have a new list yet but we will get one before the
month is October yeah yeah so we'll thank all the people who get to join us
on patreon all the time I can also get discounts no that's not true I should
say this is the shop but so I think we spend it before about explaining again we
have to stop giving out discounts to the shop because they wouldn't give us codes
that lasted long these are too many bots out there that comb the internet for
codes and offered to people right I'm sure you all have an app on one of your
computers that offers you to run a bunch of discount codes through and that's why
we can't offer discount codes to their shop anymore I thought about that today
I ordered something last night and I got that I got the thing today and as I was
ordering it they had a little like oh here's here's where you enter the
discount code oh this this never works I might as well try it and I looked up one
and got a 40% off discount code this is why our shop can't do this yeah but we
still have a shop available with all kinds of really cool stuff for sale check
that out over at store jingle dot com yeah but basically like this podcast is
awesome I mean you your podcast is something paid for very expensive
internet here as I'm out in the ocean just like a do zoom calls literally this
podcast would not be possible without the support that we get over at
preaching fun dot com head over there now and support us that is absolutely
correct
or if you also didn't know they had remade Conan head on over to farts in a
bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm it takes you over to our
patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep
this show on the air it's like Matt said we can't do it without you it pays for
everything that we are able to do here so if you like the show if you think
it's worth more than zero dollars preaching fun calm farts in a bag dot
biz those are the places you need to go right now to help keep this show doing
what you like doing and hopefully hopefully you like it because we like
it yeah I hope you do too stay tuned because we need to get into our very
passionate well thought opinions about bad bunny being the halftime show so we
didn't get into that very passionate anything you should get tricked into a
debate on online is whether or not you have very strong opinions about who's
gonna play for 20 minutes in between a football game a football game being
played by teams that are as of yet unknown I've started asking people who
do say bad things about bad bunny if they know where the Super Bowl is
actually being played this year so far the answer that question has been no
they don't know who's gonna watch the Super Bowl and want other people to
watch too so they get people who bring in a different audience than some of
his already gonna watch the Super Bowl it is almost like oh winner scoop in the
chat says I guess JD Vance said the NFL should drop bad bunny and hire Lee
Greenwood yeah as someone who has seen Lee Greenwood play live a couple of
times I'm just gonna tell you nobody wants that nobody wants that no no he
doesn't want to have to play live in front man that ain't Paul McCartney he's
like fuck this I'm retired yeah that it costs money to do like you lose so much
money in the Super Bowl halftime show and I don't think Lee Greenwood has that money
kind of jingle he ain't liquid like that all right well anyhow thanks for
listening stay safe out there we love you all and we'll see you soon
you
we're preaching like Johnson not JD Vance oh apologies to JD Vance JD Vance
I am so sorry