Hello everybody! It's time! It's time to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you
so much ice cream truck drivers! If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, preachingfun.com
is where you can go, preachingfun.com. Head over there, sign up to be an ice cream truck
driver, and you'll get thanked at this part of a future episode. We don't have a new list
yet, it's a new month so I don't have that new list just yet, but we will thank each
and every ice cream truck driver before this month is over. Preachingfun.com! That's where
you can go, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows? The life you save may
be your own. Here's a program. Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to! Great, let's go! Woohoo! I'm down to the bone in San Antonio. Oh! Make
the sound more fun than they are. I don't know if that's an expression or not. It's
time for Matt Madley's Ice Cream Social, sitting in San Antonio, that's Matt Madley, sitting
in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Madley, and in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy. We're
pre-preachingfun. Paul, you get a lot of action on the World Series. Yeah, I made all my money
back by betting on the team that spent umpteen bajillion dollars to get a Japanese man who
is an unparalleled phenomenon to just stand up there and do everything for them. That was
a surprisingly knowledgeable breakdown of the World Series, Paul. I mean, you can't
deny Shohei Atani. That guy is a once in a generation talent. I know, but now you blew
it because it was Yamamoto who was the hero of the World Series. Who? Different Japanese
player. We are back in the correct universe on the right podcast. Hey Johnny, do you want
to go to an ice cream social? We'll just start it over, here we go. Paul, you know who you're
talking about, right? All right, great. Back to one, everyone. Shohei Atani was amazing,
but in game seven, he really couldn't hold up on short rest and he was taking that again.
He had two hits, I think. I think so, something like that. He only won them four out of the
five games they needed. He's an incredible player, but they gave the MVP to Yamamoto.
Oh really? Yes. Different pitcher, he came in and played really well. They were all on
short rest. Like the Super Bowl, I made a lot of bets on the World Series this year.
I think I had 12 different bets going. Like the Super Bowl, I somehow lost all of them.
I didn't win a single bet out of all of my bets. Not one. And I had a range of bets,
but not a single one. I had weird bets, I had normal bets. Yeah, I had everything. I
had parlays, I had singles. Not a one. I'm bad at that. Well, you should know that I
was talking to my friend Ryre about making different Marvel character cards for me as
a magician because increasingly, I literally am going to stop doing this intro of my trick
with baseball cards, saying who likes baseball? Because the answer increasingly is no one.
There's very few people. No one. Nothing like starting a trick off with a light smattering
of applause. I just heard the latest episode of Player One just dropped and Phil was remarking
how his son came to him, his 13-year-old son, just the other day and said, "Dad, what's
the World Series?" Oh, man. Also, my kids came home, right? I got them psyched up in
the morning. You know what tonight is? Game seven. All teams of one, three games each,
blah, blah. And my youngest, as fancy as himself, a Dodgers fan out of nowhere. I think his
probably his friend in school likes the Dodgers. We've watched zero games. Yeah, yeah. They're
close to us. They're fine. When I was at game seven of the World Series, this is the time
to watch, right? Yeah. So they're playing with their friends. They're not home in time.
I'm watching the game by myself. Finally, they're ready to come home. I picked them
up from their friend's house. It is like the ninth inning and I go like, "It's the ninth
inning of game seven and the Dodgers have come back." They were down four to one. Now
it's four to three. And they go like, "Cool." And they watch for like five minutes and then
one says to the other, "Do you want to play basketball?" And they go, "Yeah." And they
get up and they go outside in the middle of the ninth inning and go play basketball. And
I was like, "Mother." And then I just started making them dinner or whatever. And then it
goes into extra innings. So then I'm now serving them dinner during the extra innings and now
they're interested because we're sitting and eating. Right. And now they're all in. And
then it ends up being a very exciting finish and they were like amazed. And to them, they
had an amazing game seven memory with dad of watching the end of the World Series. And
to me, I was just like... They started watching it around like the eleventh inning. Exactly.
I watched 10 innings without them. And then they came in, just top roped it at the end
there. I like that your memory of watching this World Series and their memory of watching
this World Series are going to be very different, but involve each other. Yeah. But yeah, so
I literally last night, I do this thing where I put baseball cards in a bucket and I have
this pole and I bring it out to the people. And I just had like five people shake their
head no with me. I didn't want anything to do with the baseball cards. Yeah. And I was
like, you know, it's the first and the last name, right? Like we're not, it's not like...
You don't have to be a baseball fan to participate in this trick. You're not going to be called
into the baseball fan's court tomorrow to sign an affidavit about your ability to love
and admire every baseball player. So annoying. Baseball fan's court. I was doing a show last
night, it was Tuesday and saw a smaller crowd, which is fine. I'm out in San Antonio, seven
nights a week for the old Magic Saloon out here. And so I'm doing the show, it's a light
energy, it's like a weird energy, right? Cause it's not that full. It's a big space. And
so... Oh yeah. And I'm experiencing what we're talking about here. And I finally was like,
I literally was like, "Hey, I'm sorry. You're at a magic show. You're going to need to like,
I don't know, do stuff. Like you might have to read a thing or pick a card or like get
up and touch a thing or say a thing. And I know that this is a burden. I know that this
is outside your comfort zone. I know you all came in here expecting to be comfortable jurists
sitting in the back and mildly observing magic from afar. And I apologize that only 20 some
out of you have showed up. I'm going to need you to get outside your comfort zone and maybe
do a thing." Yeah. And I get this big laugh. And then I mess with a kid with my rope routine.
And then I feel like, "Oh good." Even though it's a small crowd, they're eating out of
my hands. I got them. And then I finished arm chopper routine. I go into looking for
a couple and as I asked for a couple, six people get up and just leave. Oh. Walk out.
Okay. Shit. I wasn't ready for that part of the story. Neither was I, Jacob. Cause I felt
like I had won the crowd back. Right? Like if I lose, if I don't have an audience with
me and something, and then someone I was like, okay, I'm having that bad night. When you
feel like you've done the right thing. Right. And then they're still like, nevermind. And
when it goes from 26 people, they all looked at each other and said, "Hey, you want to
go outside and play basketball?" Yeah. They go from 26 people down to 20 people. It hurts
the energy of the room, so to speak. It's a notable percentage. I was really in my head
finishing my show. Oh no. And afterwards, someone goes, "Oh no. Those six people are
friends with one of the women who work here." And they came by to visit because they had
dinner reservations and she invited them to watch the show and they said yes, but then
they had to leave because they had dinner reservations at eight o'clock. There you go.
Wish you could have made that clearer to the magician on stage. I was like, do you understand?
That I met all the reasons of the world. I was like, oh, they did say this, but then
you said that. And so I figured, do you understand the difference between people leaving because
they had an obligation versus people leaving because they were upset with the show matters
tremendously to the performer? The only thing I want is for the audience to not actively
hate me and leave. It's really at the top of my list. And possibly leave a negative
social media review that reflects on the theater that I'm playing and all this other stuff.
Was there a moment before they left that you thought could have triggered them? No. Just
so that the energy was, it was a low energy room, right? It was simply that. Like I was
just saying, well, you did have the new, you had the new bit in the baseball card thing,
right? Where you pulled out your own bat. Yeah. I just, I just showed it off. I did
helicopter it around a little bit. I did tap my penis on Mickey Mantle like I do. And then
boom, it becomes Ichiro Suzuki. The most magic one. Ladies and gentlemen, foreskin Joe Jackson.
Yes, I did put as many baseballs as possible into my foreskin. Oh God. It turns out the
answer is six, six baseballs into his foreskin. This is a, this is a, an old baseball folk
song that I play being Crosby. And I say, this is my sack of oranges. Jokes on them
cause they're red when they come out because of the blood. I actually had like one of my
quickest jokes ever. I tried to say one was named. She was like, you're wrong. You're
completely wrong. And I said, I'm giving me your name. She was foreign. I said, well
then break it down for me. And then she goes pre and I go pre and she goes, oh, I go pre
ush and she goes, yeah. I go, oh, that's like Sean Connery driving electric car. Yeah,
that's a good one. Yeah. That's right. That's real good. I was like, no one can walk out
on that. You can't walk out on that show on a Prish. It turns out that was incorrect.
Prish. No, some of that leaf. What the fuck you, what the room manager was like, Hey,
I know the energy was weird tonight. I'm going to fill a show report. Is there anything you
want in the show report? I said, maybe if we're welcoming guests via staff, they should
stay for the whole show. Right. Maybe that should be a policy or sit inconspicuously
in the back where it is a place where they could sneak out easily or something at the
very least. Yeah. Or just give me a really big heads up about it. Yeah. Maybe a whiteboard
in the back that you can see where if anybody leaves, they write down the reason that they're
leaving on their way out. I would have wrote it into the show. I would have found a gag.
Yeah. You know, like I'm not going to work with a couple. If anyone feels like that,
that marriage is rigged and for the government, please leave now. Well, that was a combo of
situations, right? I mean, that's, you know, when it rains, it pours. You get weird energy
lighthouse, a couple of people bail in the middle. It's like, what the fuck? Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you could look at it and say these people are leaving because they have dinner
reservations. Uh, and so it's really not that bad of a thing. Uh, you could also look at
it and say this magic show could have been so good that they could have decided to not
go to dinner, but they didn't. Right. It'd be amazing if they hard sold it and got to
be like, honestly, that is enough magic. Like that was incredible. That was plenty. I don't
want to taint it with another trick. I saw perfection. Jacob, I'm afraid that the only
thing that I can do now is like magic less, so I should leave. I'm speaking purely for
myself here, but a free magic show would have to be nigh miraculous for me to not want to
go get food instead. It would have to be, it would have to be something on the level
of like, Oh, that lady just apparated through a wall and, and ate her own shit and threw
a monkey 50,000 feet in the air. And, and, and then a bomb went off, you know, if I cannot
find your food, I will hand you a one foot roast beef. So then you hang in the balance.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Are we talking like a subway sandwich? What would be the
meal of dangle for you, Paul? What would be the meal that I'd have to hold back as a magician
to make you stick around, make me stick around? Oh, you might win this meal. Oh, a Bobby.
What about a Bobby? Bobby would, would probably work. I mean, there's a lot of stuff that
would work. Uh, like a fresh, a fresh bowl of chicken and dumplings. Oh Lord. Let's go.
Oh, I went to a place last night. Yeah. It had a South West chicken and dumpling soup.
So it had like corn and beans in it. Yeah. Yeah. I'm in, I'm in, in, in the most delicious
soups I've ever had. That sounds really good. The found the Foundry San Antonio's oldest
bar Oscar who works here. Yeah. Yeah. I, uh, had the day open yesterday. So I got me a
rental car and I bolted down to our friend, Brian brushwoods compound over in Austin. Oh
yes. Yeah. And I was like, I can't wait to sit in on great night with my pals, Justin
and Brian and Justin Robert Young was occupied. He decided that he needed to be in Washington,
DC or something on election day and couldn't be dinner reservations. It was an event. It
was an event with six friends, six friends in San Antonio. It was an eventful day. You
passed him on the freeway. Uh, uh, so, uh, Brian's like, yeah, no, I just couldn't make
it. This is perfect. So you can do great. And I was like, okay, well good. You could
have told me ahead of time. I thought it was just going to be the two of us. But I, if
you listen to this episode of great night, it's just me once again, trying to keep up
with Brian brushwood. Uh, uh, he is a very intellectual and, uh, and, and, and smart person.
And so it's me doing my best to keep up with him. Uh, we're doing it. I am, uh, it's going
from covert to overt, but I am trying to coax Brian out of retirement as a magic performer.
Ah, I, I, his kids are starting to grow up. All the reasons why he stayed home are starting,
you know, it's trying to go away and he, his stuff is so original and different and is
not performed by anybody else. No. And, uh, I, I'm, I am slowly trying to coax him into
just to maybe doing a live event or two. Maybe we can get a, a straight magic performance
from him at scoop fest next year or two years. He did. Right. Uh, how many years ago? A long
time ago. Yeah. Um, and, uh, yeah, I'm trying to, I'm trying to figure it out. I think we
should try to play comedy clubs. I don't think it's trying to play theaters. That's my, this
is my pitch to him. Are you, you're, so you're pitching a duo thing? I think so. Yeah. You're
not just pitching that he should go out on tour, uh, separate from you. Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah. No. Self-interest involved completely. Yeah. Yeah. Great. Yeah. Cause as you know,
I discussed this, uh, you know, I talked to a friend who's a manager and said, you know,
what does it take to play comedy clubs? And they're like, well, if you have 500,000 YouTube
subscribers or stuff like that, that helps and blah, blah, blah, blah. And so I'm trying
to build up all my stuff with social media. And then I looked and I was like, wait, Brian
Burschman has two channels that are over a million subscribers. Yeah. Also, I feel like
he's very funny and we haven't seen him do his thing in a while. So I was like, I dunno.
So, uh, I've, I've got him. He's, he's, he's harrumping about it. I believe I left him
going like, oh, that would be a life change kind of thing. We'll see. We'll see. We'll
see. But I had a really bad, Brian, I think you should do it. I think it'd be great. One
vote for yes. Yep. Brian, I talked to your kids. They want you to do it too. Uh, Rodimus
scoop is already saying that Josie and the beta cucks could be the live touring band
with your act. That works. All right. That'd be work. That would work. Yep. No, but we
need to do it. I would love to do it as a one-off as an experiment. And if it could
grow into something that happened more often than, you know, do all kinds of things like
add, do you add Paul to the mix for an improv set? All kinds of stuff. I'd love it. I'd
love it. Do you think that, um, that Bonnie is the, is the big tripping point because
of, uh, Bonnie's hatred for you? Do you think that could be a part of it? She just doesn't
want me in charge of the meals. Uh, she just wants to make sure that Brian's eating salads
and stuff like that. Sarah's married to that guy. Jesus. She basically said, don't eat
all of Brian's food. If I go, she said, don't. Now, Matt, Brian needs to eat too. You take
care of him on the road. Food for Brian. Hashtag Brian eats first. You know who else eats first
before Brian brushwood. And that is the following sponsor. Today's show, man, man is ice cream
social is brought to you by, Oh man. I just got a text as I went to look for the commercial
thing and distracting. Nope. I'm back on board. This is from chasing the dragon in 2025 rim
Tobin's three day course on infinite wealth, extreme health and super sexiness. That's
rim Tobin's three day course on infinite wealth, extreme health and super sexiness. I feel
like this is a bit on Jim Jobin. Oh, it must be. It's a rim Tobin here. I'd like to advise
you on how you can make your life better, faster and stronger in every single way. Are
you looking for that perfect sexual partner? Are you hunting for that great job that will
bring you wealth, but also give you time for a life work balance? Hmm. Are you also looking
to get a 90 foot penis? Hmm. I can do all of these things. Yes. The 90 foot penis is
the number one thing. First get the 90 foot penis. Everything else falls into place. If
you get a 90 foot penis, then you will get a job. Someone will hire you to be the guy
with the 90 foot penis. You can stand at the top of a mountain and drop the 90 foot penis
down and people will just watch it. Right. And people will pay you. And that will be
your job. Now, as far as sexual gratification, the 90 foot penis is very difficult to actually
get erect. That's what people won't tell you about the 90 foot penis. It's really hard
to get enough blood into a 90 foot penis to get it erect. It's not impossible though.
It's not impossible. What we've figured out is that I don't fuck people. I repel them.
No, we can use. Like, you know, we talked about slap cooking a chicken. Well, this could
be used for that. You can just whip that clip. Boom. 90 foot. Oops. Oops. How did you cook
this chicken via mushroom stamp? Two problems. Two problems with the 90 foot penis. First
of all, it is nearly needle thick. So girth, girth is gone. Girth is completely gone. It's
been straight to those taffy strings. Yes. It looks like, it looks like basically somebody
pulled out hair gel and just kept going. I knew when the genie winked, I would regret
my decision. That's it. So it's, it's, there is no girth at all. It's sort of like one
of those filaments that they use for optic cable. So that's problem number one. The problem
number two, of course, if you do get hard, it will exsanguinate your entire body. If
you're not here, buckle up. Cause we know there are 11 problems. That's the things we
have to explain away. 11 problems with this. There are only two, only two problems. Only
two. They didn't pay for enough ad space for a left fiber optic thickness and exsanguination.
That's it. Rim Tobin. It's a checkout. That made me think of, of the mummy and the skexies.
And I guess there's going to be another mummy movie, which is exciting to me. Oh, starring
Brendan Fraser, Brendan Fraser and Rachel Weisz. Oh, they're bringing back the original
team. They're both on, they're both on board. I was definitely being sarcastic. They're
actually bringing it back though. They're bringing them back. Wow. Yeah. Yeah. They're
not going to continue that, uh, that Tom Cruise mummy, uh, movie thing that they tried that
one time that whole thing, Tom Cruise, like rewrote the whole thing in editing and that
it was just really not understandable at all. Dark universe did not take off. What were
the three movies in that dark universe that just all fell to shit? We don't know what
you're talking about. I have no idea what you're talking about. That was their whole
plan. Uh, it was a universal monster reboot. They were trying to do a Marvel superheroes
thing. They called it dark universe. Oh, that's right. And so we're going to do all of the
classic universal stuff. So it was mummy. I forgot about that. It was mummy and Wolfman,
which was Benicio del Toro. And then what was the one with, uh, fighting round the world?
What's his fucking name? Oh, uh, Russell Crowe, Guy Ritchie. No, Russell Crowe, Guy Ritchie.
Russell Crowe fighting around the world. I'm Russell Crowe. I was like, I thought it was
Piff the Magic Dragon for a second. No, it was Russell Crowe. Russell Crowe did, which
one did he do? I don't know, but you just keep laying these out. We're not in this part
of the cinematic world. Anyway, it might, he might've also been in the Wolfman thing.
I don't fucking know. But anyway, they only got two or three of them down. Um, oh, he
was hide in the mummy. That's it. Okay. So he was going to be a Jekyll and Hyde, but
it never happened. Anyway. Yeah. It all just shit. They'd all fell apart real fast. These
people trying to make these big, you know, cinematic universes. It's lightning in a bottle.
We talked about it before. You're never going to get the same thing that Marvel got, which
is not going to happen. Well, I, this, you know, uh, people complain about superheroes
and blah, blah, blah, blah. The bottom line is that like what, like years from now we're
studying films from Iron Man to end game will be one of the greatest achievements of a movie
studio ever. Oh, it's incredible. But they, they did more and more success with that run
of films than most movie studios ever have. Yeah. And they were the first thing of like,
Oh, would it be cool if all these movies built up to one big movie with all of the stars
and stuff? And it just, it just never was able to be pulled off. But you're seeing a
lot of different types of movies come out now, you know? So, you know, even with your
horrors on from your centers to your weapons, at first we thought horror movies were done
because no one was going to see them. But now they seem to be punching up. And now you're
just seeing, you know, weird movies, like a one battle after another. And then, you
know, whatever the Channing Tatum with a guy had stuck inside the store movies coming out.
Like we're seeing like real swings for like different types of movies. Well, man, see
the Aziz and Zari Keanu Reeves movie. Oh yeah. I did see something. Oh, and what's his name's
in that too, right? Seth Rogen. Seth Rogen. Yeah. I am, I'm sorry to say, Matt, that first
movie I've seen in forever in the theaters I saw with you. And unfortunately our contribution
to that film's box office numbers did not, did not move the needle. Well, fortunately
our contribution to that film's box office is measurable. Yeah, I guess that's true.
They can count our dollars. The math is easy to do. They can absolutely count our dollars.
We know how much we contributed to that box office. Good Lord. On a percentage level we
can measure what we did. That movie lost so much fucking money. Well, it came out on the
month where everyone dumps movies. Right. But like this is the worst October in recorded
history or something like that. Yeah. So yeah. If you look at what it takes to make people
go to the movie theaters. Oh yeah. That's what I'm saying. Like I don't ever go anywhere.
I haven't seen none of the boxes. I haven't gone in front. Holy shit. I'm looking up the
numbers on Springs. They deliver me from nowhere right now. Uh huh. Yeah. It's a bad one. The
latest dailies, the, the opening day was $8.8 million. Yeah. That's a lot of money, not
for a major film. What did it cost, Jacob? That was $8.8 million over almost 3,500 theaters.
You know, they should have done, you know, like, like Kevin Smith did with Red State.
I can't find budget yet. I'm looking for budget. Yes. You know, Kevin Smith at first just went
out and did screenings and Q&A and sold tickets that were higher than movie price tickets to go
just to kind of check that out. And then once it made. He did a big podcast junket on that
one. He was on like a Corolla's podcast when it was brand new back in the day promoting that. Yeah,
you're right. Like Springsteen, if you noticed, he showed up everywhere to promote this movie.
Every event that they had, he should have played a few songs and people went nuts and all that
stuff. They should have done like a marquee theater tour of the, of the, of the movie.
And then you have Springsteen there. He gets to talk with more humor and three-dimensionality
about his battles with oppression. And then we don't feel like we just watched one giant downer.
You know what I think? I think they should have made a different movie.
I, you already know I would have rewrote the movie.
I mean, it was shit compared to, compared to what you've told me about him. Even just like,
Matt has told better stories about Bruce Springsteen. As soon as, as soon as
he told me that that lady was an amalgamation, I'm like, get the fuck out of here.
That's it. I don't understand. I don't understand at all. Like, oh, I'm going to make up this lady
that I had a relationship with and I'm going to come out looking like a fucking bag of dicks.
I'm going to look worse than almost anyone in filmic history. That relationship, he just looks
like garbage. There's a legendary story of Jersey boys when they're trying to get it made, right?
And they sent a script over to Frankie Valley and didn't hear from him for a while. And then finally
they tracked him down and were like, Frankie, we were trying to get you, you know, we're trying to
get the final sign off on this version, you know, the script for the, for the musical.
And he goes, uh, you can't do it. And they said, what? And he goes, you can't, you can't,
you can't make this musical. And they said, why? And he goes, cause some of the stuff in it,
I don't, I don't, I don't like. And they go, what don't you like? We'll change it. And he goes,
I don't know. And they're like, what do you mean? You don't know. And they go, you guys faxed it
over. My wife read it first. She saw stuff in there she didn't like, and she shredded it and
put it in the garbage. Oh boy. Do you think that's what happened? Frankie Valley's wife
shredded this script before Bruce could read it. I'm saying someone should have said that movie
script to Patty Ski Alpha before Bruce got to read it is what I'm saying. Well, uh, Philip,
the SC scoop is saying they should have Muppets in it. I think if you went back and reshot the
Bruce elements or just did away, found a way to CG Kermit in for Bruce, man, it could be really,
really funny. That would be a knock down hilarious movie. If it's just Kermit being Bruce. Yeah.
Just Kermit the frog going through all that shit. Oh my dad hit me. Oh God. The managers,
both Bunsen and Beaker. Oh boy. No, it has to be from this eight track cassette. You don't
understand the sound just isn't there. It just isn't there. Oh, I'm sorry. Piggy. I have to leave
you here next to the dishwasher and move to California. There's no way. Oh, ow. You bitch.
I'm leaving this one. Dishwasher crumples billows with smoke. Gonzo pops out of the top
with a chicken. You guys don't understand that the artistic force behind Nebraska.
Uh, so far all of the electric mayhem is basically out of focus in the studio.
Yeah, nobody would care. No,
doesn't seem to bother anyone at all. Listen to someone who's still down about $25 million right
now with the worldwide gross, uh, not counting advertising budget. So far they've lost about
$25 million and flying in, putting a Bruce for all these public appearances. Probably doesn't cost
that much. That's probably very inexpensive, but, uh, as someone who is this huge Springsteen fan,
I, uh, it did cause the release of this Nebraska 82 album, which is great. It is awesome. It's a four
disc album. And one of them is just him re-recording the entire thing with his voice as it is now as an
old man. Yeah. Hey, little pig, is your daddy home? Did he go and leave you all alone? It's my favorite
thing that I've listened to in a while. Is the current- I got a bad desire. Oh, Fuzzy's fired.
Sorry, Fuzzy. Hey there, Scooter. Is it time for work? You better tell us on time, you jerk. Oh,
yeah. I got a bad desire. What do you call the East Street band selling Christmas decorations around
the holidays? I don't know. Tell me, big man. Bruce Springsteen. Waka, waka, waka. That's pretty good.
That's, that's, that joke alone is better than the movie. Matt Donnelly has a better Fozzie the Bear
impression than I would have guessed. It's really good. It's very solid. Very solid Fozzie. Yeah.
Well, it would make sense that he would have a good Fozzie to my Kermit. That's right. That's true.
There you go. That's right. Now we, now we have another bit we can do in our shows.
Now if we play Pollywood Squares, I'll pop over into one of those squares.
No, Miss Piggy wouldn't have put up with Bruce's shit. That's right. Oh, yeah. First time he's like,
I'm depressing not answering the calls. Miss Piggy be kicking in that door and karate chopping a four
track slayer. I'm out of here, frog. I have things to do. This is bullshit. I mean, as we listen,
I don't know how many more people tuned into this, this, this, uh, this zoom. I'm much more famous
than I was, uh, yesterday. What happened? I went on San Antonio live and performed a magic trick
for the morning host. Oh, that's nice. How did it go? You did the, you did the whole, uh, this was
like a, uh, like a morning, uh, you know, good morning, whatever town show type thing. Good morning
San Antonio. It's San Antonio live is a good morning San Antonio show. And, uh, it's my second
time doing it. The first time I didn't talk about on there cause I basically almost fucked up both
tricks I did. And, uh, it just was like, it just was pretty, pretty mediocre appearance, except that
I was funny and did help sell out the rest of the week cause I was funny. Um, uh, uh, this time,
is this your card? You're doing the cups and balls, sir. So what they do is they have you come on and
do like the, Hey, if you have like a quick teaser trick and do a quick trick and then go to commercial
break and then do a real trick with you when you come back. Right. Okay. And so, uh, last time,
uh, I was there, I had like, uh, what I thought was a quick trick and they were going to like a
mega tease and they were going to do like me plus someone there for a dog shelter, plus someone there
advertising their new store or something like that in town. Right. And so we're all lined up and I'm
doing this card trick as fast as I can. And, uh, suddenly I'm taking up all the time and, uh, they
have to, I get, I get, I get the punch line of the trick in just the last second. They cut the
commercial and I just stare at the person who's been just holding this giant dog in their arms.
So sorry. And so Matt adopted that dog out of guilt. So now Matt has a Mr. Piffles.
So this time I'm there and I have this like pencil, I can put a pencil through a bill and
it looks like I rip it and put a hole in it and boom, boom, boom. It's all, it's all, it's the,
the dollar is fine. Right. But I literally was like, uh, uh,
turned to my friend Mia, who drove me down to the route, the manager here, uh, I said, time me on
this. And, and I did it as fast as I could. And she's like 28 seconds. And I was like, well, I
won't do it that fast on air. Cause I'll try to talk. So that one's out. Ah, the time for the old
miracle third harmonica sound. Perfect. I just grabbed her little index card. She's reading her
facts off me and I made it magically sound like harmonica. I handed it back to her. We went to
commercial break. No problem. This is a nice and easy. I get down there, Brian, I, it turns out
Brian brushwood is about to start selling the harmonica trick, the invisible harmonica trick
on, and I, and I literally, cause I, cause I need one of these. He was like, uh, and so I, I just
talked to him today and he's like, he's like, Hey, are you willing to film a testimonial? I was like,
am I? I've just been doing, I've been doing a testimonial for some magic trick for months.
The fact that you could profit from it's even better. Yeah. Um, I think it's funny because the
reason why Brian might be selling this probably because it's growing popularity. And I really
think I am instrumental in the popularity of this magic trick. You were definitely,
you have created a cult following for this magic trick for sure. Like I don't often take credit
for things, but this one is like, I definitely blew it up at magic live and sold it out at magic
live. And that's got to have created a wave of people using it or talking about it in magic
circles that something they're using, looking for more, uh, places to sell it. And they approached
Brian. So, uh, new business idea, every magic live, Matt decides what new trick is going to
be the huge new seller. And we then sell said trip at Donnelly, the king maker. Yeah.
This one looks like your nose is made out of rubber and it stretches out and snaps back.
All right. Like a rubber booger. You pull a stretchy booger out of your nose. Stretchy
booger is the worst clown I ever hired. Oh, stretchy booger. That was out of your pants.
I know I'm working on a new material. Oh, what? I'm afraid that you've moved on from snot to some
other kind of material for skin for skin. Oh, yours is more like five skin. Did you have some
kind of 90 foot penis going on in there? Good Lord. Yes, but it's very thin. Oh yes. I see.
Oh, oh, I have to make a long distance phone call. Can I use some of your fiber optic cock?
Don't get roaming charges. Oh, that's the least of my worries with your wiener.
Uh, you know, who else thinks I have a dirty wiener? That's the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Manny's ice cream social is brought to you by big Jerry's house of hoarding.
That's right. Store all your collectibles with me, big Jerry. That's from dead Laszlo in 2022.
Hey everybody, this is big Jerry. How's it going? Somebody bring me some more, more cake. Hey, anyway.
Come on over to my house of hoarding. I've got nothing but places to put stuff and places to
leave it. If you got something you don't want anymore in your house, come on and bring it to
by. It'll be fine. Oh, I just had a bunch of magazines fall over and kill another cat.
And her hay scoops to check out. That was my cat.
Big Jerry. It's big guy. Big Jerry. So I, uh, did, uh, a bit I did, but I do close up, which is, uh,
look for, it's one of those, one of my favorite kinds of tricks for you. Look at an envelope.
I put it in my pocket. They pick a card to do. Suddenly I'm not holding cards in my hand. I'm
holding the envelope and in my pocket is all the cards. Then boom, inside the envelope is their
card. It's a miracle. Um, something goes wrong with TV magic no matter what. Right. So I described,
uh, uh, almost messing up the last time I was on, even when I did the arm chopper,
it like got caught for a second and then went through and it was like a moment of panic.
And I was trying to, I'm trying to troubleshoot. I'm trying to brace them, all the little things
that go wrong with this, like this little, there's a lot of little touches to this trick. Right. And,
uh, uh, anything that happens in plain sight, so to speak. And, um, I'm anticipating all of it.
Um, and, uh, and I just go to get the card out of the pocket and I just can't get the card out of
the envelope. I'm just sitting there like, pick, pick, pick, pick, pick, just jammed in there. I
just can't, and I was like a little. It's, it's, it's an envelope. There's like the size of a
playing card. Yeah, exact, exact size of playing card. Yeah. So, uh, uh, and so I'm trying to slide
it out. I'm just like, oh, all the days. It's just like, so the only thing that's going wrong
is the actual punchline of the trick. The only, the actual payoff. That's the only thing delayed
here. You know, I'm picturing like dropping all the cards on the ground by accident. I'm trying
to picture like accidentally, uh, I've done this thing where I've accidentally pocketed the whole
thing where I have to keep a gimmick in my hand from like, oh, I put everything like in my pocket,
like a fool, uh, all kinds of things. And, uh, just, and then it was like, oh, it's going good.
It's going good. You forgot to grease up your card. I forgot to grease up my card. Yeah. I got,
I got a butter. I got a butter at my envelope. Well, everybody forgets something once in a while.
That's a, I, I, uh, had a little bit of time off after our trip to decompress.
And so I've been trying to, you know, just kind of straighten up the house a little bit here and
there. Got some stuff done. You do look very decompressed. I feel decompressed. Um, yeah,
but, um, I went out and cleaned up the Halloween decorations. Nice. And I was like, you know what?
I better put the Christmas decorations out or they're not going out. And I did it. I got the
Christmas decorations out same day. Whoa. You've decorated for Christmas. We are, we are already
decorated for Christmas. We've got our five illuminated corgis that it's not crazy. It's
not a big thing. It's just five illuminated corgis and, uh, a little strobe laser that shoots on the
house and makes sparkly, uh, Christmas colors. And that's all right. Yeah. Done. But it's,
and it's running. It's, it's all like lit up and everything. Our neighbors, uh, across the street
still have all their Halloween shit up. And I was like, I did it. I beat them to the punch.
And what's cool is now driving through the neighborhood, this is four days later, three
days later, since I got my stuff set up, I'm starting to see other trees. I'm starting to see
wreaths on doors. Oh, you started it. You started the domino holiday. I put the word out. Yeah. I
was like, it's, it's on this year. Y'all let's go. Let's put it up. And I also, uh, did I tell you
guys about you to have influence over magic tricks and Christmas decorations? I'll tell you guys
about the goose that Ann got last year. So, you know, uh, she refurbished it, right? No, this is
not the, that was the, that was the gnome. So this was a goose and it always wanted a big old concrete
goose. Cause it's just one of those things, right? Oh, thank God it's concrete. But what can you do
with a concrete goose, except dress it up, right? That's the whole thing is you have a goose. What
can you do with a concrete goose? What can you do with a concrete goose? I can put a hat on it.
That's right. Well, I finally got the, uh, set of costumes for the goose.
So now how does one shop for goose costumes? Go online and type in costumes for goose,
and you will get unlimited replies because people dress up their goose all the time.
It comes up quick and easy. Jacob's going to the internet. It's up. Yeah. Yeah. It's a lot of
costumes for goose. And so I looked and found a reasonably priced set and I went for it.
And it's, it, it has not let me down. Yeah. Uh, as a matter of fact, I believe,
yeah, I purchased one. Uh, no, I didn't go there. That's just one. That's just one costume. That's
high end right there. That's a Piff the Magic Dragon goose. Yeah, that's pretty great. It's a
Goose the Magic Dragon. Well, uh, our goose now has full, uh, different stuff for every holiday.
So I already did the pumpkin on it, did a jack-o-lantern. Now it is outfitted with a turkey.
Now it's a goose that looks like a turkey. Also the goose is named Duck Duck. That's the goose's
name. Duck Duck the goose. So Duck Duck was actually, he is our memento from the Michael's
craft store where we bought it. And it's just one more sort of emblem of the fall of capitalism and
the end of all, the end of all brick and mortar mom and pop shops. So yeah. Uh,
what, so it's a turkey now. Do you know what you're going to do for Christmas?
Oh yeah, it's got a Christmas. He's got a Santa outfit. Okay. He's got a Santa outfit. Then he's
got like a winter snowflake for February, for January. Then he's got a big heart for February.
Then he's got a, uh, leprechaun suit for March. Oh God, there we go. And then April, I don't think
there's anything like April, May. I think it kind of gets sparse. July. He's got a, I'm telling you,
it's only so many costumes. Easter bunny. Oh, I'm sorry. There is an Easter bunny. There's an
Easter bunny. There's a, um, a 4th of July uncle Sam. And for me, for me, you should dress it up
either as a, uh, a stormtrooper for may the fourth be with you. Yeah. Oh, that's good.
Or may dress it up like Justin Timberlake. It's gonna be to its head.
God, that guy fell off so hard. Nice. Great. What a chump. No, he's a chump. He's a chump.
He's the definition of chump. Come at me, Timberlake, you chump.
We actually didn't talk about Halloween yet, did we? I guess we did. I was about to ask you about,
uh, uh, trunk or treat, trunk or treat and, um, trick and or treat. Oh man. Uh, I had talked
about trunk or treat already. I talked about it. Yeah. I had an awesome Halloween. So my sister-in-law
came up, she brought a big old bunch of dumb, dumb, uh, suckers and we had a lot, enough candy.
We only had about a hundred. No, I'm already here. We only had about a hundred trick or treaters,
which was down from previous years, but it's still a lot. Oh, you know, tariffs.
Dude. And then we surprised her and we went right after the trick or treaters were done. We put
everything away and we jumped in the car and ran to the Pittsburgh zoo, which was having their
Halloween jack-o'-lantern festival. Uh, jack jack-o'-lantern extravaganza. I believe this is
like the third annual one that they did. And it's like a giant oaky cookie, but with pumpkins,
it was remarkable. This thing was incredible. They had thousands and thousands of jack-o'-lanterns
throughout the, throughout the zoo. It was wild. Okay. Uh, you could get pictures taken
Paul, various jack-o'-lanterns.
I'm going, there's my spooky picture of our house. It turned out really good.
Going the wrong way here, but, uh, yeah, there's me doing the classic with a skeleton doing the
classic. Okay. They did these really ornate jack-o'-lanterns sculpted by hand. And it turns
out they had like, uh, 30. What you're showing me is not sculpted by hand. It is. Nope.
It is. I'm telling you. It was sculpted, dude, these are cut out by artisans. It's like carved
into a pumpkin. Yes. This is a, it looks like somebody just put a picture on top of a pumpkin
and it's lit up, but it's like carved into it. It is carved into it. They do use a stencil,
but then they carve. But yeah, there's like a marker for some of the darker stuff on it
to make it really, but there are like 30 artisans carving these fucking pumpkins every day.
And because it's the zoo, there's a lot of animals, but it is wild. It is fucking wild.
It's really, I'm just wondering how much more care the animals could have gotten
instead of taking all this time to carve these fucking pumpkins. The animals are all away. There
were no animals out. The only animals we saw were some flamingos that were sleeping in their own
little thing, but then Jules, worst zoo ever. Jules and Vincent, pulp fiction, pulp fiction.
Yeah. It was really cool. It was amazing. And I didn't even get the, any images of the grand
finale. It was too overwhelming. There had to have been, I don't know, 10,000 fucking LED filled
jack-o-lanterns that were timed out to music and they were playing shit like renegade and stuff.
And it was all timed out to the music. I'm telling you, it was out of hand. They were playing
renegade and it was timed out to the music. Yeah. Renegade by sticks. Yeah. I believe that's right
with the, the word is out. Is that how that would go? Yeah. Yeah. They finally found me. Yeah.
I'm a wanted pumpkin. Yeah. It was out of hand. And it was just this huge wall that stretched for
like a half a mile. It was nuts. It was extremely cool. That was pumpkins. It was pumpkins.
The kinds of things, if you get a chance to look up the Pittsburgh pumpkin extravaganza,
just go ahead and look it up anywhere. But the Pittsburgh zoo pumpkin extravaganza,
there are, do not look it up at work. It is much dirtier than you think it is. There is some NSFW
stuff in there. No, it was really, really cool. It was good. It was, I mean, like really, really fun.
We went just at the last two hours of the, of the show and it was nice and dark. And so everything
was super shiny in the light. It was beautiful. And then Anne kept telling me, no, these are,
these are real pumpkins. I was like, nah, these are plastic because a lot of them were plastic.
But then she was like, no, these are real. These are real. And I was like, bullshit.
Turns out every three days they have to reshave those pumpkins cause they go, they go south of
cheese. And so they got artisans in there just cranking out pumpkins all the time.
And I am so far out on that gig and they have a huge, a huge crew of artists going and sculpting
these pumpkins every fucking year, every fucking couple of days. It was wild. It was wild.
Yeah. Oh, that is, that is painful. And just like you, Matt, the, the guy who is the head
gourd carver made an appearance on Pittsburgh today live or whatever it is. And he was on there
showing off his, his pumpkins carving skills. So yeah, it was really something. So I had a really
fun Halloween. Oh, great. Yeah. That's awesome. Also like Matt, there was a guy trying to have a
dog get adopted, uh, just off camera while the guy was carving the pumpkin. They ran out of time.
That's so much good shit at this, at this pumpkin fair. They had a, uh, a big s'mores
spot where the fire and six people from my show showed up at the pumpkin patch. Just the,
they left my show and went over there. Well, they were excited. They had s'mores to eat.
Holy shit. But no, we have reservations for s'mores in Pittsburgh. It's only about a 25 minute
drive from my house to get to the zoo. So that was really great and really fun. Are you going to
start frequenting the zoo more often? We've gone for a couple of special events now. And so I think
we'll continue to do so. They, they put on a real fun show. Yeah. All right. I was overwhelmed by
the, uh, the amount of work and detail and fun that went into that pumpkin display. I thought
it was going to be ho hum, but it was really, I mean, I'm overwhelmed by your description of it.
So I, I can just imagine how you feel. I just, I w I wish I had it handy, but if you get a chance,
please look up, uh, Pittsburgh, uh, Pittsburgh zoo pump, uh, Jack O'Lantern extravaganza.
Easy to not look it up at work and, and just look up that, that finale. Yeah. That's it's,
it's a, it's a very quick URL. And, uh, Paul's very easy call to action Pittsburgh, uh,
finale led timed out wall renegade. Yeah. That's how you got to look up dot org,
but it was amazing. Just amazing. It's one of those things that when you're there,
like I, I, I purposely was like, I'm not recording this. I'm not taking pictures of this part.
I'm just going to experience this. And it was really, really cool.
Rich scoop and chat says, do not go to Pittsburgh Blumpkins.com.
Oh, that's, that's our new Patriot site. Oh shit. Speaking of Pittsburgh Blumpkins.com,
you remember we gave away with our, uh, prizes galore. We had some dude wipes
that were holiday themed pumpkin, pumpkin scented dude wipes. Yeah. They were in spice dude. They
were dumped in spice. That was the whole thing. Dumpkin spice. Well, they've got a new flavor
coming out for the holidays that we just started getting in at the target. Oh no. Dingleberry.
What? Dingleberry dude wipes are the holiday version.
Are they, and they're Christmas themed? They're called, they're Christmas themed
and they're called Dingleberry. Oh geez. It's kind of nasty. I'm mad that they're skipping
Thanksgiving. I want, I want stuffing scented wipes. Stuffing scented wipes. Oh,
crazy cranberry sauce cranberry C R A M. Yeah. Jab them up there.
Just call it giblets. Oh, oh, it's better than fucking jingle balls or whatever the
fuck they actually do. Dingle bells. Yeah. Jim blitz is dingle bells, dingle bells,
Matt, you had a fuck ton of kids at your house the other day. I also, there was Halloween.
You came during a rush. Jacob actually came by the place and we were running, I ran by on my way to
work. Jacob came by right when I had about like nine kids line up for levitation videos. Oh wow.
Not happening throughout the whole night, but I, I did have, I did more levitation videos this
year than last year. I think last year me dressed like Satan really discouraged some people from
stepping up and doing it. And so this year I was dressed like Elvis and a bunch of parents got
videos of their kids floating in the, in the air with me running a hoop over their bodies and stuff.
That's cute. I hung out with Matt's neighbor and we watched Matt doing the levitation videos.
Matt around kids and their parents doing these videos, you can tell that Matt deals with school
children on a regular basis. It is spectacular to watch. Yeah. Uh, one is I don't touch them.
No, you don't touch. I noticed that you don't touch the kids at all, which, um,
you know, uh, not how Paul would do it, but still fine. Uh, well, I wouldn't talk to him.
I get the fuck out of here. Uh, get out of my yard motherfucker.
And then my, my buddy Tony was drunk with power running the clown jump scare. He was.
So I think we lost the thought. It was broken. My, my neighbor Gary and I, uh,
helped help Gary who abbreviated my car together. He helped fix my, he helped fix my clown,
my clown illusion. Um, and we discovered what happened of course was my fault. Uh,
there you, so there you go. Um, but, uh, so my buddy Tony's running the jump scare of my
kids trick-or-treating. My kids like running the clown jump scare when they got back from
trick-or-treating. Sure. I don't think Jacob, you were here. You weren't there when my oldest got
back from trick-or-treating, right? No, I was not. I didn't see your kids. So the rule was basically
don't jump scare little kids, jump scare teens. And even that backfired. I tried to one kid,
I thought was older than he was. I made a kid cry. I gave him all of the candy. I just said here,
take any and all. Uh, one was a group of teenage girls. They came up. We jumped scared them with
the clown and she literally just looked down and hugged herself. And then four friends said,
okay, we're going. And the four friends just marched her off. It was the weirdest. What?
Dramatic. I am done. I'm done. I don't give a fuck. I sit out in my yard. I sit out in my,
my place dressed up like a creepy fucking skeleton. I was going to say, Paul does get mad that people
aren't scared at Halloween all the time. It's a fucking scary holiday. It's supposed to be scary.
That's it's about the dead. It's about the horrors. Oh, I get so mad. It's not Christmas.
A couple of times we were going to go take, take a video of them levitating and also the jump scare
happened with the clown and they went like, Oh wait, this is rigged. I'm, I'm leaving. Right.
Pass on the levitation thing. And I, and I'd be like, no, no, no. So at one point we were,
I was levitating people and then a kid, uh, uh, jump scared. And then all of a sudden my,
my kid goes back to Katrina at the same time. It's like a big, big hub up in my driveway.
Okay. And suddenly a little three year old starts walking towards the candy, which is right next to
the jump scare. Yep. That's next to the jump scare. Yeah. So, uh, and the parents go, whoa, whoa. And
I go, no, no, we will not jump scare the little kid. Right. Yeah. Like, no, no, no. And then Tony,
my buddy Tony was also going like, no, no, we won't. We're good. Come have her come get candy.
Yeah. My son was drunk with power on the jump scare, but he w I was watching. He was doing,
yeah. He was getting the big kids. Yeah. We were just doing the big kid. Yeah. No,
he was doing it perfect. So he, uh, and so we do that, but my, uh, son doesn't see the little kid.
He only sees the teenagers behind the little kid and he wasn't paying attention. So he slides over.
So in front of a giant crap of which we, me and Tony, both were going like, don't, no, no, no,
you'll be fine. You'll be fine. Jump scare. You'll be fine. You like sexist clown horn blasts and like
three-year-old kids to which we all just turned the key and we're like, yeah. It just screaming at
him. Your poor son. I'm sure it was just mortified. He was like, what are you like really putting?
He's like, Oh, I didn't see them. The table was above. I couldn't see the kid below the table.
And I was like, it was all we were talking about. Uh, so that was maybe the low point of the clown
jump scare. Uh, there. Oh, disagree. Disagree. Did you get, do you see your giant skeleton?
Do you see your 12 foot skeleton? You have, uh, on your property, something that you now own
is a giant skeleton. Wow. My sons are begging me to just put a Santa Claus hat on it and leave it
up through the holidays. It's the way to go, man. It's the right move. They're right. It really,
it's gotta be a three 65 skeleton. You do, you do, you make him a letter. Oh, you got the HOA.
That's going to be trouble. Yeah. Yeah. I know. Unless there's, unless there's a bylaw in there
that says what kind of decorations you can have out for holidays. I think you're safe.
So at the end of the day, uh, this is the first Halloween where I were, I pro decided to calculate
how many pounds of candy I bought. I used to just measure in bags and then like cost code myself.
And it turns out I bought 50 pounds of candy. Oh yeah. There was a question in the chat earlier
about how much of, of your giant hall of candy do you still have remaining? I was able to unload
between truck and treat, which turned out truck and treat. They actually offered candy to for,
for you to give out, which I was like, that's, that's something I should know ahead of time.
Instead I just wish that I'd been in the email instead. I refused to be subsidized by the
government for my candy supply. I decided to thank you lift my own trunk up by the boot straps and
provide my own candy. Um, and, uh, it, uh, uh, I was able to unload 30 pounds of candy. Whoa,
that is no small amount of candy. That was like, you know, normally you start off with a candy,
you go like, Oh, just take one. And the most numerous, how much candy you have, you're like,
go ahead, take more. I had a time all all from the, from, from the beginning of Halloween to
the end. I was like, grab a handful more, go for it. Be selfish, be a jerk. Um, and, uh, still I
turned out 50 pounds of candy. Uh, so you're ready for, uh, for how much was left over? Uh,
20 pounds, 20 pounds of, all right. Are you going to take it to the food bank?
Yeah. Food bank, meaning my mouth. Yeah, that's right. That's right. Go, go, go. Yes. So, uh, uh,
yes, I'm going to find a place to donate it. I'm, I obviously go right up to San Antonio,
but I will, I will find a place to donate, uh, candy when I get back. Nice. Yeah.
Funny thing is that as running bit, anything that came by my house, I held up a bucket of candy,
said trick or treat just to keep giving it away. And, uh, that was successful. People,
people still take candy when you offer it to them. Oh, yeah, they will. I saw candy the next day.
I saw one of the best little tick tocks I've seen in a long time was, uh, uh, black barbershop
and the barber would get done with the haircut. And then right before he takes the bib off,
he'd grab a bucket of dumb, dumb suckers and offer a sucker to the client. And the client would
inevitably just crack up, but then they'd take a sucker and they were loving it. It was just the
sweetest thing. It was the nicest thing. That's like, we should offer each other candy in social
situations, much more often. I remember, you know, when you went to your grandma's house,
you got candy. Okay. It wasn't a special day. Exactly. There's, there's just such a dish.
We don't have such a dish for a reason. Exactly. Right. I think I need to keep
a more active candy dish in my home that I specifically think about for, for guests,
not just for me. Yeah. A guest dish, a guest dish of candy, but you know, not with the nasties,
but he started his hero's journey. I have, I have, you know, I do this for the biography.
We'll look back at this betterment of the world. Yeah. Starting to give me a good idea. I should
get in a white panel van, drive around and find kids who maybe don't have candy and offer them
candy from my van. Oh, that is, it's like a traveling food bank. You don't ruin the candy
dish. Biddle honey. Biddle honey ruined the candy dish. That and that hard shit that just melds
together into one candy glob. Yeah. That shit was nasty. What my grandma had, which was great
was she had the little craft butterscotch squares. Oh yeah. Those are good. Holy shit. I used to eat
those by the pound. I know you can't tell, but I did fucking love those things. Yeah. My, my
grandmother's a Werther's original person. I love, love me some butterscotch. These were, these were
basically like Werther's original, but you didn't have to work for it. This was like, you just
unwrapped. They were the kind that you would use in baking if you needed to, right? You just unwrapped
a little square and oh, oh my God. I love those things. Excuse me. You guys want to do a little
Jack versus nerd? More than anything in the world. Let's do some Jack versus nerd.
Explosion of butterscotch candy. No, not bitto honey.
We got a scooper coming down to us today from Hoopy Fruit Scoop. Hoopy Fruit Scoop. You don't
know what I got. That's vaguely familiar. What is that? What's that referencing?
Little Dooscoop. Anybody know Hoopy Fruit? I don't know. Hoopy Fruit. I don't know. Hitchhikers,
I guess. Scoop Jesus is saying Hoopy Fruit. Oh, okay. After 12 years and 1800 performances,
Rating the Rock Vault will close in Las Vegas at the end of this year. Less than 10 shows remain
at the Hard Rock Cafe at the Las Vegas Strip. Dicks is available at ratingtherockvault.com.
To herald the end of the show, here's a scooperty. So it is a scooperty, I guess about the show,
Rating the Rock Vault. Let's see. The categories are Rating the Rock Vault. All right. Paul,
you're up first. What you want? I'll go with Rating for 1200, please. All right. Rating
the Country Vault ran for six years in what city? Vegas. Rating the Country Vault.
Yeah, I think it happened in Vegas. Okay. Branson, Missouri. Oh, okay. Well, it didn't
happen in Vegas. Las Vegas of Missouri. It ran in Vegas, though. I think it's showcased here,
yeah, a little bit. Let's see. I'll try Vault for 400. If you jump to the end of the show,
what Van Halen song closes the show? That would be Panama. If you jump to the end of the show,
the Van Halen song at the end of it is Panama. I don't jump. There you go.
It's possible that I have a bit of an unfair advantage on this scooperty. I might have seen
Rating the Rock Vault more than you two gentlemen have seen it. Well, yes. I've seen it like three
times. No, you've seen it a handful of times. Maybe four. Yeah. I will do The for 400, please.
Name any two Las Vegas properties that have hosted Rating the Rock Vault. The Rio and the
Hard Rock. I love it. Yeah, Rio and the Hard Rock. LVH Westgate, Tropicana, Hard Rock Hotel,
Rio and the Hard Rock Cafe. Wow. Absolutely. Paul. That show got around. It did. Rating for
2000. I got to get back on the board. What is the maximum capacity of Allegiant Stadium for a
concert plus or minus 10,000? 35,000, isn't it? I think you're low. Oh, God. All right. Well,
I'm going 35,000. All right. 72,000. Shit, my butt. Okay. I would have been low too. I was
going to get 60,000. 72,000 people? Yeah. It's very big. I guess. I'll be the first to tell you.
It's very big. That's me. I'll try Rating for 400. Raiders of the Lost Ark came out in what year?
Plus or minus two years. Let's see. That would be 1980s, right? 1984. You think it's 80? Yeah.
All right. I'll back it up. I'll go 82. I'll get the plus or minus for two years. 81, right in the
middle. There you go. Matt. The for 800, because I crushed the first one. What year did Rating the
Rock Vault start in Las Vegas? Pass. It passes to Paul. Also, we couldn't get a window on this one.
2011. 2013. Poop, poop, poop. Oh, you were close. You were close. I was close, but not close enough.
Wrong, but close. Paul. Rating. Why don't I keep killing myself on Rating?
Which year did the Raiders start playing in Las Vegas? Plus or minus one year? 2020.
2020 is absolutely correct. We know that one. Yeah. That was the year everything went to shit.
Well, how so? The Raiders. The Raiders moved to Las Vegas. Raiders moved to Las Vegas. It's all took.
Let's see. I'll try Vault for 800. Who originally wrote and recorded My Generation?
Linda Ronstadt. Linda Ronstadt. Linda L.O.D. You want the name or just the band?
Like the name of the person or the band? Because I don't know who wrote it. Gloria Estefan.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's Gloria Estefan. I guess I'll just say The Who.
Oh yeah, it's The Who. The Who? Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam.
Just Cult Jam. Matt, you're up. Let's do The for 1200.
And which city did Rating the Rock Vault first perform? City of the Mind. The City of the Mind.
Pass. Paul, does that mean it has to start with T-H-E?
I don't think so. Oh, somewhere in England.
Okay. I'll say Liverpool. Show me somewhere in England. Liverpool.
I think it's actually somewhere in Mexico. Okay.
Los Angeles. We're both wrong. The Mexico of America.
Oh, Los Angeles. The Angels. So it was The. Oh, yep. Paul got it right.
I mean, I got it. Oh, great. I got one right. I'll go with The again.
For 2000. Daily Double. Oh, here we go. I'm coming out of the hole, mama.
Lead singers Todd Currens, who's been on this show, and Travis Cormier are natives of which country?
That would be Canada. Oh, Canada. That's true. And Paul is back to zero. He's still in third
place, but he is back to zero. That's all I asked for. I'll try Vault for 1200.
What song is originally by a Beatle and covered by G&R by Guns N' Roses?
Oh, oh, fuck. It's "Live and Let Die." Damn it. Paul McCartney, "Live and Let Die."
I knew that one. I just saw him at concert. I should have known that.
You just saw that. Yeah. I do love that cover of it, too. Matt.
I will. I got to catch up here. Oh, yeah. Score check. I'm winning 2800.
Matt is in second with 400. Paul is in third with zero.
I will do Rock for 2000. All right. Daily Double!
Drummer Blas Ellis of Rock Vault Tours with this holiday-themed rock show.
Oh, oh, oh. Come on. You can get this one. I know, I know. I just have instant
cognitive dissonance on it. Yep. Nicholas Newman, his wife drags him to it every year
when they play in Jersey. You know, this started in the really cold areas of Russia.
Manheim Steamroller. Siberian Orchestra, Trans-Siberian Orchestra.
The Manheim Steamroller, the Trans-Siberian Orchestra. Blas drives a steamroller in Siberia.
Paul. Vault for 2000, please.
Name the other Deep Purple song in the show besides "Smoke on the Water."
You know that other Deep Purple song. Oh, it's "In a Gotta Davida."
"In a Gotta Davida," the famous Deep Purple song. I don't know. Is it not?
I don't know. Is that your guess? Yeah, that's my guess.
Okay. No, it's "Space Trucking." What the fuck?
I've been spacing. I'm trucking, baby. Don't you know that I...
You remember when we used to make out to this hymn?
Name a song that S.J. sings in "Rock and Roll." Oh, come on.
"Your Mama Don't Dance."
Oh, what does she sing? She sings... I don't know.
She sings, "Here I Go Again." Is Barracuda in there?
My white snake. Barracuda.
She sings some white snake. Yeah.
Let's see. Oh, she sings some Rolling Stones. What's that song called? "Gimme Shelter."
"Start Me Up." She does "Start Me Up."
She sings "Brown Sugar." She does "Gimme Shelter."
"Dreams" by Fleetwood Mac, "Gimme Shelter" by The Rolling Stones,
"Heartbreaker" by Pat Benatar, and "Alone" by Heart.
Nice. What a comprehensive list.
Yes. Yeah.
It did take me longer to figure out one of the songs that she sings in that show that it should have.
That did seal the game for you, Jacob.
Oh, how nice for me.
Matt, you got rock for four or 800.
Well, it's tough. Fighting for second place.
Yeah, if I get it right, then I'm in second. If I get it wrong, I'm in second. It's tough.
That's right. So I'll go for 800.
You could get the third Daily Double. It's the third Daily Double!
It's not.
Todd Kearns of Rockvault regularly performs with this top hat-wearing member of Guns N' Roses.
Buckethead.
A young person brought up Buckethead to me a few weeks ago, and I said, I was like,
how do you know who Buckethead is? Like somebody in their 20s brought up Buckethead to me.
I was like, how do you know who Buckethead is?
They're like, oh, he plays all this great guitar stuff and everything.
He's really good. He's a great performer and everything.
Yeah.
And I said, did you know that he was in Guns N' Roses for a while?
And the look on this guy's face got hilariously huge.
I guess he was the guitar player in Guns N' Roses.
Yeah.
This would be not back, but forward slash.
Forward slash, of course, is correct.
And Paul closing out the category, end of game, Rock for 400.
Former ICS guest and Rockvault guitarist Rowan Robertson was a member of this metal band.
Oh god. In excess.
Was he with Dio?
That's literally what the question is.
I think he was with Dio.
He was with Dio.
Yeah, I got it. Oh, I'm so proud of myself.
And Paul got the secret $8,000 question correct, so that means...
Oh shit, that wasn't the $8,000 question.
No, I still win. I win with 4,000 points.
Matt wins with a max integral $3,200 and Paul has negative $1,600.
That's from a HoopyFruitsScoop.
Thank you, HoopyFruitsScoop.
Yeah, that was great.
If you want to make us a Scooperty or any other kind of jock versus nerd,
or just send us in some email, heyscoops.com is where you can go, heyscoops.com.
Head over there, make us a scoop mail, make us a jock versus nerd,
do a Scooperty, do a Price is Stripe, do an Obelisk.
You do all those things right over there at heyscoops.com.
We are running low on the jock versus nerds.
So go over there, make us one.
Yeah. In fact, pick a different Vegas show that just closed
and write a whole one about that one too.
There's a lot more to choose from, keep more every day.
We could just do a string of Las Vegas shows closing.
We can do a Las Vegas shows close that we've been part of.
That's right.
Good Lord, that'd be like two weeks of material.
Or some would say maybe 1,260 episodes.
It is the true story of this show, Vegas shows closing.
I want to thank all the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
Absolutely.
It's a new month, we don't have another list just yet,
but this is the part where we thank you by name.
It's one of the rewards that we offer.
So go to patreon.com/heyscoops and check out the tiers that fit your budget today,
both monthly or yearly options, yearly comes with a discount.
Was that web address too hard to pronounce?
That was a very long web address, Matt.
Just Google Pittsburgh Extravaganza Lantern Zoo animal.
Pumpkin Jack-o'-lantern zoo pumpkin.
No, go to preachingfund.com.
Sticks, sticks.
Or if you've already applied to be the new pumpkin mold scraper at the Pittsburgh
Pumpkin Zoo Extravaganza doohickeything.org next year, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfund.com.
It does take you over to our Patreon site where for as little as $3,
you can help keep the show on the air.
If you think the show is worth more than $3 a month, you can do that too.
It would really help us out over there at preachingfund.com.
And of course, fartsinabag.biz.
Thanks, Penn, Jeff, for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Penn.
And thanks everybody for joining us here on our Zoom.
And thanks everybody for joining us on Twitch.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
[MUSIC]
[LAUGHTER]
See ya.
Bye.
It's the bonus material for being a Patreon.