Oh hello there, I am so glad you are here. I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. It's a new month, I don't have a new list yet,
but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver by name before this episode starts.
Not this episode, a later episode of this show. You know what I mean.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, PreachingFun.com, that's where you can go.
Go sign up, be an ice cream truck driver, deliver this frickin' ice cream straight to people's frickin' ear holes,
and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
Ah, my voice just cracked there a little bit and I realized that I set my water down in a different room
and forgot to bring it in here, so I've got that going for me.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
We have this whole vamp part where we stay with whatever we want to go with your water.
That's true. That's true, I could have gone right now.
I could be back by now with warm, high drink, but alas.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting at sea, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, that's Paul Mattingly.
In Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
We are.
Hey everybody.
What's up, everyone?
We have a guest in Zoom today.
Yes.
As I almost said in churn, we have a guest in Zoom.
I love the new studio. It feels just like home to me.
Isn't it nice? We just wanted to really make you feel right at home.
Celestia, how are you?
I'm doing good. I've recovered from ScoopFest. I hope everybody else has too.
Oh, that makes one of us.
Paul, how are you? You were hurting yesterday, right?
I have had a week, gentlemen.
So I don't know what's going on. I don't know what's happening.
I was tired from ScoopFest. Got in Monday early.
Had a day to recuperate. Did laundry and such shit.
I say a day to recuperate. It was hardly a day to recuperate.
Tuesday night, I'm teaching my free improv class.
Wednesday morning, 4 a.m., I'm at Target.
So small window of sleep there.
Right.
I get home on Wednesday.
I do a Zoom meeting about a show on Friday, our podcast.
And then I hit the hay because I'm already sleep deprived.
I work on Thursday. I'm still very sleep deprived.
Get up on Thursday. Thursday is lawn mowing day.
Come back home, take a two hour nap, mow the lawn.
Is every Thursday lawn mowing day?
Then crash out again. This Thursday was.
OK, OK.
It's also pick up poop and trash day.
So those were my big things for Thursday.
It's good to have a list.
After I did my 4 a.m. work till 10.
Then Friday, finally, this is going to be the start of recuperation time.
I'm going to go to work on Friday in the morning and then Friday.
Well, Friday is going to be busy.
But Friday we were going to go to the optometrist.
Me and Ann for our annual.
And then we were going to hang out all day, drive around, have some snacks.
And then because she was off off, which meant she couldn't get pulled in,
which is what usually happens when we make plans.
And then I was going to go and do a show at Skit with the teachers in the evening.
And then I'd be free and done.
And then today it was going to just be.
Off, I was going to sleep in, catch up on sleep, maybe go to the comic book store, whatever.
Well, and yet when yet.
So we go for our annual optometrist visit and everything's going smooth, everything's fine.
And then the optometrist says, you need to go to the emergency optical place.
I'm like, what the fuck?
So apparently I have hemorrhaging happening in my left eye and only my left eye.
There's an emergency optical place.
Yeah, there is. Yep.
Pittsburgh health care is way above what you got in Vegas.
That's for sure.
And it's just optical only optical only.
Yep. Wow. Yeah, I've never heard of such.
I know it was pretty wild.
So but here's the well, I'll get to it.
But so I'm like, OK, shit anyway, it's not both eyes.
So that kind of negates diabetic stuff, which I've never had.
I don't have hypertension.
My blood pressure is not perfect, but it's not terrible.
Right. So, you know, that's not it.
It's not bleed out of your eyes bad.
It's not bleed out of my eyes bad.
My optic nerve is unaffected.
My coronial area is not affected.
I haven't had any vision problems.
I wouldn't have known anything if I hadn't gone in for my annual.
Right. Yeah.
So you can see you couldn't like in the mirror, could you see blood or anything?
No, no, no.
The only thing that's happening are literal pin, pin prick points of blood in my eyeball at the ends of veins.
You heard him at the ends of veins that you can't you can't see with the naked eye.
You can only see it with the with the optics of a microscope looking in my eyeball.
Right. OK. Like these things are pin sized splotches of blood.
It's not my my eye.
Aqueous humorous full blood or anything.
How did you know that I was little hemorrhage, little tiny hemorrhages, little tiny hemorrhages.
We go to the fucking optical specialist and we get some more pictures done.
And the nurse there is like, I don't know what this is.
I'm not an expert. I don't know what this is.
I mean, you're not an expert.
I mean, you are an expert. I don't know what this is.
So they don't know what it is.
And then it would be really terrible if you went to a doctor and they explained to you how they're not an expert.
Right. Well, then the doctor comes in, the actual expert doctor.
This is my first day, buddy. Really?
Sorry, I don't know what this is.
And I've been in this fucking thing. I read a whole book and this was not in it.
I've had my eyeballs dilate over here.
Well, it's because it's not in tandem that's throwing them. Right. Gotcha.
And I think it's probably a vascular thing. Like something's just not.
Did you tell them about your fight club?
Right. That was the thing.
I don't know. Did I experience head trauma? That's the other thing.
Like, that's the other thing they asked me about head trauma.
I'm like, did I experience head trauma?
Well, that's it. Good head trauma. You're not going to remember, right?
Did you tell them that someone told you that you had dust mites in your eyelids and you took a vacuum cleaner to one of your eyes?
I told them that. They said, no, that shouldn't affect anything.
But I did. I had, you know, I had a lot of travel. I had a lot of work, extra stuff, extra stress.
You know, we're, we're busy. Sure. Sure. I've been doing shows.
I've been, I've been busy as fuck. One-legged man and asking contest. You heard my week when it got back.
I got the scoops. He thinks it was your, your character changes during Pollywood Squares.
It's possible. Too much pressure on your, on your eyeball.
Any of it's possible. So the other thing is.
What made this an emergency? I mean, was there, what would happen if it was not treated?
Because I don't know. Only one real podcaster in the zoom right now and it's Celestia Ward.
Yeah. Because the, the optometrist believed that it could be a, a vascular issue.
Oh, Chris, thanks for putting us on with soccer, buddy.
Poor Chris. I hope his back is feeling better. So. Oh, no, we're running into medical elements left and right.
He's old. So I, she said it could have been a vascular issue.
So she was worried it could be something indicative of, you know, stroke or whatever.
She didn't say that exactly, but that's kind of, you know, it could be something he might be right in the chat.
She says you got fucked in the face too much at scoop. I mean, that's true.
Well, here's the thing. Some evil villain meant to put tiny nanite robots into your bloodstream,
but it was supposed to be for like the governor, but somehow it could be, it could be the Borg.
They had identical luggages at the airport and like, and they thought they were going to get nanites into the governor's.
Russian spies. Who the fuck knows?
And Paul does have nice luggage. So I mean, it could be, yeah.
You know, the Irish band did a lot of Johnny Cash songs. Did they in fact damn your eyes?
Oh, they have. Oh, good question. Good question.
But I can see through this burning ring of fire, so I don't know. It doesn't hurt. There's no symptoms.
That's the thing. So there's no symptoms. So I'm in the stirrup after having my eyes redialated, rejiggered.
Fucked with forever. Wait, the stirrup? Yeah. Your chin stirrup.
Yeah. You put your head in the chin stirrup and you press your face against thing and they're looking into a microscope.
Oh, you don't know what it's like to be in stirrup, said the doctor.
Okay. Not that kind of stirrup. Thank you. That's what I was going. It's a chin stirrup. It's not a new fetish.
A chin rest? New fetish unlocked. Chin rest, chin stirrup. I don't know.
I only want to be in stirrups now at the eye doctor. That would have been some shit. Put me in the stirrups doc.
It might come to that. So he's looking at me and he's asking me all these questions.
Do you have all these, you know, health things? No, no, no, no. All this other stuff. You vape? No.
Do you use, what was the wording he said? Oh, he said do you use IV drugs? And I go, IV drugs?
Ann was in the room with me. She starts laughing. She's like, no, no, he doesn't do any kind of.
But I mean, it was just such a foreign concept to me. I'm like, IV, what do you mean IV drugs?
Am I getting a slow drip of morphine somewhere? No.
Do you vape? Do you use TikTok? Have you lost all hope for owning property or retiring?
All right, you can knock Millennial off. He doesn't have Millennial eye.
I didn't know what the fuck was going on. So anyway, I was like, no, no, no, no, no to all of it.
And they're basically stumped. So they set up a battery of tests. So I went and got blood work today.
So I'm getting blood work today, which they're checking for like syphilis, AIDS, all this other shit.
I'm like, God damn it. I had to put in my eye. I had to put in my social security for an AIDS check.
I don't know. Anyway, so we're going through all these tests. It's a fucking mess. I don't know what they don't know.
They don't know. That's the thing. I get to be. This is just yesterday. Medical oddity.
This was yesterday. And then today was the text we get from Paul yesterday is, oh, it's a good thing.
We didn't record today because we're recording a day late this week. A good thing we didn't record today because apparently my eye is hemorrhaging.
Yeah, I wouldn't have been able to record anyway because I was busy with medical shit all day.
But I was supposed to go and perform at seven thirty over at skit with the teachers and I did it and was kind enough to tag along with me still.
We were already out there in the city. So we went ahead and performed. I didn't stay for the jam, but I performed with the poor you drove with one eye.
She drove with the other. You guys drove with both eyes. But let me tell you, every fucking taillight was a spectacle.
Oh, yeah. Christmas lights. My eyes were still fully dilated. Even I had shades on and it was still really crazy.
And I was looking my eyes were like saucers. So I did that. I felt, you know, I felt pretty good about making that responsibility and coming through on that.
How was your show? Yeah. And so then we looked fine to pull. We had a show. So let's get my lights went off. Yeah.
Yeah, there was lights. They did both things. There were games played. So anyway, I think there were people I couldn't say there were there were like 18 or 20.
So that's what you were told. You couldn't see. Yeah. Yeah. I will say this.
I love improvising with Matt Donnelly. Yeah, I really love it.
It's it's a special, wonderful thing that I have in my life. And there's really no substitute.
So I will say also, yeah, then today likes it today had to go get up early. So I didn't get to sleep in again.
I'm like, I got to work tomorrow. They said no restrictions on anything, but I still feel kind of weird. I don't know, but it's all good.
Again, no pain, no, no. I'm not seeing things different. I don't know what the fuck is going on.
It's just frustrating as hell because it is a medical mystery.
But you're a day history, even though I had to get up early and get my blood drawn and I would just and has been my rock beside me the whole time.
Really incredible. She's the sweetest thing ever. She's terribly, terribly worried for me.
She doesn't talk like that at all. She's way more worried than I am. I'm more angry than worried.
I don't sound like this when I talk. I don't sound like this when I sing.
I got to follow up on Tuesday. But aside from my eye hemorrhaging and having to get blood drawn today, today might just be my perfect day.
It might be my perfect day. So other than that, Mrs. Lincoln, how was the play? We get the blood drawn.
I love the direction. The costumes were immaculate and is feeling, you know, feeling the security at the booth could have been better.
She's feeling very sorry for me. And she's proud of how brave I've been through all this.
And so we go right after the eye thing, right? Right after the blood draw.
We go. We're out on McKnight Road, which is all the stores and fancy malls and stuff like that.
It's the busiest one of the busiest streets out there.
Everybody calls it McKnight Mayor Road because people drive crazy. It's big city. Anyway, so we're driving along.
And I'm thinking to myself, the places I've been on McKnight Road, we don't go out very much to McKnight.
And I was like, oh, did special boy get a special day?
Did I ever get a special day? I'm like, oh, and can we go to the ice cream?
Can we go to the exchange, which is a Zia Records type place, right? Oh, nice.
Nice. I love Zia Records where it's all like a good a good record.
Used music, used video games, used toys. I'm in hog heaven. I go and I see and I've been I've been itching to get a new rock band guitar because I that's one of the things I let go during my move.
I foolishly let go of all my plastic instruments and you can't get one for all of the video game rock band under 100 bucks.
And I need one for my 360 because it's got to be so it's got to be old. It's got to be retro. And when you start getting into that old 360 models, a lot of people didn't treat them great.
So I don't I didn't want to risk buying one online because then I'm out like 130, 150 bucks and I don't even know if it's going to be covered in rat feces.
So which is which is one of the songs you have to play on rock band rat feces.
Really as soon as I walked in the door I'm thinking you know what I should go and look about a rock band guitar because that's really the only thing video game related I need right now.
Rat feces rat feces. So I look up and they've got a box a full box of the whole kit and caboodle.
Oh the kit and the caboodle. 250 bucks. I'm like ah shit for everything but I don't really want the drums anymore don't need the microphone right now.
But then I look over the other wall and I see and I asked the lady I said do you have do you have just like a single guitar hero guitar for 360 and she goes why yes we do.
And she goes we don't get these in very often but this one just came in and then I look up and it's really clean and it's really nice and like oh shit.
This is where the nanites got the ball. This is where the nanites came in. This is it. It was 100 bucks so it's a splurge. But I've been trying to get one for a couple years now.
Four years since I moved out here because I really want to play Beatles rock band again because that game is just so pretty. Have you ever played Beatles rock band Jacob?
No. I didn't know there was a Beatles rock band. It's gorgeous. You should do yourself a favor. This reminds me of what I'm doing tonight though. I'll tell you what I'm doing tonight here in just a minute.
Well just look up Beatles rock band at some point on YouTube and whatnot. The visuals are glorious. Oh nice. Really pretty cartoon animation.
By the way Celestia got tired of this conversation and just left. Yeah she's there. She's there. She's still here. She's not. Oh no she left. She's back in now. She's back in now. Great.
Unfortunately we're still talking about the same thing Celestia. You can leave again. I'm sorry. It was still Paul's special day. Just explaining my favorite day. So we do that. So number one I'm already ahead of the game. Got my rock band guitar. I come out grinning like a fish and looks at me like I'm a crazy man.
I'll just say for a fact that if it were not for Celestia, a frequent guest and friend of the show, I'd be really embarrassed that we're taking this long to get to our guest. No no no. Celestia I appreciate you indulging me because I know you will allow me to say this dumb shit for a minute.
I just have one question. Paul, how much did you pay your optometrist to say you had a medical mystery? To give myself a special day? Yes. There's nothing I hate more than medical bullshit going on and having to get involved in the hospital. Sure sure sure.
It makes me insane. I lucked out. And I lucked out doubly because Anne actually really cares about the whole medical well-being of me. That's why married men live longer. That's exactly right. It's true. Just true. I would not have gone to do any of this already. I would have been done as soon as she said.
What else is going down with Jacob and Ice Marriage? I'll tell you that much right now. Nope. Well every time I tell Lestre I feel a little bad. She just hits me. Our next stop is the Ross Park Mall. The Ross Park Mall where gunshots rang out just the other night.
Yeah. Big drama outside Pittsburgh. Oh man. So there was apparently some gang bullshit went down. Anyway whatever. But by the same token we drive in there's a big line all around the mall. We're like what the hell is this? And we park in. And sure enough it's a pop-up Sanrio shop. It's a Hello Kitty cafe van selling special Hello Kitty merchandise. And there's just a line around the block for Hello Kitty. So you got in line. I did not.
I skipped the line and went right for the Lego store. Thank you very much. He put on he put on his sunglasses from the optometrist and carried a cane and they let him. If they had been selling if they had been selling Batsmaru merchandise possibly. And I mean I don't say no to some cool Hello Kitty stuff. That shirt of mine is one of my favorites.
What's Batsmaru? Batsmaru is the angry little penguin with the spiked hair. Batsmaru is what I say when I finish laying out my plan of like how we're going to pull off a heist. And then I finish with like Batsmaru. Fair dinkin'. And then we go on with that.
Batsmaru is the secret code word turn off the laser that's going to cut James Bond in half. So Celestia you're running skeptic camp. Oh sorry Paul go ahead.
Anyway no I bought Legos and bought me Legos which even better. I got treated to Legos and then we went to the whiskey store. Who's a big boy? Get your Lego. And got some whiskey. Then she drove me to the comic book shop which is in its new location. I got to go to the comic book store and now I'm back home. And we stopped at Panda Express on the way home. So I mean perfect. Perfect.
The perfect day. There was somebody that commented in the comment section that this is what happens to a dog like right before they get put down. Hey don't think Ann's not thinking about maybe this is it. I better get him some Legos before he kicks the bucket. It's possible. Anything's possible.
Get him some Legos. Up the life insurance policy. Let's knock it all out. The poor woman's been traumatized. She came out here and four months later her father passes. Not even four months. Like three months. It's just like you know. So yeah. Good point Paul. Good point. She deserves to take you out and get you everything you want. She's earned it. Look. Look. It's not that. She just. It's not not that. She just really loves me. I love her too. Like crazy. It's I couldn't do anything without her at this point so.
Anyway. Yeah. It's all good. So I'm having a pretty good day except for exploding eye. For whatever that is.
You know who else is having a pretty good day all except their eyeball popping out. That's the following sponsor. Oh. Today's show is god damn it. I hit the wrong window. No. The thing's opening up. Oh I've got it. Hold on. Today's show is brought to you by Johnny Australia's
Johnny Australia's commercial undersea navigation and telemet. Telemetry. There you go. T. L. L. C. Johnny Australia's commercial undersea navigation and telemetry. That's C. U. N. T. L. L. C.
G'day everyone. I know you're looking to go down under. Really down under. Down under the sea. Well if you need to go under the sea just look to me. Johnny Australia with his C. U. N. T.
It'll take you everywhere you need to go and places you shouldn't. That's right. My telemetry operations will get you navigating the wonderful world of Jacques Cousteau.
Yeah. But mind you don't run into those manta rays. They'll take you out in a second. They don't play around. They got a vengeance for us Aussies. They like to stab us in the heart with their spear for tails with that and that's it.
And that's all she wrote. So get a cunt and go swimming. Why don't you? Huh? Yeah. And her haze group's a checkout. Yeah. Get a cunt. Buy my cunt. Okay.
Celestia Ward is here. She's helping create and run a new skeptic convention. Paul, what Legos did you buy? So I got the Game Boy. I'm sorry everyone. We are out of time. Celestia, I'm so sorry. Apologies. We're going to have to bump you.
Well, no, I like that. You've completely overstated what it is. So I should just leave it at that.
No, Celestia is starting her convention. It's going to be cool. What is the thing? Tell us about it.
It's not a whole convention. It's what's called a skeptic camp. Oh, okay. Skeptic camp. And they've been doing these all over the country and Las Vegas is kind of like, well, we should probably do one because, you know, Vegas has got kind of a skeptical history.
We had the amazing Randy here. We had years of the amazing meeting put on by him by the JREF, the James Randy Educational Foundation.
I miss the amazing meeting happening here. I like seeing those people running around. They were a fun group to have around. It was cool.
And then Randy went ahead and died. What the hell? I know.
Did any of you get to pay for bacon and donut party? One time. Yep. My wife was in the band. So, yeah, I was at every bacon and donut party. That's right. Yeah.
I even got to the one at the old, what's the country bar that used to be down, like all the way down by the south point that's at Town Square now? Not Smokies, but something like that.
But I remember, yeah, they had it. They had like the full band down there and everything. Yeah, it was all great. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I have fond memories of all that stuff.
Don't you think where this country is chock full of skepticism right now? Don't we have enough skepticism? Oh, yeah. Everybody, everybody from top to bottom is full on critical thinking.
That's what we're celebrating. We're celebrating the fact that the country is going great. It's a victory lap. There's no misinformation whatsoever coming at it anywhere. Yep. Good.
Well, actually, you bring up a good point. So it's just a big pat on the back for the community. Just job well done, everyone. Good job. Gold stars all around.
It's just on the deck of a battleship. You're all going to be in flight suits. There's going to be a big mission accomplished banner behind you. It's going to be a whole thing.
There's nothing political. That's that's actually one of the saving graces of something like a skeptic camp. It's a place where we can talk about weird stuff like we're going to be talking about UFOs and gambling legends and how to quote unquote beat the house.
And we're going to have Elvis there. And we're going to be talking about like, you know, Area 51 and I'm going to be talking about creativity and drawing and skepticism.
And it's not going to be political, so hopefully people won't have their tribal masks up. And if you can teach somebody critical thinking by talking about like Bigfoot, then they can apply those skills to other things in their lives that might be a bit more weighty, might perhaps hold the future of democracy in their hands.
Now that I think that is a great theory. Do you are how optimistic are you that that theory is going to work in practice? Are you very optimistic? Because I'm a little skeptical of that theory.
It will never work 100%. Nothing ever works 100%. Sure, sure. It does make a difference. I mean, the most recent example is the RFK Jr. came out and said, hey, Tylenol causes autism, blah, blah, blah.
What? I didn't hear about that.
All right. So is that an example of where we should exert skepticism?
I don't know what your feeds looked like after that, but mine was completely chock-a-block full of social media doctors who have made a social media presence for themselves.
Every major medical organization, you know, the College of Obstetrics and Gynecology, pediatrics, you know, every branch came out and said, no, here's how you actually read the studies. No, please don't pay attention to what just happened on TV. Here's what doctors actually figure out.
And here's, you know, the whole history of it. So that's, you know, public education. Skepticism has always been the intersection of science, education and consumer protection.
We don't want people to get ripped off. We don't want people to take wrong medical advice from charlatans, no matter what position of authority they might be in.
And we want people to understand how the world works because it's pretty freaking cool, you know? Yeah. Right.
We want to know what the fuck is wrong with Paul's eye. Right, right, right, right. Absolutely. Yeah.
And we don't want conspiracy theorists on the Internet to answer first. Oh, they will anyway. I mean, they will answer first and loudest.
What will take place at the camp? At the camp? Well, we've got a number of speakers.
We have a magician, Joan DuCour. Do you know her? Oh, I love Joan. I asked you.
I asked you and you're like, oh, I'm going to be gone. So I forget what you've got going on on the 25th. But this is happening in October.
I would have declined anyway, because if you want people to speak towards research and education, I'm maybe not the best example.
No, no, we just wanted magic. We just wanted somebody to perform magic. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I mean, as a palate cleanser. Exactly.
Now, here is a fish. Does anyone have a guess as to where this came from? Or was it actually magic?
I would love to turn your act into a TED Talk. It's full on TED Talk.
It's not going to be magic. We've got to do that. We've got to come up with all these different topics that your act could lend itself to.
I'm skeptical about whether those are his baseball cards from when he was a child and if they are baseball cards.
Well, I mean, every magician you ever watch should be watched with skepticism. You should not be assuming they have miraculous powers.
But that's why skeptic magicians get along. But actually, that is the absolute truth.
Is that like it's not like if we if we were allowed to actually making people think we were magical, that would be a really weird profession.
And that is how some magicians pursued their paths over the years, especially historically.
But no, it's exactly like the more skeptical the audience is, the more the magic tricks really get reactions. Right.
So that's that's that's what you're trying to do. So you are relying on an audience for being intelligent.
Well, many, many magicians do. Some magicians don't.
Have you had the experience in your career as a magician?
Have you had the experience other magicians have kind of awkwardly felt really weird about where somebody comes up to you after and they're like, oh, you really have these amazing powers.
Hey, my sister has cancer. Is there anything I do, you know, where they have not honestly think you have miracle powers and then they immediately hit you with some kind of big life request.
Long term listeners will remember that someone wanted to become my apprentice at the end of one of my shows.
Some guy thought I was actually doing magic and then he was writing things down creepily on a piece of paper throughout my entire show.
They came to show me the things he was writing down and wanted to let me know that he was on the path to figuring these things out, too, and wanted to become my apprentice.
And I could not get him to leave me alone for hours.
This was in Elkton, Maryland, and I am still here, though.
I would still like to be your apprentice.
Jacob's not that wrong on the voice.
And it was a really strange situation in which I was conceding like, no, you know, get out of here.
The most embarrassing story of that is that I was doing pre show for Piff the Magic Dragon when I was dressed up as a giant like night king person.
And I would just work on some card tricks before Piff and the dog came up for the VIP experience.
So I did what's called a lie detector test where I have, you know, give people cards and say, I want you to say yes, no matter what, to every question I asked, you know, is it a heart?
Is it a spade? Is it red? Is it black? Is it the number card? Is it a face card?
And I have them repeat the answers over and over again. They say yes every time.
And then I go up, you know, three of hearts and they go, oh, you nailed it.
And a guy was like, hey, I teach psychology at my high school.
Could you maybe go over some of the principles you used for that?
And I could maybe use it in my school. And I was like, oh, buddy, the guy dressed like a knight doing pre show for a dog is not someone who has mastered body language.
Well, that's that's that actually hits back to some pseudoscience.
I mean, that they I don't know if you remember that show Lie to Me.
It was based loosely on Paul Ekman's work where he honestly believed you could detect lies just by seeing micro expressions and everything.
And yes, yeah, yeah.
The Secret Service has claimed to be able to do that for years.
The Secret Service claims that they teach micro expression reading to their agents and they claim that their agents are the best at seeing seeing lies happen of all of the whatever agencies around the world.
It always sounds like bullshit. Anytime I hear somebody talk about it, it just sounds like total bullshit.
Well, everyone has a version of a bullshit or lie detector in themselves, right?
We all know or think when someone's fucking with us or lying with us or whatever.
So it makes sense that someone in a government agency would suddenly exert a lot of ego and energy into that element of things.
But yeah, I mean, it's all you know.
And that's why like even like lately there was even like a government threat about polygraphing people for trying to control.
I was about to say Kristi Noem has decided to polygraph like a ton of people looking for whoever's leaking stuff.
It is now widely known. Like I think it's widely known that polygraphs do not work.
Yes, but not widely enough.
It is the subject of television shows, books, all the like it's it is as widely known I think as anything can be.
But it's not widely known that it doesn't work.
I was once hooked up to a polygraph by a police officer.
I have been to wait in a real situation. I was applying for a job with the police department.
This is like 20 years ago. Mine was not a real situation at all.
I got to the finals. Like, you know, it was like me and like five other people for the position and they hooked me up.
And I'm like, this probably lost me the job. I was like, you guys know these don't work, right?
And he's like, well, it depends on who's giving it.
And if the person who's giving it knows how to read those, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I believe you can be better than other people at it.
But it's not it's not it doesn't just work.
It can be used as a tool to leverage people to make them a sweat.
It's it's a thing. Yeah, it can be used as a tool.
But it's not it's not Wonder Woman's magic lasso.
No. Which policy just paid $250 for a kit and caboodle at a magic shop special day.
Absolutely. Wonder Woman has three magic glasses.
So one is the lasso of truth. One is the lasso of faith and the other's chastity.
Yeah, that's the truth. Faith, faith and chastity.
I can't remember it because absolute Wonder Woman is from hell now. It's awesome.
So that's great. Raised by Circe in hell. It's it's you have roughly 20 minutes of talking material that you can do on Wonder Woman now.
Look, I'm not going back into another Celestia layout. Let Paul cook. Let's go.
Look, hey, let's just hear that. No, Celestia, what?
A winner scoop in the chat while Paul's thinking of his question says that they failed a polygraph that they had 100 percent told the truth on and they have a stress disorder.
Yeah. So false, false negatives on that one. Yeah, that's that's an interesting one that I had not heard of either.
What's the most important question to ask when you're starting to approach a topic from a skeptical or critical thinking point of view?
What do you think is like the most important way to start a position of intellectual humility?
Because you could always be your own, your own bias. I like that skepticism is is really about learning that your brain is broken in any number of ways.
Everybody else's are, too. But your own biases are so powerful.
Well, that is that is a secret between like atheists and the very religious, right? Like religious people can't believe how know it all atheists are and atheists can't believe that people of faith have such faith.
Right. And so they both accuse the other of being an arrogant know it all all the time.
But but if you truly are coming at stuff from a scientific perspective, I mean, even just as an improviser, I've been doing it for a long time.
I still don't know everything there is to know about how to do it best. I still don't know the best techniques.
And when you learn more about theater and performance, you know that you don't know.
Well, you're describing Dunning Kruger. I mean, the fact that people who are experts get pretty humble about like how much else there is to learn in that right.
That's it. He sees a 20 minute video on YouTube and they're like, I know the doctors are lying to us.
You know, yeah, but that's where I live is in Dunning Kruger.
Play not that side of it. But Paul, you just ready Kruger. You live in Freddy Kruger. I do every night.
You're mine, bitch. Yeah, very, very scary.
Freddy Dunning Kruger is a whole nother. Somebody has to have done. What do you think? What do you think is reality formed by dream or is dream part of reality?
Huh? Bitch. Yeah.
Freddy Dunning Kruger is the name of a 2024 rock music single by the Manchester based band.
Of course it has a good job. Manchester based band either.
I'm surprised it took until 2024. I'm going to have to look that up.
We're going to have to play that at the skeptic camp. That sounds funny.
Yeah, if it's the right thing. Yeah, it's October 25th Saturday.
We're starting at nine a.m. We're going all the way through to seven p.m. We're going to have a game show.
We're going to have talks. We're going to have activities.
We're going to have free lunch. You do have to register. Go to LVSOS dot com to register.
That stands for the Las Vegas Society of Skeptics dot com LVSOS dot com.
Just it's a quick Google form. You'd say if you're going, if you have any minor kids you're bringing with you, blah, blah, blah.
And we will hopefully be able to have enough food for everybody if everybody registers on time.
And we've got a lovely venue down over on the east side of Las Vegas.
It is actually at the Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Las Vegas on Lake Mead.
And I was a little hesitant that, you know, one of one of our organizers is a member there and she's a total atheist.
And there's a lot of atheists in the Universalist Congregation.
And I'm like, a church, really? And she's like, as a member, I can get us the venue for free.
And I'm like, OK. And I went over membership. Now you're talking.
It's perfect. There's like a big lecture hall area.
There's break rooms. There's like it's absolutely a wonderful place to hold an event.
Oh, yeah. Skirt Fest guys have it all figured out.
Yeah. And no, no taxes.
Hey, so Celestia, I have to say I'm a little bit skeptical.
I've heard there's no such thing as a free lunch.
I'm skeptical that it's going to start promptly at nine a.m.
You have to be skeptical about both of those things.
The lunch is not free. Organizers are shelling out some some money to help.
Actually, we are also asking people to bring some non-perishables because they run a food bank for the community.
Oh, how nice. So it's sort of in exchange for all these lectures from cool people.
We've got Brian Dunning of Skeptoid.com is coming out. Oh, great.
Susan Gerbic of she's known as the Wikipedia attrition.
She's like the organizer of Gorilla Skeptics on Wikipedia.
She's coming out and giving a talk. Kyle Polish of Data Skeptic.
He's going to be talking about gambling math and everything.
So nerds will have a really good time at this and bring some canned food or non-perishables for the food pantry.
And hopefully you'll get a sandwich from the catered sandwiches we're going to be bringing in.
Nice. Yeah. And there'll be a taco truck for dinner.
Oh, you need a whole truck? Yes.
The first person to finish the truck will win a taco.
But is it taco?
That was my is it cake joke about a taco truck.
Oh, is it cake? Oh, no, it ran. It ran. No, no, it's better.
It's funny when I explain it.
That was just as funny.
Celestia, you stopped by ScoopFest and you did filthy caricatures.
I did. And I was so mad I couldn't do it last ScoopFest.
Andy Taylor had to cover for me because I had pneumonia.
Oh, and he wasn't nearly as good. No, he was tame. He was tame.
He said he said it was more stress. If I'm remembering correctly, he said it was a bit more stress than he thought it would be.
Because really, your brain cells are going like in all different directions for weeks beforehand.
They're lined up for you. Yeah. I was trying to think of like dirty things I could draw in five minutes.
And, you know, I'm actually very relieved to not have to think about these things anymore because it was one of those like intrusive thoughts.
I just have these images going around my head all the time.
Okay, I can do somebody like that. Oh, I can draw somebody doing that, too. And if I have two people, if I have three people, blah, blah, blah. Yeah.
Did you did you have any ideas that you weren't able to use?
Yeah, I had quite a few that I wasn't able to use because a lot of more more than I expected.
People sat down and it just sort of happened like stuff I didn't even think about beforehand, like the two guys in a banana suit.
I mean, yeah, that was. I have never in my life drawn two guys in a banana suit having sex so vigorously that the Chiquita sticker pops off.
But that was hella fun to draw. Right. When you didn't draw, that's what they were doing.
But what did you draw while they were doing that? Oh, I drew them sipping cosmopolitans.
Oh, that's nice. That's nice. They were fucking each other raw.
People I showed some of these pictures off. I didn't put them on Facebook, but I showed them to some private friends and everything.
They're like, what was this thing you drew? Was this like a swinger's party? And I'm like, no, no, not at all.
This is not a sex camp thing. These are just not officially.
Sex camp is October 25th in the basement of the church.
Sex camp, sex camp. Yeah, but I honestly I think a swinger's party would be way less fun because I mean, you all are just a loving community of open minded, humorous people.
And I think I was talking to Brian Brushwood afterwards and he said, it's like the horseshoe. It's like the horseshoe theory. He's like, we've got a lot of really smart people here.
But at the end of the horseshoe, there's also a lot of really dumb people.
So we've got like the smartest dumb people and the dumbest smart people all gathered to do fun things.
I'm in the dumbest quality area. Yeah, I rely on the scoops brain power. I'll tell you how dumb I am in the dumber smart category.
I'm so dumb. I've got my old Apple computer here that has all my music on and everything.
And I've locked myself out and I can't remember my password and I'm just fucked.
I've just got to sit here for days to try and get the password on this damn computer.
And if I don't get it, I'm going to lose thousands of dollars of music.
It's going to make me so sad. Somebody popped up on socials the other day.
It was some some sporting person, I think, had lost the password to their Bitcoin wallet.
Oh, no. They had they had a bunch of Bitcoin in this wallet for back when it was very cheap.
And somebody had given him like 40 Bitcoin or 400 Bitcoin or something.
And they don't know the password. And it's a few million dollars in there.
Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, there was one.
Wasn't it somebody on here that told us the story of how they had paid an ex-girlfriend for pizza in Bitcoin?
Right. But it was it was the only Bitcoin that that ex-girlfriend had ever gotten.
So he wasn't sure if she even knew that she had some bitcoins that were worth like one point something million dollars.
Yes. And he had not talked to that ex-girlfriend in a while.
I don't know who that was. That was some story from the from the way back past.
It's a scoop mail, wasn't it? It was a scoop mail.
It might have been a scoop mail or a guest or something.
Yeah. Somebody somebody will tell us over the next over the next week or two.
I'm sure somebody will see somebody will remember that.
But I am not an economic expert at all, but Bitcoin skeeves me out.
I don't know. It's like it's math and it's I agree with that.
And I've always thought that it's so much math, so gross math all over me.
I love math. I just I just don't know if I'm comfortable with using math as currency.
I don't know if I'm comfortable with math.
I am not. Well, I know what you're talking about, Celestia, because it makes sense to everybody else.
The rest of us are all on board with it. I stand corrected.
I'll go invest.
I thought like you were you get hired to do these like crazy gigs all the time.
I saw what were you doing caricatures on mugs and calling them mug shots.
I thought that's pretty neat. I was. Yes. Yeah.
Is this what's what is the is I've never I guess I don't know how to ask this.
Is the is the character world evolving? Like what's happening?
Yeah, the industry is going through some stuff. And I always feel like this kind of indicates times of economic uncertainty when party planners call you.
And instead of just, hey, come do the regular thing you've done for years and years, they're like, we want you to do your thing.
But we've got this weird idea and we want to try and capitalize on your talents by doing this other thing.
And so they fit you into all the jujube it up. Yeah, they try to jujube it up.
And so the latest thing has been drawing on napkins has gotten really big.
Like, oh, like you pretend you're Pablo Picasso and you're drawing on napkins for people at the night going by yourself, a college education.
Yeah, go and go and take your child to Madrid. Yes.
And then go and buy a vacation home.
Pablo, Pablo, Pablo, buy you a house.
None of my napkin scribbles will get anybody a college education.
Right now. But once you're dead and appreciated.
Look the fuck out.
That's what it happens. Unless you're Pablo. Who else?
Who else got that right? Got that ride like Pablo Picasso.
Who else came came up with it and still. Yeah.
Like, I mean, who else was John Michelle Basquiat?
I was gonna say Basquiat, Warhol.
See, Paul's relying on the scoops for intelligence.
But Basquiat passed away very young. He didn't get to ride it for long.
That's right. He didn't he didn't ride it for long, but he rode it quite a bit.
I mean, he would he would he would go into grocery store gas stations with no money to buy a pack of cigarettes and then just doodle on a receipt.
And, you know, just that that was his life for a while.
OK, so he did. OK, cool. That is a that's cool.
Let's try that today. I know many artists who have gotten free drinks from it and they're not Basquiat or or anybody famous.
But, you know, it's been a longtime way to get free drinks.
But what what the agents are now having artists do, you know, caricature artists in Las Vegas working trade shows and parties and corporate events is there.
And I'm feeling a connection here, Matt, to what you do.
And I'm finally understanding the draw of it here. No pun intended.
They're having me do stealth caricatures, which means I hang out in a corner.
I stand up against a wall. I draw on a little clipboard and then I slide it to the unsuspecting model who has no idea I've been drawing them.
Whoa. And the male artists I know, the male caricature artists hate to do this.
They're like, I feel creepy. I'm sliding. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Handing them. It's like it's like the bird watching binoculars don't help.
That makes that makes it more creepy. But I got to tell you, I was born to do this.
Celestia uses opera glasses. I just oh, that would be lovely.
I'm going to have to do that now. The glasses actually help because it makes it harder for people to see that I'm staring at them from like 20 feet away.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. And and I've got progressive lenses so I can look far or near or far or near.
And technology. Well, that's what I always tell the ladies that I'm staring at.
I'm like, hey, these are progressive. I'm as progressive as they come. I'm looking far and then near.
I'm staring at you progressively. Near. Far.
From near and far. I'd like to break off a piece of that action. Come on now.
I'm Paul Mattingly. How you doing? I have never been a magician. I have never been a stealthy person.
But I am an overweight middle aged white woman.
You you put me in a trade show room with a clipboard and I am a ninja.
Nobody sees me. I am. I blend into the wallpaper.
I look like every other. The bartenders think I'm keeping tabs on how much they're pouring.
They get a little nervous. Oh, near.
That's one of the higher nups. Near. Rocks.
But when you when you slide the drawing, how do you when and how do you deliver those?
That's the magic part. Plenty of times I just handed to them and say this is for you.
But a lot of times I can slide it right next to them on if they're at the bar,
if they're sitting at a table, kind of they're at a cocktail table.
I've even been able to put it in one guy's pocket without him realizing it.
And they they don't notice. Not only do they not notice.
Sometimes only one person out of the group will notice it or nobody will notice it.
And I just skulk off and I like you can count one, two, three, four, five.
And then they're like, oh, my God, what the heck?
You know, and this explosion of like somebody has drawn my picture.
And how did this where did they go?
And sometimes they're looking for me in a panic for like the next 20 minutes.
I bet people chase me down by the end of the night going, how did you even do this?
I didn't see you. And it's people are so unobservant.
Oh, my God. If I was evil, I could I could have ripped off every single one of them,
taken all of their purses and wallets. But I just remember my password.
So I'm on cloud nine right now. I just unlocked thousands of dollars of music for myself.
Everything's coming up. Everything's coming up.
This is going to be the best day of my life before we're done here.
Also, I'm enjoying the hell out of this episode. I'm glad to see Celestia.
We've got we've had more people in the room than we've ever had, guys.
We keep going up. We had we had forty two, which is our max now that we've had so far.
And everything's happening in the universe and everything.
Things keep going up. Exactly. So things keep going up.
This is great. This is great. This is great.
I'm loving it. Yeah. You scoops are here for my best day ever.
Do you want to tell me when your password so that you have it as a backup?
I sure don't. I sure do not. I sure do not.
Winner scoops suggest that you write it down. Yes.
I am going to write it down a thousand times. Yes.
Celestia, has there once has there been any requests you've had to say no to people trying to make your your profession into something maybe more difficult?
Oh, yeah. I had somebody recently asked if I could draw on golf balls.
Oh, God, damn, that sounds awful.
And I, you know, I was a little snarky. I was like, um, I've drawn on coffee mugs and napkins and other stuff.
Golf, you know, unless the people have a lot of dimples, I'm not going to draw them on a golf ball.
Could you say, uh, who's golf?
Yeah, who's golf? Oh!
Hey, sure thing, but is he OK with it?
Welcome to my golf party. I'm Joe Golf.
You're going to draw my balls tonight.
I haven't had to draw on people. I, that's another...
You've never drawn, that's what I was, you've never drawn on skin?
Well, I have, but I haven't been paid to do it.
OK. Have you, uh, was this for like a, was this for a tat, was this for a tattoo possibly or?
No, no, that's the reason why I would never be a tattoo artist.
Everybody always asks, oh, you should get into tattoos and blah, blah, blah.
Number one, the tattoo market is flooded. Everybody and their mother want to be the tattoo artist in the 90s and noughts.
But I don't like the idea of something I draw.
You know, if you don't like it, I want you to be able to throw it away.
So drawing on napkins and cups, maybe drawing on garbage is for me, I guess.
I have never been able to get a tattoo.
You can get rid of that tattoo.
Oh, God.
Here's a question for Briar.
Have you ever had someone ask you if they could get one of your works tattooed?
I have. I haven't. I've had somebody send me photographs of it.
Gosh, it's been a while. I've had somebody, you know, because occasionally people like have their loved ones caricatured and then plaster their wife and kid on them from the caricature.
And that's happened to me a couple of times. And then I had this one guy, the only time I've actually been like, yeah, cool. All right.
He said, I'd like you to draw my tattoo design.
And I'm like, well, it was really slow. I was at a caricature. I was at the caricature stand.
Logos or tattoos. When you go to a caricature artist and you're like, hey, can you invest five minutes in something I want to make permanent for my business or my body?
You're already dealing with somebody who cuts corners.
It's not a great idea. But he wanted to he wanted to have a tattoo that would win him bar bets.
And so he explained he wanted a a rooster in a noose, like the new the rooster was being, you know, and he said this was going to win him bar bets.
And I'm like, OK, I could draw a rooster in a noose. Tell me how it's going to win you a bar bet.
And he said, well, he's betting people that he has a tattoo of a rooster with a noose on it.
And they say, I bet you don't have that. He says, ha ha, I won. I'm I'm waiting for one of you to guess. But if you don't guess, I'll tell you.
There's a chicken chicken chicken. He said, I'll show my cock in this bar.
Well hung cock. I'll choke my chicken in his bar. He was he was going to tattoo it right below his knee.
And he was going to bet people that he has a cock hanging below his knee. Oh, that's funny.
Yeah. So the person doesn't want to blow you anymore.
That's pretty funny. We know these jokes well.
We know these jokes. We all know these jokes very well. These are jokes that are better in theory.
There are a lot of physical bits that are just better in theory.
I know one of the nursing home argument, which is like the moment the nurse is like coming in there and you're like, oh, God, is this a low hanging chicken joke?
Fuck you. Eat your applesauce.
Oh, the nurse at the retirement home. Hey, hey, sweetie.
I bet you I got a cock hanging below my knee. You have dementia. That's right. Yeah, yeah.
You told me yesterday the same joke every day, Taryn.
Did you blow me? I did yesterday. I blew you, buddy.
Oh, I bet that was great. It was. Thanks, pal. Oh, well, good. You want to blow me again? I don't have your applesauce.
Oh, I do like applesauce.
You know who else likes applesauce from old men who have pictures of cocks on their knees. That's the following sponsor.
From the Gorilla Dentist from that Bjork video from the makers of Hemp Burlap Boxer Shorts.
It's Permanently Wet Socks.
Hey, how's it going, everybody? I'm a creepy Best Buy guy.
I just want you to know that sales are way, way down.
We had like three stores left and decided to expand our inventory.
Unfortunately, we rented a warehouse and all we had was socks.
The warehouse got compromised. Somebody put a bunch of milk in it.
I don't know who would put a bunch of milk on socks.
Milk socks, gross.
We got an abundance of damp old milk socks.
And if you're looking to buy some, I can get them for you real cheap.
What if I'm not looking to buy some?
Then I'm going to put them on you while you're tied up.
I'm going to slowly leech the milk out with my mouth.
I'm going to suck the rancid milk out of your socks while I leave your socks on.
The best thing about having rancid milk socks is just a couple of weeks of wearing them.
You've basically made yourself a whole vat of cottage cheese in your shoes.
It's really nice. Enter H Groups to check out.
On the one hand, I was going to tell Jacob it was too loud to hear Paul, and then I was like, I'm fine with that.
That's fine.
That was a little extra disgusting, Paul.
But that's what I do. That's what I'm paid for.
Celestia, Paul's having a day.
Let's get it straight. Thanks to my exploding eye and my beloved wife Anne McFeeters, I am on the brink of having the best day of my life.
The best day of my life.
And that includes all of you being here.
You are party to the best day of my life so far.
So far. It's going to keep getting better.
It is a commercial that Anne's going to fast forward, just so we're clear.
She is. You know what? Also, I would say that our, like, Scoop Fest for me was one of the highlights of my life.
This last Scoop Fest was really, really good.
But easily top 10 things that I've done in my life.
And I would say, Matt, you and I, our bucket shows, were easily top three performances of my life.
These bucket shows were just off the hook for some reason.
Paul was ready to retire from stage performance after this bucket show.
I loved those bucket shows so much. They were really good.
Yeah, go ahead.
Both shows found, like, a really great button.
And when we were, like, when my improv group were, like, maniacs, when we were all, like, eight equally dedicated maniacs about long form improv,
you would find those buttons in our shows. And it was, like, so satisfying.
Yes.
Where you actually bring a kind of wave of callbacks and, like, something dovetails that changes a character into something that suddenly fits the puzzle.
It's so hard to describe, but when it happens, and so, and basically, Mark Roberts did it twice.
That's what I was going to say. I was going to say, Mark, big thanks to Mark and Brenna both for bringing an amazing energy to it, too.
It wasn't just us this time.
No. And it felt retro, like we called the shows on the buttons, and I was like, man, I haven't felt like this in a long time.
Absolutely. I will never forget.
Because a lot of long form teams, including our other bucket shows, you can ape it, right?
You can kind of, like, push it the way that the audience feels like it's cute and it's enough and it's close enough and yeah, we get it.
Or even just end on a laugh. Yeah.
But these, you're absolutely right, there was a symmetry and an actual connectivity to it all.
It paid the fuck off. Both of them had payoffs.
And it's interesting because, yeah, when I teach improv, I said there's a difference between a callback and a connection.
Yes.
And it was really hard to illustrate it, and both ended with really strong connections and not just callbacks.
It was really, it was really nice.
Can I ask you guys as improvisers?
Because I have this recent fear as a caricature artist, because I've watched many caricature artists before me kind of, you get, you know, your 20s, you're kind of sucking, you get better, you learn more, you get more experience, you get quicker.
You get, suddenly you're in the mentor position, and I turned 50 recently, and you guys are kind of around the same age, where you feel like you're in your prime.
And you're like, I am bringing all this experience to bear, I'm faster than I've ever been, I'm doing well, and then you're like, how long until I'm one of the old people who loses my edge?
Because you also see that. Are you guys like, trying to milk every, no pun intended, you're trying to milk sock every moment?
You're prime here? Are you worried that like, in another 10 years, this could all just be like, you know, you're not hitting it anymore?
Great question. Can I answer first, Matt, and let you say next what you think?
You're already faster than me, right? So is everybody showing you how slow I'm getting with age? Yes, go ahead.
So, here's my thing. And I think about when I was real, I was, I've had a couple of really cooking times in my career.
And the one was when I was part-time Trek, full-time Second City, and going back and forth between shows. Well, I was understudying.
What, were you Trekking? Motherfucker. Anyway, there were days when I would do seven hours of Klingon, get a shower at the Hilton, take the monorail to the Flamingo, and do two shows at night.
I was firing on all fucking cylinders. I was a young man doing it. I didn't know at the time that that was a prime time of my physical and mental performance time.
We never do. Aha, but this is the difference, Jacob. I think with age, we do sometimes know.
Like, I am very conscious of the fact that that last, that that last Scoop Fest was great, and those Bucket Show performances were very high bar.
So I think, Celestia, as long as you know you're doing well, you won't become the old daughterer.
You won't become the butt of the joke, because unless your mental faculties completely fail you, there may or may not come a point where you go, you know what, time to hang up the gloves.
Self-awareness is the key. I think, well, and I think that's the key, but it's also, just like we were talking about with skepticism and the Dunning-Kruger and all that kind of thing, you know how good you are right now.
But you also still know, is it fair to say you still find yourself improving and growing and learning new techniques, even to this day?
Oh, absolutely. I tell people the day that I stop learning how to draw is when I'm going to stop drawing.
That's it. So I think the other side of it, too, is with the age comes the awareness of, "Hey, I am really doing really well right now. I've had 50 years of this shit. I remember when things go to hell."
This is not one of those times. Things are going pretty good. Yeah, yeah.
It does give you a certain perspective, for sure.
And perspective is the big word there. So long as you have the perspective on it all, I don't think you're going to lose it.
Again, time, physicality, mental things, your eyes hemorrhaging, those are stuff outside of your control.
That's the only way I can see something coming up to where you become the person that shouldn't be there anymore. That's my thought. What did you think, Matt?
Just the same. I know. I actually know I've peaked. I'm not as good of an improviser as I used to be.
Oh, what are you talking about?
No, no, no. I'm going to speak honestly here. This isn't like a "woe is me" thing. I think I've gotten very... someone told me once, and this might be totally wrong,
but Krav Maga was supposed to be this martial arts form where you boil down every other martial arts form to its simple, most lethal moves, where you just do the most correct, different things.
And I think as I've gotten older, I simply have developed a Krav Maga style of improv, where I'm still intellectually...
Those are the Gracies, right?
What's that?
No, that's Brazilian Jiu Jitsu. Krav Maga is Israeli, I believe. It was developed for the Israeli military.
Yeah. I used to play a lot more different characters, do a lot more different voices, do a lot more different things.
I'm very much now just kind of a very much different versions of myself in almost all of my scenes. I just have lost that ability.
I got to talk about this. For my freaking movement final in my BFA acting class, I walked around like a polar bear for an hour and a half and behaved, and that was a final I got.
And there's no way I could do that now.
Just imagine if somebody asked you to.
And there are artists, right? There are clowns and stuff that we know that can simply just commit to energy and do that kind of stuff.
Absolutely, yeah.
I used to be able to make up songs so well that I would go to coffee houses and just grab a guitar player or keyboard player and just sit in and do three funny songs for the audience and kill and just go around.
I spontaneously took over a coffee house one time and put on an improvised concert.
I used to destroy with song stuff, and Paul has held on to his song construction abilities for improv so much better than I have. I can go for one or two verses of best.
It's the weed, Matt. It's the weed.
Yeah, I party hard. I did my fair share of smoking. I did my fair share of drinking.
Oh, I thought Paul was saying he was high all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm stoned when I'm coming up with a lot of good bits. No, no, no.
I swore off short form as a long form zealot for over a decade, right?
Mistake.
Where I practiced those skills, right? And it was only moving to Vegas that I was like, oh, I actually was skilled at this. It wasn't easy and fun for everybody. It was something I was good at.
And so I stopped rapping, so that was offensive for college white dudes to rap. And so I stopped rapping.
You may not have been completely wrong about that part.
Right. And so those skills deteriorated. But I still understand improv, I think, at a high level, right?
Yes.
I think I still see the performance piece for what it is better than nothing.
Better than nothing.
You used to get a little prickly about this, and I wonder if you still do. People would comment every now and then that you were a really, this years ago, people would comment every now and then that you were a really good improv show runner from on stage.
Yes.
You used to get a little prickly about that. Do you still or no?
It's a hard thing, right? Because basically, am I actually doing what I'm supposed to be doing, which is ego-less improv, right?
When you get into long form, there's kind of like a zen approach where you're just trying to make the pieces happen and unfold, and you're really not supposed to be that egotistical about it.
And so, yes, I'd have people be like, you know, I thought you were just okay, and then I saw you multiple shows and realized how much you were doing, that kind of stuff.
That kind of copy would come up all the time. But what Paul was referencing earlier is that I see the pieces, right?
So I go, oh, this is starting off great, but it's running in this direction, and if we don't counter and do a different kind of scene over here and do something differently over here, this piece is going to implode in 15 minutes.
You're always thinking big picture on stage, for sure.
This is why we work well together.
Yeah.
Because I get lost in the sauce.
Yeah. That's what I tell people working with you, Paul, is I go, Paul, if I wanted to make a scene, simply take a half hour and two pieces, I would just come out and start a scene with Paul, and Paul would play that character unflinchingly for a half hour.
He wouldn't give me a look. He wouldn't give me a wink. He would not look up. And other performers I perform with would kind of give me a look, like, are we really doing this kind of thing?
Paul does not. Paul buckles in and goes. And so, yes, I think my biggest compliment to Paul is that I can create, make sure we create different worlds, make sure we're not imploding, make sure we're peppering different people into different universes and making sure that we're--
And while I have elements of those thoughts, you're thinking in a very elegant, structural way about what does the show need.
Yes.
Then when you make an initiation that will facilitate that, I have the luck and the, it gives me the opportunity to then shovel in something that also wedges with that.
Yeah.
You know, but like, on my own, I wouldn't necessarily make as good a choice. That's what I always tell my students. There are no wrong choices in improvisation. There are better choices.
Right.
And what Matt helps me do is he sets me up with better choices. He aims me towards the better choices.
And that's why Paul encourages his students to go to Matt and ask to be his apprentice.
No, because on my own, I will be a crazed goofball. And while it may be entertaining, it won't necessarily hold together.
Right.
The way it does when we work together.
Yeah. I mean, Paul and I have taught workshops together and Paul will teach these crazy character workshops where he teaches people just to buckle in, make choices, double down, go harder, you know, take it to a, take it to a 10, you know, that kind of stuff, be unflinching.
And I will teach pattern play and rule threes and all kinds of stuff just so that all those things that kind of pepper a thing. So like an example for everyone listening is we're getting so in the weeds on this.
That sounds like good cop, bad cop.
No, no, no.
It is, guys.
It's not completely disrelated from that.
We have totally different education. Paul and I have a totally different improv background. Our teachers and our schools of thinking are completely different from one another.
And, like, if you watch a show and there's multiple people, there's a thing called a tag out where someone from the background will come in, touch the floor on the shoulder, and the person staying on stage remains the same character.
And that person becomes another person in that person's universe. You can change locations wherever you are. You just go to another spot and that person and that character's life.
And the biggest thing I do is an example of what Paul's talking about. As I say, that is a challenge to everyone else on the back line.
Can we make this a rule of threes?
Whatever this person does with that character, can you all follow that lead and make it two and three?
And then when you do that, you look brilliant to an audience that you all can play that way, you know, and stuff like that.
And so that's an example of, like, that's just a technique thing and creating triggers in people's brains that make their forms better.
But all right, let's change the subject. I think you're going to have to charge up tuition. This is like a workshop.
Well, but that's more like a camp. To Celestia's point, Matt, given that that whole talk there. Yeah.
What do you think keeps you and what do you think will keep Celestia from falling into the obsolescence category?
I remember going out to Improv Olympic when I was, you know, 20 something years old. I think I think maybe just even 20.
You know, my whole improv group, we went out to Chicago and just stayed on the couches of Mission Improvable for a week and we took workshops every day.
Chicago went to shows every night at Improv Olympic.
And that was when I realized I really liked long form more than short form is because I saw older guys killing it on stage, like doing really great funny scenes.
And I was like, oh, good, because I'm becoming that that's it.
I was like, that gives me hope. Right. Because I felt like when I watched and this might be wrong and I'm sorry for any listeners who do this fits.
But like I felt like when I saw older people doing short form, it looked kind of cheeseball to me when I was young. Right.
I don't know if that would be that way now, but it did look that way then.
And so I was so excited that you could still be characters. You could still do whatever.
And it was and it was it was still like, OK, so that was pretty cool.
And so I think as long as you are when you're doing something more theatrical, I think you have so much more freedom to age.
I'm here with you. Yeah.
And I am more worried about it for my magic career specifically, because once you become an old guy magician, it totally changes the lanes you have to pursue gigs.
Like it is just a different world when you're old. There have been so many amazing old guy magicians, though. I mean, but it takes some like curating.
Right. Like people have to kind of like you in the community that they kind of put you on a pedestal.
You have to kind of be people's first recommendation.
Well, maybe if you get in good with some classic magicians, maybe you can find some some guys who have made it made their bones and become friends with them.
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe you could maybe you could actually deeply befriend one of the greatest magicians to ever live in the history of the planet.
That might set you up for success. I'm not guaranteeing it.
I'm not. I've had Hondros in stuff. All right. Well, let's go. Let's talk.
So let's get Hondro on on the foreign and see if we can get you in the pocket with him good, because that might make things a little bit smoother.
Like my my my joke is that my my magic career has been that of a foreign star.
I've gone from babysitter to MILF like instantly. And and and it's and it's and it's and it's difficult.
You know, like the key to having it is difficult to go to MILF.
That's if I were probably don't never go ask the MILF if I was if I was if I was five or maybe 10 years older than I am right now, I would not be on the gig I'm doing right now.
I'm telling you that right now I would not be hired for what I'm doing.
You know, you would not be on the gate because they wouldn't hire you, not because you wouldn't do it.
But correct. Yeah. Right. But Matt, now that you are and you're gaining the experience of it and you're getting into that system somewhat,
do you feel with some degree of confidence in 10 years should things be where they are?
You could then book that gig because of the experience you're getting now.
I think a really good example of someone's doing something that I would probably love doing is this guy named Sean Farquhar out of Vancouver.
Sean was the first one of the one of the first people to fool Penn and Teller on Fool Us.
He forever was a cruise ship warhorse and just and private gig guy and just did everything all over the world.
He's won all these awards for being master magician and that kind of stuff like that.
He's one of one of the most respected magicians out there. He's very funny, very funny.
And he now runs his own magic theater in Vancouver that has like 40 seats.
It's in like a speakeasy. You have to like find it in this like old antique shop. That's where I've heard that name before.
Yeah. Yeah. His speakeasy there is a big deal. Yeah.
And so he got off the road and now he runs shows every Friday and Saturday and he sells out.
He adds another show and he does so he does like sometimes two, sometimes four, sometimes six shows a weekend.
And and the math just makes sense for what people pay to go see him do his thing.
But he has enough of a reputation as like as like a fantastic magician to do that.
And so that is definitely like a trajectory. And he's older, not not that much older, but he's a little older.
And so like that to me is an example of like a trajectory I could try to follow or ape or whatever.
Yeah. Cool. The chat is going crazy right now. They're just doing different MILF things and making Magician the Ilm.
And there's just all kinds of different things coming up in the chat right now. It's really pretty funny.
My favorite so far is from Rich Milb, magician. I'd like to book the magician. I'd like the Milb chaotic clumsy magician.
I'd like to feed the reasonable plan because I don't know if you've heard, but speakeasies might become a thing in Vegas, Matt.
Well, that's a U.S. about side effects of changing times.
I mean, yeah, right. The entertainment industry as we know it, the mainstream entertainment industry as we know it is dying.
And so that is that is a but here's the thing.
That's exactly like that's the only way I could work in Vegas right now.
Like my dream is to work in Vegas and be home with my children more, maybe even like a coach of soccer or basketball team or something like that.
And I and I can't write and I'll never gain the notoriety it takes to launch a show on the strip.
And that could because launching a show on the strip means millions of dollars no matter what.
Yeah. So even if someone to give me a million dollars today, I could in good faith be like, yeah, we can figure it out, you know.
But if there is a venue like a speakeasy that hires multiple entertainers and the reputation for the speakeasy is like, you got to come here and have an awesome time.
And I just happen to be someone who's part of that awesome time.
Like, that's the way I could work in Vegas. And if that happened tomorrow, I would do it tomorrow.
Yeah. Well, I think there's hope for that. And I think Celestia, too.
You've probably been on the end of this, too. I know for myself, I've had to invent and create spaces to perform throughout my life.
Yeah. Right. It's just, you know, from from the the shows I'm running over at pod duty, just because I went to that space was like, this is a duty.
This is a place to do improv like this is going to work. And it's working, you know, free free classes and whatnot. But it's still it's it's working really well in that little thing.
And like I started a coffee house so I could do improv, you know, and that I think that's the hard part about getting older.
When we were younger, we would create all of our performance situations because we could create a social scene around them. And that's like goes away when you get older is that you can't create a place because everybody's busy.
Yes. And yeah, and tired. Yeah. Well, this is the net. This is my busy and tired. This is my big dream, too, is the future name of Matt and Mattingly busy and tired.
Somehow. And I think like you're talking about, like, you know, with incorporating us, but like, I want like a coffee house, tea house, comic book shop, small theater kind of environment.
But it's all about just trying to trying to grow community. But it just takes a long time to grow community. It just really takes a long time.
And I see myself at the bottom of the bottom rung of that ladder again with what I am entering into right now.
And I see I see that fucking ladder and I'm like, God damn it, don't want to climb this shit again. And I do. I do. And I'm going to do it. And and I think magically, some other magical shit will happen.
That's always that's always the hardest part about improv is you can't take your resume with you. You always have to start.
Yes, it's all starting fresh. Makes sense. Yeah, it's all starting fresh.
You got to prove it. Because even look at Steel City Improv is rolling out the red carpet for you. Right. Right. Yes. Even still, like, their audience doesn't know who you are yet.
Right. So you still have to, like, get that going. Absolutely. It's all new, baby. It's all new. Now it's moving in the right direction. I've got my class sold out. I've got a waiting list now.
Awesome. But the first but the first class didn't sell enough timing wise. So it ain't like, you know, but it's coming. It's coming. It's not it's not instant. It's not. But yeah, it we're building a building a building straight up.
I'm just I'm just excited for the artist in Pittsburgh. Like, it's crazy, like the embarrassment of riches you got with Paul. And so the fact that, like, people are finally catching on makes me so happy because we're going to get there.
We're going to get there. We're going to make some magic happen with all this shit and with my love of comic books and I was gonna say, but what I oh that the point I wanted to make was that it is in no small part.
Because of this podcast and the wonderful community that I can continue to do this stuff with the degree of enthusiasm that I do coming off of scoop fest and coming here to just start stuff again and to really lock down and teach a free class on stuff.
I am enthused because of what we can create and what this community means to me and how I want to show up for them in the future by continuing to build stuff here too.
So just I can't thank scoops enough for what they provide for me every day. It's yeah can't do it without you guys.
Yep. I'll tell you what else you can't do. You can't win Jack versus third but we're gonna try anyway. Fuck you.
October 25th. Get the cam get there.
When we get the budget.
Hey, I tell you what a basement. So Celestia, will you be our go to lifeline? Sure. I'll hang out and be a lifeline. Yeah, fantastic. Thank you.
And Celestia toss out all that information for the for the skeptic camp. One more time. It will be Saturday, October 25th, 9am to 7pm.
We're gonna have lunch and snacks and even some limited childcare. If you sign up, you must sign up. Register today at LV s o s dot com. And yeah, it's free. You just have to register.
There you go. So go sign up. And we got a scooper. He coming to us today for rum rum raisin Berg. Hey, you face fuckers. Here's a scooper. He all about the fun stuff to do in Las Vegas this weekend instead of attending scoop fest. I kid it now occurs to me that this scooper.
He is being sent very close to serve scoop fest and it probably won't happen before the event takes place. Oh, well fucking with the face rum raisin Berg. You are correct in all of those things.
The categories are shows, sports, food and activities. I'm up first. I'll just go top left shows for 200.
You could see this multi species magic act at the Flamingo Hotel and Casino. X Burlesque. Ever since ever since X Burlesque added that chimera, it's shot tickets.
I believe it is piff the magic dragon. Yes, of course. Oh, see, now I was going to go with what's what's the Popovich Gregory Popovich.
Yeah, instead of going piff the magic dragon, you were going to go Greg Popovich. Look, he's the only one that I know of that has the multiple species and more.
He's at Planet Hollywood. More live pussy on stage than X Burlesque. Oh, but how much did should be his should be his catchphrase, by the way, it's his cat's face.
Cat's phrase. Ozzy Robb says RuPaul's dog race. I'd watch that show, too. We missed you at the scoop fest Ozzy Robb. Good to hear from you, pal.
Absolutely. A year from late April, early May, 2027. That's when we're doing the next scoop fest. Yes. Sports, please, for 200.
You can see the Las Vegas Raiders play host to this salmon eating shitting in the woods NFC North team.
Wouldn't it be great if every professional sports team had to live their life like the Mascots?
I didn't know. I don't know if paleo CrossFit gym had a football team.
Live and learn. That would be the Vikings. The Vikings is incorrect. It's the Bears. Oh, I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot.
Well, there's a Viking shit in the woods. I mean, I think so. I think all those things also apply to Vikings. Sven will never know.
We just said we just had fat bear week. Did you guys see that fat bear week? I did see that because bears are getting fat for the winter.
You get to vote on them. They've already crowned the winner. The fattest shit that these I just I did see that a lot of a lot of uptick in bears going for people's trash cans to get loaded up for loaded for bear.
They were all just getting ready for hibernation. And so like there were a lot more bears in residential areas just this last week. Yes, this has been your bear report from Ice Cream Social.
Just the bear facts. I will try activities for 600. Oh, yeah. Here we go. You can attend the Zombie Rumble at Area 51 highlighted by live music and a blank show.
I wonder if I bet this was supposed to be area 15. Maybe maybe I think maybe the numbers are transposed. I don't know. I will say I will guess burlesque. Oh, and the burlesque show.
Oh, no, I'm sorry, Paul. It's a classic car show. I mean, that's close. Right. The burlesque of the auto world. Get to see what's under the hood. Yeah, tassels on it.
I'll stick with shows for 400. This is a concert. A tribute to blank at the Orleans Hotel and Casino.
This is terrible. I was texting with someone about this show two days ago. Do you have a clue? I live by the South Point or not. No, the Orleans. I'm confusing myself point with my Orleans here.
Yeah, I messed up a Viking and a bear. So don't feel bad. Is it John Williams? I don't know. A tribute to John Williams. It's not a tribute to John Williams.
Shit, I got to pass, Matt. I don't know. Is it the band? Is it the concert? A tribute to the band? Oh, the band, the band. I haven't been to the Orleans in years.
Officially there last week. Oh, well, I still don't know. I will. I will have to pass. Wait, I know for a fact that we walked past advertisements for it. I have an answer. The Viking. Oh, go ahead. The Viking.
The Vikings. Here we go. Let's try the Vikings. Oh, it's Abba. Abba. Now I remember Ozzy Robb coming through with it. The worst part about that is I had a long conversation with one of the owners of the show downstairs during Scoop Fest. Oh, shit.
And you forgot that. We ran at each other in front of the in front of the theater. I invited them to come up to Scoop Fest. I don't think they did. Oh, that's too bad.
I was like, oh, yeah, bring the cast. Preferably stay in the Abba costumes. Come on up. Yeah. Yeah. My mind is fucked. Matt, you're up. Sports 400, please.
You can catch the Destructathon, which features battles between blank combatants from around the globe.
Is it robots? Between robot combatants from around the globe? I mean, that would work. I think that's right. What's robots? All right. Let's try robots. Battle bots fighting robots. That is like my favorite show in Las Vegas.
I've seen it three times. I still haven't seen battle bots live and I really want to. It's amazing. It's the only show in Vegas where they have it like a disclaimer on the marketing that says normally shows run 90 minutes, but occasionally the robots catch fire and that could cause a delay.
It happens. I'll try activities for 800. Get some points back on the board. Daily double. Perfect. I'm dead.
You could dance the night away at this nightclub, which won best nightclub in Las Vegas is weekly to 2025 best of Las Vegas. Oh God.
Is it Drays? Jacobs Whiskey Pit. Is it Drays? The real winner. Nice one, Jordan. We know what the real winner was. There's Drays. Do you have any ideas, Celestia? What other nightclubs are out there now? It's not Drays. They just closed.
Okay, that saves me. I'm thinking Tau or Omni. Oh, right. Omni. I think it's Tau. I think Tau is coming back with a vengeance. I'll go with Tau. Okay, I'll try Tau. It's Zuke. Those are like the driverless taxi cabs.
Yeah, it's kind of like that. What the hell is Zuke? I think that's the club at Resorts World. Oh, for fuck's sake. Doesn't Josh Gad run that? It's called Gad Zukes. Is that it? That makes sense. That makes sense.
That's probably it. Gad Zukes. I'll go back to shows for $600. You can go see Magic Mike Live at this Las Vegas casino. While it used to be at the Hard Rock Hotel and Casino, which is now the Virgin, it is currently at the Sahara.
Used to be SLS and now Sahara. Yeah, it was Sahara, then it was SLS, now it's Sahara again. I don't know why. Matt, you're up. Show is $800.
You can see this Grammy Award nominated artist known for doing backflips at T-Mobile Arena. Who's known for doing backflips? You saw the show, Matt. I think. At T-Mobile?
I think this might have been a one night only concert type thing. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh really? I don't think this was a repeating show. Oh, Celestia knows. I'll go to Celestia.
It's that Benson kid. Somebody Benson. He's like, don't you beautiful, beautiful thing. Okay, I'm terrible at singing it, but you'll know the song when you hear it. Robbie Benson? No. His last name is Benson.
And that's all you need for Jeopardy. Who is Benson? I thought it was Pink. Are we going with just Benson? Can we just say Benson? Benson Honeydew from the Muppets. Try it. Is Benson enough for you to get as the Arbiter?
Benson Boone. Oh shoot, it was his first name, not his last name. Oh shoot. That's alright. Benson Boone. Paul, Paul, be the Arbiter. Yes or no? Yes, because we got Benson.
All right, got Benson. Also, we would have also accepted Rene Aberjong-Wong. Who was on Benson, yes. That's precisely why we would have accepted it.
Paul, you're up. I will go. Matt, great job on that question, buddy. I'll go Food for 800. Let's get some points back on the board.
According to BoydGaming.com, these are the two open 24-hour dining options available to ScoopFest attendees at the Orleans Hotel and Casino.
What are the two 24-hour options at the old Orleans? I tell you, it ain't fucking Ballywick. I'll tell you that much right now.
Ballywick is open for roughly 42 minutes a day. Mike and Lori's suite. That's it. That's it. That's pretty much the only option. Fuck, man. I have to pass. I don't know.
I've never been to the Elsroth suite. Nor have I. Isn't that funny? It's just Jacob. That makes sense that it's just Jacob.
It's just Jacob. And I don't hang out. I just go in and have a drink. I mean, I think the diner that I ate at in the Orleans.
Chaotic Road Ice Cream and Dale Jizz.
One of those things does last. Jizz, mate. Jizz, mate. Jizz, mate.
I think the diner is open 24 hours, but I don't know what the diner is called.
I'll accept diner if you can get the other one. Oh, OK.
Then I think TGI Fridays. 24/7 TGI Fridays? I kind of think it is. I'll say the diner and TGI Fridays.
Nope. Sbarro and Fuddruckers. Holy shit. I ate a piece of Sbarro pizza while I was there.
That could have been sitting there for 24 hours. It could have been. Those are the two funniest names for any food establishments.
It is true. Fuddruckers is hard to beat. Is Fuddruckers the one where they make fun of you?
No, that's Dick's last resort. Oh, that's right. Yeah. I think also that Fridays is closed. It was not even there during Scoot Fest.
Was it gone? Oh, yeah. I mean, there was a facade still there, right? But, Matt, is it closed 24/7?
That's what could have confused me. It is indeed closed 24/7. It's not open 24. Oh, it's closed 24/7. OK, now I...
Ozzy Robb says both of those phrases are Mormon swear words. You're right.
Oh, Fuddruckers. Well, Sbarro. Let's see. Score check. Matt is winning with a thousand points.
I'm in second with zero points. Paul's in third with negative 14 points. We got one daily double left on the board.
Let's see. I'll try food for... No, fuck it. I'm going sports for 800.
You can see all of the high-flying action of this small independent wrestling federation at the Nerd Bar.
Oh, shit. I know this one because I've been trying to get people to go with me to see this for weeks on the rare occasions that I'm actually available to go to it.
It is called Micromania. Micromania midget wrestling. Their words, not mine. Wow. OK. Matt, you're up.
I'll do food for 200. You guys remember Micro Machines? Now I'm just thinking about Micromania. Oh, yeah. I love Micromania.
It's like I can talk really, really fast. Well, you can combine the wrestling with the BattleBots. You've got Microbots.
Take it, but it's Chick-fil-A. We can just move on. You get a chicken sandwich.
It's from this chain in Caesar's Palace Forum Food Hall, just not on Sunday. What? Chick-fil-A. Just click it and say Chick-fil-A. It's Chick-fil-A.
The part of that that's confusing to me is I don't know where Chick-fil-A is in the Caesar's Palace Forum Food Hall.
Neither do I. I just said not on Sunday and know it's Chick-fil-A. That's it. You're like, "Church on Sunday. Fuck you."
I work in Caesar's Palace. I didn't know there was a Chick-fil-A. Paul, you're up.
I will take food for $600, please. By the way, I'm fine with that. I don't need Chick-fil-A. Let's get some points on the board. Here we go.
You can stuff your face at this buffet, which won the best buffet on Las Vegas' Weekly's 2025 Best of Las Vegas.
The Caesar's World Buffet? What's it called? Oh! Becca Boonch or Meet Yourself. The Forum Buffet? The Forum? No. What's it called?
You want me to tag in? That is the entire question. I can tell you. Oh, yes, please. Celestia, help him.
It is The Bacchanal Buffet at Caesar's. And it's either that one or the Wicked Spoon at Cosmo. It's always a battle between those two.
Oh, Celestia, throwing shade at the Wynn Buffet. Which do you think was the winner this last time, Celestia?
Well, I think it's going to be Caesar's. Right. Telling Bellagio's Buffet to fuck right off. Celestia Ward.
I know my fucking buffets. Have you met me? I love The Bacchanal. Yeah, The Bacchanal is fucking good.
The Bellagio Buffet is endless water from their fountains. You can just. That's right. Oh, God.
And they've got the chocolate fountain there, too, but you're not allowed to touch it.
Did you see they put a boat in the fountain this morning? There's now a boat. It looks so weird. It's so stupid.
It just makes it makes the fountains look less impressive to stick this big like fairy.
Because now you realize that it's not that big. Yes. Do they put people on it? Is that what it is?
They just get more money on people? I guess. I don't know what they're doing with it. They literally just put it in the water this morning.
Is it for the F1 stunt? Is it just for F1 or are we going to have to deal with that all the time? Probably.
I think it's there as part of the new Carbone restaurant that just opened there. I think it's a stunt from them.
Really? I think it's there like going forward. Do you think that they I bet they will have people you can pay to go out into the middle.
Oh, yeah. And they had some captain on the front of the boat like he was steering this ship. He looked embarrassed.
It's a living. Oh, is there law of the sea? Yeah. International waters. International waters, baby.
Law of the sea. International gray water. Also gross. If you're in that gray water, you're in that place getting squirted on by old laundry detergent, right?
That is true. Yeah. No, thanks. I don't know if I want to get on that boat. What's it? When you talk to me out of it, the maiden of the mist.
This would be the maiden of the pissed. Yeah. Oh, they are not going to be happy with us.
Which buffet won Las Vegas. We went with the Bacchanal Bacchanal Bacchanal is your answer.
OK, let's see. I'm sorry. It is the wind. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That's all right. Jacob tried to help you.
Did you know about the wind buffets that is overpriced? It's good, though.
Well, yes, I tried to help you for trying. Chris Angel invented the buffet.
That's right. And I staffed it with all homeless people. They had nothing when I met them.
They had nothing. They didn't even know how to cook. I taught them how to cook. I taught them how to be there.
And now, thank God, you know, who here likes food? Let's hear it for food. Everybody stand up for food.
Everybody stand up. Thank you. That's my show. Thank you. Let's hear it again.
I'm not going to sit back down before I leave. I guess I'll just stay standing. I have a Chris Angel little person dwarf story that I forgot to tell.
Wait a minute. I'll have to tell it to you next time. OK, that's a teaser.
That's a hot tease. I'm going sports for six hundred.
You can watch the Las Vegas Aces compete against this team in the semifinals of the 2025 WNBA playoffs.
You would have to watch it on TV as the game is in a different city.
I think that's the Mystics. I think they were playing the Mystics. I'll go Mystics.
Now it's the Fever. Indiana Fever. You give me fever.
Indiana. Fever in the corn at night. Fever.
Indiana. Food 400. What an awful place to live.
You get to eat at this iconic 24 hour American restaurant known for its large portions and neon retro interior founded in 1972 on the northern end of the Las Vegas Strip.
Oh, shoot. You know this one. Yeah, it's a wonderful place.
Go ahead, Celestia. Help me out.
It is the pepper mill. Oh, right.
I was thinking about the other place that had the tractor and the thing and the tractor. Oh, the old red hash house.
Hasn't been around since '72. Yeah, I know.
That's why I was hesitating and asked for Celestia's help, Paul.
Good move. Paul, you got activities for 200 or 400.
You are, let's see, three thousand six hundred points behind Matt.
Eighteen hundred points behind me. Let's take 400, get some points on the board. There you go. Get some points on the board, baby.
You can catch Tomorrowland's event Unity at this iconic Las Vegas venue.
Oh. Oh. Unity.
It's got to be Sphere. Maybe. Let's try it.
It's the Sphere. Oh, so that's interesting. So Disney is using some of their ride stuff in the Sphere.
Like, did you guys ever go on Spaceship Earth? Not Spaceship Earth. What was the alien encounter?
What was the one, remember that Disney ride where you sat on, it was like you were in a rocket ship and you went up into space.
Do you remember that? It was a giant theater that turned into a rocket ship, basically.
Oh, I don't remember. Captain EO?
No, it's not Captain EO. Chat, anybody know what I'm talking about?
Not Small World. No, you got in the Mission Earth maybe.
Yeah, I guess it was at Epcot. It's not Spaceship Earth. It's not the-
Was it the thing where they spun you around and it felt like you were on the Gravitron?
No, but there was a shake to the seats when it took off.
I'm closing out the category as the game activities for 200.
You can celebrate the 40th anniversary of this time traveling 80s movie at the Composer's Room.
It might have been Mission to Mars.
Was it Captain EO?
Yeah, it's Captain EO. Yep.
It's Space Mountain. Space Mountain final answer.
Back to the Future.
Yes, I know it's Back to the Future. I'm still naming Disney things.
Oh, okay. Okay, Dark Cauldron.
Dark Cauldron.
That is the game Black Winds with 1600 points. I'm in second place with 400 points. Close game today.
Paul is in third with -1600 points.
And that's the Scooperty for today. It's from Rum Raisenberg. Thank you Rum Raisenberg.
If you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price is Skryte Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jock vs. Nerd,
head over to HayScoops.com. Right there on the homepage you can do all those things.
You can also send us some Scoop Mail. Do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
Oh, Matt is so distraught over losing. He's going to jump off the edge of a boat. Don't do it, Matt.
He won. He won.
I'm so distraught over winning. I'm going to jump over the edge of the boat.
Either way, he's not used to it.
Don't do it, Matt. You won.
I just want to show Ryre how he said, should I piss off my balcony? I want to show him what would happen if I pissed off my balcony.
Just ride onto a lifeboat.
Go right back into your face.
On someone's head.
What deck are you on? You're pretty close to the water level.
I am. I asked to be just underwater so I could really crack the door.
Give everybody a shot of the ocean real quick.
Look at that.
Somewhere over there is Canada.
Law of the Sea. How glorious.
Matt is just standing there not restrained by any international law.
Nice.
It's beautiful.
He just murdered someone right on camera. It doesn't matter. Law of the Sea.
Beautiful out there.
We're probably going to do another episode, but it's my first time on Virgin Voyages, and obviously, this is totally up above.
It's pretty nice.
Yeah, this is nuts.
Yeah, it's pretty swanky.
I'm not having as good a day as Paul, but it's really nice.
I have to thank people, yeah?
I would just thank people in general. We don't have new lists yet. It's a new month.
I'll give some personal thanks.
Thank you. This is a guy who gave me an excellent Americano.
Thank you to him.
Good.
I want to thank everybody who supports us over on Patreon. If we didn't have Patreon, this podcast would not be killing it.
It's been killing it now for almost 11, was it 12 years? I lose track.
12?
More than a decade.
And that happens because people want us to exist, and we're not a podcast that relies on hot takery.
We don't try to do sizzling things to go viral. We just try to joke around and keep people's days a little more amusing than they would be otherwise.
And if you think that's a cool mission, then go ahead and support us today over at preachingfun.com.
Or if you believe the opposite, if you believe the opposite of everything Matt just said, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's right, fartsinabag.biz, that along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air if you think it's worth more than $0.
Preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those are your destinations.
Keep this show rocking and rolling for another 12 years.
We'll do it if you want us to.
I guess that's about it.
Yep, I want to do this for another 12 years. I seriously do.
I really, really do.
Then we can go back and listen to this episode of how we thought we'd be when we were older.
And then when I leave up here...
Then I can remember when I had a functioning left eye.
You'll be there in an eye patch, and I'll be there showing everyone my new tattoo with a chicken with a rope around his neck.
Guys, I've got this great new bit!
Huge thanks to our guest, Celestia Ward.
Thank you so much for coming on the podcast.
The most patient guest we've ever had.
Yes, thank you for indulging my bullshit, but this was my best day ever. I had to share it.
I was blipping out a couple times. Zoom hated me for some reason today.
If Paul loses an eye, I'll have my Patreon.
Oh, you're doing great.
Never affected the episode, so it's all good.
We will definitely share your information for SkeptiCamp on our socials and spread the word.
And please, Scoops, help spread the word, especially if you're in Vegas, know people in Vegas, or just know some skeptics who might go,
"Hey, fuck it, I'll go get free lunch in Vegas for a weekend. Let's do this shit."
Free lunch and critical thinking, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's a pretty great combo.
Oh, I'm so good at one of those things.
Help us, help Celestia spread the word on SkeptiCamp. It's a positive thing for the planet and America for sure.
Yeah.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah. Thank you, Celestia.
And Paul, you've got to ask Fact Check Andy about his eye. He had a retina detachment scare.
Oh, I know. We've been through it. We talked through it.
That was one of several hundreds of things that have kept Crispapus2 from getting done. It's almost done. It's technically done.
But that was one of the-
Christmas is coming!
Huh?
Christmas is coming already, yes.
Christmas? Oh, no, but it's- oh, Christmas is- forget it. If we could get Crispapus2 by Easter-
Christmas 27.
Because the Easter Bunny is a big part of the show- is a big part of the story, that'd be perfect. I don't know if we're going to be able to get there.
I've got to see what Andy's up to, but we're close. We're getting closer and closer. We may need to call on you again.
Can we put no work demands on Andy's plate right now?
Exactly, because he's- well, no, he's working now. He's doing caricatures right now, but he's had a fucking rough year of it.
Yeah.
And Andy, I love you the most, buddy. You're my art hero. I adore you. You're my book partner. We'll get the book done when we get it done.
But, Celestia, while you're here, at some point we may call upon you for your editorial skills on old Crispapus2 as well.
My pleasure.
There you go. All right. Cool, cool, cool.
All right. Well, thanks for listening, everybody. Thanks, Celestia, for being here. Thanks, Penn, for creating this podcast.
Thanks, man.
We love you all, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
[Music]
See ya! Hooray!