I would love to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers, thank you so much Ice Cream Truck
Drivers.
I'd like to thank right now, Richard Dunn, Sarah Boyle, Sax Guy, Jimmy D, Scoop, Scoop
Brady, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Kata, Slurpee K.A., Motherfucker, Thunder Cougar Falcon, Scoop
and Travis Jagare.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFund.com,
where you can go sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver and who knows, the life you save
may be your own.
And now, a show!
We are!
So you're in some alien jank right now?
You know I'm always into aliens, you know I'm always interested in the alien stuff.
So Ann, Ann brought this up to me yesterday and I don't know if you guys have heard about
this.
Any bets?
I bet I haven't.
Any bets on what you think this might be?
Aliens!
Well, who knows?
The Senate is made up of lizard people?
Nothing so, nothing so gauche.
No.
Oh, how great would that be?
Do you have any idea how nice it would be to just find out that they were all lizard
people the whole time?
We'd all be like, "Oh, at least they were just lizard people."
It would make more sense.
Would you rather discover that the entirety of the Epstein List is just lizard people
and not pedos?
It would weirdly, I think, make me feel better.
Technically, yes.
About life in general.
I guess, right?
Less pedophiles on the earth.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Pedophilia, lizards, I guess that's a new problem we have to deal with.
Ann brought this up to me and I was like, "What?"
And I haven't really looked into it too much, but I've just seen a couple of these headlines
and it just popped up against in my feed and it says, "Breaking.
A new study suggests that a potentially hostile seven-mile-long alien spacecraft may be headed
towards earth, scientists say."
Scientists say.
And what I love is that-
All of them.
All of the scientists say.
This was tagged by an account I follow and their headline over this is, "What did Trump
do in those Epstein files?"
It's like the kind of shit that people are coming up with for excuses.
It's just ridiculous.
But yeah, Ann was telling me about that.
Do you guys remember Moa Moa a couple years back?
Yeah, the song, Moa Moa, Moa Moa.
That's right.
Moa Moa.
And that song is all about the cigar-shaped turd-looking thing that came flying through
our galaxy.
I do remember the cigar-shaped asteroid or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you remember it?
Yeah.
I do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And folks are still torn as to whether or not it had any kind of intelligence behind
it or what it might be, if it was just a dead probe or what it was, but it was a very uniquely
shaped space object and passed close enough to us to be an interesting thing.
So we'll see.
Yeah.
Bazzi says, "Yeah, it makes a lot of sense that a species capable of traveling over light
speed has no stealth capabilities."
Right?
I mean, things fall apart when you look at it too quick.
Don't start looking at stuff.
You're a part of the problem, Bazzi.
You're asking questions.
No, I honestly...
I don't know, Wayne in the chat just says sometimes a cigar is just a cigar.
You'll get no argument from me, Dr. Freed.
I'm afraid not.
But that makes me laugh.
And who knows, maybe the spacemans are a-coming.
Maybe.
That's the big take.
Maybe the spacemans are coming.
That's the first one.
See you, everybody.
Maybe spacemans.
Maybe they're coming.
I just got back from Saratoga Springs, New York.
Oh, I'm sorry, Matt, you don't want to talk about the spacemans anymore?
I was looking for an inn, and just that it's seven miles long and it's a-coming just didn't
give me too much.
I mean, right.
I need to go find the article.
There's really not a whole lot more, I don't think.
Why start now?
It's too late.
You should have found the article before we went on air.
No, it just popped up in my feed again, and the fact that it hit again reminded me that
Ann brought it to my attention.
When Ann brings something to my attention, I find it newsworthy.
It's go time.
That's basically it.
I'll look it up.
Oh, good, good.
Yeah.
But you were in Saratoga Springs for the horsies?
Yeah, when I saw the ponies, and Nicholas Newman once again cemented himself as an honorary
Donnelly child by writing up very hilarious pink sheets for betting sheets for it.
I do have to break the news to Nick via this podcast that as my older brothers were losing
more and more bets, they became less and less interested in the comedic bits of Nick Newman.
They weren't interested in laughing and losing money at the same time.
Was Nick giving them tips?
Nick has a hilarious breakdown.
He breaks down every race in Saratoga and does things like highlights which horses are
from Ireland since we're Irish.
He'll give me gossip by the horse's owners.
He'll make fun of the whole race as a whole.
We were there Friday and Saturday.
The Friday slate was the oddest slate of races because the Saturday, of course, was the Jim
Dandy.
The Jim Dandy.
What's the Jim Dandy?
It's a big horse race, but it's called the Jim Dandy, and I was like, "What a finer
race is this?"
It's like the Jim, but it's dandier.
I've never understood that fucking song.
Have you guys ever understood that fucking song?
Break it down for us, Paul.
Go, Jim Dandy.
Go.
Jim Dandy to the rescue.
Do you know that song?
Yeah.
It's about a fella named Jim Dandy who is going to come to the rescue.
What the fuck is it from?
What is unclear about this song?
I'll tell you what's unclear about it.
What's with Johnny B. Goode?
What are we asking him to do there?
Yeah.
I understand everything about Johnny B. Goode.
Way down in Louisiana, close to New Orleans.
That's where he lived.
In a cabin.
A shaggy.
In a cabin made of earth and wood.
Yeah.
He played his guitar there.
He could play it very well, almost like he was just ringing a bell.
He had that much skill with the guitar.
I know about Johnny B. Goode, but the Jim Dandy song explains fucking nothing.
It's just like, hey, Jim Dandy, go, go Jim Dandy.
Jim Dandy to the rescue.
To rescue who?
He's being helpful.
From what?
Why?
Anything.
Bullshit.
Jim Dandy.
Jim Dandy is a traveling do-gooder.
Jim Dandy is a crisis actor.
How dare you?
Jim Dandy is seven miles long and one light year away from earth.
Hey, look.
It's shaped like a cigar.
I typed in seven miles and it went right to seven mile spaceship, so shit is real, y'all.
But right to it.
The word is, the interstellar object that I was referring to, it is known as 31/Atlas.
It has been observed.
It's quite large.
Oh, 31 Atlas.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It's been observed and it's quite large.
It's confirmed not to be a comet.
It is confirmed to be a comet, not a spaceship, and significantly further away from earth
than a spaceship would be.
The idea of constructing such a massive structure in space is a topic of ongoing research and
discussion in the field of aerospace.
Well, they fucking just poo-pooed it all.
Okay, so it's just an interstellar object.
It's not a threat.
It's just a big old thing.
Here's the thing.
I have never been happier about an article that Paul looked up.
The person poo-pooing it, are they a scientist?
Because the scientists said it was an alien ship seven miles long on its way to Earth.
They are and they're...
The scientists have clearly weighed it.
It starts off with the concept of a seven mile long spaceship is currently hypothetical.
Though there is an interstellar object called 31 Atlas.
It is a comet.
So I guess people are just buying at this.
31 Atlas, what do you get?
Another galaxy older and deeper in debt.
People get that debt.
Every summer, my brothers and I get together with my dad and we go to Saratoga and spend
a couple of days betting on the ponies and usually it's right after Fool Us.
Me affording my own one person vacation on top of a family getaway, no problem thanks
to the generous coffers of CW.
It's not this year and so I've been a traveling magician man and so I used points to try to
get there cheap and I used points to try to get me a rental car because basically my points
wouldn't fly me into Albany, the closest airport to Saratoga.
Was there a restriction?
It just wasn't.
Yeah, I tried to use my points and there was no flights to Albany from Las Vegas.
But it would fly me to Connecticut, just a hair and a two hours away.
How's that bad?
So I was like, "Oh, I'll do that.
I'll run a car and I'll drive.
I don't care about driving two hours, no, it'll be the wiser, no problem."
And I'm a fancy traveler guys, right?
I got the clear, I'm a global entry member, pre-check, nailed it.
I walk into the airport and I'm not checking any bags, I'm not doing magic.
And so I walk up.
How does that feel?
Do you get a whole body vibe when you're like, "Oh man, I don't have to worry about like
shit tons of trunks and stuff."
Yes, love, yes.
Very happy to travel without checking two giant bags that I know to the pound how much
each weighs.
I'm very happy.
So I zip right through, scan my eyeballs in the thing, fly, land myself in Connecticut,
walk right up to the rental car counter, which is right across the street from the thing.
And they say, "Give me your license."
And I go through my wallet and I cannot find my license.
I am having a panic attack because I don't, I'm not the kind of person that misplaces
those things.
You don't take your license out of your wallet too often.
No, no, no, no, no.
And I am going like, "Oh, I don't have it."
I do have a picture of it.
I always keep a backup picture of my license and my phone.
And they took that and let you ride onto the plane, right?
He's not on the plane, he's going for a car.
I'm already landing in Connecticut.
I'm already through Las Vegas, landed, no problem.
I didn't have to get my ID out once.
Oh, right, right, right.
Okay, okay.
I didn't have to get my ID out once to get through the airport.
And so I'm in Connecticut, two hours away from my family.
And I say, and they go, "We can't rent you the car without the physical license."
Oh, man.
And I was like, "I have a global entry card.
This is my ID.
I have a passport.
I have a photo of my ID."
It's definitely you.
They definitely run it up the pipe, get on the phone and they pretended to talk to someone
like a car dealer does.
They really pled my case and they're like, "We can't rent it to you."
And I was like, "I'm not going here.
I'm going to Albany and my whole family is like, 'What do I do?'"
I had a total meltdown of like, "What?"
I'm in Connecticut.
I don't plan on being in Connecticut.
Are you familiar with a show called Fool Us?
Good, good.
You tried to hide a little bit.
All right, you're dropping that.
Have you ever laughed at a toss to commercial or welcome back to commercial on the show
Fool Us?
No?
You fast forward those parts?
Interesting.
Outrageous.
That's too bad for me.
Those are arguably the best parts.
Now, that's not a winning argument, but it's arguable.
Arguable.
Did you watch VH1 20 years ago?
Do you know who I am?
No, I just literally look at them like I basically is like, and now I'm just like, I can't rent
another car.
I can't.
Right.
I can't do this, and I am like, I guess I can look at the flights.
Did you explain to them that if they didn't rent you a car, that you were just going to
stay there with them?
I was kind of doing that by like sweating and mumbling and going like, "What am I going
to do?"
You're like, "Wouldn't you like me to leave?"
They definitely, it was like a team of three of them by the end, and they were like, "Yeah,
we're so sorry."
You know what I mean?
"We got to get this guy out of here."
I was like, "I'm going to sit in that chair over there and look sad all day."
So I call my brother, hoping I catch him on the way to Albany where it's not too far out
of his way to come pick me up.
Got it.
I'm wrong.
It's way out of his way.
Wayne Geo said I dropped ... Have you ever heard of the Donnelly Herald?
He's already there.
He's in Albany.
Oh shoot.
And he goes, "Well, I don't know what else I'm going to do tonight."
So he just gets in the car and he drives two hours to come get me.
And then my other brothers jokingly said, "Boy, did you call the right brother because
we would not have copped right in the car."
Shout out.
Which brother was willing to come get you?
Brian.
Shout out to Brian, my hero.
Thank you, Brian.
Well done, Brian.
And then I fronted the money for the tickets to Saratoga and I was like, "Well, now I can't
ask him for that money.
I can't ask him to pay me back for that."
No way.
He's paid you back already.
I'm done on that.
I'm not going to pre-call that.
Paid in full.
So it ended up costing me a little bit of money, but still, nonetheless.
Hey, but you got to ... Now, you didn't have to pay for the rental car, right?
I didn't, right?
So it's all in points.
Basically, I was going to use the points.
There's a savings.
Oh, you were going to do it in points anyway.
Oh, dude.
I was doing it all in points anyway.
And so I said to my brother when he drove here, I said, "Okay, either we can put the
rental in your name so we can get it out of here, or you have to drive me back here on
Sunday."
Oh, right.
Right.
And so they let me, even with points, they'd let me switch him as the driver.
Okay.
Oh, that's nice of them.
And then we had to pretend like he was going to drive the car the whole time, even though
everyone knew the circumstances.
The jigs was up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He drove here.
Of course.
And so we had to do the theater of him driving out of the lot.
Oh, I've decided to leave my car that I just drove here and take this rental car.
I can pay for my car to be parked here while I drive my new rental.
Now for some reason, the cheapest rental from Enterprise was a Toyota Tacoma.
It was not a tiny little- That's a pretty big coupe car, right?
Right.
That's happened to us in Texas.
That has not happened to us outside of the state of Texas.
In Connecticut, I was not expecting the Toyota Tacoma to be the least one.
And so we get out into the lot and the person helping us with cars says, "I don't have
any Tacomas.
You can take one of the Ford F-150s."
You can get bigger.
And I was like, "I drive a Corolla."
Right?
Right.
Happily.
You happily drive a Corolla.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Since my first car was a little Volkswagen Golf, I've always enjoyed just being a guy
who darts around town, not big on big space.
We share that.
I do not like a vehicle that takes up much room.
So I go, "Well, I don't have to take a big Ford F-150.
If you're going to give me, I'll take one of the SUV trucks or whatever."
He goes, "No, those are an upgrade."
Oh my God.
But the truck isn't.
By the way, I'm talking for my brother, he's to be driving.
I'm just the one talking.
Hilarious.
I am the mouthpiece, he is the driver.
It's my opinion that counts, but he's ultimately the one behind the wheel.
I'm the negotiator.
He's the muscle.
He's the silent muscle.
So they're like, "Nope.
That's the only car you can get."
They won't even give me a tiny car.
They're like, "No, the only car you can leave this lot in is either a black or a white Ford
F-150."
What did you go with?
A white-
You'll be leaving this lot in an F-150 or in a box.
Or you don't leave at all.
Now did you go with the white one-
The options are, drive an F-150 off this lot or we will murder you.
Did you pick the white one as just a kind of a knee-jerk, instinctual move because of Vegas
training?
Correct.
I was just thinking, I was like, "It's summer, it's hot, I'm going to take the white car."
Yeah.
Also, I was like, "Modern political sensibilities, we're limiting DEI, I should take the white
car."
Geez.
Smart.
Was this rental place at a target?
Otherwise, I'm going to get collected by ICE for being a traitor, and they're going to
go through my phone and find all my names.
Damn it all.
Damn it.
Damn everything.
Already, when leaving Connecticut, you're going to have to go through the border checkpoint
anyway.
I was like, "I'm in Connecticut, right?"
They're like, "Yeah."
I was like, "White.
Yeah.
This is a white town."
Oh, God.
So, Jacob, you live this life.
I live the truck life regularly.
I drove around in a Ford F-150, it is different living.
All I kept thinking the whole time was like, "This is what Jacob does all the time?"
Yep.
Really, honestly, we were just having this conversation last night, SJ has become a very
happy truck girl lately.
Yeah.
Because SJ has been driving the truck around a lot over the summer with gigs, so I've been
in the electric sports car most of the summer, and she's been the truck gal all summer.
So, yeah, driving a truck around is a different experience than driving a little car around
town.
Oh, my sons are with me.
They would have flipped out because they love going in your truck.
They would have loved going around in a truck for the weekend or whatever.
So every time you pull into a parking lot, you have to go like, "Oh, shit."
Every time.
You go like, "All right.
Where do I fit?
Oh, there's a spot."
I was just pulling out of the parking lot this morning.
This morning, leaving work, I was pulling out of the parking lot, driving normally in
my lane, headed to a stop sign, a truck is coming in.
The truck had to stop and wait for me to go around so it could physically get into the
parking lot because there just wasn't enough room in the two lanes made for the parking
lot.
It was outrageous.
That happens from time to time.
Yeah.
So let me ask...
That is something that just occasionally happens.
So, yeah, we were going out to dinner, and I just go like, "All right."
I let it go, I drop everyone out, I'm like, "Everyone go in.
I'm going to need a minute to figure out what I'm going to do."
Me and the truck need a minute.
I'm going to just order for me.
Can you just flip the thing, just smash three cars and park there?
That's it.
So this is it because we went to two days of races.
The first day we took my brother's car, he drives a hybrid Accord, like the woke hippie
jerk that he is.
You know, they just signed the hybrid Accords over in Scotland.
Yeah.
Finally.
Boo.
I don't think the hybrid Accords will stand.
But my dad, you know, we're celebrating his birthday, '87, he certainly enjoyed getting
into the truck more than hunching down into the old Accord.
Oh, interesting.
Interesting.
'Cause my mother-in-law, whenever she comes out to visit, her knees are bad enough that
she doesn't enjoy climbing up into the truck.
So I was going to ask my dad getting up in there.
Oh, he was liking it.
He's got those new knees though.
Nice.
Yeah, he's got those new knees.
He's got those robo knees.
He don't give a shit.
He's '87.
Those knees are like two or three.
Right.
Those are baby knees.
Yeah.
Don't fuck those knees.
They are not of age.
Trash baby knees.
Those knees are in the Epstein files.
You could fuck every other part of Dave Donnelly, but not his knees.
Don't do it.
Oh my God.
So we were taking the truck everywhere.
So the second day we go to the races, you know, it's the Jim Dandy.
Go ahead, Paul.
Go Jim Dandy, go Jim Dandy to the rescue.
What the fuck is he rescuing?
From whom and why?
No one tells you, no one tells you.
And so, you know, Saratoga is a tiny little town.
So when the races come up, it's like all these small businesses just open up and let you
park in their little parking lots and sometimes their lawns and that kind of stuff or whatever.
Right.
So we're driving around and all the lots are a little full because some people got there
earlier.
They got there for a lovely brunch where I literally was like saw something that said
valet and I was like, should we go there for brunch?
I was like, get this out of my hands.
Somebody else can park this.
I can only shop and eat at places with valet.
And so we go and we pull up to this lot and all the lots a lot full, the guy is wearing
a tie-dye shirt and he just stand there and he goes and he kind of looks and he and he
points at me and I nod like, yeah, I'm looking to park even though it's full and he and he
and he kind of hustles up to my car and he goes, you're looking to park?
Yeah.
I go, yeah.
I go, is your lot full?
He goes, I'm going to give you some VIP parking.
Whoa, I said, okay, and he goes, I'm right next to like the front of this little tiny
storefront business next to the larger lot that's full.
He goes, you're going to park right there in the lawn in front of that in front of that
business right there.
I said, what?
He goes, yeah, yeah, VIP parking, man.
And they go, okay, he goes, uh, $20 because that's how much it was to park in the lot.
It's $20.
Yeah.
In the chat says best case scenario and I can't agree more and and I'm living my dad
whips out the 20s.
I got you.
And I was like, yeah, dad, sure.
But I don't know if this guy works here.
Yeah.
He's like, you're going to park on that lawn.
I don't know if he hates that business, right?
And wants to just fuck with them by putting a big truck in front of it.
He's just out there causing havoc.
You are overthinking this.
I already would have been gone.
I'm going to give you some VIP parking.
Yeah.
So we give him 20 bucks.
He helps us guide us in and then he's looking at me because at first I go about it like
the wrong angle.
And he's going to be like, what a mess all.
And I'm like, this isn't my truck.
I don't know how to park trucks on lawns.
Of course.
This is your first truck on lawn experience.
And so, uh, uh, we finally get it in and as soon as I'm parked right, yeah.
He literally takes off.
He just runs.
He just runs away.
And that, that made you feel better.
I was like, what am I?
Does anyone know that I'm supposed to be, am I committing a crime?
Yeah.
So let me, I'm looking for the, for right now just to show you guys that I can, I can,
I can, uh, put it on social media when the, when the episode comes out.
Um, God damn it.
Where is it?
It's only gone for a few days.
Was there anything else on this guy's tie-dyed t-shirt?
Was it just tie-dyed?
Just tie-dyed.
So no, was he had to have a hat?
Grateful dead shirt.
It was just a hat.
Did he have any, like, uh, what are those things that the, uh, airline guys use?
Oh, that is just like a front lawn.
You just parked on somebody's lawn, filling up the front lawn.
Yeah.
And that's a, and that's a business in front of there.
What do they call those things?
I don't know.
Semaphore flags?
And, and there's a business there and that business was not like the guy didn't go inside
that business.
He just ran away.
So I was like, wonder if a guy was going to come out the door and be like, God damn it.
Yeah.
Park it on my lawn.
No, nothing.
Matt made somebody park on my lawn again.
It's probably his business and he's just going to go get a drink.
It's probably fine.
The kid was like 20.
I don't think it was his business, but oh shit.
Okay.
I was thinking it was an old guy.
And you know what?
I will say maybe because you know what we owe people bitch about other generations lately
as old man, uh, on the, you know, on the front lawn, um, the amount of young people that
I've run into working lately are crushing it, are doing great jobs working like the
super young people in the early twenties.
And the thought that popped in my head, I could be totally, I'm totally out of pocket
on this and I'll happily be corrected.
But I was wondering, I was like, Oh, the young people working now weren't working during
the pandemic.
That's true.
They didn't, they didn't have that weird bowling ball wrecking ball come and smash the way
they were getting by or anything like that.
Yeah, that's probably true.
And I feel like the people who were covering the pandemic and working and working in like
these, you know, food industry and like in hotels and low service industry, you know,
that kind of things really had a hard time coming back and like getting back to the grind.
And so we were like bitching about it as people who were using these services, right?
Right.
The young people are lately, I've just run into young people who are just crushing it,
just doing awesome.
And so they're just doing it.
Yeah.
And so I was like, I was wondering if it was just like, it's still like, I think it's still
like a, a pandemic versus non-pandemic thing, but maybe that's just my theory.
That's my theory or just some generations are better than others.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Those are the only two.
You know, it could be both.
It could be both.
Maybe you're just running into good young people.
There are a few out there.
Maybe everyone knows like the singularities around the corner.
So they're like, let's just work now.
It doesn't matter.
We're going to be just goo in five years.
It's fine.
I have heard from several sources, I'll tell you who else like Matt Donnelly really
admires a lot of very, very, very young people and that's the breaks, the breaks.
Like my dad's knees.
Today's show is brought to you by country Gators, Gator country, country tours.
That's right.
Country Gators, Gator country, country tours.
Hey y'all, I'm an alligator and I'm going to take you on tour if you're ready to go.
What I do is I take you through my swamp, what I like.
It's out in the country.
It's a country swamp.
And what you're going to find is a lot of these here trees, they got knot holes in them.
What looks like vaginas.
So I call them countries.
So you can fuck me if you want to.
I ain't saying don't, but I mean, you know, splinters and whatnot.
But you know, and some of them knot holes got critters in them.
You might find your wiener up against the squirrely squirrel.
So just be careful when you're doing it.
But most of the trees I have in my swamp got big old vagina looking knot holes on them.
The trees as I was saying, and yeah, that's what I do.
And also I'll eat the smallest member of your tour because that's part of my Gatoring ways.
I am still an alligator.
Gator country Gator.
What?
I'm supposed to not be a Gator?
Huh?
Yeah.
What?
I'm supposed to be nice?
Not eat you?
Yeah.
Man, I got you, I'll come up in here and fuck my trees and I ain't get allowed to eat one
of you at least.
Leaving a bunch of nut leavens in my trees, vaginas, and I can't have a little snackity
snack.
Please now.
Come on.
And her hate scoops to check out.
Nut leavens.
I just went back, I just got back from Portugal.
Did you see Bazzy?
Did you actually have an encounter?
No, we didn't have an encounter.
Bazzy, you missed out.
My trip to Portugal made me like New Jersey less.
Oh shit.
I can be offended except that I know what happened.
You know part of what happened.
No, like I literally have to fly back to, my sister's coming in from Paris.
She's staying at like a shore house and I am thinking of, not to get too far ahead of
the story here, but I'm thinking of flying into Maryland and driving up my brother to
fly out of Maryland because flying into Newark has been a disaster all summer.
Yeah, we lost an entire day from our vacation because of Newark.
I'll tell you, my wife would not recover from that if we were on a family vacation and lost
a day and got stuck in Northern New Jersey for a day instead of Portugal.
That would not be.
Did you have to stay overnight somewhere in New Jersey?
No, we stayed an extra night in Las Vegas so we were able to come back home.
We had a flight to Newark and then from Newark to Faro, Portugal, on the southern end of
Portugal there, and our flight to Newark got delayed, delayed, delayed, delayed, delayed
and then finally got delayed enough that we were going to miss our connecting flight on
the only flight to, to Faro and so we ended up just coming back home on Sunday morning
and we try to get on Monday morning, Monday morning at work.
It was, it was going to overshoot your destination?
No, we were going to get there too late for the connection.
Oh, I thought you said to Faro.
I was confused.
Trees with vaginas in them and shit.
I eat the smallest number.
To Faro.
And of course the reason we couldn't fly into Newark was because they did not have adequate
air traffic controllers in the tower there because fuck our government.
They fire everybody and then don't hire the, whatever.
No, I only read one article about it, but apparently it's crazy, but they are actually
are actively trying to recruit people to work in the air traffic control industry and it
is so, it has gotten so basically fratty, like people are so kind of like hard on the
new people and like, and like really break it down that people quit left and right and
don't stick with it.
Oh, it's super clicky to be a air traffic driver.
I mean, it's A, it's super difficult and then it's like all of this other shit on top of
it.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a strange thing and this is like one of those weird things you keep hearing
about like all these jobs are going away, but then you hear about things where like
we can't get enough people to do this job that we definitely want to hire people for
and those things, it's always so strange to kind of figure that all out, but I guess it's
super hard hours and then there are so many-
And of course, super stressful.
Super stressful.
Right?
Gigantic planes filled with people coming.
Yeah.
I was going to say, Carolyn Albert has scooped, she has talked to us a couple of times about
her air traffic controller stuff a little bit and yeah, air traffic controller stuff
is nuts.
Right?
That's nuts too, but we don't have to worry about that here in Vegas because no one's
coming.
No one's coming here.
That's right.
We got that.
Yes.
No problem with that.
We're building a new $20 billion airport here.
Now I keep seeing conflicting reports here because I keep seeing posts from Vital Vegas
and he just put one up yesterday or maybe even today it was like, the locals are like
you guys, nobody's coming, ring the deaf now.
And then-
I'm not there, but okay.
Right, but then other-
Jacob started doing weird pillow art on Etsy as a backup brand for-
Right?
Yeah.
I mean weird, okay, you say weird.
It's hurtful, but okay.
Restaurants or whatever are like, okay, yeah, we're not going to make as much this time.
But then he's like, but then also like Bally's just posted like, yeah, our room rates, our
room occupancy went from 99 to 97, we're still going to have a banner year, who cares?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so it's weird.
Like there's conflicting stuff, I guess.
I don't know.
There's, Vegas is just changing as it has done a couple of times in the times-
Vegas change?
I can't believe it.
It's just doing its change thing and people are going crazy about it the same way they
do every time.
Yeah.
I think like I actually see in our Zoom, we have Canadian Scoop Crystal labeled Canadian.
So Crystal, if you feel like unmuting to talk for a moment, we can actually check in with
the Canadian.
Self-identifies as Canadian.
Because one of the storylines is Canadians don't feel like coming to America.
No, we're not getting this.
You're not getting the snowbirds.
But-
Yeah, our Canadian tourism is way down.
Our international tourism in general is down.
So Canadian Scoop Crystal, is that the sentiment?
Is that true from where you're neck of the woods?
A lot of people don't want to go down to the States and they're kind of avoiding it.
I'm still coming to Scoop Fest, but it took some thinking up my arm to get my partner
to come with me.
Well, and I don't blame them.
And we appreciate you guys going for it.
Yeah.
It's a little scary.
You think we're going to be taken at the border, like that they could like hold us and-
We've already spoken to ICE and everybody to show them your Scoop Fest ticket and you'll
be fine.
Just be like, "Here.
I'm going to Scoop Fest."
They'll be, "Oh, right this way."
I wish I could completely allay your fears, but I cannot.
I don't know.
Well, you need to pack a fake tip sheet of where aliens are hiding out, illegal aliens
are hiding out.
And then be like, "Here you go.
I'm doing my part."
No.
It's-
No, I've had multiple Scoops write saying they don't want to be stopped in airports.
They don't want people going through their text messages or checking their social media
and that kind of stuff.
And I, in my gut, say that's very unlikely to happen, but I also can't go, "No."
Yeah.
I mean, I just came in through customs the other day in Philadelphia and it sure seemed
like everybody was having a very easy time, but that's one time and I don't know.
Yeah.
And Chris Gasman checking in the chat saying, "Of course, he doesn't want anyone going
through his pics," and that's for multiple reasons.
Mr. October, Mr. November, Chris the plumber, just-
It's because he keeps assigning himself as Mr. That Month.
Yeah.
It's the Gasman calendar.
They don't call him Nice Pipe because of his job as a plumber.
Do you know what I mean?
No, no, no.
They don't want to do those pics.
Crystal's got a kitty on the video there.
What's the kitty's name?
She's already muted.
She's done with us.
Well, we couldn't agree on names, and I have a boy too.
It's got two names?
No.
So, this is girl, and then I have another cat named boy.
Oh, how funny.
That's great.
You know what?
That's how couples stay together.
You compromise.
That's not unlike how we named our cats growing up.
We would name them Black Kitty and White Kitty and Mama Kitty, et cetera.
I like to be original, but I haven't been so much lately.
Yeah.
Kyra, that's original enough.
I also have a pet dog named Sonic.
That's lovely.
That's also not original.
I don't know how to tell you this.
What neck of the woods are you in Canada?
I live in Toronto.
Toronto.
Okay.
Do you hear a general sentiment that people don't want to come to America right now?
I feel like it's mostly from my partner being like, "Oh, no.
People don't want to go."
People aren't walking around saying, "Oh, we're not going to the U.S."
Right.
It'd be really weird if they were.
The first stop, I'd go whatever.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for chiming in.
I appreciate it.
Yes, Crystal.
Thank you.
We appreciate boots on the ground reporting like that.
We do.
No.
I think right now, it's specifically in the summertime.
In the summertime, we used to get a lot of European travelers that would come here to
Beijing, and they're not coming.
Also LA.
LA is right now currently on Tsunami Watch, still recovering from the fires, and obviously
had honestly been fighting political stuff in their own front yards.
Those people are not blowing off steam to make sure they come out to spend some money
at Vegas and hit the pools and the day clubs and all that stuff.
I think that's what it really is.
More than people not wanting to travel and everything, nobody's in that mood to blow
off steam.
That's it.
Everybody's got shit going on wherever they are.
Nobody's trying to come here and put a 20 in a slot machine.
No.
Sure.
Can I get it?
Maybe occupancy is only slightly down, but I can tell you if people who are in shows
that the show attendance is way down.
Now, show attendance goes down in these months anyway, but they're going away.
I also, anecdotally, traveling around, talking to people who would come to Vegas.
My brother said it best, "Vegas has become spirit airlines."
Mark, not Brian, not my hero, but my asshole brother who would not come and get me.
He said-
Well, you knew better than to call it.
I'm interested in this analogy here.
Why is Vegas now spirit airlines?
I think I know right where this is going.
It seems like it's cheap to come, but as soon as you come you get charged for everything
left and right.
As soon as you turn anywhere, suddenly you're just nickel and dimed and charged for every
single fucking thing you do.
You leave feeling like, "Holy shit.
I thought I was going to spend a lot of money and I did, and I didn't even gamble, and I
only saw one thing, and I'm leaving broke."
It's becoming a real buzzkill for the town.
It seems like some places are starting to combat that.
It seems like people here seem to be realizing that, and some people seem to be going the
other direction on that, but it hasn't caught on in the big time yet.
No.
Like I said, these are small temporary measures that people are taking just for the summer.
Some people are waiving resort fees, some people are waiving parking fees, and that's
exactly what this whole town needs to get back to doing as a whole.
Yeah.
Free parking.
I think also it's a comment on the fact that gambling has just become so ubiquitous.
You can just gamble on your phone.
I'm sure.
It's funny because it's these companies that spearheaded it.
That's the weird thing.
Yeah.
You think Vegas would be protectionist, but these companies aren't protectionist of Vegas.
They're simply saying, "If anyone's going to gamble anywhere, it should be through our
company."
Right.
There still is a Vegas element connected to it all.
That bet in MGM is like, that's their whole tagline, it's like, "The casino created in
Vegas."
Da, da, da, da.
But it's simply not as exciting to sit in front of a slot machine at Mammoth Racetrack
in Ocean, New Jersey and spend a day pulling levers there.
That's just not going to create the same deal.
No.
Right.
Well, I can tell you out here, we got these fucking skill games.
You ever heard of these fucking things?
Oh, yeah.
What are skill games?
Skill games.
I put a fiver and was like, "You got to go try the skill game."
I'm like, "All right.
Whatever."
I put a fiver in.
I didn't know what the fuck I was doing.
It is confusing and weird.
I didn't understand it.
It had a bunch of symbols.
You press stuff, you lose your $5.
It takes a little longer.
It doesn't make any damn sense.
Didn't make any damn sense to me whatsoever.
I was like, "What am I doing with this thing?
I need a lesson on the skill games."
But I don't know.
It just seemed really, really dumb.
I don't have the skill.
That's true, Wayne.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think that's it.
You went into a skill game unskilled.
What did you expect, buddy?
No.
I don't know.
I didn't understand what I was even doing.
The good news is that we're protected from the aliens that are coming because they can't
afford all the resort fees and the cocktails.
Well, apparently, it's not even aliens.
It's just a theoretical thing, about a seven-mile wide comet.
It passed the comet test.
It did.
It took a test.
There's a little box at the bottom that said, "Check if you are a comet," and it checked
it.
I checked it.
I am a comet.
Comet.
And Ranch Slunk is asking, "What is the part that is skill?"
I don't know.
I played it for 15 minutes, and I'm like, "I don't understand what's going on here."
All has never known what part of it was skill.
I take it back.
My memory's getting jogged.
I do remember.
Once you get to the bonus round, I basically was playing Simon.
The bonus round was Simon, and I made it through five things, and then I fucking messed up
the pattern.
That's the skill, but it still made no fucking sense.
So yeah.
All right.
Nathan's letting us know that this is all a big buildup.
By next year, it will be fuck Mary skill.
That's right.
Fuck Mary skill.
Yeah.
I tell you who else is going to fuck Mary and skill, and that's the following sponsor.
A new service that helps Paul buy back all his toys when he feels seller's remorse.
That's from the Red Baron in 2021.
The last one, by the way, is from Country Scoop.
This is a service that helps Paul buy back all of his toys when he feels seller's remorse.
Hey, what's going on?
It's me, Country Gator.
I actually also run an Etsy shop, and I deal in secondhand toys and collectibles.
But I tell you what, if you in the market for an original Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle,
or maybe an old school transformer, I got you covered.
But really, it's a front, and I sell logs.
I sell logs that have the vagina part, knot holes in them, and I can get them across country
lines.
So you can look up, you can say, I'm buying me a toy.
It's a toy, all right, but it's a special toy.
Yeah.
It's a knot hole tree that you can put your willy in, and I can't guarantee there ain't
going to be no squirrely's in there still.
I can't say for sure.
But also, if you do just want to go to trip down Nostalgia Lane, buy yourself an old toy
that you used to have, you can get it.
Just come on over to my Etsy shop.
It's Country Gator's Conti Toys.
Yeah.
Wow.
So it's Conti Toys, huh?
Yeah.
It's one of those things where you do your advertisements, and you make them real controversial,
and then people are like, oh.
Did you say countryversal?
Countryversal.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like Schmuckers.
You know, Conti Toys, they must have something on the ball, calling themselves that shit.
Sure enough.
Enter Hayscrumbs to check out.
Now are the toys Conti, or are they for Conti children?
They can be.
Anything's a dildo if you're brave enough, friend.
Guys, I just got a text.
I'm so glad.
It's Amazon looking out for me.
They texted me and 19 other people who happen to have a North Jersey area code, their phone
number.
Oh boy.
That's just more convenient.
They're looking out for safety and quality issues, a product that I bought.
They won't say which one until I click on the link.
No, of course not.
Safety is their top priority.
Yeah.
So there we go.
I don't want to, I don't know.
That shit was on the rise for a while, but it seems a little more prevalent in the last
couple of months.
Am I crazy?
I don't know.
I get, I get, I get, I get every day, every day, but I'm getting a lot of these fucking
spammy things.
Yeah.
In my day.
All I know is that Democrats are feeling more confident because in the recent days I've
gotten a ton of different people asking me for money.
And I think that's hilarious.
And I always hate when it's like, Oh, did you see Pete Buddha judge just top roped Trump
into submission with this, I swear to God every time I am so done.
I don't know who thinks that messaging is working anymore, but it is fucking not.
It is not working for anyone because nothing's changing.
Nothing's changing.
Nothing's happening.
Now, if someone sends me a things like this motherfucker ran off the Senate floor with
a can of barbersaw and a razor blade and shave that motherfucker's eyebrows off, I'd be like,
here's $20.
Click.
Thank you.
Here's $20.
Clicking on that.
I appreciate your fucking service, but nobody's doing anything of any meaning or merit.
So it's just preposterous.
Yeah.
I did see, they made me laugh.
It showed, it was an AI image.
It showed Trump using a comb over and his hair is covering the Epstein files on top
of his head.
It really, it really made me laugh.
It is the strangest.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, that's really funny.
It is the strangest fucking thing at this point, right?
Yes.
It is just, I mean, we are, we are through the looking glass here, people.
I mean, it's, it's bizarre, right?
There's no defense for any of this.
And I think that's the other crazy thing is there's a lot of folks like us who, you know,
we hear these talking points of like, Oh, Bill Clinton might be on that list.
Fuck that asshole.
Get them all.
Bury him under the jail.
I don't give a rat's dick.
Put them all in the cemetery.
Yes.
Everything should be, collapse the whole government at this point.
I don't give a good goddamn.
And I think-
I'm going to steer off from that, from the, from the government conversation in a very
easy way.
I could tell you about my trip to Portugal this last week.
Yeah, it's just, yeah, it's just, yeah, there you go, Scoli.
Thank you very much.
Scoli's on, Scoli's on point.
That's all you need.
That meme is what we're living right now.
Absolutely.
The hot dog guy.
We're all looking for the guy who did this.
So we get down to Portugal.
We fly into Faro in the south end of Portugal.
Yeah.
It's fantastic.
And Guia or Gaia, depending on, on how you say it, different people said it different
ways.
Derived from mother earth.
Yes.
Well, I mean, it sounds like that.
Yeah.
I didn't name it.
Did you find out what Portugal means?
In America, we pronounce it grapes, Jacob.
Grapes.
Yeah.
Like bossy, the Portuguese scoop in the chat here says Gaia.
Okay.
And then another friend of mine says Gaia and then people there, some people there said
Guia.
Some people there said Gaia.
I stopped saying the name entirely just to be safe.
I bet you it's a bit to just correct Taurus no matter what they say.
Fine.
If it was good bit Jacob, it's pronounced Chimera, but go on.
So we hung around up there.
It was just wonderful.
Our friends, Scott and Paula, we hung out with them and boy, we had great food.
We had all kinds of just wonderful experiences there, a couple of different beaches.
What was your favorite meal, Jacob?
Oh boy.
We had a meal at a winery that was just fantastic.
We also had this spicy chicken at one place that was, it's a main dish of the region and
it was so fucking good.
It's like a hot oil that gets poured over the chicken.
It gets cooked at a really high temperature for a short amount of time.
It's just quick fried?
It's not fried.
It's not fried at all.
It's like roasted.
I assume that there is some kind of preparation to it as well.
I don't know if they soak it in the spicy oil or whatever first.
Marinade?
Yeah.
I don't know if they do any kind of like the marinade or whatever, but it is so fucking
good.
Slap it.
The slap cook it, remember?
That's right.
They give it a good old slap cook it.
Period, period.
That's it.
Winter scoop.
Thank you.
Period, period.
Chicken.
That slap cooking chicken is the wildest fucking thing.
Slap cook that chicken.
Those videos are awesome.
Those will forever stay in my brain, slap cooking the chicken.
Well that's cool.
So we did that for a few days and then we took the train north to Lisbon and I'll tell
you about the part in Lisbon because everything in the south was very relaxed.
We had just a wonderful time.
So much beautiful scenery.
It was a wonderful week.
It doesn't make for the best stories on the comedy podcast.
So I'm going to tell you about Lisbon instead.
We got on the train to Lisbon.
First of all, we got off the train earlier than we were planning to.
We had booked a passage to this one station and we decided to get off a couple of stations
earlier once we got to Lisbon because we were like, oh, it's a little closer to our hotel.
It's in the area that we want to be in.
We're just going to get off here.
So we get off the train.
It's pronounced Lebanon.
Sorry.
We get off the train in Lebanon, Kentucky.
It was a very long train ride, very wet.
So we got off the train.
The fact that my hometown was called Lebanon.
I know.
Look, Lebanon is fucking crazy.
Life is crazy.
Don't forget.
SJ went to high school in Palestine.
It's not just Kentucky.
No, it's not.
They're all.
So we get into an Uber and the Uber driver that we got in in Lisbon spoke the least amount
of English of any one that we had interacted with the entire time.
Perfect.
So everybody spoke English at least to a passable degree.
No problem at all.
We get in the car and the first thing I say to this guy is that do you speak any English?
And he goes, he holds up his fingers very close together and goes, very little.
All right.
No big deal.
Now did you think I can use Google Translate or one of these automatic?
Oh, we had been doing, we had been doing that to some degree, but he, he spoke enough English
and you know, it's an Uber.
So he's already got the destination.
We don't have to have a conversation.
Did you think about just yelling English slowly at him?
That does seem to work, right?
I started really over pronouncing English words loudly.
The winery please.
Turn left here.
Oh boy.
But it's no big deal.
He doesn't speak a lot of English.
No big deal.
He's got, he knows where we're going.
He's going to drive it.
It's a 20 minute drive.
So he says in broken English, he says, get comfortable.
It's going to be a little bit of a drive.
No big deal.
We go great.
And so we sit back.
We're having a little conversation between ourselves.
We're kind of figuring out what we're going to do that evening.
How many are in the car?
And then a small, a small pane of glass comes up separating him from the group and then
gas just fuels into the back of us.
You all wake up in bathtubs with a phone next to you.
Your kidneys have been taken.
We ride in silence for about 10 minutes.
And then he started talking and his lack of English did not stop him for long.
How strange.
Yeah.
So he initiates a new conversation and he just starts talking to us.
In English, in as much English as he, as he could.
And so we're, we're having a bit of a conversation with him and then he starts talking about
the blacks.
Oh no.
Quote unquote.
No, no, no, no, no.
And he starts telling us how the blacks are taking his, are taking his jobs.
Oh my God.
And we are sitting there going like, what the actual fuck?
Why is this guy telling us about the blacks?
And he talked about the blacks for about five minutes.
Yeah.
And then he said something about Uber.
Right.
He went, Oh, Oh motherfucker.
He's talking about Uber black language barrier.
He's talking about cause he drove an Uber comfort.
Okay.
And so he was saying there's more and more Uber blacks now, and they're taking business
away from the Uber comforts.
Don't let, don't let these people know about the Uber blacks.
That's, that's the last thing they need.
That's the last talking point.
I am sitting in this guy's back seat.
It is, it is very nice Tesla that he's driving us around and I am just laughing to myself
relieved right, he was talking about the Uber blacks and not the black and then he pointed
at a black person on the side of the street and said, Oh, I don't pick them up.
No, no, he did not.
He did.
Oh, for God's sake.
It was a, I was like, Oh God damn it.
So he was actually talking about it.
No, he wasn't.
He wasn't.
He was talking about Uber blacks.
You wrote the full roller coaster of racism, right?
But this guy's clearly an idiot.
So maybe he thinks Uber blacks is just for black people.
Maybe, maybe what a dim wit.
And so he, he then tells us, he says, he's, he's taking us to an area.
Our hotel in Lisbon is in an area, kind of at a downtown area.
And right, right nearby there, there's an area called pink street and pink street used
to be, I guess the, the red light district, it was the brothels and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
There's restaurants and bars and there's a lot of live music there, which is why SJ and
I were, you know, heading in that direction.
We're going to, we're going to go hang out in the, in the, in the pink street area that
evening and listen to some live music.
It's going to be great.
We're really looking forward to it.
And then he starts telling us that this is after the conversation about the blacks.
And then he starts telling us that, oh, by the way, don't go to pink street tonight.
And we had not said that we were going to pink street, but the hotel was just nearby.
And so he goes, don't go to pink street.
Under no circumstances, go to pink street.
That's all we say.
Why?
And he goes, and then he goes on his second racist tirade of the ride, but this time it's
about the Roma.
Oh, and so, and so then he said selling telling us how the Roma are in town and they are shooting
each other on, on pink street.
But that's a festival tradition, the shooting of each other.
Right?
You ever been to a San Gennaro?
Come on.
What are we talking about?
Roma the Bulls in Pamplona?
Everyone knows the Roma just shoot each other on pink street.
That's just.
And at this point, I really am just sitting there going like, I'm ready for this ride
to be over.
It is a celebration of the patron saint of ammunition.
You celebrate him.
Bossy in the chat is, is hurrying the story log and tell it saying that of course that's
not true.
And of course, bossy is 100% correct.
Right.
Spoiler alert.
There was no shooting of anyone.
And yes, we hung out everywhere.
We wanted to hang out.
This guy is just a racist asshole.
That's it.
And honestly, the entire ride and still right now, I think he was being racist, but I'm
not entirely sure because it really may have just been a language barrier.
No, no, I'm telling you, I'm still, I'm, I'm pretty sure he was being at least racist
some of the time, but yeah, oh, about the Roma, he was definitely being racist.
He was deaf.
Sorry.
Let me be very clear.
He was definitely being racist about the Roma.
I'm not sure if he was being racist towards people who were dark in skin color as well.
Jason has a great question for you in the chat, Jacob.
Oh, what is it?
Did you give him five stars or did you get out of the group?
I honestly don't think that I ever got back around to reviewing and doing all the stuff.
Yeah.
You're too stupefied.
So he tells us like, Oh yeah, don't, don't go down there.
It's dangerous.
Whatever.
We finally get out of the car and we're like, our hotel was literally above pink street.
Like you had to walk out of our hotel and walk down like a ramped alley and you were
on pink street.
So I mean, we were directly above it.
We were in such a party area of this, of this place here that our very nice hotel gave us
earplugs to sleep in.
Oh my gosh.
And rightly so.
Really?
Absolutely correct.
How long, how, how late into the night did the party go?
I mean, by the time I fell asleep, it was still going.
What was, in Portuguese, how do you say to the bric-a-bric-a-dawn it's on?
That's a bric-a-dawn.
Oh, okay.
That's actually, that's actually Portuguese.
Universal.
Yeah.
That sounds right.
Did you understand that you were going to be staying in that type of an area when you
shopped for your vacation?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, we were only staying there overnight because we were flying out the next morning.
So we were only in that hotel one night.
And, and you, coming from New Orleans, you've done your share of Mardi Gras and Fat Tuesdays.
We understood what we were getting into.
You know what it's about.
Right, right, right.
We, we were not, we were not upset by this.
We were just, we understood what we were getting into when we, when we stayed in that area.
It's actually funny because I was on my flight back from Connecticut to Vegas, there was,
there was some Roma on my flight and they just shot each other right there, right there
on the aisles.
Just right there?
Just dead.
Just two, two shot dead.
Oh yeah.
And he went into all this stuff.
He was like, uh, he went into all this stuff about how you can identify aroma if we, if
we see them.
Oh, we're not identifying aroma.
This is getting weird.
He was telling us how they all wear white t-shirts, which I thought was very vague.
I was like, okay, that's weird.
And then he started telling us about how they all had, um, he didn't say the words meth
teeth, but he was saying meth teeth.
Summer teeth.
Yeah.
That's it.
He was saying their teeth are a little meth-y.
Uh, so we went to pink street though, and we had a wonderful time.
Uh, we, we went and saw some musicians.
It was great.
We had some, we had some cocktails.
It was really wonderful.
Uh, we walked, well, we, we went and had a nice dinner in Lisbon first and, uh, walked
all over and looked at some, uh, some different statues and walked down by the pier.
It was all great.
We got to pink street and literally, I don't want to overstate this.
I don't want to make it clear that this is not me exaggerating for the show.
Within the first five minutes of us just walking around on pink street, I was offered cocaine
three times, not drugs, not party favors, specifically cocaine.
I was offered that, uh, just walking out of Cozumel at like noon, so I don't think that's
a, I just like, I turn and walk onto the street and the first person I see literally makes
eye contact with me, puts his finger to the side of his nose to gesture for cocaine and
then says, want some cocaine?
Are you sure that wasn't Santa Claus?
Cause that's his move.
There must've been some magic in that old white powder he found.
I was like, why did you gesture for the cocaine if you're going to explicitly offer me the
cocaine?
Well, there are other ways to take it.
Sure.
As Paul takes it, you can take it intravenously.
Or he could, you know, he might've, you don't want to go up to the drug dealer who's like
pointing to his asshole.
Cocaine?
Do you want some Bolivian gunpowder?
Bolivian marching powder in your shorts?
Do you want Bolivian marching powder, which is slang for cocaine?
Would you like some of that?
Do you ski?
Would she of course insert penally?
And by ski, I mean, do you, do you do mountains of cocaine?
So we've got three, three offers of cocaine in the first five minutes, uh, two offers,
two more offers.
It was candy with a candy is cocaine for your nose.
So it's not made of cocaine, but cocaine, not even a whole lot of cocaine.
It was great.
Uh, there were traffic circles in the area that we were in, especially there were traffic
circles everywhere.
Uh, not a lot of streetlights, which I kind of enjoyed.
Yep.
Yeah.
Roundabout traffic circles.
Uh, we saw one fella, uh, at a, at a large traffic circle, you know, in the city, uh,
big, big roundabout, uh, you know, huge statue in the middle of the whole deal.
And uh, anyhow, you get on a roundabout and you get on a roundabout, it might have a four
entry exit points and it'll say like, oh, you get off on the second exit or you get
off on the third exit in the roundabout and that's how you, that's how you do the roundabouts.
We saw one guy in the middle of Lisbon, uh, turned the wrong way onto the roundabout and
uh, he was yelling and it looked like crying all at the same time while, while they were
trying to figure it out.
I just wanted a can of Coke, an actual can.
That's it.
He just, he was just trying to get somewhere and he, he didn't know how to drive in Lisbon
and he was very strong.
Oh my God.
Bossey says there's a city with 32 roundabouts there.
Oh yeah.
I would lose my fucking mind.
In the South especially, we, we saw like two traffic lights the whole, the whole time we
were in the South of Portugal.
They're building more and more of those out here in Pennsylvania and nobody knows how
to use them and I am also in that club and I do not like them and I do not like them
building all these roundabouts.
They are more efficient.
You're, you're right.
Pete, people in, in, uh, people in the chat are talking about how they are much more efficient
than a treat street lights and they are just correct.
If you have people who can use them, right.
There is a bit of a learning curve.
There's also a regular curve.
There's, there's a 360 degrees of learning curve on those motherfuckers.
Oh, cause there's a circle.
Yeah.
What else is around your nostril?
Do you want some cocaine?
Oh my God.
I walked right into it.
This man won't stop offering me cocaine.
So we get on the flight the next morning.
We head to the airport the next morning.
Uh, we get through the Lisbon airport, which the Lisbon airport is confusing by the way,
if anybody ever flies through the Lisbon airport, give yourself an extra few minutes.
Yeah.
To, uh, navigate the Lisbon airport.
Uh, but we got there, all the air traffic controllers run cocaine.
You know what?
Whatever they were doing and they're very clicky, but they show up, but they show up.
They show up.
So we get there, we get on the flight.
We're going to Philadelphia this time.
We're not doing new work anymore.
We're going to Philadelphia.
So we get on the flight to Philadelphia, by the way, I really appreciated my seat mate,
the stranger sitting next to me.
Uh, it was a seven hour flight.
She did not speak to me until there was about half an hour left in that flight.
And then we had just a very pleasant conversation for the last half hour before we left.
A pro.
What a pro.
Look at you go.
I appreciated that so much.
Was this an American that you were seated next to?
Uh, this was an American.
Yes.
Was it your wife?
It was not my wife.
She was seated on a different row.
Oh, you guys don't fly together?
Uh, we, we ended up not flying together on that leg.
I forget why.
I think it was just too full or something.
My wife likes to do like, you know, like there's a, there's a tier of cheap seat where you
don't choose your, your, your, your seat and so you can lose that gamble.
And it sounds like maybe that's, that's what happened there.
That may have happened here because SJ did set up these flights, so I'm not entirely
sure, but yeah, something happened on this one and we weren't sitting together.
Did I tell you guys about my return flight from Vegas last time that I was...
No.
Were there, were there any dirty filthy Roma's on there?
Not that I could tell, but I did fuck up.
Were there anyone in white t-shirts?
Cause those were the Roma's.
Are Roma's from Italy?
Where are Roma's supposed to, supposedly from?
What's the culture of Roma?
I don't even know.
The...
It's, it's what we used to call gypsies.
Okay.
Got it.
Romanians.
That's it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Uh.
Thank you.
Everybody chiming in.
Yeah.
Cause Roma to me is always like a lot of like Italian places have like Roma as a, as a Italian
pronunciation of Rome.
They're a small tomato.
Yeah.
They are a small tomato.
Well, I, I messed up and didn't get my pre-book Southwest early registry thing, so I was pretty
late on getting on the plane.
You were at the end of the line.
Yeah.
On the plane.
So I sat in the middle of two people.
The lady to my right was at the window.
She was fine.
The guy in the aisle next to me was having issues.
Oh no.
Cause we were coming out of Vegas.
So the air conditioning was up and coming into Pittsburgh, he was shaking and rocking
like he was freezing to death.
I don't know why he didn't ask for a blanket or something.
I don't know.
He was having issues and he brought an entire sandwich on the flight with him.
Rookie.
Yeah.
Oh, rookie for sure.
For sure.
Not an experienced traveler, smelly enough that I was like, I, I, I know what you're
eating.
Yeah.
He should have, he should have just dumped all the innards of the sandwich and hide inside
the bread like, like Skywalker.
That would have been the move is like turn that into a tauntaun for your arm, buddy.
Oh, you know, but no, he, uh, he didn't, but he was, he was shaking, shaking like a leaf
leaf.
It was strange.
Did you feel like he was going to lose it or do you think it was just done out of, uh,
coldness?
Once or twice.
I was cut.
I got a little like, what is happening, bud, but he didn't an eye on him once or twice.
I was keeping an eye on him once or twice, but he didn't, he didn't go completely off
the rails.
Uh, but I didn't, I didn't sleep that flight at all.
Uh, I was just listening to podcasts.
Did you think to offer him a coat like a gentleman?
Did you think to, uh, had I been wearing any extra garments?
I might, I may have, but I was, you know, here, take my pants.
I was just in Vegas, you know, pajama mode.
Basically.
I'm wearing my sweats and a t-shirt.
I was just ready to go.
So, uh, yeah, it was easy peasy.
I don't even think I had a jacket on, um, yeah, I was just rolling and it's different
for men of size.
Did you think if he was maybe rocking, did you think to maybe cradle him?
Maybe just like support him, lift him up a little bit.
I did it.
Ranch Lunk says possibly autism.
No, I don't think this was the case.
Uh, he was truly just cold.
Oh man.
Speaking of autism on my flight home, I watched the accountant too.
Oh, I watched the accountant too on my flight home.
Ben Affleck playing an autistic person made me very uncomfortable.
I'm so happy.
I was watching it going like, this can't be okay.
And uh, the great actor, is it John Berenthal, is that his name?
I think so.
Yeah.
The Punisher.
He's so good in it.
Yes.
And he's his brother.
He's Ben Affleck's brother in this.
I was like, thank God he is in this movie.
And this movie was in the middle of seven rewrites and they pressed go.
I mean, some of it's like a, like a romp, like buddy comedy, like, like, like, uh, like,
uh, uh, was it Will Smith and, uh, bad boys.
Oh, bad boys.
Yeah.
Some of it has, yeah.
A lot of us like got like bad boy humor moments.
Some of it's like, some of it's like Taylor's share, like right out of a Taylor Sheridan
show, uh, uh, where they're like, they go into like a honky tonk bar and that's like,
they get like an old fashioned honky tonk bar is the weirdest scene in cinema.
It doesn't need to be at all.
It doesn't make a damn bit of sense.
And then they don't show the fight sequence, which I'm like, they go for like a gag.
We're like, Oh shoot.
And then just shows guys like coming out of a window and they get in a car and right off
like a Taylor Sheridan show, like a Taylor shirt.
And I was like, and I literally was like, I was like, what, why am I watching an action
movie where you skip the fight sequences?
This movie is filled with hyper violence the entire time and we skip over the bar fight
scene.
This was like, what is it happening?
And Ben Affleck, I guess he like studied a particular kid and has a good relationship
with him.
And he already did this in the accountant one, which I didn't watch because I heard he was
playing an autistic person in the first one.
Um, but I love John Baranthal.
So I was like, wait, wait, you didn't see accountant one?
No.
How did you keep up?
How did you keep up in accountant two plot wise, man?
And it is just the strangest, like it is both like, it is scored like a nineties thriller.
There are parts of it that are like John Wick-like, like where it's like this network of people
that just keep reporting to other people and like an underbelly and both sides have too
much access to like crazy amounts of information.
One woman's trying to like just be like a good voice in it.
Like it's all over the place.
It is really, really is.
There is so much going on at all times in this movie.
It's ridiculous.
It is a chaotic C plus of a movie and I, I not only watched the accountant too.
I also watched the Jason Statham vehicle.
The beekeeper.
Oh, I was, I saw a beekeeper when it came out.
I love Jason Statham.
I was like, these are both very much Matt Donnelly movies.
But Beekeeper doesn't waver.
No, Beekeeper is a good old, it's Jason Statham just doing Jason Statham stuff.
By the numbers, right?
Just what you want.
Hyperviolence.
No, they don't, they don't take a break for me to feel good.
They don't try to make me laugh.
It is just, you shouldn't have messed with them.
He was trying to retire too bad.
He's killing all y'all.
I'm looking forward to Nobody 2, which apparently is the exact same movie.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I love Nobody 1.
So yeah, I'll take Nobody 2.
It was great.
No, no.
I mean, here's the thing.
I like the idea of portraying autistic people in mainstream movies.
Of course.
We have this thing where we like, we don't like when actors now try to portray different
things like you, you know, unless you are blind, you shouldn't play blind or whatever,
all that stuff.
Do you agree with any of that?
Ben Affleck is not a transformative actor.
He never has been.
Ben Affleck always plays versions of Ben Affleck that we like him doing, charming guy, trying
to do good things.
Yeah.
You know, he's not Gary Oldman.
He's not like, I don't know.
You know what I mean?
What?
He's not?
That's what I mean.
There are actors we would give credit to like really go and play.
You know what though?
I mean, the Gary Oldman, have you seen the one where he plays the little person on his
knees?
No, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
My point.
I didn't want my point to boomerang so quickly.
No, no, no, no.
I'm just wrong.
Never mind.
Gary Oldman does a whole movie on his knees.
All right.
Forget everything Ben just said.
We're going to edit that part out.
No big deal.
Cut out shoes.
We're editing that whole part out.
That's fine.
Take, take two.
Boop.
We don't give Ben Affleck the credit of being a transformative actor.
Like I don't even know who.
I can't think of anyone right now.
Like other actors.
Like other actors, but we sometimes allow other actors to kind of be transformative different
characters.
Yeah.
Is it just because we used to do it?
No, this, I know what Matt means.
I couldn't get it out of my head the entire film.
Yeah.
The whole time.
Every time he does it, you just go, oh my God, that's Ben Affleck trying to be autistic.
That's all.
Like you're just watching him act and going like, oh, how do you feel great about this?
Yeah.
Oh, the Gary Oldman movie on his knees is called Tiptoes, apparently, according to Winners
School.
Oh, geez.
He's, he's, he's brothers.
He's brothers with McConaughey.
Oh boy.
And McConaughey is a full-sized man, whereas Gary Oldman plays a smaller man and it's outrageous.
And McConaughey doesn't like him.
Like he has beef with his brother.
It's very strange.
What kind of beef?
Short rib?
Short rib beef.
Short rib beef?
Oh my God, Paul's playing a clip and it just showed a split second of Gary Oldman being
tiny.
Doing the thing.
Oh, that's, that's not great.
It's the preview.
Oh my gosh.
So that Paul stops showing this video, I'm going to bookend my Portugal story.
His mom and dad are regular, see, and they, and the mom and dad of the other people, it's
just like, it's outrageous.
Anyway, uh, yeah, no, that's horrible.
It's just crazy because, but Gary Oldman's, I mean, have you seen True Romance?
That's a wild swing from Gary Oldman too.
But I like a lot of his stuff.
I think he does, you know.
He takes wild swings.
Okay.
Here's an example.
When he played a crazy vampire, right?
And, uh, what was it?
A Nosferatu or whatever, or what was it?
Dracula.
Bram Stoker's Dracula.
Bram Stoker's Dracula, right?
I would want to see Ben Affleck in the same amount of makeup doing like a crazy old vampire.
You're absolutely right.
He couldn't pull off full makeup Affleck.
Yeah.
He's just, he's meant to be just like likable, relatable guy in whatever role he's playing.
He's that Boston guy over there.
That's why Batman didn't work for him because he's got 80% of it.
That's why.
Well, I mean, Snyder didn't do him any favors, but he's got 80% of it, but the Snyder take
on Batman was so morose and unhappy.
And when you introduce him in basically a 9/11 scenario, it's like, where do we go from
here?
9/12.
Well, I mean, it was, it was 9/12.
It was, it was Superman causing 9/12 basically.
Oh, I went and saw the new Superman movie the other day.
Yeah.
I was so bored.
Was it?
It was boring to you?
I was just so fucking bored the entire time.
I saw it, I was like, I just don't give a shit.
Animal adaptions went up like 500% after that movie came out.
Oh, that makes sense.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Cause it's all about the, the super dog is all over the place.
Apparently Crypto's the star.
Yes.
Yeah.
Which that credit to James Gunn knowing what he's doing, right?
I agree.
They took two really big swings because you have to try to reinvent the wheel a little
bit.
Yeah.
And yet you still have to deliver a blockbuster.
And they started the movie where it would be the start of the third act in any other
superhero movie.
They start the movie in the middle and it's not, there's no, there's no origin story or
whatever.
Again, I think we pointed out another episode, but none of us had seen it yet.
At one point he ends up back at his home that he was raised in Kansas and it pans around.
Lois looks around and sees, oh, this is the room that he grew up in.
He's been so secretive about his life and yet here is his home and it pans to a shelf
that has a bunch of trophies on it.
And I'm just like, what was Superman doing in high school?
He just was going ham.
Just fucking wrecking people in wrestling.
What?
Football?
Basketball?
Speech and debate.
It's speech and debate.
What was he doing?
It's like, it's like that moment in the Incredibles where they, where Dash is doing the, yeah,
track and field.
The race.
Oh yeah.
Track and field.
What?
He's like, whoa.
Pull it back.
I was like, what are those trophies for?
What the fuck were you doing, Clark?
Debate club.
Ranch slugs.
That's debate club.
And maybe you're right.
It could have been forensics.
Who knows?
It could have been all trophies for spirit of the Latin club.
Oh, you only get little medallions for that.
No.
Yeah.
They didn't look like.
The woman in front of me on the flight was watching, she was also watching a fine film.
She was watching speed two cruise control.
I appreciate, I appreciate this person watching speed two cruise control on this plane.
The same danger as speed one, but now in knots.
Now on the boat.
Who was that Keanu replacement?
What did he end up doing?
Oh, I forget his name.
He had a little run.
I forget his name.
He did.
Jason Patrick.
Yes.
Yeah.
Anyway, Jacob, please.
Oh, I was going to tell you this too.
Your Portugal story.
Yeah.
So the woman on the flight back watching this woman watch speed two cruise control, they
serve a meal on the flight back and I saw the meal and it was some kind of chicken something
or something like that.
And they had a couple of other options.
I wasn't especially hungry.
So when the flight attendant comes by with the meals, I just said, Hey, I don't want
the meal.
Do you have like a little snacky something though, like a bag of chips or some pretzels
or something like that?
And she goes, I do, but it'll take me a few minutes.
I said, Oh, no, I'm not in a hurry.
No problem at all.
I make my own pretzels.
I make my own nacho sauce.
Whatever you get through doing whatever you're doing, no problem.
I'll, I'll be right here.
And she got a smile and was like, great.
And so she walks away, she finishes up and then like 10 minutes later, she comes back
and has two bags of salt and pepper potato chips and two little bags of pretzels and
hands me those four items.
And I go, Oh, this is, this is great.
Thank you so much.
This will last me.
Uh, you know, for the, for the rest of the time, uh, great.
Thank you.
And I have my drink and I'm, I'm happy as a clam.
I'm sitting there.
I'm watching a little movie.
Wayne says that'll be $73.
All gratis, all gratis.
Nice.
So, so, uh, I'm sitting there, I'm enjoying that.
And then I hear behind me in the, in the road directly behind me, um, woman says, Hey, I
never got my chicken because they had, I guess they had run out of, of chicken for the meals
at some point.
Ma'am, we're still, we're still slapping it, ma'am.
We're still slapping.
We're slapping it as fast as we can.
It's harder to slap at this altitude.
You understand?
And so they had brought over all the plates and everything, all the meals.
And then for like two or three people right in that area, they had run out of the chicken.
And so they had gone to get more chicken from the, from the galley or whatever.
And they come back and they serve those people chicken.
And I guess this one woman had missed the, uh, the chicken on the, on the second round.
Okay.
And so she ate her, uh, her plate of food and then she, uh, was mad that she had not
had any chicken.
So here comes the guy cleaning up.
He's not even the, uh, the guy serving food.
He's just the cleanup guy.
Yeah.
And so he's coming along.
He's cleaning up.
He's collecting the garbage and she says to him very loudly and I'm sitting at the window.
She is sitting in the window directly behind me.
And so all I can do, I can't see her.
I can just hear her and she says, look, I never got my chicken in my meal.
And at this point I thought she was kidding because I was like, this is such a ridiculous
thing.
I think this woman is fooling around.
She's laughing and clapping good bit, ma'am, a little bit, a little bit good bit.
And I w I was like genuinely smiling and like, Oh, this woman's going to do a bit about where
she yells about not getting chicken now.
Nope.
Wasn't doing a bit.
And by the way, chicken is code for cocaine.
I would like cocaine, please.
I can tell you one thing about Portugal is they don't use code words for cocaine.
Under no circumstance will they use code words for cocaine.
Oh, you thought you were getting cocaine?
No, sir.
I said chicken.
I explicitly said chicken.
I said chicken that I didn't, I didn't say cocaine.
So she says to this young man flight attendant who is collecting the garbage, she goes, I
never got my chicken.
And in exchange for that, you can make it right to me by bringing me a bag of potato
chips.
Oh, she wants the same salt content.
That's right.
So he says, uh, miss, I'm just, I'm just picking up the trash right now, but the flight
attendant will be right back by in a few minutes and you can get, you can get the potato chips
from her.
That is not good enough.
Of course not.
She starts raising her voice indignation over the ocean.
People get crazy on airplanes.
She is raising her voice about how she wants some potato chips.
And he says, uh, actually miss, and again, not the flight attendant, the guy picking
up trash.
He's holding a trash bag, picking up people's garbage here.
And he says, actually miss, I'm not sure if we have potato chips on this flight.
Uh, they actually forgot to load the potato chips on this flight.
And now, but right ahead of her, there's a man eating chips.
She says, Oh no, no, no, this guy right here, I assume she's pointing at the back of my
head.
Yeah.
This guy right here got a bag of potato chips.
Who is this?
Uh, royal Prince that you pamper in front of me while negating my chicken.
Everyone knows chips equals chicken.
Now at this point I had eaten my bag of potato chips.
Just one bag.
I had eaten, well, I had eaten the potato chips cause they, yeah, they brought out like
the two little, like you ate both the bag.
They were both bags of potato chips.
So when you heard him say that, were you like, go, like, did you know before she even pointed
you out?
I was trying as hard as I could to sink into my seat.
Right.
Cause I was like, this nice flight attendant did me a, did me a solid, brought me some,
uh, some nice salty snacks to enjoy on here.
So I wouldn't be eating the airplane chicken contraband snacks.
Maybe well, well I found out later they had a few bags left over, but they had in fact
not been resupplied.
So they didn't have enough bags of chips for the entire plane, but they had like a few
bags of chips around, ma'am.
I will baby bird those chips into your mouth.
Yeah.
So he looks at my tray table there and he sees a bag of pretzels on there and he goes,
Oh miss, he doesn't have chips.
He just has pretzels.
Oh no.
Oh shoot.
This guy's digging it even further.
He's only trying to help.
He was trying to help so hard and I just wanted to be like, shut the fuck up.
Move along.
Stop talking.
Just stop it.
You are literally a garbage person.
Get out of here.
Go.
Get out of here, trash man.
Do your thing.
But this woman, you're not helping.
You're trying to help and I appreciate that you're trying to help, but you're not.
Please, please continue on with your day.
This guy also has headphones.
Do you want his headphones?
He also has a, what else?
He's got a hat.
You want to wear his hat?
So he says, well miss, there's a button there right in front of you.
If you hit that button, that's the flight attendant call button and she can come get
you whatever you need.
No, no, no.
And she goes, that's not good enough.
That is not good enough for her.
She goes, no, no, no, I just need a bag of chips and I would like them right now.
And so finally this poor guy flags down one of the flight attendants.
So strange to be demanding like this alternate, like I need you specifically to change the
way you do things.
That's it.
And so finally the flight attendant who had helped me out comes back over and this woman
is now, she's not quite yelling, but she's yelling.
She is what we in Cooth society would refer to as yelling.
This guy got about, you brought this guy a bag of chips.
Do you know this guy?
She's now questioning the flight attendant.
Do you know him?
Is he someone that I should know because he got chips?
Oh my God.
No problem.
This bitch.
What a bitch.
She keeps on and keeps on and finally a flight attendant comes back over and goes, Hey, I
found a bag of potato chips, uh, lucky that yo comes back and tries to like defuse the
whole situation.
Right.
And goes like, Hey, good news everybody.
I found a bag of potato chips.
This bag is just for you, ma'am.
Enjoy your bag of potato chips.
Enjoy the rest of your flight.
I would have loved for it to be over at that minute.
So it's like, she is amped, right, like she will not.
She's on.
Right.
So it's like going.
So now the flight attendants drop everything off.
They picked up the garbage.
I've now broken open one of my bag of pretzels.
I'm making eye contact with the flight attendant while she was there and just mouthy, I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to start all this.
I don't write these people.
I'm just trying to do anything to distance myself from these people in the eyes of this
flight attendant who again did a nice thing for me.
Yeah.
Unlike, unlike enterprise where we were joking, you should have honestly turned around and
be like, do you know who I am?
Do you know how lucky you are to be in my airspace?
And then this woman gave me the perfect bookend for my entire Portugal vacation without even
knowing it.
The flight attendant walked away.
The flight attendants have now walked away and now she is just talking to her seat mates.
She's talking to two other people who she did not know before this flight started and
she's now loudly talking to them and laughing and she goes, ow, they didn't know who they
were messing with.
I as soon as I saw this guy get chips, I knew that I was going to get chips and you don't
even know.
You see, I'm from Jersey and in Jersey, I get what I want.
No, in Jersey, you cry and call your brother for help.
No.
Of course this woman's from Jersey and is now going to loudly proclaim it.
I wish I was on a flight.
I'd be like, please stop speaking for all of us.
Please stop doing that.
Stop speaking for any of us.
It was terrible.
Oh boy.
It was so bad and I just looked at my seat mate at one point when she started talking
to me and I just said, do you remember when air travel used to be pleasant?
It was just nice.
I believe she deserved a slow clap.
I think the hands from your seat going right up and just slow clapping.
Just above my head so she could just see my hands.
Exactly.
Good job.
She wouldn't even get it.
I picture her telling this story to anyone after she lands, just watching whoever she's
talking to just eyes glaze over with like, what are you talking about?
You are in some psychotic state where you turn chips into currency and you could not
get off your own emotional high point.
You were over the Atlantic Ocean and you had a breakdown over potato chips.
Even your brain just said win instead of assessing the situation for what it was.
You just had to find a way to feel like you were winning.
She had just had a tray of food.
There was a salad on there.
There were side dishes.
She had had the whole meal except for the chicken, but it was not a small amount of
food.
It was a full on meal that they served on this.
Wow.
Yeah.
It was bizarre until she said she was from Jersey and then I understood all of it.
I married a California girl so what can I say?
Apparently she also spends part of the year in Miami and believe me, she knows how to
get shit done in Miami too.
There was cocaine involved.
I knew this was a cocaine story one way or the other.
She's doing that cocaine.
No, no.
That's not how you do cocaine, Jacob.
Cocaine.
Right in the vein.
That's the rhyme.
Cocaine.
Right in my vein.
Jim Dandy.
Go Jim Dandy.
What the fuck are you here for?
Who asked you to come?
What are you doing?
Nobody knows.
Lovely, Jacob.
What's up?
It was great.
It was a great week.
Glad to be back.
Glad to be back on the old scoops here.
This is great.
It's good to be back.
Thanks, everybody, for joining us.
We've run out of time.
We didn't have it.
We don't have any Jock vs. Nerd time.
We just talked.
We'll be back here and we'll be recording.
For anyone joining us live, we'll be recording again on Friday for the Monday episode, as
always.
And so you can join us there.
I was going to ask you guys if we can go an hour early on Friday.
Yes.
Yeah.
Great.
We'll send that invite out to the patrons.
Yes.
Yeah.
There'll be an hour earlier on Friday.
The reason why is I'm heading off to Arizona, so if you're getting this, you can come tonight
Thursday, Friday, Saturday in Mesa, Arizona, seven o'clock shows at Mystique, the Magic
Experience.
It's no dinner.
It's just me, an hour long show at seven o'clock.
Come out and check it out.
And the reason why I'm asking to go early is because I am bringing my sons with me to
Arizona.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
And so I'm going to, we'll get out and we'll do other stuff during the day and have fun
with my kiddos.
Oh, that'll be so great.
Yeah.
So I'm excited about that.
I want to thank everyone who joined us here today, especially Canadian Scoop Crystal for
hopping on there.
Appreciate it.
I want to thank the Jacob's Racist Cab Driver.
So again, not a hundred percent sure who he's racist towards.
Sounds like everybody to me.
Maybe everyone.
You made quite a case for someone who's unsure.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
But of course, this podcast wouldn't be possible with the generous people who've been supporting
us on Patreon.
So we've gotten a bunch of new signups that we appreciate that as we head into both scoop
fest and trying to find a new churn at the same time, a lot of bills are becoming due.
And so people supporting us there, we will be finishing a revamp of our Patreon with some
adjustments heading into this month, heading into August.
And we'll announce all that when it's all settled, probably the next episode.
And I'm going to thank some of the people who support us on Patreon right now.
And all these people love to shoot people on pink street.
That's us, Sir Tramps, Six Foot Scoop, Scully Wall Scoop, Slightly Slutty Scoop, Skirpy
Kaye Motherfucker, Smells Funny, Smitty Scoop, Solar Powered Scoop, Solo Scoop, Soundman Scoop,
Spring Loaded Scoop, Stab and Dash Scoop, Stacey Coleman, Stacey Westerlin, Steets Magreets,
Stephanie Young, Stephanie Clively, Stephanie Landon, Steve Swenson, Steven Biggs, Steve
Eames, Steven Jerome, Steven Marinelli, and Steven Swindeman.
These people are convinced that they are on a seven mile long comet.
Turn the page, Tess Miller, Tess Sterling, Thanksgiving for Werewolves, That Thing in
the Attic, That Thing in the Attic again, The Bad Humor Man, The Bad Humor Man once more,
The Sensey Scoop, The Civic Crew Scoop, The Damsels of Dorkington, The Devil's Lettuce
Scoop, The Devil's Lettuce Scoop once more, The Didgeridoo Twice, The Famous Ball, The
Going Over Our Friends Podcast, The Ice Cream Headache, The Ice Cream Headache once again,
The Lapis Lagomorf, The Nano Scoop, The SCOOPOP, The Salty Squid, The Scoop Lockian, and The
Spirit of the Latin Club.
The following people all know that a bag of chips is worth it, worth the fight, worth
the steadfastness, worth taking all the way to the Supreme Court.
That's Steven Verne, Stuart Wilson, Strange Uncle's Podcast, Strap a Chicken on Scoop,
Where's My Strap a Chicken on, Sugar Rusts Ocio, Supergeek13579, Sweetest Scoop, T Patrick
Smith, Ticket EV Podcast, Ticket EV Podcast, Sustainable Transportation for All, Tamara
Hamilton, Technical Scoopport, Teddy Mueller, and Temporary.reality, Pierce.
These people are convinced they do not need a license to rent a car.
The Upside Down Under Scoop, The Upside Down Under Scoop once more, The Dirty Scoop, The
Man, The Myth, The Scoop, The Man, The Myth, The Scoop again, Thomas, Thomas Beach, Thunder
Cougar Falcon Scoop, Tim Warnocky, Timothy Reed, Timothy Sutton, TK4T1 Scoop please,
Tom Krieger, Tom Mankerdy, Tom Merritt, and Tom Stott.
And the following people all pick Matt Donnelly up at the airport when he forgets his driver's
license.
Tommy Harrell, Do you know who I am?
Tony Cowley, Tony Scuprano, Travis, Travis Jurguri, Travis Murray, Tristan Guevara, Tristan
Vanoz, Tristey Perry, Petty, Troy Anthony Townsor, Tuba Scoop, Tyler Bartlett, Tyler
Scoop McDuck, Udo Gerhards, Ul Ricky, Uncle Don's Wood Shop, The Verge, Warren Breaux,
Water Eye Scoop, Wendy Cooper, Wendy Bumgarner, Wendy Loomis, Wes Coughlin, What Was Like
When Scoop, Who Dat Scoop, Will Beardy Dan, Will Kellner, Will Pritchett, William McDonald,
and Wind Walker Scoop 23.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air or get a myriad of other prizes galore at different
tiers that fit your budget on a both monthly or yearly basis, we could use your support
over at PreachingFun.com.
Come visit PreachingFun.com.
It's better than hanging with your mom.
Better be bad.
Or if your name doesn't sound anything like any of the names that I just said, head on
over to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts, fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $2 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Matt's right about all that stuff that he just said.
It's possible that we're going to be moving into a new studio the same month as doing
Scoop Fest.
You fool.
Smart idea.
How do you use that support over there?
You fool.
That might just be how it ends up.
Yeah, but this is a great time to support us if you enjoy what you're hearing.
And also, now that we're doing more of these live Zoom things, this is a great time to
become a patron so you can get the invites and come and join us live.
It's wonderful to see all these lovely people that have supported us for some, for a long,
long time.
And we really do appreciate each and every one of you.
And it's a really fun community in the first place, but to become part of it live, that's
really special.
We're really enjoying this.
At least I, myself, am really enjoying this new vibe.
Paul speaks for himself and himself only.
That's right.
Only me.
I'm the only one that's really enjoying all of you lovely people in the chat.
I find seeing laughing faces when I make jokes to be a burden.
Yes.
Well, lucky you.
But thank you, each and every one of you who are patrons.
We really appreciate it.
Couldn't do the show without you.
It's true.
I was invited onto this live recordings, and I wouldn't have known to make that cocaine
or a runner, except I kept seeing people laugh when I did it.
So there you go.
There you go.
That's how it works.
But yeah.
Scoopfest stickers are still on sale.
Go to scoopfest.com and check that out.
We have a hotel discount as well.
So call the Orleans and demand to be part of the discount block of rooms with a discount
code of...
Paul?
Superman?
Catwoman?
Invisible Jet?
25?
Catwoman again.
Right?
I think that's right.
That sounds right.
And if this code doesn't work out, just tell them Scoopfest when you call in and make your
reservation.
Just call the Orleans.
Tell them Scoopfest.
It'll work out.
But please do make an effort to come out to Scoopfest.
You're going to have a great time.
If you're on the fence at all about it, get off that fence, talk to some scoops.
There are lots of groups.
Oh yeah.
Flash.
I missed Flash.
Thanks, big sexy.
What's Jeff saying?
If you don't have a ticket, you need to reconsider your life choices.
Jeff is right.
Listen to Jeff.
He knows what he's talking about.
Reconsider your life choices if you're not already coming to Scoopfest.
It is a wonderful, wonderful time.
We have a great time.
Our community has a great time.
And if you come once, you're going to want to come again.
But that kind of holds true for everything.
But yeah, please, please come on out to Scoopfest.
SCFI 25C.
There we go.
Mikey Newman confirmed.
So we'll be having movies with Mikey.
We'll be hosting our trivia battles.
He's excited that we're doing four battles this year.
He's so good.
Just made Travel Registration for one of our other special guests.
I'm very excited about it.
It's getting pretty exciting.
So many special guests.
So many special gifts.
So many special things going on.
It's always greater than the sum of its parts.
And it becomes this really special thing.
We are eternally grateful and always surprised by how cool it ends up.
Someone reached out to figure out technically how to make Paul's Hollywood Squares graphic
work.
And so we're excited about that.
I still want to do like really basic cardboard.
I think that's fine.
Yes.
Absolutely.
We'll see how it goes.
But it's going to be exciting.
So yeah.
Come out to Scoopfest.
Thanks for this everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Thanks everybody that hung out with us on Zoom today, and thanks everybody that hung out
with us.