Oh hello there I am so glad you are here because it is time to thank you the ice cream truck
drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Jason Klepper, Jeff Harris, Jonathan, Laurie Elsroth, Leon
Casam, Malia, Mike, Paul's brother and Pyro.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks head over to preachingfun.com
where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows for the life you
save may be your own.
Just may be.
Boom.
A program.
Here we go.
Hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah I'd love to.
Great.
Let's go.
I also want to thank a ranch slug.
We owe him a bunch of thank yous.
That's right ranch slug.
I'm going to thank him at the top of the show.
Thank you ranch slug.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social.
Sitting in Las Vegas that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania that's Paul Mattingly.
Also sitting in Las Vegas it's me Jacob.
We're preaching fun.
Hey everybody.
I'll tell you what I am preaching fun but I accidentally just bummed myself out yesterday.
Oh.
Oh no.
What did you do?
So it's.
Did you read the newspaper?
Well this is the thing right so I don't listen to news podcasts anymore I'll listen to Justin
Robert Young when I feel like I can take it.
Right sure.
When I feel like I'm okay.
It's absolutely yep.
Because he tells it like it is and the way he's telling it.
I don't like the way it is and the rest of the time you normally just play myself with
sports podcasts and right now there's not a lot of sports happening.
And so.
Right.
I was going to the back catalog of Pablo Torre explains was it explains all that's Clarissa.
I also always get Pablo Torre and Clarissa confused.
Yeah.
Easy to do.
Finds out.
Pablo Torre.
Melissa Jonard.
And they're talking about this like obscure statistician guy from the 80s doing like a
deep dive and this guy who was kind of ahead of the Saber Metrics thing before that became
a thing.
If anyone doesn't know what we're talking about it's like the basically the nerds won
breaking down baseball and the nerds won breaking down basketball and he was the first nerd
to break down basketball and he was.
Is he the is he the moneyball to basketball that the moneyball guy was the baseball correct
the guy Bill James who started who started the moneyball craze he was in the moneyball
GM but he was the guy who first started kind of breaking down baseball as a solid thing
anointed this guy whose name I'm forgetting as the moneyball basketball.
Yeah.
But that guy did not go on to have different success and basically I guess I guess trigger
warning suicide oh no we yeah.
He didn't have depression he didn't feel like he should have done something he literally
laid out an argument like he that have arguments for basketball players he was a very laid
out argument oh wow that he basically wanted to end his life specifically on his 60th birthday
and just be done with it and.
When you say this bummed you out huh.
This this super upbeat story somehow you're out you've got like three years what are you
worried about man.
And I'm thinking I'm reading you know I'm at the gym I'm walking my kids soccer practice
I just was like reading about the subsurface statistician you know yeah and then that takes
a turn and I'm sure there's a warning in the notes I never read the episode notes you know
right.
And so but it was like also fascinating you know like he wrote all these emails to his
family and put them to be sent hours after his death.
He made sure he like he really set it all up yeah he made sure to do it at the back
parking lot of a police department so he could call nine one one so he could be an organ
donor and no one who hadn't dealt with death would have to see him besides people who were
in charge of doing that.
Like it was this very crazy intricately thing yeah yeah yeah and it really I'm inspired
I'm not depressed by this I'm inspired by this pump the brakes we got a scoop vest today
Jacob slow down slow your roll oh you are not helping your case sir I know I know.
And I was like oh man and then I was like well I'm going to get off you know I still
had some walking to do at the soccer practice and so I was like I'll switch over and I decided
to listen to two characters and a clown.
Which one?
The last one oh it's over right so I'm just gonna tell you this it is a fascinating one
to listen to because when they start the episode they don't know they're doing their last episode
really oh yes it's that much that much of a thing huh oh I did I had no idea right it's
not a bad blood thing is it no it's fascinating again another really fascinating it's just
a mutual agreement that they're done yes but everybody's still amicable the everybody's
still friends still working with each other backstage and still loving each other what
happens is you kind of listen to the episode and I knew that this was their last episode
so it was fascinating to listen to it unfold it was fascinating to hear them realize it
yeah but so I knew it was their last episode but I thought it was going to be them coming
on air to talk about why they're going to do their last episode and instead I listened
to 11 minutes of them talking about crab cakes and fish cakes and I'm like this is really
weird and then it's like so clear that they have and those words have to forgive me for
I mean I don't know I'm just going to talk about it but like it's so clear that there's
a bunch of straws on the back of the Campbell's so to speak right now they're talking about
how things are changing at work they're talking about that things that those are dealing with
at home and then they talk about getting a complaint email from a listener and then they
kind of get into like why why no I don't want to go I want to talk to you guys but I don't
want to talk about stuff on there like I don't want to worry about what I'm saying oh hey
to you guys right and like it is it is it is a fascinating listen because it's very
clear Jimmy is the first one who's out right but realize yeah so yeah so for this you have
to know that the podcast is two characters and it's three friends of ours they all work
backstage at a Cirque du Soleil show they've been doing a podcast for three and a half
years and well they all work on stage they're all three performers at a Cirque du Soleil
show yeah they're literally two characters in the show and a clown yeah yeah and and
and you still have if you're just skirmish now you have three and a half years of fine
episodes yeah for instance I just subscribed to it I'm really looking forward to catching
up when there's like a half hour left maybe a little more RJ makes a big like dark night
of the soul speech to Jimmy like really tries to get Jimmy to like understand and feel his
like value things like this and Jimmy is having none of it like none of it and that was really
that's what really it was hurting me it was like hurt it was like yeah to listen you know
it does that doesn't listen to that I was like so buddy you know he's he's telling Jimmy
how valuable Jimmy is and Jimmy's like yeah okay yeah and Jimmy's not buying it right
what come on Jimmy exactly and then it's really funny because then Johnny just comes in right
and starts talking and I timed it RJ doesn't speak for 25 minutes after his big speech
nothing so I was like oh Johnny's the only one who knows who thinks this is still a podcast
right now I think RJ knew on the big speech and when it was just letting with nothing
he was like no we're done we're done and then oh wow and then so you know I mean spoiler
it's it's a fascinating listen so I'm not even I mean I'm it's all spoiler but it's
all yeah it's all fessing listen oh listen anyway RJ just goes back and he goes so why
don't we just stop doing like right like F is not speaking at all wants to do it Johnny
is caught off guard I don't think people realize even even RJ's friends even me yeah I I fall
into this trap too I forget what a thinker RJ is yes RJ will sit and think and ponder
over something and then when he comes back into the conversation he's got it all straight
and out total and you don't realize it for a minute or two yes big heart big brain that
boy of course just yeah really loves his voice and he literally just he says let's stop doing
the podcast on there you can't hear you know you're it's an audio podcast Johnny's struck
and RJ goes look how big the smile on Jimmy's face is and Johnny does it goes oh you're
right it's over and then and I was like walking around my neighborhood like I had to push
pause to like make dinner for my kids and I was like god damn it I was like riveting
I was just like kids ruined everything crawling with discomfort my friends and also like totally
enthralled and then I had to like table it for an hour and then go finish it on a nightwalk
and I was just like I was teary eyed walking I was like just it was the most crazy podcast
episode ever like I couldn't believe it I think it's hilarious but I had honestly been
saving it because I was saving it's the strong word but I've been saving it because I was
like oh they've got their last episode up I've got a you know basic time to listen to it
now I'm just fascinated yeah no I know cuz like you know I was trying we were lining
them up for a trivia battle right and so that's when RJ let me know that he's like oh I don't
I don't think that's a good idea I was like what and same thing I was like bad blood anything
he's like no no no no no everybody's happy and so it just it was just so clear that the
choice to be a podcaster just wasn't what they wanted to do you know well it was a secondary
there's a secondary choice well that's it they bring us up at the very end they bring
the big up this podcast at the very end and and saying they don't want to become what
we are right they see our they see our world as a burden and well they also have real jobs
that was like I could like scream across the my headphones what's I was like I was like
you know I we this podcast is what we are like yeah right we we we weren't very successful
guys doing something else I thought you know I know shed a little light this is this is
our successful thing and then we use this to bounce into other possibilities and entrepreneurialism
this is our Cirque du Soleil this is yeah this is what we're walking the tightrope right
now baby this is the thing when we tell people about this thing people go oh exactly when
they tell people about Cirque du Soleil people go oh right we tell people about our little
podcast and people are like oh that's very nice for you guys no one goes up to them after
their shows it was like should you guys podcast also because I really want more of you guys
so scoop scoop Jesus is say Jacob was successful and that's true but I think Jacob will also
make the point that as successful as he is and he is very good at his job and has a lot
of success as a sound guy he still gets a lot of interactions with fellow performers
who are like this is a different thing how do you make this podcast thing cook how do
you write this is a very different thing than what I do and I tell you what to to to Matt's
point and you're talking to the guys about you know doing there doing the Cirque shows
and then doing the podcasting stuff I would be a very different podcaster if I didn't
have a day job every time I talk about quitting running shows SJ lets me have it she's like
what are you talking about you're just gonna podcast all the time if you don't run shows
you're just gonna podcast all the time what are you gonna talk about on these podcasts
right it's true it's true you gotta have you gotta have some external life you gotta
have some external life before it comes in yeah yeah yeah this is this is a whole different
thing from from what I do when I go to when I go in and run a show I mean I sit back there
I'm executing somebody else's vision I'm doing all these types of things here you know it's
us it's it's like we're this is our thing we get to do whatever we want on this because
it's us yeah also we also all three don't work with each other right like so like one
of the fun I was gonna say we don't share a dressing room we get yeah we get a break
but but no but with that like the whole reason why I love why I wanted to do the podcast
with Paul in the first place was I was I was a dad and I was and all I like to do for my
entire teens and 20s was bits all I want was bits all I want to do is bust balls and make
jokes with friends and I knew that being a dad would make that go away a lot not all
the way but a lot compared to what I was sure and so I was like oh get let's get in a space
where we can make fun of stuff and good calls and so it was definitely like a big time branch
for me both personally professionally to like get this going so yeah but that but and that's
things like so I said texting with RJ afterward like like yeah this is what podcasting is
to me and you guys don't require any of it you know right you don't require any of it
so it was really interesting I mean because they do all three of them share that dressing
room right it was there yeah yeah and like I don't know how we would do that I would
say I don't know if we had if we had a dressing if we saw each other off microphone and off
camera all the time I don't know how we'd still do a show totally yeah and especially
if it gets like uh touch and go whether we can talk about where we work together or not
right right oh yeah that's huge um and I would say that I think I think that the maybe the
toughest time for this actually the pandemic second toughest time for this podcast uh was
when Paul and I worked together worked together oh sure I think I think 50 shades was probably
the a harder spot yeah and it became the dominating uh talking point like we'd had to we had to
purposely branch out from that yeah yeah yeah I mean we literally butted heads were like
I didn't care about biting the hand that fed me and Paul was like this is a bad idea to
bite the hand that feeds you well yeah and uh and and it was a long term right Matt didn't
care about it and Paul did yeah and I and I shouldn't have I shouldn't have given a
fuck shouldn't have given a roaring fuck but it's easy to say that when we're when we're
out of it it's easy to say we shouldn't have cared about something that we're no longer
inside of yeah yeah yeah it is it's like people it's hard to say you don't care about people
while you're inside of them it is hard to say that I've I've done my best yeah uh and
that's not the only time Paul did that when we did the scoop cruise I was making fun of
the opening uh show in the elevator right and they and our passengers got off the elevator
and Paul let me have it and by the way that was very helpful Paul was like do not talk
shit about anything everyone reports everything to everyone on cruise ships everybody has
ears you cannot yeah uh as an entertainer talk shit uh he was right then even though
I my pride didn't want him to be and um and I don't think I was too mean about it you
were you were not I was probably serious about it you were very serious and very direct about
it you were not you were you were direct about it I wouldn't say you were mean about it but
you were direct about it well because I I'd done nine months on a cruise ship yeah yeah
you were just you were just real about it live that fucking life baby yeah well on some
things like I'm not like that moment was would turn out to be very key to what I'm doing
now like so like I'm not saying you're out of you're wrong in any way I'm saying like
in hindsight like I was like right not only were you right then but I'm even more grateful
now I go right I go on cruise ships like everything is bugged exactly and it is because it is
it fucking is I mean seriously fucking Orkin man you go to enough ports where everyone's
toting machine guns and you get a little sense in your mind like oh there could be some shit
going down I bet people are really looking out for stuff yeah you know what I mean like
you know yeah you go to enough places where you're like oh there's some serious military
hardware like back in these ports they're not gonna they're not gonna let games get
played yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah uh I'll tell you who doesn't let games get played in their
ports and that is the following sponsor today's show no I don't believe it today sure the
show that the show I don't think anything anytime soon it's brought to you no they didn't
think it was either uh Matt and Mattingly's meet the wolf man act for scene three Matt
escapes the wolf man by prepping him to perform unfool us from scoop John Fink we now take
you to act for scene three of Matt Mattingly meet the wolf man yes great job wolf man love
the pizzazz you have to get that giant dirty thick fingernail underneath two cards but then
at the top of the deck with him hold it as one you're gonna lift it up oh man I'm trying
these paws ain't cooperate very good it's just called a double lift you can still lift
up both cards and show it to the artist like one what do you say we rearrange my appointment
time for a full moon and I could just do my straight transformation routine the problem
is that Lincoln that fools likes to bump people around depending on the schedule and your
local so he knows he can bump you around so you're not gonna get the spot that we can't
rely on that's fine I get it I get it but I mean I'm a rare reverse werewolf I'm wolf
man all the time except during a full moon I understand I understand why don't we just
rehearse some of the lines like so so Penn and Teller did I fool you want to try that
one so Penn and Teller did I fool you okay I feel like the fool is a little long oh I've
been going to speech therapy for a long time but it just don't take yeah yeah no I understand
I think you got a rabbit I could eat can't you pull one out of your hat yeah come on
stereotype my ass that's why I got in the biz oh did you win your team's high school
basketball championship while we're doing while we're doing stereotypes back and forth
did you come here riding on top of your friend's van just because my best friend happened to
be Stiles very common team will preferences is there a young lady named Booth that has
some of your attention but not as much as it should I can't believe her name was boof
man what was her name remember proposing that we should just end the show at episode one
thousand oh yeah yeah and that bothered Paul a lot what I even just well I I quickly fixed
it and said no that's the beginning of season two we're off to the races oh I saved myself
for another thousand episodes season two might be the last season it might be the season
one might have been the penultimate season that's we're going to the third season here
I think we don't know how long season two might be oh well I mean it's gonna be a thousand
episodes at least at least I guess we know a season is at least a thousand episodes maybe
for for for bit sake it's a thousand and one and then season season three starts on one
thousand two oh that's are explained to a friend the other day that asked about a friend
of mine was asking about podcast season remember that note for seven years but yes keep keep
going I'll remember that easily we need at least seven seasons says bossy I will be dead
by season seven so that's gonna be tough that's gonna be tough not to say someone couldn't
pick this ball up my children and all and all of your dogs my dogs will be long dead
before that you won't whatever incarnation of whatever whatever sled dog team you currently
are adopting or fostering okay oh my god you're right it's never gonna stop yeah so speaking
of my dogs talking to Matt's kids the reason I was a little bit behind today was we're
working with a contractor who their mascot is a little corgi dog in a hard hat so it's
really cute so that helped get all right all right let's say let's say percentage give
me a percentage how much of a percentage of of you selecting this contractor had to do
with that image oh eighty percent easily good okay because because that was part of it and
and sent me that link and everything and we we saw that so we're like yeah like we're
good to go so uh yeah it was really you know they know their market uh yeah these are exterior
house uh painters and what do you call it and so uh ann had been looking to get some
work done on the exterior of the house for a long time and she's already had you know
ideas sent out to uh professional planescapers that can make it look like you know how they
want and so she's got all the great the paint ideas set everything set and we got finally
a consultation today they had to move their time back a little bit just because they were
super busy but the we're supposed to be meeting at noon we ended up meeting closer to one
so that's why i got pushed back a little bit time-wise but looks like everything's gonna
move forward and hopefully by october we're gonna have new exterior uh colors and uh things
done and also the big thing the brickwork the brickwork which i might add that allowed
for the entrance of one squirrel into my basement so the uh so the lack of brickwork the lack
of brickwork so we're gonna get that all touched up they can do that as well so we're gonna
get that all patched up and they're gonna do this process uh called uh lime washing
cutting the brakes in that truck they absolutely are they went in but we're gonna get it limed
washed and uh it's gonna look really nice so the brick the brickwork's gonna get touched
up masoned in fixed up and then what's the lime washing do uh it makes it look white
essentially okay instead of you know different shades of of white instead of the regular
brick color that we have got there right now oh so oh it's what it makes it lighten up
okay exactly some of it is kind of like falling apart there is a piece of brick missing from
the very front of our house where it's really close to a vent for the air conditioning system
and i could look in that vent and i could see outside of my house and so i was like
okay so currently well that's event the mattingly fix that's going on for that piece of brickwork
right now is a big goopy chunk of great stuff i scored it into the wall so you've got all
this brick and then this hunk of yellow nasty just hanging off the side but you can't get
back i would have suggested a towel i would have suggested just shoving a towel in there
no it wouldn't have a towel wouldn't have worked it wasn't that big of a gap but it
was big enough okay the great stuff worked so there you go uh yeah yes i know ranch slunky
we can't paint uh exactly so the lime washer allows this that's interesting look at that
perfect ranch slunk coming through with the info ranch slunk in the chat says uh brick
should not be painted as it needs to breathe lime wash allows for this so that it does
not crumble due to weathering exactly uh gosh that's a big shame because all of the brick
on the on my house is all painted we finally gave him his thank you and then he's coming
off everywhere with these facts it's pretty great i doubt well i'll tell you i'll tell
you jacob your brickwork is probably safe given the environment that it's in i don't
have any there's no moisture getting exactly it's so bone dry it's not going to be a thing
but he was just telling us about a painted brick situation that they're dealing with
on another home they spent four days trying to get the paint working to get the paint
off so the brick can get worked on again so it's just a nightmare if you actually do paint
your bricks incorrectly jason we knew about that that's what i'm saying yeah i have painted
bricks but maybe maybe the dryness will save me in my house i think that's it and it's
also it's also probably depends on the mixture of the brick and what kind of like these are
like straight up bricky bricks are yours more like uh non-bricky bricks you know no no i'm
fascinated where this question is about to go i am so curious number one las vegas masonry
podcast let's roll i don't i just kind of believe there are different kinds of compositions
of the masonry i am i am so curious what paul what knowledge of bricks paul is about to
reveal are they and what level of brick knowledge he thinks that i have great are they grade
a bricks are they grade b so i'm looking for to get some work done on my bricks now these
are bricky bricks you'll know brickety bricks yeah these are brickety brick brick bricks
uh these ones have the same intelligence as a u.s senator oh my well brickety brick uh
everything about our our house is 1980 it the house looks like the ford tempo that we
used to own if we still had that ford tempo it would it would even mean you could park
the ford tempo we used to have right next to our house and it would disappear like camouflage
you know how uh the the enterprise d has that beige and and uh would sure and oh yeah yeah
no matt and i were just talking about that earlier the enterprise d with the beigeness
with the different browns and tans extra dick the different browns and tans so it was a
uh a ford tempo from 80 82 maybe it was a brown ford tempo uh from 82 uh i think brown
ford yeah around 82 or 84 uh 84 go 84 needs to be a little bit newer than that then i
love okay so we're for those of you listening we're building up the uh the pictures here
uh of a brown ford tempo from oh yeah that's that's good and brown yeah it was just like
your house it was two-tone though like it had the top of it was was light beige and
the bottom was dark beige and then the seats were beige it was just the beige-iest fucking
thing and our house is just beige you got a beige house the crazy thing about it too
they just replaced the windows she's a beige house she's mighty bland boring as all get
out she's a beige house no curb appeal at all just making you forget it exists uh yeah
it is i mean for me personally i could give a shit what the exterior of the house looks
like because i've made the interior look like at least my basement a vomit of color and
craziness you know i mean it's it's it's nuts down here uh yeah yeah it's it's it's it's
special i love it i love it down here it's crazy uh it makes me happy um and and it is
very a very nondescript home like if you were looking for like a place to just hide forever
this would be it but uh it's going to be this beautiful cottage blue and whites but they
when they put the new windows in on the house the windows that they got had a green interior
trim that was just part of the the build like the it's metal green and it just looks whackadoo
so anyway we're getting everything fixed up and it's going to be really lovely and the
fact that this company can fix them windows the fact that this company can fix the brick
as well makes me really happy because like i said some of it's being held together with
great stuff so there you go yeah well squirrels are being held out with with great stuff i
yes yes great stuff single-handedly keeping squirrels out of the mattingly household it's
keeping something out it's keeping some stuff out yeah uh latter-day scoop says my basement
is the suburb equivalent of stabbing a person in the attic just to see color i i or the
arctic just to see color oh yes okay yes then that makes more sense uh yeah kind of yeah
i drive along i pull up to my every time i go up into my attic i go completely colorblind
it's terrible i do pull up to my very nondescript uh drive and then i open the basement door
and then i just hit with a flood of color and also in the chat canna clumsy knows what's
up because that dog ain't no dog that's three squirrels in a dog costume it's a heist oh
yeah it's a heist it's a heist it could be could be if only we could get in but there's
so much great stuff i'm i'm seeing some some faces in the chat here that they're going
to get thank you videos uh from my son uh uh but uh it's that time of year for my son
makes adorable thank you videos if you donate to him this year the theme is uh if he wins
his donation contest he gets a big annoying beach ball that'll be in the house to annoy
his mother so he's putting out videos that says help me annoy my mom and you can donate
to it and scoops party stepped up but uh but but but do do step up and uh and if you want
i'll the link is on my instagram if you go to my noodler and click on my links it says
donate to my kid's school but you can see the uh it's weirdly not on your wife's social
media at all it's almost like she doesn't want it to happen so uh public schools still
need a little extra funding believe it or not yeah no i don't i can't i can't imagine
you kid me he is he is like 150 bucks out of the top 10 so oh uh he's he's close to
getting some real real recognition there but that's fantastic good for him does he get
a prize if he if he finishes in the top 10 i think he has extra like some some doodad
bullshit sticker he gets to graduate eighth grade yeah look they'll they'll make him stand
up at the graduation or something yeah oh spirit of the funding drive let's go spirit
of the candy bars spirit of the candy bars man that i am the spirit of the candy bars
spirit of the funding drive uh jacob bring our buddy jobeth in here for a minute here
that's that's fine jobeth here yeah well you go ahead and talk i'll bring you up jobeth
is uh gonna take his show to spain and so he's trying to uh crowdfund that effort and
uh he was he reached out to me to say if you could talk about the show i said yes but i
also wanted to come up with something for the scoops to put on his kickstarter and so
aha oh great um he he uh he's going to announce what that what that is um when you find him
jacob jesus jobeth start talking i can't find oh you need me to start talking so you can
find me i'm sorry i thought matt just picked up on it and started running with it there
it is i wanted both of you oh there you are i found you awesome so yeah i um producing
i was like i can't find him in the fucking zoom thing i don't know from times being in
the churn and otherwise uh past handful of years i have kind of shifted lanes a little
bit into doing hypnosis shows instead of the normal mentalism that i was doing before and
it's it's kind of really blown up and it's taking me all over the place so yeah i got
an invitation to go and participate in this year's 2025 barcelona fringe festival in
barcelona spain which is oh barcelona exciting and we're uh i'm dragging my wife along we're
making a big adventure out of it so we're gonna end up hitting a couple different european
countries on the way there um but i'm looking to really build exposure with this thing so
the the purpose of the kickstarter they all look like they're there to raise money which
is which is great and there's some fun perks and we'll talk about some of those that per
matt's suggestion which i think is fantastic and i would love to do um some specific add-ons
for the scoops really i'm trying to get this thing to hit so it you know it triggers the
algorithm and i get more of a a global exposure for this thing because it's if anybody's ever
performed at a fringe festival and i know that some of the scoops have and i think i
mean matt you did the one in uh fallout fringe recently it's one of the best investments
an artist can make it's just it's just it's just a license to print money it really is
uh wait you had a decidedly different experience than than i did um almost every fringe festival
in the language is like hey we will not let you make a profit like it's almost guaranteed
it's almost guaranteed so like you can you can ask to break even at best there's usually
language in the application that says that so before i decided to launch this kickstarter
i talked to my wife into coming with me and i said exactly that in some version of that
said there's the best that you can hope to do is break even we're going to make a vacation
out of this that i happen to be doing a run of shows that way nobody's mad about the money
yeah that's all but i want the exposure i want full rooms my shows are far more fun
with a lot more people in the room and it's a really different type of show because usually
hypnotists they do their thing bring people up get whoever they can into trance and then
they've got this script of routines that they go through of the silly shit that they make
people do i am doing a show where as audience members enter the theater they are prompted
to put down ideas for stuff that they want to see in the show and i'm going to write
the show basically on the fly there there's going to be some cheating involved with respect
to the kickstarter so if you are interested in the kickstarter and i thought you meant
you were going to fuck other people's spouses um just right there on stage if they wrote
on the paper it's on the paper fuck my wife the kickstarter will give people a chance
to suggest routines that i'll bring with me and drop into the bucket nice as potential
things so ultimately again i want these full rooms the full rooms one of my real call to
action here is less about funding the kickstarter more about because right now it's in pre-launch
okay everything is at carnivalofdreams.com so that's the name of the show and again the
audience i'll throw that in the zoom chat for people who are there if people can jump
on and follow this thing because the the follows that you get in pre-launch are also part of
triggering the algorithm and getting it exposure i'm trying to put as much of the full court
press on this thing as i can thank you jacob um and but there is some cool stuff so for
as little as five bucks people can join a private whatsapp group where i'm going to
be giving updates throughout and everything up to getting swag from it suggesting routines
everything's got a price so if you want it to be guaranteed that i use your routine in
the show there is a level where you and i will hop on the zoom call before this thing
and actually plan out and write a routine so you know what you're getting i video all
the shows so there's one of the levels that you can get video of all of the shows from
it and for the scoops since i'm going to be in europe and in three european cities there
will be an add-on there that will make sense to almost nobody other than you all where
i will yell salt pork in front of some sort of famous monument somewhere in either berlin
paris or barcelona and you know you don't even have to put hey scoops at checkout you'll
know exactly what it is it actually even says that you don't have to put hey scoops at checkout
i don't even know if there's promo codes on get started i've backed so many damn projects
whether they are magic related or other weird tech stuff and like the number of decks of
playing cards that i have that sean farquhar has designed i could probably build a house
with them but um yeah i'm sure you see that with the foam that paul used to keep the mice
out of the basement right a little great stuff goes a long way otherwise three squirrels
at a trench coat will steal it yes so i i thought it was really funny to have jobeth
yelling uh salt pork out loud to different at different different monuments and stuff
around europe oh wait are you going to yell the are you going to yell salt pork in front
of the monuments or are you going to yell salt pork at the monuments as the monuments
have done something to deserve being yelled at dealer's choice and if for anybody who's
back to kickstarter before you know that once it funds once you get the submission and everything
there'll be some back and forth and and you know i've been a member of this community
since i brought matt to elkton to really kick off us having the elkton magic shows and i
kind of backdoor obelisk myself because of wanting to kind of do some research for a
second i thought you were going to tell a fun story about you and matt in the early
days hey oh um i mean there's plenty of plenty of fun stories it was very similar wolfman's
appearance on fools very similar so um you know the the the scopes i i don't know that
i feel like i quote owe a lot to them but i i certainly owe a lot of enjoyment to everything
that is here so the amount of levity that's going to exist in you sending me a message
saying can you do specifically this consider it done um again the following job that came
with an idea for abracadabra and maybe other people on here might like that one too okay
same thing only you hold up a rubik's cube and you go you know there's one and 43 quadrillion
combinations of things on a rubik's cube did you know that and then i'll pan to my wife
and she can do rj sigh so for those listening it's my biggest pet peeve with every magician
has dumb pet peeves and mine is that anytime anyone does a rubik's cube trick they say
there are over 43 quadrillion combinations you can do with rubik's cube and i just think
like that's true i agree but do you want me the audience member to think that you the
magician knows 43 quadrillion combinations because that's obnoxious that's obnoxious
if you want me to think you're that much of a math whiz but also yeah you know are going
to find my eight of hearts later like it just seems like a really weird thing to add to
a show you are the smartest person i've ever seen and you're doing rubik's cube magic exactly
exactly this is perfect jobith i've got a question for you absolutely the shows in spain
are they going to be done in english or are you learning them in spanish uh they are going
to be done in english so that area in barcelona apparently has a a thriving english comedy
scene okay which is which was what became the birth of this fringe festival there this
is the second year that they've done it so i'm sure that i'm going to have some spanish
speaking or bilingual or or folks who speak catalan because it's in that region um i i
took five years of spanish in high school and i'm surprised i'm sure that'll help as
i'm 60 couple days into a duolingo streak how much i both remember and forget from that
time gracias perfect oh you're ready then i'm going to order a cerveza all that i want
i will have no problem finding the library yep yeah la biblioteca muy bien you're you're
so fast on that day nada you're ready you're ready to be there jobith anything else people
need to look for what's that anything else people need to look for carnival of dreams
uh carnival of dreams dot com over time that is going to evolve to just go to the kickstarter
site and then when kickstarter's done it's going to be ticket links so if anybody's actually
i don't know if you guys have scoops that are specifically in barcelona if you happen
to be there uh if you're a scoop reach out i'll i'll comp your tickets uh because obviously
we've already written off any profit from this thing and i love to have we've accepted
that we're not going to make money we might as well lean into it let's get the butts
in the seat exactly oh awesome i like it i like cool hey thank you for uh for giving me
a little time and thank you for putting enough time between the the the recap of uh two characters
in the clown r i r i p while you were going through all of that i'm sitting there i don't
want to follow this i hope he doesn't put me on right after so well luckily everybody
had forgotten about it until you brought it back oh now we're all sat i'm here to self
sabotage myself anyway i can thanks buddy i'm following you on the kickstarter looks
good yes beautiful all you have to do go go over there to that website that we that we
said earlier that someone will repeat now that i've forgotten what it was called carnival
of dreams dot com go over there uh all you have to do is sign into your kickstarter and
follow it on right there and it will alert you when the kickstarter goes active and you'll
be helping joe without so go over there carnival of dreams do that right now especially if
you're sitting there watching us on zoom you can just go over there on your device and
do it it's all you're still right here you're right there it's right here you're already
here buddy you're already here i'll tell you who else is already here and will probably
be performing at um oh shit i just muted matt sorry matt i just muted you on your zoom sorry
that was a uh a not too subtle hint i understand i'll check myself i forgot what i was gonna
say uh following sponsor disco daycare that's right i heard somebody say disco daycare i
don't know
do
baby
tonight it must be real cheap with a zoom delay there's not a single chance i'm ending this
this is the rest of the show
do
i'm watching your baby
tonight
making sure that your baby gets fed
making sure that it gets into bed
get some sleep
get some nap
get some snack
i'm watching your baby
watching your baby
tonight
why is my baby doing cocaine in the bathroom?
look i'm watching your baby as much as i can
i can't watch him all the time
and i can't go into the bathroom with the baby
that's against federal law
daddy
i need more cocaine
don't we all?
tonight
i'm watching your baby
snort coke
off the back of a urinal
tonight
well the baby's not that tall
oh man
it's using the short urinal
the baby urinal
better hay scoops to check out
doing cocaine off the baby urinal
oh lord
i wouldn't saw clue on the big screen last night
oh yeah that's out in theaters right?
they were playing it at the south point here in las vegas
so i wouldn't saw tim curry and martin mall do clue
flames, flames at the side of my face
madeline kahn
when she enters the movie for the first time
i started laughing instantly
holy shit
i love madeline kahn so much
she's so good in that movie
and they did the thing
they did the thing like the original one
where they didn't show all the endings
oh they just showed one
they picked one ending and showed that
because that's how they did it when the movie first came out
that's right
to show all the different theaters had just one ending
and then i think comedy central started
i think they're the ones who did
all the endings together
when comedy central started re-airing the movie
i think they did it on the
vhs, the vhs release had all the endings
oh is that what it is? yeah
the vhs went and maybe it went like this
and maybe it went like this
oh so comedy central showed that part
yes and i think
that kind of inspired
waynes world
oh yeah that makes sense
first waynes world had multiple endings
but yeah it was so good
matt what were you going to ask?
i forget now
oh cool
i love watching those
i'm no longer a good podcaster i quit
but i have fishcakes
oh nevermind i'm back in
urinal fishcakes
they gotta hold one podcast together
yuck
gross
there was a group behind me
who was just saying out loud
every single punchline
before it happened
oh that's so annoying
it didn't bother me that much
because i knew all of them too
so i was also
oh yeah these are coming
do you think this is an effect of
it being a tim curry movie
kind of just vibing on that
rocky vibe
yeah i think so i think they were just
having a good time i wasn't mad at them
but they were doing a lot i was also sitting
next to a uh
i don't know you know me i can't tell how
old kids are but it was a little girl
she seemed to be like i don't know 12
maybe 12 13 something like that
and uh it is
really great sitting next to
someone at a movie that you
love and as
you're watching it you realize how
formative it was to you especially
to uh to your comedy
oh yeah as you're as you're watching it
and you're sitting next to
a preteen little girl
who is
so unimpressed with everything
the screen might
as well be blank
it was so
great it was it made my
night like this kid doesn't give
a shit about this at all just hated
it just hated it
really it was like just sitting
there you could tell every reference to it
because there are it's a it's a more
dated movie than you think it is there are
a few sure references in there that
you're like i if you don't if you don't
know what it's like uh
hoover
is on the phone at one point jager
hoover is on is on the phone at one point
and somebody makes the the comment
uh tim curry makes the comedies like he's
on everybody else's phone why shouldn't he be on mine
right right right right
that's a funny jager hoover
running the fbi joke right
that is not applicable in twenty
twenty-five and uh uh
now how old is this individual
oh the the kid was like twelve
or thirteen oh okay so yeah no no
no no no she was just i was like
why did your parents bring you to this
you clearly hate all of this
well and it's also just a factor
of movies were a little bit
more slow paced
back in the lower yeah so
you know that's hard to
it's hard to shift that brain especially at
thirteen my god i get it yeah
i get it
you forget that the whole mr
body's a real acting flex you
totally forget there's a big build up before
before the murder happens
and mr body has
to be like i'm the greatest actor in
the world i'm the biggest
he has to come in
it's like the only actor in the movie you
don't know who it is yeah
exactly and he has to come in and just
try his damnedest to take
it over while tim curry is on the
other side of the room just being
tim curry exactly
exactly so yeah you just feel
terrible for this guy i watched it again
that's it i was like i watched it again
like uh like four years ago or something i was like oh
i forgot this guy really tries to
throw a flamethrower it just really
isn't happening
it really comes across as a big
failure
yeah it's just poor guy
he's just trying
uh yeah when i was younger
i did not appreciate i did not
comedically understand how subtle and awesome
martin mull was being so we were watching it as an adult
he's so funny
it's like it's so subtle and he's such a
groveler like it's so great
his looks are great uh
he keeps on like
touching mrs scarlet
in just vaguely inappropriate
ways and she just keeps on
being annoyed by it and shooting
him looks or hitting him or something
and nobody ever acknowledges it
no i was just a little too young
when they started doing the fernwood tonight
reruns on uh yeah
yeah just it went over my head
i was still just wasn't there but i'm sure
now i'd appreciate it a lot more yeah i missed
fernwood as well yeah
oh yeah oh yeah we did it
guys all right we're just gonna sit around now
and and think about nice things that we
enjoyed from our childhood think about those
movies we watched let's just think about old movies
for a minute guys just quietly remember
there were movies oh man
what was your favorite movie when you were 14
years old 14 years old 14 years old
14 years old
fern gullywood
that's the one where they had to shoot the dog at the end
oh my god
well they didn't have to shoot the
dog they got to shoot the dog
they got to do it they got to shoot
the dog spoilers
sorry latter day scoop spoilers
let's do some scoop mail
message for you son
we got a scoop mail today from house dad
after watching reya and
the last dragon what is reya
or is that one thing
reya and the last dragon
one thing yeah okay
so after watching reya and the last dragon i asked my
daughter is what animal they would like to put a saddle
on and ride around i told them that
i would put a saddle on a hippo because
they are spectacular plus the land
and water speed and maneuverability
really checks all the boxes if you
ask me the three year old chose
a cow which is incredibly on brand
for her personality wise the two
year old went giraffe
which is very koala like of her
and a solid choice please allow
me to ask you that same multi million dollar
question besides my mom
what would you like to saddle and ride
around lovingly that's
the house dad so
other than house dad's mom what would
you like to throw a saddle on and give a little ride to
let's make it exciting all the choices are only
people in this chat
okay okay
so we have jobeth we have
i
would like to do a giant
bumblebee giant
bumblebee oh oh so we're not
even in real animals and we're already out of real
animals i'm already out of real animals
i'm going to giant bumblebee because i don't
want to hurt a real animal i
want to go with a giant bumblebee
because also i want to fly around it'd be like a
sektar yeah
a gazoon type yeah yeah
oh you guys you guys all remember sektars
right of course you do
that short lived uh toy line
sektars do you not remember sektars
jacob no matt do you remember
sektars i don't
so sektars how many times can
paul say the word sektars
sektars is a toy line i know what it is
before he decides that we don't it was
a little expensive the figures were
a little closer to seven inches they were
pretty tall and they would ride on
the backs of giant bugs
and the bugs were the big feature
of the toy line so the bugs
had these big wings that you could manipulate but the
cool thing was they were
puppets you put your hand
into the bug and
your hand became the bugs
legs
oh yeah i do remember that
of course you do because sektars were fucking
cool and so you would fly
you would fly them around and they'd be riding on your back
and they had a huge playset
their playset was
ginormous the sektar
it looked like just a
chasm wall
it was really cool but yeah
sektars
would fly around and they're redoing
sektars now
all right say sektar again
sektar
i think i want to ride a giant
train like a mechanical ball
like wheel the giant train
what you heard me
oh you want to wheel
a giant train
and catch a ride at
choo-choo come on ride the train
and ride at choo-choo
that's what i want to do
all right then
i guess i won't stop you
that was bad
in the chat with the
say sektar one more time over
that was really fast
say sektar again
sektar don't sound like any toy line i ever heard of
you know what they call a quarter pound of sektars
in france
what? nerdy
they call them
le bugs and warriors
le bugs de fingerlegs
that's what sektar translates into
i just found out in the chat you can ride inside a train
that was really
what a waste of time
so silly
shit man
i don't know i think hippo
hippo is a good idea hippo is a
solid rideable animal
it's tough to ride
get your legs all spread way out
well you can do some kind of saddle
situations kind of seat situation
maybe a nice side
hippo saddle
paul is holding his phone up to the camera now
to show off
what i assume is his amateur porn video
i'm just letting people
again this is the benefit
of joining up on the patreon
and coming into our feed
you get to see extra content like this
sektar see they're finger fighting
as sad as
this statement makes me paul's video
has made me oh paul your package has arrived
i like seeing paul's notifications
my notifications coming up
this is pretty great
also paul's video has made me realize
i do know what he's talking about
of course you remember everybody remembers sektars
i'm sad that paul's video did
something useful they were expensive
back in the day they weren't
i never had any that's what i'm saying
they weren't a cheap a cheap figure
they were very expensive
sektars
i have no idea what i was saying
before that oh animal
winter scoop put a cool picture there in the
in the chat as well
oh wow in the in the chat here
uh lawane buddy
mcqueen buddy uh has
selected horse
you know
i'm gonna go with uh with buddy on this one
horse seems like a really good one
but i got news for you
both you guys live your dreams
you can do that tomorrow
sektar
that'd be a good one leon cassab
it's been a long have you guys ever
been to horse i have it's been forever
when i was a kid yeah
yeah when i was a kid i wouldn't do it now
do you think you could still ride a horse i have more
respect for a horse than to put my 300 pound
butt oh no no not that but like
if you were on a horse though
do you do you believe that you could still
command a horse and ride a horse well
enough yeah i think i could i think i could do
okay it would depend on the horse
of course of course of course
you really legit
of course
he legit of course that
legit of course it depends
on the horse of course of course
uh i don't know but yeah i think i
could i think i could um
i would love to ride
a clidesdale
oh those are uh
i believe just impossible to
ride i guess yeah they're probably so
big you'd have to be so bow legged
yeah they're just so massive
oh my god winter scoop saying
mr hands
that is the horse that rides
you winter scoop
actually for my birthday this year we're gonna get
we're gonna get a pony ride so i'm gonna ride a pony
on my birthday oh good
good nice do you
do you guys know the horrible story behind
mr hands
what's mr hands mr hands
is the horse that was involved in
one of those early freaky
online videos that
apparently
was uh a cult
of horse fucking people
and the
mr hands was fucking
guys right they were getting
fucked by this horse you know the horse
didn't want to do it or whatever but
uh what i know
but
you were well
aware of the whole bean situation and all
that kind of thing and
you know horse
business is a bit bigger than human
business and the story
was the story was that mr
hands got this guy
but ruptured
his intestines
and he's died over time
from being fucked by a horse
um i have
i have found it i found
the wikipedia page on it
this is
upsetting it's dark it's a real
dark thing and it's one of those it's one of those
very early internet things i gotta
tell you for really remember
for a masonry podcast do not screen share
i'm not screen sharing i'm not screen sharing
no
it has taken a turn well
uh of course of course
you gotta fuck the right horse
of course
or don't how about don't fuck horses how about
that oh i've been watching
uh i've been watching hard knocks on hbo
the uh the the season
the season camp for the buffalo bills yeah
and one of the linebackers
i think either a linebacker or a defensive
lineman uh he's really into horses
and he has horses he rides
horses and so they take the cameras out
watching a huge professional athlete
on the back of an equally
huge because he has like very
large horses to accommodate
his very large frame right
and uh it is
so funny because
he's just an enormous man on the back
of a horse and no matter how big that horse
gets it still doesn't look right
it looks like
looks like you riding a kitten
yeah yeah it looks like it's it looks
weird that his feet aren't touching the ground
because it looks like they just
almost should give it a
flintstone that shit just yeah
side he just give it a little kick
to help out the horse a little bit
no big deal he can
he hey flintstones the horse
he's just running with the horse
hunter
his legs touch the ground
cuts into the horse
it's a living
[laughter]
let's do a
little jock vs nerd
because you're about to lose your living
[cheering]
ladies
and gentlemen
it is
time
[music]
for jock
vs
nerd
[music]
explosion
of sectors
[laughter]
of mr hands
we got a scoobity coming to us today from
leon cassab
the categories are before they wrestled
small facts, second biggest
facts, and cocktails
leon in chat
so if you can criticize anything he's right here
oh good good
paul you're up first what you want
i'm gonna go ahead and before they
wrestled for 800 i'm gonna shoot the moon
oh before becoming
one of the world's biggest
one of the biggest stars in the world
this wrestler did quote
the work of three men
end quote as a farmer
oh boy
uh
[silence]
ooh
i'm gonna guess iron chic
oh okay let's try iron chic
andre the giant
andre
leon paul hates your game
no i don't not at all
oh shit i also
fucked that score up
nobody guessed paul got it wrong
well there's no point it's all good
right uh you should have negative points
oh no no i don't agree with that
was that before or after jack carowak
drove him to school
i think it was after jack carowak
but before ral doll
okay um
i will take small facts for 200
please
at 32 days this 9th presidents
term is the shortest in us
history um i guess
william henry harrison
william henry harrison is absolutely
correct
i died in 30 days
died of pneumonia
tippecanoe and
tyler
tyler that's it
tippecanoe and tyler too
it's me i'll try um
you learn your history so you don't repeat it
that's why we learned our history today about mr hands
that's right that's right
don't fuck mr hands
between that and sectars i've saved some lives today
good job good job
i'll try small facts for 400
need to be more toys
infinite wrong answers
the smallest incorporated town
in the united states is monowea nebraska
what is its population
within 20
oh
home of future
i'm gonna say
uh 21
one
its mayor
lcm eiler is the only
resident
wait is 21 within 20 of one
what's that election process like
very
it's either very simple or very
complicated
it takes all year
i think i get that right
i don't know i'm saying i got it right
i said 21
within 20
leon said fine so there you go
uh paul
before they wrestled for 600
despite being part of a famous
wrestling family this superstar
had his hand at professional baseball
before stepping into the ring
damn it that's the only one i was gonna get right
macho man randy savage
oh wow i didn't know that
randy
uh
i know that the saints used to have
the kid of one of the
legion of doom on there
oh really he was an office of lineman
yeah he was uh animals kid
animals child that makes sense
uh he might still play i don't know
you're up anthony and buddy
are right next to each other in my chat
windows are they right next to each other in your chat windows
it looks like they're trying to punk us by like
twinning right now it looks like they're trying
to do the same
i can't see
even buddy now just lowered his screen to match
him
ah i see him now
oh that's funny
it's like we're playing guess who with our
zoom chat right now
we've been defeated preachingfun.com
join us on zoom yes
you get to see people
do those those kinds of things
shenanigans
aplenty on the zoom chats i'll take small
facts for 600 please
this point guard
was the shortest player to start in the
nba oh
it's either spudweb or muggsy
bogues oh i forgot
about muggsy bogues
it's gotta be spudweb
alright
muggsy bogues
y'all were both so confident on it
i was sitting over here thinking like
i think it's muggsy but y'all were both so
confident that it was spud that you convinced
me
i'll try small facts
for 800
england's shortest adult
monarch was charles the first who was
estimated to be five foot four at the start
of his reign approximately
how tall was he by the end of his reign
i'd say approximately
five foot four
probably lost his head right
is that what they're doing they're taking into
consideration he's like six inches
shorter because he got his head cut off or something
oh yeah so yeah i'll say he's
approximately one head shorter
approximately four uh four eight because
his head was chopped off any answer
gets credit yeah great just like what happened
with muggsy bogues
just like what happened
he would have been a much taller basketball player
yeah if he had kept
his head if he had kept his head
paul uh before they wrestled
for 400 please
prior to becoming a wrestling star
he played bass for the band ruckus
presumably before
sj joined
oh
i think this is
hulk all right
hulk hogan
yeah
now this is where he came
he started saying like he almost
was in metallica it's like
oh that's right all the way
off you lied
you lied racist and he was supposed
to be uh mickey
mickey roark's part and the wrestler
oh my god he's just so full of shit
it's unbelievable yeah
uh matt you're up
well now he's full of dirt and worms
well not yet i don't think
i think they're still getting an autopsy there's some
some weird what yeah
there's some weird stuff about medical malpractice
going on with his death
i don't know oh wow yeah
it seems to be uh
yeah kind of sketch
gawker will tell us okay
um i will great
gawker
so insidious
i'm gonna do cocktails for 800 please
all right
three ounces of dry gin
one ounce vodka one half ounce of
lily blanc
stir with ice and strain into a chilled cocktail
glass with a lemon zest for garnish
i think this is a vesper
a vesper
you're absolutely right
it's a vesper
it's me i'll try
uh cocktails for 600
two ounces of gin
one half ounce of
maraschino liqueur
one quarter ounce of cream
de violet
three quarter ounce of lemon juice shake with ice and strain
into a cocktail glass garnish with a brandy
cherry or a flamed
lemon peel
hmm
uh huh
i don't
really drink much with the violet
in it is that the
the old rosy tit flip is that what that one is
that's what it is the rosy
tit flip it's one of the few answers
both in breast sling and in cocktails
that's true that's true
rosy tit flip is a move and
a delicious drink
i'm passing paul
i'm not gonna guess rosy tit flip i don't know
pass coward
i don't know this one
oh it was the rosy tit flip
oh i'm so close
the aviation
that's the aviation that must have
been a howard hughes beverage
yep
uh paul
before they wrestled please
for two hundo
before wrestling he was a bodyguard for the
shaw of iran
that is the iron chic
that's the iron chic i knew that one
matt
uh cocktails 400
daily double
now it's the
daily double of the day
still for 400
two ounces of bourbon
three ounces of lemon juice
one half ounce simple syrup
one egg white shaken with ice
and strained into a rocks glass or
coupe
interesting is this a proper
this is
i used to make this drink all the time
it's in
my old old cocktail book
that i have on my bar and i don't remember
the name of it
it's not like the first recipe of an original like old fashioned
i don't think so
because the egg white in there
throws that off
uh
what is a kentucky omelette
show me kentucky
omelette
a whiskey sour
whiskey sour
that's not what i was thinking of at all
i'm dumb
but the egg white
i don't get the egg white in there
the original recipe is called for egg white
because it gave like a froth on the top
when you shook it in the cocktail shaker
that's true
i'll close out cocktails for 200
oh shit it's the other daily double
holy rosy nipple flips
now it's for 1200
one cube
of sugar muddled with
i never know how to say that word bitters
angostura
angostura i think you got it
bitters and a tablespoon of water
add two ounces of bourbon or rye
stir with ice strain into a rocks glass
garnish with an orange twist
your mom
it's called chimera bitters
that's it
but go on
that's the old fashioned
yeah there it is
paul you got second biggest facts
for 2, 4, 6 or 800
score check
i am at 2400 paul is at 1200
matt is at zero
try and keep it fresh
800 second biggest facts
second most
abundant gas in earth's atmosphere
farts
nitrogen
is incorrect
oxygen is number one
nitrogen is number one
fart
matt
i was told it was hydrogen that's why i never lit any canvas
good idea
smart play it safe
stay in the dark
i will do second biggest facts
for 600
second largest country
in the world by area
causing all kinds of hysteria
this is the worst
beastie boys song ever
land maps
let's do it
i don't know
there's a move
a group right now trying to advocate
for more accurate maps
because africa the way we show on maps
is basically too small
so they're trying to like
create a different map so that we show how large africa is
yes
that's been a movement
for a while
i think it's worth dedicating your life to
i don't know
pass
oh that passes to me
yeah i mean it's gotta be
second largest country
by area
oh i've got points i can play around a little bit
so russia's real big
china's real big
this isn't gonna be one of those where like
because the maps are drawn
drawn wrong
it's like greenland or something
no i don't know
so russia or china
i would think so one of those
it's gotta be
i think russia is
smaller than china's i'll say russia
canada
blame canada
i will
canada is number two
russia is number one with 6.6 million
oh miles
square miles i guess
yeah great canada
that's me i'll try second biggest
fact for 400
what is the second longest river
in the world
uh let's see
the nile oh wait shit
i always get confused
you got the nile and the amazon
the yucatan
and the yucatan yeah the nile the amazon
and the yucatan and the old man
that's it
the old man river
uh
i
think i think those are
the two i'll say the
nile
it is the nile nice
amazon number one
and paul closing out the category and the game
second biggest facts for 200
second longest reigning monarch
in world history
ooh um
the second
longest reigning monarch in world
history uh which
monarch stood in the reign the longest
which monarch stood in the reign the
second longest i think it's queen elizabeth one
queen elizabeth one
is
incorrect it's queen elizabeth two
ah
70 years uh louis the 14th
of france was first with 72
years oh man
uh paul got that wrong
uh but that doesn't matter i
win with 2200 points
uh matt is in second with zero
points and paul is in third with negative
600 points if i had done all of the
score keeping correctly that's from
leon cassabre thank you leon cassabre
yes if you want to send us a scooperty
or a price of scryte jock versus nerd
or a regular jock versus nerd uh what's
the other one price of scryte obelisk
that was it uh those are all the jock
versus nerds out there matt is drinking
from his phone so come on over there
hey scoops dot com right there on the home page
you can make us a scooperty you can make us an obelisk you
can make us a price of scryte jock versus nerd you can do
all the things you can send us some scoop mail
all there at hey scoops dot com
hey you know what else you can do at hey scoops dot com
what you can buy your tickets to scoop
fest what that's right that's
what you need to do the scoop odyssey come
join us in beautiful las vegas
nevada in september next
month as you are listening to this
episode september 2025
uh the last weekend the last thursday friday
saturday and september come on down to las
vegas stay at the orleans tell
them that you're here for scoop fest they'll give you a discount
room right there and do everything
with us there at the orleans
uh come on down to scoop fest oh there are even
still some tickets for the jacob's whiskey
barbeque left we opened up a couple of new
tickets so i think there are like four
tickets a handful a literal
available left yeah yeah
jump on it uh only because we opened up
a couple of new ones so we have opened up
a couple of new whiskey barbeque tickets
so if you were hoping to come out for that
come on out yeah but yeah do
it we have some fun surprises both scoop fest
and we do uh for
uh the whiskey barbeque itself
look that's the second wife spotting
two wives oh there's another wife spotting
two wives in a single podcast amazing
that's right no one trank dart her
never been
done before
uh yeah get on scoop fest
uh did you send us thank yous
i did all right
i should uh look at those
okay i want to thank uh the following
uh people who support us over on our
patreon page and these people also
uh put egg whites in
all of their drinks uh
that's curt henderson curt eggner
kristin cladick colin
tony colin tony kiwi fruit
uh king scoop kimchi
douche scoop kevin dory kevin
chamberlain kenneth soto
ken fargy kelsey kundari
keith robert corning scoop
heaster sunday k mathis justin
robert young judy schneider
juan galavis j rock
scoop and joshua wilson
big thanks to these
people who only in the middle
of it did they realize they were in
their last podcast jay
shapiro jason yanowitz
jason victor jason vasquez
jason street jason speckland
jason jorkostas
jason clepper janine lancard
jamison fisher jameson hubble
jameson dawson james
dawson jake schneider jacob
dinklaker i want to scoop
baby ice blue scoop ice cream
manwich ian soto
ian a chapman i don't
have a scoop name and hilly
and scoop i want to thank
the following people who all
played bass in the rose
tit flip trick band
before becoming wrestlers
uh joshua wilson joshua
watar josh robert joseph
pulvero joseph foster
jordan campbell jonathan johnny
parker john jacob scoop
alheimer schmidt uh
john holchin john gloor john
carter jimmy sloanina jill
short jesse rain jeremy
hudson jenny ebarb jeff lumis
jeff libby jeff harris jeff
faust and jed taxon
big thanks to
these individuals who also
have their own head cannon for the
true ending to the clue movie
house dad scoop holly
marshmallow lightly heather divine
hansen hatchet scoop
guarthock guy wade
grill sergeant scoops green
wolf scoop uh gravel
scoop greater sunday scoop
gizmo scoop carola garcia
uh george guskov
genetic scoop
gene zinc gelato steve
gelato problems gazpacho
scoop gasman scoop
and garret godfrey
and the following scoops were
all thoroughly unimpressed when their parents
took them to see a movie that was dated when it
came out that's galen digs galactic
president scooper star mc scoops a lot
galusha scoop fudgy the whale frozen
cusser frozen 49th scoop freeze
dried scoop freehold scoop frankie's
tiki scoop flat kidney finn steffensen
fifi fade out scoop evil
monkey erotic scrape scoop
eric neilson elton magic scoop
alissa walsack edward
bender edlas scoop
ed wagner uh ed undrick
ed arms
are marcus dwayne webb
duke scoop duck flambe
dr tobias scoopy dr scoop little
dr science scoop doug lea
don't say scoop name don dotty
doc scoop distiller scoop
dirty old scoop dip and dot jack
dole whip scoop derrick dozer
dead lazlo david walker
and david sorensen thank you all
so much thank you all so much if you want to be
thanked on air if you want discount code
to scoop fest um if you want
invites ad free episodes
all that stuff head on over to
uh preaching fun
three wives dot com we did it
three wives we did it
we did it three wives
three for three
amazing
it's better than hanging with your
body
deeper
or if you
I don't I don't know my wife is
a dog you're attacking me
farts in a bag dot biz
farts farts farts farts
farts
farts in a bag
dot biz
that's farts in a bag dot biz
that along with preaching fun dot com it takes you
to our patreon page where for as little as two
dollars a month you can help keep this show on
the air if you think this show is worth more than
zero dollars head on over to preaching
fun dot com farts in a bag dot biz
I think I just said two I meant three
for as little as three dollars a month you can
help keep this show on the air join us
over there at patreon it gets you into fun
things like our live zoom sessions
during the show and there are also
all kinds of fun new things coming
for our patreon supporters over there
preaching fun dot com farts in a bag dot biz
do it now yeah
thank you guys so much out there stay safe
we love you and we'll see you soon
we'll see you soon
we're recording matt on a new microphone today
it's very exciting
we're gonna see how it turned out
oh boy
by this point in the episode if you're listening to it
you already know how it turned out
we're preaching fun
see ya
you