Hey everybody Jacob the audio guy here Tierney's Tavern Thursday October 23rd
Montclair New Jersey 7 p.m. It is going to be great the doors open at 7 make
sure you get there Tierney's Tavern Thursday October 23rd doors open at 7
p.m. It's a night of improv stand-up magic Matt Donnelly and Paul Mattingly
that's right Matt and Mattingly will be there Kurt Braunler will be there Dion
Flynn from the Tonight Show with Jimmy Fallon will be there the didgeridoo
scoop and so many more it is going to be amazing if you can get to Tierney's
Thursday October 23rd 7 p.m. get there it is going to be a night to remember I'm a
little jealous if you go and I'm not there just know that I'm jealous of you
that's right here we go I've been working all day
already it's fucking bullshit that's the thing about you want to go to bed or
yeah I scream truck drivers that have joined us today thank you all you ice
cream truck drivers I don't have a new list with your names on it yet but we
will before this month is over and we will thank each and every one of you by
name here at this part of the show if you want to be an ice cream truck driver
and I sure hope you do preaching fun commas ring go go to preach it fun calm
sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you say may be
your own and now a program your wife is right do you want to go to an ice cream
social season yeah I'd love to great let's go
what would you do show of hands everybody who's doing this show from a
balcony on a cruise ship
it's time for Matt Madley's ice cream social just sitting in a regular room
it's Paul Mattingly different regular room it's me Jacob the audio guy we're
preaching fun I don't like being called bougie I feel like nothing about me is
being bougie at all Matt Donnelly is wearing a bright pink hoodie after the
Beatles sergeant pepper album which one are you which one is that a little pink
one mr. pink who is that John yeah I think that's Paul yeah I think it's why
would you get the Paul John one is the yellow one that none of the none of the
three of us wanted I think you would pick the rainbow one and I think I had
the George one makes sense all right I'm here to give sage wisdom here to give
sage wisdom this hood on this large hood it's great because you want to why but
it's so windy but I still want to get my steps and I can put my headphones on and
over the headphones and then tie it tight and I can walk around with my
headphones on it is a it is a bigger deal than people realize for for large
headed individual a hood on a hoodie that actually fits our head and same
would goes with those you know I use real headphones because the little ones
that go in the ears again when you have a large head you also have large
ear holes and so those those of you got earbuds just fall right out of your head
yeah I can't wear earbuds like throwing a hot dog down a hallway with you I can
do I have a gaping slutty ear hole Matt with his lobe gashes just completely
wide good good how do you think he gets that good some serious oral stimulation
earbuds fall into his ears tweezers he's got four Raycon stuck in his hurry I
just keep hearing Spotify ads the helicopter is coming by Matt right now
it's it's great I'm sure they're not looking for him it's no big deal
citizen are you on twitch what is the content of your creation which is really
cracking down air wolf it could be air wolf it could be air wolf they could
always be a string fellow Hawk coming through so yesterday is this is a jet
that's a jet I think we're gonna be done by so soon I'll go back inside why this
is great radio apparently there's a drawback to doing the show outside you'll
never convince me hovercraft I'm just gonna keep I'm just playing an old
sound effects CD spike Jones bit they're invading Normandy right behind Matt we've
got airplane helicopter next comes a slide whistle and a cymbal crash the
chicken squawking so I was supposed to be at sea today yesterday we're supposed
to spend the day in Maine and one of the things that's interesting about Virgin
is that they basically when you go to ports that you can't dock at because
your ship is too big you have to take boats little boats from your ship to the
to the shore right okay those are called tender boats I prefer dinghies and it
was really interesting because I didn't know that and I was like oh we're gonna
tender can we tender tomorrow are we gonna tender or how do we tender and I
was like what is going on you didn't understand the lingo eh I was like I
brought plenty of actually let's do this rock and roll I'm an open-minded
individual I assume my wife is as well but either way she's not here if she
wanted she wanted me to do it she want me to do a tender that's what that's
what you know if I know her so then we were in Maine and the seas were too
too rough the current too strong to tender boat from the from the ship to
the shores in Maine oh no so that means no none of their excursions got to go
through right so excursions are over that kind of stuff and then also met
that like for the time being we were just spending a sitting and looking at
the shores of Maine was it kind of rocky even while you were docked no not too
bad no because you're you're lassoed in pretty taught yeah yeah cuz it's also
more of a current issue and currents weren't affecting the anchorage gigantic
boat interesting but it's different when you're at sea and you're moving you're
like oh it's a sea day but here we're going it's everything when you're at sea
day you're like we can't go there and we're gonna sit here right and bless
their hearts I'll say it bless their hearts over there at Virgin they made
some calls and like about two hours into everything being canceled they're like
hey we're going to Boston like right now so we're supposed to be in Maine go at
sea for a day then be at Boston in the morning and they're like no we're gonna
haul ass right now and go Boston right now and so you're gonna have an overnight
two-day Boston excursion and and so I thought those pretty heads up on their
end it caused chaos and entertainment department shows going if the if the
boats moving you gotta have shows going right well yeah I mean also at the show
if we're at sea your your show is a primetime show right if we're going
overnight in Boston it's the only overnight of the journey boy is no one
going to your show right where did you fall I thought I was not on either either
way I'm gonna get until Monday so I don't have to worry about it but yeah so
I'm off and out speaking of that how is your life of leisure going between your
your one and a half shows a month I'm going fucking nuts okay so now it's time
for you to get a handheld console of some kind that's your next move I don't
I just think yeah yeah I'm all cut up on my boom beach of nailing yeah you got to
get a proper Gameboy or some kind of yeah yeah we got to get you a modified
Gameboy that's got like thousands of games on you far from I watched some
weird way with Wyatt Russell in it I watched I'm binging task which is not a
real heart-warmer not really doesn't really warm the soul and and I and I
bounced off of that on the first episode we got 30 minutes in she was like no I
can't do it it's dark oh that's yeah it was that I single part of that show that
looked that interested me enough to even turn it on well it's just so it's so
depressing yes and just said straight up she's like there's enough happening I
don't need more made-up pressing I'm good yeah no no when you're when you're
living as a little cabin boy with room service looking at looking at people
living in a total hellscape with no hope is really really makes those eggs taste
as extra delicious speaking of Matt sitting and living as a little cabin boy
and other people living a hellscape I saw Matt's wife the other night after we
get done recording poor poor hellscape I'm doing four shows in two weeks and my
wife is doing like she is handling the speaker world pride parade yep today she
is hosting auditions for a showgirls musical at Troy's theater uh-huh she is
running an after-school program for the children uh-huh she's also basically
some sort of manager of the disco show some sort I don't know her exact position
but she's she's a she's a she's a managing member of the disco team sure
sure and there are people down at absence and so Sarah is filling in for
two people and covering everyone's shifts over at absence right now doing
all the shows and getting my boys to soccer practice and band practice and I
have to do four shows in 14 days I feel like such an asshole I saw her on
Wednesday evening and she comes over we're chatting and somebody also asked
how you were doing and she went oh I think he's doing actually she looks at
me you saw him this morning how's he doing I said he's fine he's a little
stressed about just sitting in the cabin while you're running life here and she
gave me the biggest eye roll that I have seen come out of oh boy I'm familiar
luckily for you though luckily for you it was her birthday and I'm going on the
first day the show it was on her birthday but everyone at the show was
just coming up to her and telling her happy birthday and singing to her so
everybody at the show went really out of their way to make sure that your wife
had a good birthday evening no I think I think that was I think that was really
good that was that was a good ending of the day especially for Matt Donnelly who
was it some of Amy Poehler's interviewing a woman she's in that Leo
Leo DiCaprio movie that's out right now Paul Thomas Anderson oh cool who's that
lead actor I forget her name and she was joking she was like you know every man
in their marriage says their wife is their best friend but if you ask the
wife of the best friend is they have a list of friends she's like men don't
have friends she's like well women have friends
my husband and said good thing that you have this podcast because you've got male
friends my wife was was showered with with cards and gifts and people take her
out to lunch and all that stuff and I sent some vegan dark chocolate gift
baskets from far away oh yeah I want to thank you for that that was really good
oh shoot I wasn't gonna mention anything I saw that dark smudging all around your
mouth hole I thought that's probably chocolate but I don't want to you know
put him on blast mostly chocolate it's 85% chocolate Jacob have ass we'll eat
it Smith
Brogan there's your sticker oh my god I'm straight-up delirious today from work I
just oh yeah yeah just work just makes me delirious at this point is it all
Christmas stuff now you're dealing with we're about to hit Christmas yeah we
were getting we're getting Christmas scented shit meanwhile yeah exactly we're
getting like pine needle glade plugins and we're getting fucking leaves leaves
an autumn soap hand soap like today like we got the Christmas sense before we got
the autumn sense is weird and that doesn't make horse sense no make a damn
lick of sense what does oh boy so yeah and then just being up so early today
but then I couldn't sleep today because I had stuff to take care of at home so I
haven't got my nap in so I'm kind of just in that and then that's true well
then right before right before we record at about a half hour ago and calls me
says hey can you look over this resume I put together and do some you know edit
you know just edit and copyright not copy copy any resume it was a it was a
Tinder program resume so she sent me a resume and so I really sorry I'm just
refilling from my recently refilled vase of drinking water you've got a fucking
fresh carafe fresh carafe oh my god life is tough man cruise life is tough I've
been there I had the exact same or similar situation but mine was even
crazier because I couldn't get off the boat for four or five months oh yes so
like major life events would happen and I was just stuck no you have and I could
only call Anne once a week sometimes once every two weeks though there are
people that are on here like that for like forever right and so I heard things
like I just get the burger the day just experience something different I don't
care whether I like it or not I just get the burger the day yeah yeah yeah I know
it's got pear on it it doesn't sound good I'm interested some vinegar dipped
pear gruyere oh Jesus it looks really pretty in the picture I know it's not
gonna taste that good but I'm gonna try it has got something a little different
bar foe that's so you were you were tasked with punching up a resume yes I
was tasked with doing a quick you know what do you call it cop not what editing
editing yeah copy copy copy they're doing like copy editing a resume and then they
went and whatnot and I think a copy edit and I did a I did a bang-up job if I say
so myself yeah as long as the words copy edit didn't have to be in there
anywhere thank God thank God she's not a copy editor I barely am you know I agree
Paul you are barely a copy was it her resume or someone else's resume no is
her resume so yeah so exciting things I was gonna say I was like enter inter
company okay okay everybody keep your fingers crossed for he's applying for
the role as ICS host yeah she's come she's coming on I would I would cross my
fingers Paul but I have so much to do I have so much going on I get it I'll get
around to it okay oh he's halfway there this is good yourself I don't want a
rush job happening if it's if it's hurry what quality yeah finger-crossing over
quantity finger-crossing but so yeah I was just doing that right up to the end
and then you know shifting the dogs around because I got I got to run the
giz and adora warden so I got to switch them oh yeah one has to be away while
the other gets to roam free and then back and forth back and forth you got a
balanced yard time they still don't get along no oh I thought it was like I
thought there's like a temporary growth like no no no this is a forever thing
this is not something that I would be okay with as a pet owner it's a it's
aggro simply not be okay with some of my pets be like no no fuck you but now
Agra leaving yeah it's agger damn bait and that's for sure either she is on my
lap next to our next to Anne okay or she is put away or one of the other one is
put away but so yeah I spend no all the time no babysitting is making sure gives
is there and safe and then and then she'll start going because she needs to
go out or want some water or whatever then I had to go and lock up a Dora and
then put her out and then take her back and get a Dora back out and when Anne's
home you have to put her up to right oh forget and adore I don't get along
forget it they are vinegar and water just I think that's right is that right
vinegar vinegar and water and also that's gonna be on the new burger of
vinegar and water does not sound good I mean it is gonna be on there it will be
something water vinegar and vinegar I don't know why not oil and vinegar it's
you know it's the reason these oil spills are a problem is because they
don't mix and not snow as your copy editor but I ask if you want to do oil
oil and vinegar instead of water and vinegar he doesn't know what copy editors
mean I do though I do I just don't remember what the phrase is right but it
was yeah no boy so well yeah fingers crossed for whatever she should she will
crush whatever it is yes yes I only you know shake my head in disbelief anytime
she's passed over for anything because fools fools they know not the power of
Anne McPheeters yeah that's right get shit done she gets to put Matt and I
down as references okay I'll do that I'll do that I'm sure she'll do that I'll
face time with weather wearing wearing this sweatshirt oh I'll be ready where
where the fish head miss McPheeters we were gonna hire you for this we called
one of your references he was sprawled nude on a cruise ship balcony during
the entire zoom call that we had with it we couldn't really hear him over the
helicopters yeah it's just a lot of helicopter sounds and we couldn't use it
was from an actual helicopter or just the way he was rotating his wiener he
was harpooned by someone in a lifeboat to make sure that he jumped it seemed
effective it's a defective tender that man I'll tell you who else wants to get
tendered and that's the following sponsor today's show Matt manley's ice
cream social is oh come on now brought to you by you without the internet's
come on oh I thought I thought you read something scary no no no no what could
be going wrong in the world now my phone's being a dick one second oh yeah
I've got one you say that one for the next one okay we got one for crazy Jeff's
propeller hats for corgis that's from street scooper crazy Jeff's propeller
hats for corgis hi my name is crazy Jeff I sell propeller hats for corgis
now for a long time I couldn't maintain a job or a relationship at all because I
was crazy and I just could I couldn't get it together for anything except the
thought of putting propeller hats on small Welsh corgi dogs and I started
doing that and they let me you want to know how I got these hats let me tell
you well spoiler crazy Jeff was eventually gonna go totally crazy in
that yeah too long a fuse for your jake of the audio guy for sure for sure he
was you know he was coming off as relatively sane Jeff for a pretty long
while yeah so yeah I saw so those show their production shows here on board oh
good oh yeah those are always a trip what's what is the title of one now this
was one's called out of time oh good is that is that banking on the whole
musical musical ization of back to the future I see why you would think that
Paul it's actually a Jersey Boys style musical about Huey Lewis in the news
yeah I would Huey Lewis on an arena stage don't take money don't take fame
don't need no credit card right on this train hey hey you know I'm saying it's
very sudden it could be cruel sometimes but it might just change your life they
say that all in love is fair yeah you don't care you know Joe Pesci is also
in my musical yeah well you know what they do when it gets hold of you with a
little help from above you'll feel the power of love it's not that Joe Pesci
knew all musical stars before they became famous he's also he's actually a
key component into making anyway no so Paul Paul's right it's a it's about a
time machine thing the time machine thing oh oh it is just about a time
machine yeah it's raiding the rock vault it's raiding the rock vault was still
conceptual and had a giant Mayan temple those of you who don't know as
astronauts invading a giant Mayan temple and discovering ancient hieroglyphs of
rock federal archaeologists yes they were talking about the federal
archaeologists that was when they were having auditions and our friend who is
our friend SJ Brandon got in Brandon anyway someone told me I had no audition
right away and I said I'm in LA with my family and I said well they're always
I was in I was in fucking California do the same time we were both fucked for
the day yeah I so I flew home yeah to make it to the audition time and he said
oh just kidding they're not seeing anyone else today and I was like okay
time thanks for having me leave my family in California and fly home to do
this audition thanks buddy our friend our friend our friend Brandon yeah our
friend later on it was like hey can you get pen and tell no not Brandon Brandon
didn't do Brandon actually got the gig eventually oh yeah okay yeah no no wasn't
Brandon sorry yeah Ryan Ryan yeah right right yeah Ryan was in it for a long time
right had me fly home and said just kidding and then and then later on was
like hey can you get pen and tell her to do this thing and I was like you know
what I can't know you know I can't you know what give me give me give me 180
bucks back and maybe we'll talk dollars and some time with my children which has
a price let's be honest it does people it does I'm sitting in a cabin the price
is here the price is right motherfuckers prices right my little golden bottomed
glass of water matches there with magic fish scaring housekeepers too much too
much rating the rock vault is finally closing this year and in Las Vegas yes
I think I think just like a couple years past for this might be the year we're
talking about a lot of shows closing but yeah my sincere some touring but yeah
they're gonna they're gonna close at the old Hard Rock Cafe here in Vegas finally
at the end of the year after I think like 12 years my sincere hope for rating
the rock vault goes to the old wrestling adage how can they miss you if you never
go away I agree and I really think that maybe three years from now they can come
back really well let's see 2028 provided things are still intact she's shaken out
in a certain way let's say 2028 maybe yeah okay just as a just as a arbitrary
possible gotcha yeah okay I'm not picking that date for any specific reason
no a little Vegas in parking whether they're trying to do a couple things or
some because you know so you're like not gonna charge for parking for locals other
people try deals and the whole point is just like man Vegas is a town of bold
swings so if you kind of inch back little things and expected to have a big
impact you're a fool yeah Cosmopolitan I just got an email about three minutes
ago a report about Cosmopolitan they are doing a new special to try to entice
locals and quote-unquote industry people to come to Cosmopolitan and what they are
doing is they are offering free parking to these people every single Monday
Mondays Monday is going free parking to locals on Monday when I was in my 20s
and Monday was my night off after I worked on Saturday and Sunday yeah I
started a thing with my friends called Mondays the new Saturday and we would go
nuts on Monday nights I'm not even saying that I won't take advantage of
this ever I'm just saying it's a dumb promotion as it worked in a very small
group of friends in the 90s and 2000s early 2000s I would like you and that
group of friends to hang out at the Cosmo on Monday nights going well I
believe what let's see how long this going what the Cosmopolitan is missing in
this calculation is there need to be industry people employed in Las Vegas
for the discount to apply and if all the people are getting let go here's an
example of what I think would would would be fun okay free parking and free
valet again because it used to be free valet when you first came here right for
an entire month if all of November it was just free parking and free
valet because that would make people I think from Los Angeles and stuff go like
oh maybe funders roll in there and toss the keys and go into Vegas for a weekend
or whatever like they might like that would be something that would at least
make people go like oh shit you know like you know like there you go scoop
Jesus has got it no fee November I was gonna say no pay no Ben November to go
along with no nut November as we all celebrate of course yeah I'm getting a
jump on it that was low-hanging fruit that's why I can't resist touching it
boy yeah that's a good idea Matt it does need to be a big move right silly or
stupid it needs to be like oh like oh what like it needs people go like whoa
like it needs to like make people go like oh shit cool Vegas is back that's
what that's like so like these little inching things of like oh well you know
we're not charging for this over here we give this much and maybe that will get
enough people in the door to move the needle a little bit yeah but we won't
change too much yeah yeah but they won't do it well I don't want to give away too
much production stuff here but I feel like our dealings with the Orleans
reflected very much sort of zeitgeist of what's going on in Vegas and I see this
quoted by local Vegas and Las Vegas locally and and you know some of our
favorite Twitter bloggers and whatnot how you know this vicious cycle of oh
shit we're losing money because no one's coming let's charge everyone for
everything right every little thing because everything that used to be free
now are our charges things that used to be just considered complementary now our
charges things that we used to be able to make a deal on now we can't negotiate
a fucking penny you know and then that gets even worse because you start to
tighten the strings on the people who are actually paying to utilize your space
and then they don't want to utilize your space and then it's like yeah yeah sorry
I wasn't listening what you could you start from the beginning again so I
don't want to give too much away here regarding our yeah you wouldn't talk
about the oh he's talking about Vegas as a whole so Jacob I had both leaned in
and leaned out yeah no I didn't want to give too much away oh I don't mind
telling the audience that we had a very fucking hard time dealing with yeah yeah
no they were tough this year yeah and I think but I mean I think it's part not
just for us I talked to what to other people that had right events there and
and everyone had exactly the same complaints and I think it's in no small
part due to that whole effect of the tightening of belts all the way around
and the rejiggering of employment employees to where there's all people who
aren't familiar with their now prior roles you know and if you don't want to
give too much away here but we actually had kind of a hard time dealing with
your liens this year okay I don't want to spill all the beans but this year our
relationship with the Orleans was strained that was yeah yeah yeah yeah
but not to give too much away let's keep some cats in the bag here but let's also
say so far as us go into the Orleans that was tough this time around that was a
real dick kick there's a really there was a free place for me to park on
Mondays then it would all be better then I'd hang out on the strip some more yeah
and yeah and they get a whole casino full of people wearing our robes and
pheasants good point Lori else Roth like we add ambiance to that win-win I mean
I'll tell you who loves us at the Orleans is our bartenders the bartenders
love us and the production guys love us yeah yeah yeah yeah but every day I would
check in with the bartenders and be like how'd you do today and the bartenders
would be like fuck me these scoops are awesome I'm telling you magic there it
is I've seen the party ultimately those motherfuckers who are working those are
the only people I care about actually making happy true I do want them to be
happy that is absolutely true and and one of the brothers said it was like I
can't wait for you guys to come back and we were like don't wait in one hand and
not shit the other like one of the bartenders that he had been with us for
our two previous show our two previous oh really so he made sure to get up here
I saw you guys on the schedule I made sure to get up here yeah he was he was
having a fucking you remembered it's a good time right yeah yeah I'll tell you
who else remember that it was a good time and that's the following sponsor
today's show is brought to you by sweat house roofing company hot shingles just
waiting to be nailed that's right sweat house roofing company hot shingles just
waiting to be nailed that's right it's time you know what time it is time to
check your papers for openings and try them to check your openings for papers
go ahead and look into class acid fides right under the acid fides you're gonna
find our sweat house roofing hot shingles in your area ready to be nailed
anytime yes indeed whether you like it hot or whether you want it wet even if
you need it metal we got you covered we always got you covered at the sweat
house roofing company uh-huh uh-huh how about a little Columbian tile if you
know me huh huh how about some do I huh do I know what you mean do you do I do
you I'm talking about doing drugs and having sex oh that's the secret of our
roofing company it's actually a front for drugs and sex in a van okay right to
your house and fuck you you can fuck me my own house why do I have to go in
that van oh a van just pulled up in front of my house somebody's ringing the
doorbell hey how's it going neighbor your roof looks like it needs some help
wink wink exaggerated wink deep exaggerated wink I'm saying it for the
benefit of the listening audience wink wink exaggerated wink innuendo hand sign
wink wink would you like a new roof wink wink innuendo hand signs oh yeah no I
would like a new roof yes great get in my van and take off your clothes is it
give me your credit card oh I see on it okay now you get it it's a fraud
protection thing yes also would you like some Columbian tile oh I know what you
mean do you I do do yeah yeah that's confused the first enough but you got it
right away yeah yeah no it's Columbian tile okay there yeah enter hey scoops to
check out yes I'm just slow you'll get it first you get the mortar then you get
the pestle then you get the Columbian tile so I don't know first you get the
pestle then you get the mortar I guess that's probably the better way because
how you go to transport the mortar without the pestle first you get the
pestle then you get the mortar then you get the tile say hello to my little roof
oh wink wink deep deep wink
yep I was watching the time-traveling show people have a there's a time machine
it's really what is it what is it top of a rack what is it it's a microwave
sitting on top of a rack that's spray-painted yeah it's a pushcart and you
put stuff in it and then when the screens go all crazy and then they go to
a different time oh and I was laughing cuz like it would like just like go you
know went to like 1950 something and then it was in a diner and then like they
had to get fuel each time they need to leave so the different fuel had to go in
the microwave to to power the time machine to go to different okay I'm so
in the diner one gigawatts and whatnot in the diner this is elaborate bit to
like during a dance number like steal a cheeseburger because the cheeseburgers
the fuel needed that was enough fuel to go and I it was like it's a diner just
order a cheeseburg like you don't need to steal that one just order a burger
like what are you doing right it's a 1950s diner your dollar will go really
far and I was laughing is like you know it also goes it went to like you know
10,000 not the spoiler for those of you who want to go see the show but it goes
to like you know 10 million BC or something like that right laughing
because yeah I was laughing is when it went to like very far in the past very
future there are people around me that were like whoa
like well I mean 10,000 to get out of this one well this is this is pre humans
right I believe so yeah not in this one no no okay there are some tribal dance
oh wait cuz cuz humans have been around this is the biblical one 300,000 years
yeah they I didn't write them I didn't write the years down maybe they got it
right now I got it wrong I don't want to despair don't come to me for exact dates
I don't fucking know but I mean oh my savings scoop Jesus is putting on the
chat like I've noticed some plot holes in this cruise ship jukebox time travel
musical no I get it that that parts like no it's ridiculous of course it is the
story to note that like just be like whoa like it was blowing people away I was
ready for time travel but not extreme time travel what they think of next I
don't know the most logical thing did they do jungle love they did not do
jungle love although yeah they do walk the dinosaur when when it featured
tribal people it did go into more ethnic and rap songs oh no suddenly it's a
Busta Rhymes video yeah that's kind of like maybe don't maybe don't put those
two together like that you know what kudos to them for really addressing our
troubled past everybody was definitely a lot of races all getting along and
everyone got to sit wherever they wanted there's a chance I could add some real
commentary what I would like to see on a cruise ship more a cheesy song and dance
show where they're traveling through time or a show where they really examine
all of the problems in America's racial history hey there daddy oh where'd you
zip in from I'm from the future I'm from the future I'm from 2026 Wowzers what's
that like well it's not too far off from the 1950s segregation but none of the
prosperity fuck us right yeah how'd you build a time machine God knows why don't
you want to stay here I'm ignorant I'm going back to where dinosaurs are
because I've got a better chance of making a life for myself in the time of
dinosaurs than I do in my time you're right I do want to see the educational
show on the cruise ship yeah exploration it's Saturday night I'm gonna go to the
Rosa Parks musical let's do it look man I'm a Tyrannosaurus Rex not a
tyrannoracist Rex everybody gets along in my time unless you're prey but you
could still sit anywhere you want in our dino diner
oh the diner is still there oh yeah the diner is the through line show the dino
diner it's always been a diner no matter what time
period I would love to me you and Sarah and maybe even Jacob and SJ honestly all
of us I think it'd be really fun to take a swing at trying to come up with a
cruise ship show that we could put together a jukebox musical for cruise
ships I think we could fucking crush it that might be the next episode of this
show like seriously we could crush one the four of us all together with all the
experience we've had like on both sides like Jacob could come at it with the tech
stuff and we could come at it from a writing perspective and and you can come
out from a performance perspective and it would just you know we could make
something really interesting I think all right we're gonna stop doing this
podcast from now on we're just writing cruise ship musicals step three profit
all you need is one all you need is one it'll play like you know like you have
these young people who are crazy talented right they have to get to do be
if you do so many dance numbers and sing so many songs to get on these these
things and they have like their songbook and they can like kick-ass choreography
then you put them in these musicals that are so strange where every costumes like
a million dollars and you're like I was gonna I was gonna showcase myself but
instead of playing like a secret spy scientist wearing a dinosaur tail that's
that's where I'm doing that's where I'm living my life but the money is yeah
yeah but it was it was fun it was it was it was certainly worth seeing so did
they go to the far-flung future eventually - yes they went back to like
before the big bang no lightsabers yeah what indicated Jacob when they were
hanging out before the big bang I was like where are you hanging out and where
are you staying they went to before the big bang they went to before the big
bang now wait a minute what they said that was it yeah the big bang that's
where they had this a real soul-searching Paul it's where they
really start to discover who they were and their feelings for each other well
it's because they didn't have any lights because they just went to pitch black
they're like oh this is where the big bang all matter actually how is it the
one tiny particle I was like how was our sound traveling from my mouth to your
ears before the big bang again with the big bang again I don't want to poke
holes in a cruise ship musical I don't I just I was curious about it there's so
much happening here before the big bang
really a really great image of dinersaurus dinosaurs dressed up like
line cooks pretty great
well the diner it could be it's sort of like a hitchhiker's guide the diner at
the end of the universe right yeah yeah yeah but how is this diner even here who
knows before the big bang who the fuck knows we're all just hash brown cakes not
before the big bang they don't exist yet we don't even have moons over Miami
because there are no moons hey how are my hammy my hammy welcome to Miami Ben
Vinito on me hammy how about the Giants equals last night in the in football huh
that's pretty fun that's pretty fun what happened Giants beat the Eagles with
with Jackson Dart I only bring the New York Giants look like the best team in
the football league that's right that's what happened I only bring this up
because Jackson Dart absolutely is the boyfriend of the daughter from land man
like that's watching when a press conference I was like oh my god it's
just the boyfriend from the show land man the football high school football
player oh yeah he's totally the same guy and Paul went away but Paul I'm here he
wears uh he wears like a black splotch on his cheek yeah he doesn't do the the
black face paint below both eyes he just does like a big splotch below one eye
and he does it because it's a tribute to Anakin Skywalker is it really he was
playing in high school and he was inspired by Anakin Skywalker and then
put a little black splotch on his cheek and some said look pretty cool so that
became his thing from then on and it was so funny because Herb Street and Al
Michaels and Al Michaels is like almost 80 years old he's done all like the
greatest right you know called the mystery the miracle of ice in the 1980
Olympics like and Herb Street's like of course it's a Star Wars reference Mike
you want to take it from here because Al Michaels I guess Al you want to take it
from here no no yeah you know I love me some Star Wars but no you go ahead Kurt
you break it down for the audience Al Michaels was like do not make me talk
about Star Wars wow well I mean you know that generation they really did love the
prequels yeah you know it was very impactful for them that was their big
movie going experience and I gotta say Hayden Christensen was doing a lot of
heavy lifting he tried with that shit script that he had you know so props to
him but I guess so the blotch is to indicate like when he got burned up in
the yeah oh it's from it's the scar it's the scar okay yeah now I see I thought
it was just on his cheek oh no it's the scar okay okay yeah he's like blacked
out one eye yeah he gets a scar okay well he's a handsome little Hayden
Christensen looking dude himself yeah yeah the quarterback of the New York
professional football team is very attractive and is going to do just fine
in his life yeah yeah he's gonna be okay he's gonna have some really nice Star
Wars memorabilia I'll bet he already has some really nice Star Wars memorabilia
New York transfer not not known for their looks Eli was never hold your
tongue apparently he did he often would sit on the sideline and just hold his
tongue I'm Eli Manning I throw ball I make I make touchdown go happen
I hold tongue hey I hold tongue hey sideline man you hold tongue for a minute
have make phone call I can hold that for you thank you
make phone call while someone else hold tongue hello this is Eli Manning calling
from Eli Manning phone yeah I would like a large cheese that's right
deliver it to Eli Manning please good night well that went good I expect to
eat pizza later I'll hold tongue now thank you yeah so yeah
Eli Manning hold on tongue this one's about a good-looking Jackson Dart was that's all
let's do some Scoop Mail
boy I want here from bus driver scoop dear Matt Paul Jacob and the entire
scoop community how does an introverted extrovert that is unbelievably damaged
mentally by life express how incredibly loved and accepted they felt at their
first scoop fest oh how does said person express the amount of confidence and
self-worth they obtained simply by being in the presence of this community for
four days I really do not know where to begin with the thanks the hugs the
heartfelt face fuckings I really can't find the right words to tell each and
every single person that I cross paths with that you are amazing and I am
infinitely grateful not only for your existence but also for you for your
acceptance into this spectacular group of humans thank you from the bottom of my
heart for being all that you are love and licks that's Tracy the bus driver
scoop oh yeah whatever that's a bad prank this is like that now this is
wonderful this is wonderful yeah yeah we got us pass that on to JD for yet
another scoop confessional or maybe it made it into a scoop confessional we
didn't even oh yeah I don't know we aren't privy to any of that we don't
know no I hope to see them at some point we got one from Masshole scoop dear
gentlemen an episode 1244 you guys discussed the song darling Nikki by
Prince the first time my mother ever heard that song was in April of 1985 I
had been born in March of 1985 my name is Nikki Jacob gave a good rundown of
the song on that episode but for context the very first lyrics are I knew a girl
named Nikki I guess you could say that she was a sex fiend I met her in a
hotel lobby masturbating with a magazine my poor mother was completely
horrified she said that if she had just heard that song a month earlier there is
no way in hell that she would have named her baby Nikki my name would have been
Sarah and that would have been weird so I'm glad it all worked out
people named Sarah are weird breaks in the same episode Matt talked about the
band G love and special sauce oh yeah coincidentally they also have a song
that references a girl named Nikki performing sex acts on the singer it's
called kick drum and it's actually a really good song it is a good face
that's a mass hole scoop who is a brand that's a brand new scoop name no
fantastic yeah thank you mass hole scoop so that's another question for the ages
and I'd love to get the popular opinion Matt Jacob what is your take on Nikki's
actual physical situation during this scenario is she reading and perusing a
magazine and did live the beam rolling up the magazine to some sort of phallus
and inserting it you know Paul there by masturbating with a magazine I have to
thank you Paul because I thought I was gonna have to ask that question and so
thank you thank you for being one of the turtle burning questions Nikki actually
doing with that magazine option B is eternally burning that's for sure and
then ML Kennedy says the magazine was also masturbating right that's another
reading on it it could have been joining in on the magazine's master magazine
there's masturbating I think Prince forgot word for reading and replace it
with masturbation you think he just did a search and replace better in a hotel
lobby reading a magazine that word means I don't know let's replace it with
masturbating reading too few syllables doesn't work linguistically also you
would hope that that's a very glossy tone because if it's just straight news
print oh he's gonna disintegrate you're basically she's gonna have a paper
machine good check for paper luckily it was a glossy magazine yeah when you read
the lighter notes is that do not try this at home do not utilize lighter
notes for who high insertion when I read the lighter notes they were all smudged
from being in my hoo-ha we got one from Trav hi I have over a decade of
professional experience in kitchens not to mention my continued learning and
growth in the 20 plus years of my adult life that I haven't gotten paid for
cooking I say this to only say unfortunately Paul is right about
microwaving hot dogs he's an absolute potato when it comes to
microwaving bratwurst though you see cooking a hot dog just involves warming
it up most of them you can eat it raw for the most part they're cured and
fully cooked therefore the only thing that needs to be done is to make it hot
to be tastier the traditional method for a ballpark hot dog is boiling cooking a
hot dog in a microwave is essentially the same thing it's akin to steaming as
long as you don't overdo it a microwaved hot dog is perfectly acceptable one could
argue even efficient I'm not saying you microwave the bun never microwave bread
it makes it tough now there could be arguments that grilling a hot dog adds
more flavor and a bit of texture that's not wrong but that doesn't make a
microwaved hot dog unpalatable it just makes those options better let's not
pretend that a hot dog is some culinary masterpiece it is a way to dress up the
leftovers and sell some cheap-ass shit love y'all fuck you the face that's
Trav aka ID H a S in okay yeah it hasn't I don't know I appreciate that Trav
thank you for coming to my defense yes I did say that you're a potato for
microwaving bratwurst look I did it once okay I've learned my lesson potato yeah
yeah it's just it's just a convenience thing yeah tell that to my intestines the
science is tight on this it's not it's not the same the science is out and we
got one here from Robert hi folks loved episode 1227 Rob's story about his
heroin neighbors reminded me of our old family friend Tim he was about 60 at the
time and this took place back in the 80s back in Poughkeepsie New York every fall
Tim would wander into our woods and collect giant quote-unquote basketball
mushrooms that not a nickname they were literally the size of basketballs I got
he had the he had the foraging know-how to tell the good from the deadly and had
sliced them like bread and fry them up said they were delicious we weren't
brave enough to find out for ourselves then one year Tim just stopped showing
up he was dirt poor and had no phone so we had no way to check on no our best
guest he finally grabbed a wrong mushroom and joined the network in the
sky years later surprise Tim reappears turns out he had gone to prison he went
to prison he just went to prison for mushroom thievin who knows I like to
think it was for mushroom thievin fast forward these turn things around got a
place even a phone he calls my grandfather and asks if I the family's
designated preteen tech wizard can help him set up a fax machine grandpa and I
head to his sketchy apartment one of the in one of Poughkeepsie's less than great
neighborhoods I plug in the brand new fax machine and ask if he has anyone to
fax or someone who might fax him then we spend 20 minutes explaining what a fax
machine actually does he seems surprised by the concept thanks for coming over I
got something for you he leads us into the into the kitchen and they're stacked
like techno Jenga are 50 brand new fax machines oh I decline no thanks I don't
need one either Tim nods you're right I've got something better for a kid into
the bedroom we go and now there's a stack of 50 boom boxes oh new shrink wrap
still on I should grandpa look grandpa just shrugs we both left with a boom box
yeah drain D batteries like it owed the energizer money money baby and that is
from Robert that's amazing I think the best not stolen boom boxes in the 80s
still drained those fucking D batteries like they were going out of style yeah
it was crazy those things like you could not run them on batteries for very long
you like five five or six good hours tops yeah yeah it's a shame Tim had to
go to jail for a little while he was always such a fun guy yeah I wonder why
well I asked him I asked him if it was for stealing mushrooms he said more or
less you can't get a straight answer from that cat it's time for Jack vs.
nerd truck ladies and gentlemen it is time! time for Jack vs. Nick! explosion of Jax and Darkface Pings!
we got a scoop and it coming to us today from the OG scoop the categories are
brands in song uh NURB words noun verb oh yeah noun noun verb words I guess
homophones five and before and after Matt you're up first what do you want I'll
take oh geez coming at us hard with this five look at all the pretty flowers all
in neat lines oh rose rose rose rose yeah rose rose yep rose rose rose they
grows gently that's me I'll try NURB words noun verb for 200 a cleaning chore
where what you are doing is removing something that is known by the same
name oh to dust like dusting yeah there you go yeah all right I got it now we're
all on board I'll try to know what these categories are brands in song please for
200 what gas company is mentioned in Bruce Springsteen's jungle land oh shit
I'll I'll pass cuz I don't know Matt yet
God that song is long for me to go through all the lyrics in my head shell
or something is it like people's gas like we have out here for our natural gas
is that what it is no it's the people's gas it is the people's gas for time I'll
just have a pass Dwayne Johnson came right to my house and said if you smell
rotten eggs evacuate your home they'll meet me that giant X on side brings
this city lights yeah yeah yeah it is I'm at
tried to get your springsteen song in there I know he's always looking out for
me before and after for 200 all of it Jacob all of that in see double a
basketball tournament with Frankie Valley
the final four seasons of course oh final four seasons our good buddy Noah
was just on that tour that's right you're good buddy but fine the final
four seasons let's see I'll go back to brands and song for 400 what car
manufacturer is mentioned in the song American Pie by Don McLean okay so the
the springsteen song was too long for Matt to go through American Pie real quick this comes up
pretty quick in the course excuse me Oh Chevy yeah I was gonna make you go
through that long long time ago time ago no galaxy far away
no galaxy galaxy Ford thought me and Qui-Gon Jinn could finally talk the
Federation into maybe cutting them a little slack let's go to oh brands in
song again I like it for 600 what camera country company is mentioned in hey y'all
by outcasts Polaroid Nokia picture shake it like a Polaroid Nakia I still feel
like that song is new ish to me and I know it's not and that reference was old
when he made that reference yes yes we're like what what is he talking about
and we were all Polaroid cameras were already gone by yeah yeah yeah I mean
this they're out there still but yeah yeah yeah but now it's like really
they're gone gone now they're just a Lego says me we talked about doing a
Polaroid camera thing for scoop fest I'm just now remembering that I'm gonna
order some Polaroid cameras for scoop fest like I got one vetoed that shit
that's true Matt you're up that's why I'm not going back to the Orleans next
year I'll do before and after 400 please the boss and blondie combined these 75
and 78 tunes awesome blondie
so this is a coming and going thing yeah yeah 78 heart of Springsteen have
something with the rapture at the end of it
shoot I'll pass that passes to me I'm passing to Paul I feel like this is
gonna be very simple once we finally see the answer I think you have to know the
the Springsteen song oh no that's the trick with these questions is you do
have to know them yeah it's the entire trick with the questions all right she's
the one way or another that's a good one yep that is a good one I'll try I'll
close up brands and songs for 800 what technology company is mentioned in Mr.
Roboto by Sticks SEO hmm I don't know I don't know I passed Paul IBM IBM all my
heart is human my blood is boiling my brain IBM yes good job Paul I ate a
sandwich I am a robot I have IBS let's go with her boards down for make the
connection Ollie and cardboard
they're both boxers boxing okay boxing the box yeah yeah yeah
Paul our back before and after 600 please daily double all of it Jacob all
of it a rowling magical novel with a new character a stunning wrestler oh I mean
Harry Potter who's the stunning
there's a stunning wrestler what I know the stunning wrestler Paul yeah who does
the stunner that's his I don't know most of the administration has suffered at
the hands of this wrestler a stunner like a good like over 50% of the
administration there was there was a great picture that came out last week of
of what's his name the guy who one of the guys who runs WWE now I used to
like yeah triple-h yeah I him and his wife who's Vince McMahon's daughter yeah
and man and her mom yeah Linda McMahon who's the secretary of whatever it is in
the Trump education right now yeah yeah and the thing without was like stone
cold Steve Austin has stunned all the people in this picture oh who who Jacob
stone for the record I still don't know the answer to this question it's Harry
Potter and I don't know this stone I don't know this I don't know the stone
it's a it's a daily double so I guess I'm gonna say so I'll also say Harry
Potter and the stone cold Steve Austin cold Steve Austin there you go so close
oh in my defense I got 80% of the words yeah you stunned 80% of it you know I'm
kidding go ahead it's me I'll try noun noun word or nerve nerve words noun verb
securing a box for shipping securing a box for shipping closing it oh tape tape
yeah yeah there you go Paul I'll do homophones for 400 upgrading the
offering table upgrading the offering table let's see that's a oh altering the
altar alter the altar alter the altar oh there you go alter
alter well done Matt you're up now I will do for an after 800 a bond theme song
plays as John McClane kicks ass in this movie live and let die hard there it is
Oh live and let die hard of course I'll close out nerve words for 800 sometimes
on a wall or used to beautify something hung on the wall sometimes on a wall or
used to beautify something hung on the wall
picture you could picture a picture I'll try picture I'll paint you could paint a
picture that was a stretch I think oh so was picture in fairness for 600 a rough
path a rough path and rough path huh trial and trail they spelled the same
no no they're not so it can't be a trial trail you did make me spell both of them
in my head though yeah right I know I had to to rough path
I don't know but there was only one set of foot a road road a road road no it's
a course course course course course course course course course and we got
homophones for 800 Matt closing out the category and the game and this is
double right no here you got both of those oh if I get this I'm in second
place and if I pass I'm in second place right I will take them all but not that
one oh this is a homophones this is homophones yeah I will take them all but
not that one oh I think I've got a guess I don't know if it's it though I don't
feel super confident I will take them all they're not the best I've ever had
not even close something like the lot not that one I just don't know I'm gonna
pass it passes to me I'm gonna I'm gonna try for second place here I think it's
except except ah yes look at you those well I couldn't think of a good way to
give a hint on that one that is the game Paul wins with 1600 I'm in second
thanks to accept except with 1200 Matt sin third with 600 that's from the OG
scoop thank you man thank you that was great I'm really very good at the
before-and-afters and I didn't get any of them good job OG job OG if you want
to send us a scooper tea head over to hey scoops calm right there on the home
page you can set us a scooper tea you can send us a jock versus nerd an old
school jock versus nerd you can set us the obelisk style you can send us what's
the other one price is straight you can set us a price is straight jock versus
nerd or you can just send us some scoop mail you can do all those things right
over there at hey scoops calm also if you try to send us some scoop mail from
the form there at hey scoops calm and you have a hard time or you have a hard
time with attachments or anything like that you can just email your scoop mail
directly to us admin at Matt and Mattingly calm oh Brogan has already
made a sticker for Paul's computer it is me telling have ass will eat Smith says
remember your password my hat says what's my hat say in that picture Paul it
says eat ass suck a dick and sell drugs and your mouth has a suspicious
thing around are you a my wife's chocolate you maybe it's clearly just
chocolate chocolate that's amazing work amazing work Brogan that might not have
I want to thank all the scoops are doing us here on our twitch feed here hell
yeah and I so I want to thank all the scoops to support us over at our patreon
we'll get them with the names up for the next episode let's know that this
podcast would not be possible without the amazing support that we get from so
many of you you know if you're out there and you have a little bit of room in
your heart and your wallet for us check out all the different tiers that fit
your budget over at preaching fun calm
or if you like and McPheeters don't get along with all of Paul's dogs head on
over to farts in a bag dot biz
your dog just did this or that your dog just brought a dead bird in the house I
get the same thing yeah I know I know how it goes oh yeah they're my dogs with
the bad uh-huh farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm it
does take you over to our patreon feed where for as little as three dollars a
month you can help keep this show on the air how else can you help keep this show
on the air we can go to our shop you can go over to a scoops comm slash shop
there's a lot of good stuff over there if that if that URL is too long for you
though just listen to this door jingle door a big door it's on we got a store
cha-cha-cha dot com that's right one take Donnelly there it is oh just go
baby just go it's hard to believe that was embarrassing at the time where's your
poetry but thanks for everybody stay safe out there thank you pen for
this podcast and we'll see you soon
yeah