We're not privy to the Twitch chat when we switch that off of our stack
This is my favorite part of the show this is the part of the show where we thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers up. It's crazy. We have a new list
I can't figure out how to look at all of it who can say what's gonna happen in the future
But hopefully you don't even hear this and you just hear me thanking people in case you don't I decided to put this hilarious
Anecdote in right here if you want to become an ice cream truck driver
And I hope you do preaching fun calm preaching fun commas
We're gonna sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save
May be your own
And now a program hey Johnny
Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah? I'd love to great. Let's go
We have some guests here in the turn today
Mike for sure should be so needed from a list casting the web series
It's true
Ice cream social sitting in Las Vegas that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pittsburgh PA. That's Paul
Also in Vegas. It's me Jacob the audio guy. We're preaching fun. Oh
Yeah, but before we get started fuck land man right in the neck fuck it fuck that show
fuck that
Piece of shit
So happy that we didn't dive into this season from what I'm hearing about this season
This season's been terrible many people been writing about it, but they did a scene
Okay, this is second the last scene that the series is about to end and they spend again
This is a show about a whole series. Does the end end? No, it should be but no, it won't it will go on
We're heading to the end of season two, this is a show that is about an oil company
aha trapped in doing business with a drug cartel and
the episode 9 of a 10 episode season I
spends
90% of it with like really deep
Conversations about relationships and about like their daughter going to college and all this other stuff
Okay. Now, that's just a big waste of the premise, but
In this episode this is things I watch the show because it is mediocre
I watch the show because it's easy to watch some of it and go to bed. That's why I watch it, right?
so I'm watching it and the daughter goes to college and
She it's like this really sweet moment and she even makes like a little like, you know
prayer gesture and then opens up her door and walked inside her first dorm room and
they have written a character to be a
like Charlie Kirk
Every liberal valued
Person becoming a nightmare possible. It is a trans roommate who says that they are vegan
They can't hear certain words because it's triggering. They said they have to meditate they have a pet muskrat. They miss take every possible thing
They have to take every possible thing that you could
that
Every like shitty liberal stereotype. Yes
Like here's all and like not even stereo stereotypes the wrong word because it's not even stereotype
Because like trans isn't a stereotype, but they just look at that and go like well, well trans is a problem
So we're gonna make this into a list of problems
See, they took everything that any kind of liberal value and made it an antagonist. Yes
I'm trying to make it an assault on the daughter and they literally have the mother come in to save the day where she rents
A hotel says invite all of your cheerleader friends because the daughter is gonna be on the cheerleading squad
They literally sit there sipping margaritas. Okay, everyone's underage except for the mother. They're also
Margaritas saying this is what college should be like and then talking about the roommate and saying like she's just unhappy with herself
So they purposely misgender the roommate and then lecture each other at the pool
Saying, you know basically saying that if you have liberal values, you have no fun. You have no friends
but if you you know, just just
Hate all those things and just value totally being selfish and fun life works out for you
And I'm supposed to go to bed and I'm stead. I'm fucking livid and angry
That this fucking for no reason just multiple shots anti-trans
Multiple shots across the bow just hitting transfer. No reason not for no reason
Fair fair
There there's a reason there are several psyops going on right now, baby
But this is it like I get it like we watch entertainment to give ourselves
brief respite from this hellscape of issues that we were constantly assaulted with from the time we wake up to the time we go
To bed, right and on the one hand we shouldn't be so concerned with the news
On the other hand real terrible shit is happening and it is affecting people. So where do we find a balance?
I don't know but one place to try to find balance is like for an hour before I go to bed
Right, like can I make a recommendation as to my bedroom viewing routine?
Just just your own penis where you put googly eyes on it and you just well that step one is
because
Bobo, that's his name Bobo is always watching along
Well, he can't watch without it. You can't watch without his eyes put on the uniform
You got to put the googly eyes on or Bobo is blind and a blind Bobo. Nobody wants to see that
anyway, I strapped Bobo's eyes on and I throw on tubi and
tubi has the giant selection of
Mystery science theater and rift tracks and that's all I do
I start a mystery science theater or rift tracks and let it play in the background forever. It's a mediocre film
If it has anything problematic in it, it is being lampooned by voices of reason who happened to be based out of Minnesota, by the way
Mystery science theater mystery science theater was from Minnesota. That's where that that all jumped off
that brilliant stuff so
That's how I soothed myself to sleep every night by watching old episodes of mystery science theater and rift tracks that I have seen
Hundreds of times and it's wonderful. Yeah
I will anything's better than what I'm doing. So I can't I can't say whether I do or don't like your idea Paul
I'm not a good judge of character as to how to spend an evening
So the best part about it Matt is that it especially with the rift tracks
Yeah, you've got the voices of the guys who are very left-leaning
For the most part Mike's not but still he wrote
you know, like I I used to just watch mediocre dramas because
Comedy makes me can get me in my analytical brain, which makes it not shut off
And so I end up like in a in a like joke construction
Kind of whatever and I can just I can just stay up for for hours and hours and hours and hours gotcha
So that's usually why I try to watch thing about rift tracks is because what you're watching is not funny, but they make it silly
Yeah, and so I take what I can watch I can watch
Man hands down. I haven't even watched season two. It's already better. This is who's definitely better than the season two of land man
I've ever even watched definitely
Is it out yet? Are you just about to roll out episodes? Where are we at from from the sake of a viewer boys?
We have five episodes out. So we have only three more so you have some catching up to do. Mr
Donnelly deal deal clearly my schedule is now open. So there you go. No problem
Your viewing schedule has opened up. So remind our audience about what your show is and where people watch it
Absolutely, we are a list casting
Jimmy are my esteemed actor here who keeps randomly changing his wallpaper and
Currently has a massage table
That's exciting who's never mind, I'm not even gonna ask who I've been in that spot that's happy beginnings. I know that place
Casting season two is located
Happy beginnings at the beginning. I mean not that I'm overly familiar with the industry
but I'm guessing that would work actually better right like I
Think it's way more comfortable than a casting couch. Let's just go with that
Let's get that crazy part out of the way and then now I can really relax into a mess
Okay, but I'm just gonna say you're missing the market
It's actually about a show about two casting directors and their assistant who have been blackballed by Hollywood and
now they are stuck in Las Vegas because when
Hollywood spits you out
Vegas sucks you in
That's true, I mean you guys are writing season three
Jimmy plays Roger and Roger is the owner of happy beginnings and no Roger Roger
Jimmy started out in
as sad actor and in the pilot episode and
we loved him so so much in the pilot episode that we gave him a name and
He's been a series and he's you got Urkel buddy. You got Urkel look at you go
Yes, it's it's a it's a very proud day, you know, I'm a classically trained actor I studied Shakespeare Chekhov
Decorated with awards and now here I am dressing up as a clown
and
Playing these sad actor
Before I actually get actually get my name. So finally got my name and it's Roger. Oh
Is there any Rogers do we do we do you know any like actual Rogers in the wild these I know a Roger
I mean, there's the American dad alien
And and that's the other one that I could think of yeah
And the American dad alien guy Jimmy I am stunned by this question
I have to actually look at my contacts with Roger Moore Roger in my okay. No Roger Whitaker Roger Whitaker
American treasure actually, I think he's English English treasure Roger Whitaker. Do I know Roger?
Yeah, the only one that popped up in my phone is the one that I mentioned
He is the only Roger that I that I have in my content
I do squirrely as Jimmy just asked the same question over and over again while you guys continue to stretch the parameters of the question
Roger Stone, I do not have in my Rolodex
Do you get a Roger ring at the massage parlor Roger Dodger
Happy Roger. I dodger on my Todd. Don't have anyone with a first name Roger in my contacts. Yeah
Let me shout out Roger. That's it. I'm gonna make another kid. I'm gonna name him Roger the market's wide open. I
Do want to say that his name almost was Kroger because when we were writing it I mistyped
Roger and
my creative partner Zack
Loved that it was Kroger and he was like, I love it. His name is gonna be Kroger
I can make Kroger work. Well Kroger is not only the grocery chain, but you've also got
the Nickelback fame Kroger, right like that's
Jack Kroger is Nickelback, right?
Hence why I had to cut it back to run. I guess have three Kroger nowadays. He's known as
Mrs. Avril Lavigne, right? Yeah
Okay, I wish I was for that weird marriage
Yeah Avril Lavigne Mary nickelback, did you guys not know that
Yeah, I thought Avril Lavigne died didn't she die well like one of her guys
One of the Levine's died, but there's lots of clones of her
Okay. No, she didn't die. She got Lyme disease, right? Isn't isn't she the one that got that guy? No, that's that's somebody else
That's what's her name from bikini kill who's married to a Beastie Boy?
I'm with Jimmy on this one. I think
She might have put
Kathleen Hanna also got Lyme's disease
Good Kathleen Hanna though. So what I'm the initial riot girl
Yeah, what I'm taking from this is if you marry a musician you get some kind of disease
Avril Lavigne contracted Lyme disease from a tick bite in 2014
Oh, no
Yeah, Jimmy knows everything about Lyme disease. Gotta stop this camera. Everything about Avril Lavigne except for her nickelback husband
Kroger who's apparently named Iraq air who else got Lyme disease?
Anybody who goes outdoors, which is why I never do it the outdoors. Yes, like
That was really like something that was like kind of like brought to me as like a selling point of just like yeah
We go out for a walk. We go through the trees. We petted a deer and then we go home and check each other for ticks
I'm like, I don't want type 2 entertainment. I don't want it
This entertainment pitch this is a terrible salesperson
Yes, you're right terrible
Now Jimmy once your character went from sad actor to Roger
Did you start doing a lot of like hmm? I don't know if my character would say it this way or my character do that
Roger doesn't kind of person who would like did you really take ownership now of your scenes, right? Right?
Yeah, no, I I had plenty of notes. Well, I didn't have them. I didn't give the notes my agent gave
Directly, I mean I don't got time for that shit
Thank you again for being here by the way, oh sure it's my pleasure I'm the envelope is slip slipping through the door
It's on its way we're paying him Michaels to be paying
Pay them in sandwiches
As long as the money in the sun is green. Oh
This is gonna be this is gonna be so awkward. I have them slipping a sandwich under your door right now
It is a capriotti sandwich like it's a it's a big it's not gonna fit under the door it's gonna be a mess
So Michael I know
Now I'm hungry
You guys have a studio where you're filming a lot of this but are we looking as you keep growing here to do more on
site possible shoots and things like that to make Vegas even more of a character as
The series progresses as I know LA is quite the character in a lot of Los Angeles productions
So are we hoping to make that more of a reality?
I know there were talks at one time of Las Vegas investing in some tax breaks for filming and stuff like that
That may have just been pissed in the wind
Yeah, I don't think that's really come to fruition
But what's the what's the ability to how how film friendly is Vegas right now for what you're doing?
Um, actually I found filming in Vegas like really
Embracing like it's actually a lot easier to get permits
It's a lot easier to okay find locations for people to film that the problem is
a cost a lot of money to transport an entire crew and to rehearse in a space and all that so
Yeah, as soon as a list casting gets funding from a bigger network
we'll definitely be able to okay take advantage of all these things, but
currently we tend to pick one location outside of our casting office to go to and and this time
It was a local dance studio where we filmed that but in the previous season
We went to Millennium Fandom Bar, which I'm sure you guys are familiar with. Yes one bar got to film there and
yeah, so I
Think that if we could afford it, I would absolutely do but you know
This is definitely an independent project where we pay Jimmy and massages and sandwiches
Yeah, so if any locations wanting want to let us film there for sandwiches and massages then
Example that's a great example of local business chipping in and wanting to be represented on the on the screen
So an example of businesses that love massages and sandwiches
Jacob what was that bar that you went to that turned into two bars last the other night? Maybe those guys need some
Film broadcast. They look like they need some promotion, right? Tony two bars. Don't need to buy Tony to bar
Was that it wasn't right? No, the guy dragged you over to a second bar for a drink and then left you high and dry
Yeah. Yeah. Well, the owner of this bar like took us out of his bar to a different bar and
Seemed like he was gonna buy us a drink and hang out with us in this other bar that he was taking us to and then just
left
He was like he was in the other bar for a grand total of two minutes
Well, you don't want to mention either of these bars, it was the weirdest thing I've forgotten both of the names
That's one thing. Well, then they definitely need some promotion. So the second one used to be the downtown lounge
That was that it was it was the same word twice. It was a nice place, too
Was it boing-boing or something like that? No, it wasn't boing-boing. We're calling it. Hatsy-tatsy. So it rhymes with that
Yeah, all right, hoochie smooth. It was like it was like Potsy Potsy
Potsy pot. It was Potsy Pots with the other one was Potsy Potsy. Good. We figured out guys. Go ahead and film there
Yeah
As far as we're concerned, well at least I'm glad to hear that at least on the locals level Vegas is still
Helping each other out in that respect
statistically I
Also, I feel like he is I also volunteer at Jacob's house. Oh
Yeah, yeah, how's your house is it good for does have a casting couch and sandwiches and so many
So many cast the couches so many sandwiches
You'd be you'd be doing me a favor if you got rid of some of these sandwiches actually
He actually has like a dog accessible casting couch, which is pretty amazing
He's got a little puffy stair staircase that goes up to his couch for his puppies, so that's it's a good it's good for
For dogs almost sleep their way into roles
Right. Oh, I see. Mm-hmm. I wasn't sure that was for me to get on to the
Very high couch
Person but no seriously that you know
It's it's I think it is a love letter to Las Vegas not so much in terms of the landmarks or the the the
places but like the characters that you'll find yeah in Las Vegas which I mean
I challenge you to find something that has that sort of thing where it like kind of explores the strange
Weird people who are in the entertainment field on the fringes that are not circa or Spiegel or whatever and
and how they
Make their lives work in this town because you know like LA actors left and right but you know, what are these?
lowly
Sad lawyer turned actors and you know all these all these other kind of characters
So I think that's it's that's one of the benefits of it
I mean, no no city on earth has better people watching than Las Vegas
and so to have a show that is kind of dedicated to a
Bit of that spirit is is a fascinating idea and something that people should check out
I mean that that's a that is a weirdly niche thing that I think people are gonna really love
and
More importantly Jimmy in episode 3 is dressed up as a birthday party clown trying to steal craft
crafty, which is the catering at
services and and
Him and I get in a shouting match with each other. So whoa
Is that because Jimmy?
Is that because Jimmy came to the shooting from his side gig as a birthday clown? No, no, no, no
he is for so the backstory of the movie that we're filming is that he's the clown in a world of mimes and
He feels lonely and left out and so he has to it's very dramatic has to jump off the roof to end everything
I can't wait to watch this. This is all backstory. This is all backstory that you will not know. Of course, you're hearing it first
Jimmy knew this
I
Was wondering why there were all these minds and me there that that was kind of confusing but now that makes no makes total sense
Now you finish season 1
Just does suddenly like did you always you're gonna make the season 2 season 2 simply just like I we can't something of funny casting
Adventures to go on or did you think of somewhere new to go with the show?
How did it all come together creatively for season 2?
Well, our writer Nick Adams he had already started writing
Season 2 unbeknownst to us. So we're like we did season 1 and our executive producer Chuck Prater was like, you know
I I think that we need to get a season 2 going away
I'm gonna get some funding for you guys and stuff and then Nick was like funny enough. I have
eight episodes ready for you guys to go and I was like
That's great. I was like
okay, and I was like this is great now we need to make them twice as long and
with much more characters and much to my chagrin doing
27 pages a day I was in three days
We talked about this last time I was on but yeah, we tend to shoot three episodes per day it and that was
It turned out wonderful. But also I was like, I'm never doing this again, which I say after every season
I was gonna ask you when he when the when the writers said, oh, I've got eight more episodes in the in the bag
Ready to go. Were you more excited or more terrified? Which which direction did the needle lean?
Because I know at least I know both both were on the scale for sure
We were very excited actually because
You know, we love doing this. This is you know at Jimmy having this whole family together having everybody on the set
It's it's definitely been an experience. We've been doing it for five years
So bringing the crew together and and doing everything it feels like at the end of 16 hours
Like everybody's just like oh my gosh
But then you get to see what you did and what you achieved and that's that in itself is always always gratifying and
Actually, Matt and I had a conversation about magicians
You said you never do you said you never out me on this you said you're gonna give us anonymous
You're supposed to say a magician friend I
Know well
We I told it to the writer and so now it's too late. So if there is a season three
There's gonna be a magician episode. So hopefully we can get some
magician
Adjacent type people maybe Matt Donnelly will make an appearance. I can't tell whether you're saying I should do this or stay away from it
I'll do it. I would love to do it. Yeah. Oh my god, if you can see on the background, there's
There's Jimmy's clown spoilers, but that's me. Oh, yeah Wow
Pretty dope for the video for people who aren't on on twitch or zoom. Yeah, there's a little little bonus something
I'll let you know. I'll just speak as my agent for a moment. You should make Matt part of the last episode because he tends to
Cause schedules to go off the rails with
You definitely want you don't want me holding up another episode. I'll just tell you that much right now
You oh, you'll be the grand finale, baby. There you go. There you go
I'll get you we give you your least amount of patience and I'm doing the most amount of improv. You're gonna love it
Why the show ended
Oh
Yeah, I had a friend working on a project that I was like
Oh, I would have been fun to work on that one and then they described the working process is like
Oh, I would have been a nightmare. Thank God. I didn't try to be a part of that project. I just pissed everyone off
They would have hated me but it's good
Somebody just put Jimmy with the dude wipes dressed as a clown
Dude wipes, I'll have you know, that's Blumpkin spice. That is not Photoshopped. That is legit. That is
I didn't have that picture
Yeah, Jimmy Wow, Jimmy
That's good lighting. Look at that
That's download that shit. Yeah, that's a good picture
Jimmy how many that's going how many months now with no podcast? Do you miss it at all?
Do you hate not being part of the audio world?
No, see now like this is the perfect opportunity for season 3 the all a list casting goes all podcast
Just goes to totally man Michael only Michael I'm gonna tell you right now you're gonna love the format change
You know what if it's not 16 hour days and we're doing three back-to-back podcasts, I'm here for it's way shorter days
We only do two on on our hardest days. We do two in a row. We've we've tried three in the past and it doesn't work
If I ever they don't even go on location anymore. No, they just do it all from home
Ship or wherever the hell they are
That's like take bruises, what can I say we've evolved
No, I'm good. I'm I'm good
saving my
conversations for my therapist good and not for not for
Some two dudes that I that I work with that I love
Yeah, you guys are getting together for the occasional meal. He's still keeping up with the guys. It's just not as regular or
Yeah, yeah, sure. You know, it's you know, and you know, we got the dressing room has to say you see each other all the time
Wouldn't it be great here? If it was like actually we have built walls between our stations and the dressing rooms
Literally not spoken since that last episode like you know when like restaurants were desperate to open during kovat
So they put up all those little micro walls and stuff
Yeah, so the dresser was like now atmosphere and the best part is all you need for Jimmy to stay private is a micro wall
Get the part buddy you want to massage you want to get on the massage table you gotta
Ah
Now I so the last time I was on this episode all we could talk about was docking
so I was like I'm gonna bring Jimmy on so at least like he'll keep these guys in line and
Good job, Jimmy. Good job, Jimmy
Actually, I'm glad you brought up docking because I have some things I want to discuss with that
So, thank you
Jimmy maybe maybe this is unfair to put a button on it, but we should say
You since you last were on air
Your case got thrown out you weren't you were not being it did you were not exonerated?
You're not being good. I go into jail for going to your own place of business from a bar
Yes, it has been dropped but it still could be I guess I just found this out the other day
It could be it takes a year for them to like actually close it
So like at any point if I act up or you know
Oh Jesus still like yeah, so you're
List is that what we're hearing still kind of tell me that Las Vegas has like a delete folder for 365
So like if you move into delete, but it actually stays in this folder for a year
Exactly so I still get to mind my P's and Q's no happy endings at the massage
Got to the beginnings are on the table beginnings. Oh, we have to be happy. Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely
but yes for all intents and purposes that
that that case is now now done and
The future is still is unclear and my lawyer says I shouldn't talk too much about it. There we go. That's fine
We'll leave it. We'll leave it
Let's leave it there. Yeah. Yeah, I was want to celebrate
I mean, I've not put it like a little no my calendar like wait a year to celebrate. Yeah
Good to know 11th the fateful day June 11th
Well, I have I have faith in the fair and 611 you turned around it's 9/11. Oh my 9/11 Wow
Illuminati never forget guys Machiavelli
You know when we started this episode today, I thought to myself, you know
I really hope I could find out one day what Jimmy Sloaneen is 9/11
Jimmy's personal 11. It's just actually now gonna be an icebreaker for all of our guests. Hey, yeah, what's your 9/11?
My 9/11 is finding out my character's named Roger
When it could be Kroger the whole time
He looks so much like a Kroger
My 9/11 is watching episode 9 of of land man over and over again
There's a character in a list
God help us her name
The actress name is Katie and we we turned her. Yeah, she's hilarious
you'll see her in episode 5 and she says so in episode 3, but she's featured in episode 5 and
Unfortunately, we made it a bit that her name is tall actress
So that's what she's called in the show and she doesn't get a name. No one can remember her name
It's just sort of nice
So she hasn't been given a name and she is very careful to remind us every time we do any kind of promotion
That she doesn't have a name yet. And I'm like, don't worry. It's gonna be a big reveal in season 3 Kroger or 5
So her real name is tall actress
Her name is also Roger. Yeah
It's also Roger
Everybody is Roger. This is all on YouTube. Yes
Yep, you can find it all on YouTube. I
Think you just look up a list casting and you will see me you will see Jimmy
you'll see a lot of Las Vegas actors and
Jonas Wilberton. Oh, wow. There's so many people you guys know who's who of scoop guests. Yes
Tons of them. Yes, Karina Harney Jones. Yes
Nicole Unger, I heard there's a lot of pressure to up the sex appeal for season 2 to boost the ratings. Is that true?
That's very true
Jimmy
shows his nipples on every podcast and
Whether he's asked to or not
yeah, and
much much like
Brett Alters he gets naked at the top chance. You know, you don't have to ask Brett once
I've got one more testicle in that guy
Somewhere Brett Alters is just getting like things in the universe
He's got a little baby
One is enough the ringmaster of Big Apple Circus. Now he's touring with Piff again. Fuck that guy
Yeah, but fuck you Brett Alters. You'll never be on a list cast and your nudity
But we'd love to have you back on on the podcast. Oh, yeah, come on by Brett any time. Yeah
I don't think we ever had bread on which is a mistake. No, did we have it once?
Maybe a long time ago. Oh, yeah, we've done this podcast. I don't know. He'd have to tell us
He'd have to tell us
Now we knew this podcast and Piff stuff. Yeah, I have no idea you guys talk about how if you you know
You had a budget you go maybe shoot some more locations and that kind of stuff
Modern entertainment is a fucking crazy
Making entertainment was always hard. It's harder than ever to take the independent project like this to a major
Streamer but but small entertainment like this like these smaller episodes and being able to watch from your phones that kind of stuff
Like that's all on the rise, right?
Yeah has have you thought about possibly simply trying to do like a Kickstarter or a crowd funder to try to maybe see if you
Could just get a budget you'd want for to maybe make this a little a little more dynamic and spicy for you guys
Yeah, I mean that's definitely on the portfolio, you know, we're looking at where things go
With this current season and then we're gonna get together and talk about okay
Do we crowdfunds like what's our goals? Like what are we gonna do with season 3?
What can we do to make a season 3 happen, you know that sort of thing or
You know with the help of all the scoops in the chat and everything
They're the subscriber base and the viewers watch and everything goes up so high that we can
You know take that to more of a network type style
So there's two different ways to go we kind of have to step back and examine exactly where we're at
I would love like, you know, this this show is is
Definitely a love letter to Las Vegas and and to the entertainment here
So I would love to continue making it and everybody enjoys
The process of doing it. So there's many there's many opportunities where we're gonna be looking at
But hopefully one of them would be to crowdfund and to kind of get it enough of a budget to make a season 3
The other option, you know
take it to some more networks again now that we have more of a fan base and stuff and
Show them the analytics and that kind of thing and see if it gets picked up. So all right
Well, do you crowdfund Paul Jacob and I are in for five dollars?
Yes
Between the two of you
Switches your background to Jimmy and Jimmy's background, which is pretty good
It's a Russian nesting doll
This is what I put the link I put the link to the a list casting channel on the chat
There and hit that smash that subscribe y'all. Yeah
And if you're not on the chat a list casting just do a list casting search it on Google search it
YouTube it pops right up. Yeah, subscribe to it. It's gonna be fantastic
You're gonna love it
All right. Well gentlemen, we're gonna do a little ad we want to thank you for plugging the the episode
You're welcome to stick around and fuck around with us, but we're gonna move on to other other topics
So if you want to go I get it. No problem. I do have to run. Okay. All right. I love you all
Love you. Love you. Love you. Good to see you
Bye buddy Michael. Thanks. Thank you so much for being here
Our pleasure. Thank you guys. All right, like and subscribe a list casting on YouTube
Yes
Happy beginnings everyone gettings, you know
Really happy to be on a show that has so much talk of dirty massage parlors and that is the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by Captain cut berry cereal. That's right
From the microscope that is captain cut berries cereal in 2021
It's taken four years for this gem to make it to the top of the shuffle. And here we are
Captain cut berries cereal. Oh, hi there everybody captain cut berry. Yeah. Oh
Boy, oh boy. My pussy's as dry as a heron. I need something to lube up this twat of mine
What's that? What's that ahead? Oh, it's a soggy. Well, come on
My place soggies and get in my poon because I'm as dry as a 90 year old's cough
Yeah
Captain cut berries
I've got sandpaper twix my nethers right now. You know what I'm saying?
That's why I definitely need the help of the soggies and you can do it too. Go look for captain cut berries soggy
lubrication
Affiliate. That's right. The soggy lubrication affiliate
Goes right in your zone
Drips on down smooth like a roaring river and stays there guaranteed for at least three hours
Plenty of time for ingress and egress. That's all you really need get it in get it out get it done
That's what captain cut berry says. Ahoy soggies stay in my poon
And her hey scoops at checkout stay in my phone that's the same in my poon famous deal there
Hi
Jacob do you have a time I have a topic if you don't have a topic a topic you go. I have a top
Pick who feels strongest about their top. I got too quick. I got two quickies
First of all, I'm gonna let y'all know I got to experience a little slice of heaven the other night
Let me tell you what a slice of heaven is
So I went to this massage part a slice of heaven. Happy beginnings
Happy beginnings is a Pennsylvania CoC Costco
On a on a Steelers playoff Monday night. Oh man
Ghost town
Was wonderful and and I had the run of the place there couldn't have been 50 people there workers included
It was wonderful
Were the workers all furious that they were there? No, nobody in their right mind wanted to watch that game. Give me a break
Are you kidding me?
Anyway, I watched a few minutes of it and then just dozed off
Up at some point right around it was almost halftime. I mean it was right after halftime and
Looked at the game. It went. Nope. It turned it off and got up. I just did other things. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, as someone who loves watching Aaron Rodgers lose and be a dick about it. It was a fucking chef's kiss
More perfect than an interception turned touchdown as you're fine
Everyone else out on the sideline and they just showed up shouting at everyone. Yeah, I was like, ah
Well, he's the reason I didn't watch a single lick of it this whole season and I'm a better person for it
And now I'm completely off
That and you don't care about sports. I don't I really don't
Forgot that you don't care about sports. I reminded myself real quick Rogers
Just reminded you if anything you owe Aaron Rodgers. Well part of it too was for two years. I was basically
Immobile from my damn leg. So I that's true
I didn't have a whole lot of options but to connect with the outside world through live sports entertainment
It was either like sports or become a card magician. That was kind of it. And so I think I chose wisely again
Alright, so that was a great that our scoops right now are all catching each other up on football and they also don't care
I know that much about it. So right now the chat is just a litany of like wait bears wait
Somebody just mentioned the Brooklyn Dodgers
Yeah
So anyway, that was great fun Monday night going shopping with Ann. That's really funny to hit
Truly the perfect time it was the perfect time it was insane like I mean ghost town so there was that and then
and for holiday through her work got a
gift card from one of her associates for
Applebee's so we decided to burn that Applebee's gift card yesterday. I
Don't know if you guys have been to Applebee's Applebee's. We had to use it at Applebee's. Well, you shouldn't have burned it
Well, we that was you know, we probably it might have been a better move. I don't know but we went to Applebee's
Applebee's currently has on the menu on the menu currently. They have an item called the
om-cheeseburger
Om-oh, this is the one just yes. I just saw the ads for this, too
This was on every playoff game this weekend. So they cut a cheeseburger in half and let it rest on them
melted dish of cheese
Not just a melted dish of cheese. The wording is served in a molten pool of cheese
Sir in a molten pool of cheese
This is what Matt and Matty Lee's ice cream socials served in a molten pool of cheese. I was like, yeah
I'm gonna have to move. I'm gonna have to move throsian to second place as to what to do with my dead body
Put me in a ball pool of cheese
Why wait till you're dead though serve me
Fondue
Do you put like a long fork oh
You have to get a fork in there to get the cheese that's left and I'll tell you this
Oh Applebee's missing out on giving people a long fork for their hamburger to dip it in the cheese
I didn't eat super fast like on the time. I went for the second the second half
You're too late bozo you missed your train
Half my burgers on the plate and I saw I saw on the menu I was like limited time only I'm like
Yeah, you have a limited time to eat it before it glues itself to the dinner where there it is
And then put the two flat halves down in just a plate of cheese, that's it
Video up there this feels like something that like some mother does for like one of her kids
And like right you serve it to me with the cheese on the plate. Can you can I have melty cheeseburger tonight? Yeah
Melty pool burger and then that kid goes to sleep over the first time and he asked me to cut his cheeseburger in half
Is this you put more cheese on the plate you guys do melty pool burgers?
They go. What the hell are you talking about kid and then he shows it and they never eat a cheeseburger the same way again
And then those children went on to open an Applebee
Well, like I say, I'll say it wasn't bad. It's just that that second time experience
It should come. Yeah, it should come like fondue should have a little little fire. Let's have a little heater
Yeah, it it comes on a skillet. So it comes out bubbling like a fajita plate
so it is truly like
Like it is molten cheese like you cannot
I dare you to consume me is the cheese just is the is the cheese in the in the little pan just like cheese
Just like cheddar cheese or something. It's a it's like a
Mexican cheese blend I would say like a matcha jack style
This is a fucking this is a fucking miss on their part not to do it in a pan of queso. Yeah whiz
Yeah, I mean, yeah, if you're if you're going for it, you should go for it
Like they do serve like kill it just do some skillet. Okay, so there you're done
I think they serve skillet queso at Applebee's. Come on Applebee's. I'm giving you gems here
you know, I went to Sonic the other night and I
You know, they have a pretzel twist like a cheese dip, but they're at a pretzel twist. So I still order the the the the
dip
Yeah, I ordered the dip and put my tater tots in it tater tots. Oh
Smart each Applebee's each shit Applebee's well, I think I think they're on to something
But I think you guys are exactly right if you're gonna go for it fucking go for it
but then I think it becomes just a you're spending too much on your cheese and
So I think it just becomes an arms race at that point
I think then all the restaurants are racing to see who can put what in queso
Yeah, and I mean it would probably just end the world
I I mean if if you so if you put on your menu menu in queso emergency
burger I
Am I am buying that sandwich? I will be at your restaurant every day every day in queso emergency eat cheeseburger
Fuck yeah, and go ahead like make that just an option in case of emergency as an option
So I order a chicken Caesar wrap cut it in half dip the two hands into a bone thing of cheese and give it to me
I get that in queso emergency style, please
Sir you you ordered a drink you ordered a coke so I'm aware of my Pepsi fountain drink order
I also would like it
Very good, sir. Are you unwilling to place my Pepsi in a molten pool of cheese?
Please
See in a molten pool of cheese you understand me
This is not an idle threat. I have ordered my Pepsi in queso emergency style. I
Shall not be I am the owner here. I will not be refused
Theo Appleby at your service
Mr.. Appleby
Have you a bone that I might pick at sir for I have a bone to pick oh, I have bones
I have I have bones because I myself I just ordered buffalo wings in queso emergency
And so I cut each wing in half and I put the top and the bottom end of the wing injury queso emergency
The shards fall where they may
Chef has like a bone saw back there and just
Yeah split the riblets and send them into the fucking cheese sewer
I'd like this whole chicken in queso emergency
I have brought my own Kirkland brand chicken sir, and I would like this served in queso emergency style
Charge me whatever yeah
Is that like a corking fee? What is that? Yeah? Do not deny me spatchcock it if you must
Please do
Please
In queso emergency style
I even that is ours so
Nick Newman famously taught me the sonic
Secret hack which is that what they they often say their name welcome to sonic my name is Debra
How can I help you whatever we would like to order and you say their name back? They give you a discount
Yeah, and I oh and I remember this every time I go to my local sonic
But every time my sonic people don't say their name and it drives me crazy because I'm like ready
I'm ready like a ninja to say their name the last three times. I've gone to Sonic
They don't introduce themselves, and I was just make up a name and start addressing them as that name. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Thanks Tara
Thank you Roger
I'll have some
Nuggets what's a good one?
Tots Jesus Christ
Chili dog or the corn dog nuggets, I have my brain in case of emergency, so I just have it just
Can't remember the name of tater tots you split both hemispheres and put them in a pool of molten cheese
Cheddar bites in queso emergency
Yeah, we got it
Yeah, the apple is about to find out how lazy they are. It's gonna happen is that they've opened a door here
And now other people are gonna walk through it's gonna be that's exactly right
They they have given away a real move to just throw your food in a bunch of cheese
Hog fucking wise chilies that already has the skillet queso
Yes, see that's gonna start cutting their burgers in half and throw it in the skillet queso
Yeah, do it with the big mouth bites. I mean if you're not getting triple dipper, you're not eating right at Chili's anyway
I don't know. I don't know who's going to Chili's order anything besides a triple dipper. That's right shots fired fucking fools
idiots
In a minute come on now
Oh
And he's asking if we've seen the new KFC bowl, I haven't tried it yet Andy, but I've seen it
Oh, that's a seasonal items and my friend Jen said the funniest time so saw an advertisement when we were living in New York in
A bus stop so that for the KFC Bowl and she just looked at it goes for those who've just given up
But mad KFC you go through a KFC and get you a KFC Bowl you're not gonna be mad about it. No
You're not gonna be mad about it. You're gonna be perfectly good. Yeah
It's gonna be great
Class it up KFC
I'll tell you who else wants to put some bolognese and some queso and that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by
Slunks for skunks. That's from magic shell scoop in 2024 the product slunks for skunks
Hello. I am how do you say papilla pew? I am here to kiss a dead calf
Oh, I am looking to smooch on a expired cow, baby
Give me some dead cow babies to kiss a smooch smooch smooch
Where can I find such a service?
Oh
slunks for skunks
This is the answer to my prayers monsherry. Oh
Look at this beautiful dead calf this stillborn baby heather who I will smooch
Your skin it is like a dead cow
Has anyone ever tell told you your cold dead eyes remind me of the sea
Oh
When I give you tongue I can take the entirety of your cold slimy dead tongue into my mouth
And you don't care you don't find it
Slugs for skunks you have answered my prayer by giving me a dead cow to kiss
Do you have a friend or a loved one that believes that they are cartoon skunk?
Send them over here to slunks for skunks. We'll take care of your family friend or relative
It will just put them here in our warehouse filled with slunks. They can't hurt them. They just play with them
They have a real good time come on down slunks for skunks enter. Hey scoops at checkout
It took a dark turn
Oh
Of queso. Yeah, we got a scooper today from Chris angel has a chimera
Categories are photos and movies number one single 60s through 90s
Binders full or name the candy. Oh, yeah, you're a first all of these. I know
Let's do binders full, please for 200
What group of people have the first names?
Vesper, uh
Honey child honey child pussy Tiffany Solitaire and Holly. I
Know exactly what this is
I
Don't it is a group of people
And all of these people have something in common. Yeah
I'll pass
Paul I'll have to pass. I don't know this one. Those are all bond girls. Oh
Yes, yeah best for yeah. Yeah
Paul let's do um, oh
I'll try number one singles
for 200
1983 recognized as the song with the most radio plays in history
What at first sounds like a gentle love song is actually more like something a stalker might sing to their target
Someone call the cops. Ah, this is every breath you take from the police
Every breath you take indeed. I'll be good clues
That's me. I'll try a name the candy 200 taste the rainbow
Tuesday evenings. Oh
Skittles smarties. Yeah
Matt
I'm going back for binders full. I gotta get this right
All right for 400
What group of people have the first names Katherine and Jane and Katherine and Katherine?
I don't know this pass
Queens
Queens let's try Queens
Wives of Henry the eighth. All right wives of Henry the eighth coach rat bastard literally did the double head smack
Disappointment that we couldn't we didn't know that one. Well, they're Queens. I
Think did you did you mean Queens like they're did you know that they're wives of Henry the eighth because I feel like that's the bigger important
Part, right? Yeah, I mean, but they were all Queens. No, that's a no
No
We were both ready to give it to you if you said like, oh, yeah
They were Queen they were all married to Henry the eighth the old cheers episode to age myself over Cliff answered
Who have people who have never been in my kitchen for Final Jeopardy?
Technically true. Yeah. Yeah, Paul
I will try
60s music out or the 60s of the 90s for 800. Let's go for the big money. All right
1973 this song ostensibly from a
Paroled prisoner to his girlfriend asks for a sign that she wants him back
It was covered by Bing Crosby Perry Cuomo and Dean Martin and had renewed popularity in
1979 during the Iranian hostage crisis. Oh boy
Huh, I am going to guess tie a yellow ribbon
Let's try it
Tie a yellow ribbon round the old oak tree. Yeah
I'm sorry Paul. You just said tie yellow ribbon
Sorry, that's not enough. They're all Queens the whole song
I got it, right
It's me I'll try
The chances of using me Nick Nick Newman just got up and grabbed a yellow
Cloth and tied it in front of the camera to give a clue
I didn't see that. I know you didn't I'm just I'm just shouting out or I'm using scoops here
We have some very fun typing in the chat is lazy acting it out on camera. That's that's that's that's
Shit right there. Yeah, it's a fine lifeline shit right there. I'll drop binders full for 600
Who are Jane? Oh, this is a this is a bad start Jalen Weedland Belinda Carlisle
Charlotte Kathy Gina stock shock and Kathy Valentine
Huh, come on pass it the Bronte sisters
They're all Queens. They're all Queens
That doesn't even
Like ring a bell in my brain I pass
Matt
Is it Oingo Boingo fucking Belinda Carlisle you're halfway there me
Or you're more than halfway there, I guess
Linda Carlisle was it was in
Shit, I'm blanking out. All right, Pam Paul knows it. I'll pass this the go-go is the go-go's
Go-go's that's a map. Okay, so far. I've been bad at everything. Let's
Go to photos and movies for 200
Let's try something new a group photo of the guests at the July 4th ball in 1921
The guy front and center looks awfully familiar
But I think the last time we saw him he'd just had his hair and everything else frosted
What's the movie beautiful moment is the shining?
Yes, of course, I know but my buddy Dion, you know writes for The Tonight Show and he did a bit with as an
As it did like a bad improv singing bit with Jimmy with Jimmy calling him on like just doing the same thing over and over again
and he says I'm off stage and for no reason the the show gets really crazy and
Dion was so proud of it. Just cuts to a photo of an old
Ballroom and Dion's character is in it singing in this old shot
And he said it's from The Shining and I go buddy. You don't even know
Like what you've done because in that movie he says here's Johnny
That's The Tonight Show and you wrote that bit for The Tonight Show. You didn't even realize it in sept. Yeah
Inception we're just all got accepted looking at each other's inner eggs. Okay, it's pretty pretty cool, man
Ball. Oh
great
I'll keep going with the singles. Let's do it for 400
1665 the only Rolling Stones song to be included in the Library of Congress recording registry
Notable cover versions were recorded by Devo and The Residents
This is a number one
Paint it black. I don't say it's a number one. Paint it black's not on my guess. Yeah, I was thinking about that
Satisfaction shit you fools you fools
It's me I'll try
I'll try singles 600
1999 this song pioneered the use of auto-tune to distort the vocals and won the Grammy for best dance recording
The only Grammy this legendary performer with a multi-decade career has won
Thank you. Wait, so you want the song or the artist do both if you get one you're getting the other on this one
I can't think of the song name though. Oh
The
It sounds like you tell me the artist you get that turn back time the share share turn back time no
No, no
Well, Paul doesn't know that Paul just thinks that's not it just to be no I know right
Okay, he knows it. All right
You're on the right track
It's not something right? It's not the right song. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
It's a good turn back time is the one on the battleship. Yes
Yeah, so that'd be too late
That's too. Ah, the battleship was too early. That was in the 80s. I was it too early. Yeah. Oh wait. Yeah, sorry
I'm 99. I'll say Nick Newman is singing his heart out
If you want to if you sing he's mouthing everything I can't even I can't I can't even see the chat or the alright
I'm sharing the screen so that everybody can see the scooper. T. Yeah, I win. I'm seeing an amazing performance
I can't fucking think of the song I pass now if I could turn back time
It is turn back time. No
No, no, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry. Wait, I
Didn't know it was do you believe in life after love?
Why I did the whatever the thing is where you switch the thing this is why I'll never perform a handstab
Because you did get this
In this case, you only lost some points. Yeah, you didn't stab yourself in the hand didn't lose a digit
I just I literally was thinking do you believe in my head over and over again?
And then the other words came out of my mouth and here we are
Yep, turn back time
Matt get those points back. I'll take more share trivia, please Jacob
Let's do photos in movies for 800
I'm thinking of a celebrity that was married to share. Oh, no
Correct. Yeah
An autograph photo is stolen off a restaurant wall and gives this movie its title
The photo is of a Tony Award-winning singer dancer and actress famous for a recurring role in an iconic television series
Me out. What's the movie?
What's eating Gilbert grape?
It's just a picture of a great too long food Julie Neumar
So Julie Neumar was Catwoman, but that's not uh-huh you got you got half of it what's in the middle
You you got the right movie. You just got you have to get the title. Oh
- one foo
Blank Julie Neumar. Yeah. Oh
Well, here we are. I made it this far guys. It's been good pass
Paul - one foo. Thanks for everything Julie Neumar. Thanks for everything
Thanks for everything no matter how much Newman acted it out
I was so sad that was passing the ball Paul. You're up binders full, please
Let's go for eight hundo closing it out. Who are Winona LaDuke?
Geraldine Ferraro
Sarah Palin Kamala Harris sissy Ferrant hold and Lena Springs
Queens
Women these are Queens. Oh wait, did they yeah women who ran for vice president?
Okay
Female vice presidential candidates. Yeah. Yeah, that's correct
Queens and Queens
It's me I'll try
Name the candy 400. Oh, it's a daily
Give me a break now Carter me a break give me a break of that Milky Way candy
Turn back time
It's like a battleship here fuck it for
Name the candy 800
Happy
My dick
Candy right there. He's so emergency. Hey, so emergency my ween ween. Oh
Mounds dicks in case. Oh
Slim Jim's
Not to you. Oh, that's your opinion. Oh gross
Slim Jim, please come in in case of emergency. Yeah
Snickers
Milky Way, I don't know
Pass
Paul Twizzlers
Twizzlers
Just make smells happy. Yeah, I was close with Slim Jim. I mean
You know
licorice sense from from like an alien's observing humans
Shay shape sensation. Yeah. Yeah like a thermal camera. You can't tell the difference between
God
How many of our poor boys in uniform have suffered that
I was on the thermal sergeant couldn't tell the difference between a sling Jim. Oh, it was so upset
600 isn't life juicy. Oh
Thank you Kardashian, I think it's Kimberly j
Kardashian, I think it's Starburst
Starburst is
Paul run in the candy category
Huge lead 3800. I have 800 Matt has a negative or how do you say an agent?
I was on I was on an online candy store last
Andy
Of course you were oh man, it looked this is a damn tik-tok shop got me
I didn't go on a tik-tok shop, but they they do this thing where they scoop the candy in a very
ASMR kind of way all these different very exotic candies. Oh, man
So many exotic candy. That's exactly what their whole gig is
I'll go photos and movies for 600
Jacob this is my chance to keep second place a framed photo of the protagonists brothers
Girlfriend to avoid insulting a young actress. The photo was actually of the art director's son in a wig. Woof. What's the movie?
This is oh
No, it's not that shit
You fool. Oh wait. No. No, I think it is. I think it is home alone. Oh
I think it's home alone. It is motherfucking alone motherfuckers. Oh, wow, Jacob really
winner
It's a McCulley Culkin's brother he like has I can't believe that just popped into my head
Is that is that Butch or whatever his name is? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I got a Canadian girlfriend. Yeah, and it's like it's like a silly-looking picture. Yeah. Yeah
Matt closing out the category in the game photos in movies Matt trying to hold on to third place for $400. Let's go a
Photo of three siblings where two of them seem to seem to fade out of existence. That's heavy. What's the movie?
Also weight has nothing to do with it Baron von Munchausen
My proxy to out of existence
What is the come on you know this I do? Yeah. Oh, yeah, everybody knows this
This is the reason that for like two years
I wore a Mickey Mouse shirt if you don't get this right because this this photograph in this movie if you don't get this right
I'm gonna call you a Huey loser
Wow
hip to be square in
In high definition, okay, that's it
Matt if you don't get this I am gonna go outside. I'm gonna get into my lifted Toyota pickup truck
I'm gonna drive over there, and I'm gonna take you on a camping trip
With Elizabeth shoe
She's gonna be there Harry and the Hendersons no adventures in babysitting
Matt you're gonna feel silly in the future when you don't get this fine. Let's just let's just make that the present
Paul it's back to the future back to the future. Oh right right right right right I
I did not love those movies when they came out and my
Did and then I was always on it like parties and sleepovers and stuff
But I was always half paying attention to those things as a seminal movie for me
A lot of people know it's an age thing
Yeah, I'm a little older than you I forget sometimes and those early years are big right like that was a big movie in the theater for me
When that was it was big for me because back to the future 2 came out at I was whatever whatever age
I was when back to the future 2 came out
I was the perfect age for that and so that got me hooked like back on back to the future 1 and yeah
And yeah, then I was back in
That's the game by the way Paul crushed us what?
2200 points I have 1600 points at least I'm respectable because Matt only has negative 400
But if I've gotten that share question, right, I would have only gotten the third
That's right. So you got that right?
Was it Chris Angel has a chimera that was actually a very well-written
Trivia that was great. I love I love that's good. Even though I got because I won over by it. It was really good
Thank you send us a scooper tea or any kind of jock versus nerd. Hey scoops comm is where you ought to go
Hey scoops comm right there on the home page
You can make us a jock versus nerd quiz to play on the show
You can also send us some email send us some scoop mail right over there at hey scoops comm do it now
I
Definitely thought I was gonna have name lists by now by this point the episode to thank people and I don't
Well, we're gonna think a lot of people are really working on it
Are we gonna add it in or do you think we're just gonna go one more episode?
Because this one comes out tomorrow. I think we're gonna go one more episode great
Well, let's know the time we thank all the people support us on patreon
Obviously, we're in a transition of going from any to no one
Other people a lot of people have offered to hop in there. Yes, we're still getting our
We did and we may still take them up on me
We are going to experiment see if we can do it ourselves, which is a little weird
But we should be thanking everyone the way they should be doing it
But the way we simplified our patreon it seems like we will a be able to just be able to get lists ourselves and be
We don't have a lot of
Crazy deliverables anymore. So we can't have people write us and yell at us, which is also why we had any
We think we're safe sure I think with the way
Safer the digital rules are mostly doing kind of hang stuff and that kind of thing. So yes
Which is coming up soon beyond the lookout. We'll have that sometime next week. I'm planning great
But we've been more community oriented with our patreon and it shows as our patreon has gone up a little bit and we appreciate that
It really helps us out tremendously. It helps us in all that we do for us and our entire scoop community
Yes, you want to contribute and you have room in your heart and your wallet for to support us head on over to preaching fun
dot-com
Or if you used to do some boring mundane job that you absolutely hated but now you're a Las Vegas entertainer
Who's out there in the exciting industry of entertainment life in Las Vegas go over to farts in a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun.com it takes you over to our patreon page
We're for as little as three dollars a month. You can help keep this show on the air
I was just looking through our patreon page earlier today and
I was looking through the the full list with like everybody who has ever been on our patreon at all and
It was just a little walk down memory lane. It was so great seeing all the names of
Current and former patrons and people who have been on there for a long time
And I it has like they go away and they come back and then they were and I think you know
And they go sorry. I had to take a break
Look, you know no explanation any time you can find a little time to support us is just amazing and we're so grateful
And if it can't be for your entire lives, that's that's okay, you know, we appreciate it
And of course, we appreciate our long-term supporters very much as much. Yes, so
But we truly we truly have such a soft spot in our hearts for everybody who supports us over there at preaching fun
Dot com and farts in a bag dot biz because we couldn't do the show without you just very frankly
We are dependent on our patreon supporters. We are dependent on our paid subscribers
So if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars preaching fun.com farts in a bag dot biz
That is the place that you can go. Oh
It will scoop. Thank you for reminding me
We do have our billionaire experiment still in the works
The experiment is you're gonna give each of us a billion dollars
So we need three billion dollars. Mm-hmm before taxes three billion dollars gross. I don't think we're completely clear on the financials here
It can be crypto. It can be that fine with paying it paying back some of that
Yeah, yeah
No
If we have to tax on it and whatever is income or however, we have to do that
We'll figure that out on our end. Yeah, you don't worry about that. You just come up with the three billion even
We might even bring any back to help us figure that one out. Yeah, we might we might
Maybe a contractor fee. Yeah
But yeah
You give us the three billion dollars and we will see if we are better at being billionaires than the current billionaires out there
You know, I'll go ahead and say it will even bring back the hands-less eating reward
We learned the first time around we have to do it all in one we can't do like multiple sessions
We have one hands-less eating session, you know, yeah, you know what the next has to be available at the where do we go?
Eat that famous last night, you know the pepper mill menu the big step lucky for you
Everything's on the pepper mill bin, right?
You need to just sit seriously reinstate that on the patreon at the three billion dollar level
We need to make a legit three billion dollar level on the patreon. You're right
Eating video eating video three billion dollars
You get three you get three
Three billion you get one from each of us. Yeah, I like that before the government even right away
We're giving away five percent to patreon like we would increase their stock price
right
Yeah, it would be it would be a big win day for them as well. If someone had three billion they give away
They're gonna do it through patreon and not
Pretty great. I just give it right to us. I mean, but you know what? Maybe they really want those videos
And the other benefits that come
There are incredible benefits for being a patron at preaching fun calm
Hit the production meeting music
One hundred fifty million dollars by the way is what patreon's cut would be
Patreon celebrities forever my
Probably get an invite to their parties
Improv group possible side effects. We took out fame now org
Because it was a place for our fans to demand our fame now
These are the kinds of things you got to put out in the universe baby three billion dollar patreon level
I'll just you know, not not to let one, you know influence either too much, but I'll let you know how the fame now
worked out
Different timeline my friend
Oh Jesus three billion three hands for eating videos does not include lower-tier patreon
Jesus three billion three hands for eating videos Asterix does not include lower-tier rewards
As we continue this bit we should credit like every manifesting author there is out there like everybody just keep
All right, actually thanks to the secret. Thank you for Jimmy and Mike. My partner has been exceptional lately. I don't know about you guys
Thank you to Jimmy and Michael for stopping by god go go like and subscribe to a list casting on YouTube
Thanks pendulum for giving this podcast. Thanks everybody join us
By putting us in their ears this week. We really appreciate you listen to us weekend and week out
Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
Oh
Yay, everybody