Oh
Hello there, I'm so glad you're here because this is the part of the show where we thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers right now. I'd like to thank Tony Cowley Travis Jaguri
Wendy Loomis, I have one other one here technical school poor. Thank you so much
thank you so much Tony Cowley Travis Jaguri Wendy Loomis and
Technical school port if you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks head over to preaching fun
calm preaching fun calm is where you go to sign up and who knows
The life you save may be your own. Oh
Look a show what Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great
Hello s Jacob and I to watch the
Masters of the universe movie trailer. That's right
This episode is all about the new Masters of the universe
We're preaching fun preaching. Yeah, we got are we twitched up. We're twitched up
Matt is still freezing his took us off over there in Indiana is me too
You're recording this on a Monday my feet are a little chilly. It's it's just shy of 70 here and
I am a slightly uncomfortable. I have my house shoes on there. They're taking care of most of it though
So don't worry about me. Did you get a snow measurement Matt?
Is that this at 20 20 to 24 inches fell here? Oh my goodness. That's double what we got. That's crazy. Yeah and
Because of that they don't serve breakfast anywhere
Very long a long walk with Mike Mills and our tech guy scooter
we were inept but it changed our opinion of where we were staying so
We were finishing up our show. We just show let's say, Kentucky. They made two shows in Cincinnati and
We're supposed to go at the Bloomington and do a show that was canceled and then we're heading to Chicago
But it's another show being produced out here
by
Mike Mills and so
We were going to come out here to see a preview of that show anyway
I don't know if it's public yet, so I can't say which show it is
It's a tradition that okay people may or may not have heard of but
so we're deciding whether to snow ourselves into Cincinnati and
Then just see if the roads are good to come out Monday to watch the show. Yeah, they go to Chicago after that or
Snow ourselves in Indiana you're at and be right there and then just be here for three days and that'll be fun
And so we we voted for going to Indiana
So we finished our show and it was already snowing when we were packing up our van. Yeah, it was really exciting
And then we did you have that like that that that feel of like we got to get the fuck out of here or we're not
Gonna yes. Yeah. Yeah, and and so off we went
I don't like that feel at all off we went hit the snowy roads driving at a brisk 40 miles an hour
Good as we head out through the snow and we're in a big spreader van. It's nice and heavy
So we're not worried about we were feeling good. We weren't slipping and sliding
Last like hour of the trip. It was supposed to take like an hour 45 minutes took three hours three and a half hours. Yeah
And we were following a snowplow which is one good because we're we're driving on a plowed street
But plows go about
15 to 20 miles an hour. Yeah, they're not they're not known for their quickness
No, don't you do so we were just like it was a crawl
To the to the place now
we're staying at this spot called the Grant Street in here in Bloomington and
We called ahead twice to be like we might come out late tonight. Is that okay?
And then we're definitely coming out late tonight. Is that okay?
And so we pull up and the Grand Street is actually like three houses converted into a hotel
So okay you check in the main house, but then you get sent across the street to the other house
So we pull up at about three o'clock in the morning
Mike goes in and we hear nothing for like ten minutes. We're just taking three and a half hours here
we're finally at the place we want to be and now we're just sitting in the car and then Mike says
You guys might want to come in or whatever
We couldn't find anyone
At the hotel and then finally someone woke up and came our way and said oh gosh
I don't even have the passwords for the computer. I don't think I can check you guys in
York's
Right
This is things like Mike Mills
I've had him on an abracadabra. I should have him on here. It's very funny guy also
Calm like a jacket again. Oh shoot. You're clipping on us
Calm guy. Yeah
Like and all this is what time though. This is what time in the lobby of the hotel 3 3 15 in the morning
Yeah, and you've been and you've been driving behind the snowplow for how long about an hour and
I asked him to chat earlier
Who who drives who was driving?
Initially, I was driving as I picked up the car in Cincinnati
And I drove it to Lexington and I was trying to drive and Mike Mills does so much for the tour
I produce it and also does all of the you know logistics and stuff
So I thought I would drive but because it was snowing and he lives in New York and I live in, Nevada
He thought he was maybe a little more qualified to drive in the snow than me
He's at least a recent practice most likely. Did you tell him?
Jersey born. Yeah. No, he's aware. He's aware
Don't have an argument about it though. Yeah much like springsteen
People know where I'm from
They figure it out
Yeah
So we go
So so your dreams so right where he's from like well, we got to stay here
I guess like in the main building like at least you got to have at least in the lobby
No, but like a key to open up some room somewhere like they have something right? Yeah. Yeah, that's right
so
She says yes, and so we start opening the van. It's still snowing right? This is this is the start
This is the start of the god. Yeah
so we're unloading all of our stuff and then one of the really funny things that happens that both Mike and I have
tricks that involve
Liquids cans of stuff. Oh
Yeah, okay, we can't leave that in the van old. No, we bought we bought enough for the whole tour
So we had to like haul every all of our liquid props
flats of
Cans of water in yes, so to unload everything and we get halfway through unloading our vans
Oh, no, I figured it out. We can get you guys checked in across the street. No problem. Oh god damn it
So then we pick up all of our stuff and load it back into the van I
Again
Mike
Mike when he came out explained this he was like I can't fucking believe this right like he occurs
He never curses he's I can't fucking believe he's he's shoveling snow off of the thing because he hasn't told us yet
I've got to unload our van, but he's clearing the way as he's cursing to let it like he's clearing a path
So I try to like do an end around and I grab the shovel and I run across the street to like pre I start shoveling
The other house out so that we can load stuff into the place that we are staying gotcha. Okay, you're thinking ahead
Yeah, the van
Can't get out of the parking space that it's in because of the snow
It's like we're doing the wibbly wobbly, you know rack rocket back and forth thing trying to get some grip
You know, and we finally get loose it goes up. It's 330 in the morning
We finally get loose and it's a we're on a one-way street and it's snow covered, right?
So it's definitely one way street one lane one way down
And we get to the middle and we're about to unload our stuff and just another car just pulls up behind us
Oh shit
It's four in the morning, yeah
Mike drives around the block, right? It takes like five minutes like that. I
And I'm like just shoveling away. I have no gloves. It's 15 degrees and
I'm just shoveling away waiting for the van to return
Luckily you're only 19 years old
Fiercely shoving away. It's still snowing like a mother and
And then he pulls back around yeah, we open the door and another car pulls up
Also this area really is a grid right like it's not complicated like you can go around us, right? Yeah and
Then so Mike pulls up and he actually pulls up just so we can get the car out of the way that reverses back
Yeah, do it and we unload half of our van
into the through the through the through the path I've shoveled into the into the house that we're staying at and
Halfway through a car. I can see it coming from blocks away. Our hazards are on is a giant Sprinter van
The doors are open. We are moving in a chain of four people unloading. There's clearly something happening this thing happening and
A car it just eases right up behind us and stop
And I just said we're finishing the unloading and I yell at the team and I shot the dirtiest look to the person
You can literally right now reverse 50 feet. Yeah and drive left and just go a different way. Yeah
So they waited better than where I was afraid the story was going. I was afraid the story was going like I saw the headlights
He was coming ran right into the van. Oh my god. Yeah
But so yeah, so we loaded in
Scoop says good thing know there when they change in your pocket
Right, right. Right. So anyways didn't have the password text to the wrong place
like we were pretty kind of a we were making fun of this hotel for a
Minute, you know, right come with it. So
Look at us. We're still doing it got the two mornings later
We said we're gonna try to get breakfast now, you know, famously
There's a restaurant here called the runsable spoon, which I have loved visiting here
I've talked about the runsable spoon runsable spoon is what it's called. What's that mean? Who knows?
What's the word runsable the runsable is the word?
What's that mean and we looked it up before but it was unmemorable because we've had this conversation before but
I cuz I came here when I came I played
When I played Washington, Indiana
Aces bar grill. Uh-huh. I know that we've had this conversation before because there was it was
Google remembered it. Yeah, I cuz I call I call me Jacob
It's a nonsense word invented by Edward Lear
Most famously from owl and the pussy cat. Okay, great. Yes. He will never remember that again. No, we won't forget next time
But it's a it's a nonsense word. Oh, it's like a Jellico cats
Yeah. All right. Great, but even dumber and I came here
I said I said it was like it was like it was like all the waitress were like different Manson girls
Like that's what it was like college. Oh, yeah. Yeah, whatever and it's
Walls I remember that part. Yeah, exactly. Well, that's what we all remember. That's why we all want to go back
right
So runsable spoons still not open for the blizzard didn't recover it 24 hours
No dice. Oh man, we walk out and about
To all of all of Bloomington and all these restaurants are still closed this morning. Yeah
we came back into the the host house of our three house hotel to get coffee and
Very kind host who wasn't the guy who was up at 330 mornings. Like you guys do it. All right, you know
We're like, ah, well, we just try to take a walk and we didn't make breakfast here this morning because we thought we're gonna walk
Somewhere else for breakfast, but every place is closed or whatever. He goes
Oh, oh, well, let me see if I can get some at least get some like fruit stuff together for you guys
Some vittles rustled up. Oh
And he goes downstairs and he comes up because you know, the cook hasn't left and we still have eggs and bacon
You guys want us to make you up some eggs and bacon?
Yes, yeah, they went out of their way and gave three of us like an amazing
Immaculate breakfast. Wow, and I was like we and I just turned to Mike. I was like we are eating our fucking words
We've been trashing this place for 24 hours and they totally outclassed us
They turn today and they were just everywhere. There was an
Incredibly nice it went above and beyond and so I have nothing but amazing things to say about the Grand Street in
Right except that maybe they should have that past check-in process is a little
Taped to put a post it know with a password somewhere that everyone knows, you know, so
Password password who cares?
We were just pissed about driving, you know
42 to 15 miles an hour for three and a half hours, but you had also called ahead and now giving them the heads up
That's it. That's a lot of you gave them the heads up a couple of times
That's something that is something I'll tell you who else is something these folks really are something and that's the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by
Go go phone go
Michael Jackson's my skulls Jack's son head exercises for dancers
My skulls jackson head exercises for dancers
Hey everybody, I just want everyone to know that I have opened a whole new store
It's called Michael Jackson's my Jack's on skull
exercises for dancers
And many of you don't ascribe to phrenology, but that's ignorant. That's just ignorant
Phrenology is key when it comes to dancing the way your heads aerodynamics work with the breeze
That's if you'd be a better dancer that way
Are you saying that you that you're a good dancer because of your head shape, that's exactly right
Michael Jackson's head shape is perfect for being a good dancer. If you know anything about phrenology, then you'd understand
But you don't know what no phrenology is the study of the shape of the head and the discovery of
Attributes and traits has been disproven time and again by science but embraced by horrible racists
for generations
So, why are we talking about it because that's the only way I can open my school you ignorant you ignorant
I had to open my school based on phrenology because I'm not a medical doctor
The only doctor I know gives me mama's meal. Give me milk. Give me some milk. I need to sleep. Give me more milk
Check out
I
Will speak
It happened ladies and gentlemen
There is a new Masters of the Universe movie coming to theaters this year June 5th
Yes
Are you excited about this? Paul? I'm very excited about this. Okay
Are you excited about how excited Paul is about this? I know you excited for the inevitable crash. I watch
Oh, yeah, he's gonna hate the movie
I don't know. I don't think I am
So they've been trying to make different master the universe projects for a while and this one finally came to fruition
Do you know behind that? Well, I mean the other ones have been put on the back burner for several different reasons
probably because they were shit and
Mattel didn't want their brand damaged. But here's why I'm hopeful
the Barbie movie the Barbie movie made a fuck ton of money and was also critically lauded so
That combo put into Mattel's mind
Hey, if we put some autours and some actual directors in charge of this stuff and maybe hire some actors
That actually know how to perform
We can put a little gravitas or stuff. Yeah
well, but they got a lot of other really great people in this movie to a lot of really great people in this movie, uh-huh, so I
Think they've learned their lesson with Barbie that this can be another
real bankroll move and
Possible, you know legacy protector if they do it, right? And so I don't think they're fucking around. I
Know support. What are your thoughts on the trailer? I
It looks great
You just think you're just generally excited about it. There wasn't there wasn't a single part of that you really stood out to you
Nothing. I mean it all looks so like okay. So here's the thing
I already talked to the scoops about this in the chat before but I'll talk about so
You've got Marlena Glenn who was an astro a human astronaut from Earth. That is Queen Marlena
Adam's mother right and the trailer focuses on her talking to him as a child
Sending him away to earth for protection
because
likely because
Adora had been captured and war was continued. That's all that's all real story. Yes. That's all that's all lore
What's the word cannon? This is cannon? Yeah, this is legit. This is why I'm excited is because the real ones know
No, I assumed watching this trailer that this was
Made up something like this this whole premise of like sitting to earth and then and then no protecting all this stuff
Now that never happened that never happened
however
Adora did get stolen away by Hordak and it would make sense for Marlena to want to protect
Adam as the last heir to the attorney. It's really hard to take you seriously with their names like Hordak involved
Tell you how it went down Hordak stole baby Adora. It's pronounced sex worker Dak now
Pimp deck for those who know he keeps that pimp deck hand strong. I
Mean Hordak's not even in the movie is he's even he's even higher up than Skeletor
He's the one that trained Skeletor. So, you know, this is gonna be they're leading
It's gonna it's gonna end up leading to like sequels, which is gonna be really cool. But no, this is legit
Marlena is from earth. Uh-huh. He man is half earthling half Eternian. That's part of the lore
That's part of why he is magically imbued. That's part of why he is this
You know character that transcends world or just fuckable Mormon. I
Mean now the blonde hair and all that that's an unfortunate side effect from hey, we have to make this unique IP
Conan doesn't have blonde hair. Let's do that because another the origins of the Masters of the Universe toy line are
Steeped in a lot of weird shit, but not least of which
Mattel was in talks with the Conan movie guys to possibly do a movie line, right?
Yeah, and so there's some of that then they had to really deflect hard
So they made it sort of sci-fi a little more spacey a little more weird a little more fantasy even than Conan and
Changed the look of he man drastically to keep him away from the Conan comparison. Oh, yeah. Yeah
No, he man and Conan could never
They change it super drastically
One of them is a mostly naked dude with a big fucking sword and the other one's your mom
Absolutely, it's absolutely
From Conan. Let's let's don't get it twisted. I know that I know where that stuff like yeah
But Fisto shows up in the trailer, which is fantastic Fisto's in there spy cores in nor in there or deck man
There's no hordak in the trailer, but Fisto's just just a coincidence in the IP. I'm sure Fisto's in it, but it's great
I mean they start off with showing Adam in on earth and he's working for HR and they pan over his desk and it says
Adam Glenn, which is you know, his mom's last name and
It's got the he him pronouns on there, which is a hilarious joke. Of course. He's he him. He's you know he man
Just fucking hilarious. Oh, so hilarious. I laughed so hard when it's
Not only was it funny, it's also a litmus test
How much would Paul hate that joke in any other movie? No
It's a litmus test for people who can't stand pronoun shit
And if you if you focus on that is like a negative thing and don't get it the joke of it all
I don't I don't know hope for you. He's called he man. What the fuck
He is all pronoun
So then you know he goes into this toy shop
Somehow he finds out that the power the power was the trailer if you're just gonna walk me through it
This what we're doing is we're reacting to it
Have you not watched any reaction videos do you not know how this how reaction and break down videos work
I didn't know we were turning our podcast into a reaction video to the trailer. Oh, it wasn't what?
That's what's happening. All right. Well, what do you want to talk about about it?
My question to you was going to be why did you make Jacob and I watch this? What was your plan?
You just revealed your plan so we could talk about it. Yeah. Yeah, I had already figured out that that was his plan, Matt
And so I was about to pivot by saying Matt. Did you have any thoughts on the trailer? I
Here's okay. Let me just address why I don't think it's gonna do the same thing Barbie did. Okay
Barbie was a comedy
Yes
was like a really
like fun comedy like Casper like really
sophisticated comedic performers, right and
It had a nice kind of feminist anthem and it was coming on with against Oppenheimer, which was incredibly masculine
So there's a good way for like women to rally
on opening weekend because
There's a good any contention that just basically wasn't interested in watching a move a three-hour movie about a guy who invented the atomic bomb
Was gonna maybe go. Yeah, it go out and have fun
This I did the Barbie Heimer day. It was a great day. This movie is made for neither crowd
I mean, he's made for kids. It's made for
It's made for Paul
That's what I think. I think it's really made for Paul because Paul you said you can make your kids watch it
I'm trying to think if watching this trailer whether whether my kids would be into it or not. I'll find out
I'll find that's what I want to know. That's what I want to know
I want to know if a generation removed from all the hype has any interest at all if it does it
Does it look interesting to people who don't already know what it is? Yeah, I'm seeing I'm seeing yes from a lot of people who don't
Know in the chat tell us it in the chat
I'm curious if you were not familiar with the he-man IP already
Did this trailer make you make you want to watch it or
Continue to not care about it. Mm-hmm. And actually like I I was just trying to make jokes. I mean, I'm not I
Wasn't like oh what the fuck about this movie? I just was like, oh, this is kind of I basically like I thought the trailer's kind
Of weird and I was like, who is this for? That's what I thought when I watch. Yeah. Well, I mean here's think
We don't know
How it's gonna be and I'm ready to hate it. I'm ready to hate it. I hated the first one. I did not like that
Paul is always ready to hate movies about things that he loves
That's what I mean, like I'm not I'm not leave Paul is sincerely prepared to hate this film
This is a rare is though where I'm optimistic going in even after seeing the trailer. I'm just shocked that your optimistic me, too
Believe me. I am as shocked as anyone. I was ready to just be like, oh fuck they did it again
But no, this looks very hopeful to me when you text us last night to watch the trailer
I thought it was that we were gonna rip it apart. No
That you can rip it apart if you want to I've already erased my notes once I heard your change of the tone
I raised my notes. No, do you have a fucking notes?
My notes
full of shit
If there's anything that stood out to you is weird. I mean I was ever taken notes
It's hard for them to it's hard for them to fight the whole Marvel influence. So that's clearly there
Yeah, that's clearly there and they and they've definitely toned down the colors of everything
So it's not quite like it's not that 80s bright
I'm concerned, but it's also not as dark and dreary as the first movie. It's brighter than I'm first
about the giant cartoon tiger
You have concerns about Cringer and battle cat. I have concerns about the giant cartoon tiger and being able to take
Scenes with the giant cartoon tiger seriously
I mean see this is another thing that have two options to go with Cringer or battle cat and you insist on saying cartoon tiger
I do because that's what it looks like in the trailer. He's a giant cartoon tiger. He's a giant cartoon tiger
I don't know. I I there's something. I mean, I I'm a sucker for that kind of stuff. I'm a sucker for I
Morphized kind of animals and I did love he man as a kid
And I did love it because I loved Conan Conan the Barbarian. I definitely did
Definitely did connect the two and like it. Yeah, accordingly
And I watched the cartoon and stuff when I was younger
I say I liked it. I liked the toys. I never really watched the cartoon
You guys are younger than me. I watched Sierra. Yeah, no shit old man
I know but you really are I mean I was that thing that fucking show got me right in the zone
Like it hit me exactly right and I know I'm a victim of the Reaganomics
Fair broadcast standards
half-hour commercials
Fuck every Gen X kid train them to buy shit thing. I know I know I
Don't know
I just I really I was impressed with what they're doing with the source material
I'm pleased to see good performers in key roles Idris Elba as man-at-arms
that is
Idris Elba in the movie does definitely that is a
Check in the plus column for sure. I was a brie is evil Lin. Sure. Alison Brie is awesome
Um
And I'm genuinely a bigger Jared Leto fan than you are in general. Well, that's great. And Monarella Buchanan is the sorceress
in our from Firefly
Nice like yeah, like that's a great choice for the sorceress
They've made some really good choice and I don't know who the actress portraying Tila is but she looks wonderful, too
And you know you talk about the whole feminist thing Matt
I think not tequila tequila. It's not tequila tequila not get the role. I think you have to remember
Matt that scoop shooter on the same page that
Filmation did a really good job
Of putting female characters forward in the time when that was not common like Tila was right there with Adam and and and he man
Like she held her own
She held her own same thing with the sorceress being the key to the whole secrets of greyskull and the leader of the of the whole
You know good guy forum and then of course she were being the evolution of that and then it being a very female fronted show
In fact, they hate women
Who else hates women and that is the following sponsor
By
We shouldn't do this one, but I'll read it
Bill Cosby's guide to consent with a new special forward by Sean pity P. Diddy combs
That's an excellent joke we're moving on I'm reading that for haiku scoop, but we're moving on
Yeah, this is much much cleaner
Gloria's glory hole hand drill from the sound man scoop in 2021. That is
Gloria's glory hole hand drill keep it clean
Gloria I
Heard you got a hand drill
Drill I heard you use the hand drill
Weeners ticking through the holes
You don't have to use it if you don't want to it's fine
Just leave it all behind
hand drill Gloria
Gloria
Watch out for the wieners
Here come extra wieners
Sticking through the glory hole
Grip them with the hand drill
Don't touch them with your hands
Your clients will understand
Gloria's hand drill glory hole
And her hate scoops to check out there you go
No, what I will tell you Matt back in the day the Mattel executives were very upset because he man
Was cutting into Barbie sales
Because they had they had some female forward characters and especially when Princess of Power debuted
You know, that's kind of why they so I hear you know, I don't mean to cut you off in that like I do it
I didn't know no, no, I didn't process that. I was talking about like current marketing power and
They have some great females of great prominent roles. The title is literally he man
It's literally and the Masters of the universe and the Masters of the universe
Is it what is it called he man in a Masters universe, I think this one might just be another Masters universe
I can't remember. Okay. I don't know. I don't know
I don't know who's got top billing. I can't tell you what I'm trying
This is like that can all be true from a writing standpoint. It's not from a marketing standpoint, right? Like it's just not oh no for sure
I didn't know it was called Masters of the universe
Is called Masters of the universe great of the universe and it's femininity like there's nothing nothing about the trailer that I saw
I was like, oh girl girls gonna love and rally around this that's no powering
Well in the poster has you know, they do love man facing off against scale tour two dudes looking at each other to fight
So yeah, I get that but it's not this it's not the same brand as as Barbie
It's not but this is but this is like, you know when the Barbie I'm more like coming from this with like the Barbie
versus Oppenheimer thing was such a phenomenon and everyone in Hollywood was racing to figure out what the takeaways were going to be and
None of it seemed to be that women led things can be funny
That said it was like we could do more movies with other toys and I don't know if that was the right take away from an executive
Yes, but learn the wrong lesson or not. They've got good people on the project look
Now maybe you know it is existing IP that's been out there and those are things that people want to make movies out of and so
Yes for people like yourself and other people who grew up with him in and yeah
Maybe my kids will their friends will want to go see it and they'll revitalize the franchise for the kids
You have to do that. You have to try that. I mean you yeah
Yeah, and scooper Nova girl in the chat is like what you don't think women won't love a mostly sexy naked man with abs fighting
of course
It's not you know, you can put me he meant some serious man candy
He made point
You know, so there's something he said there episode title
He man candy that reminds me of a story I heard over the weekend of your good friend Murray Sawchuck, Jacob
Yeah, I love Murray
Guy played over this bit has just morphed into just being Murray just being genuinely good
He gave me that amazing parking spot at his wedding. That's right
Oh
Someone said they're put a college gig and they're like you were so different than the last guy we had and I was like
It wasn't they go
They go Murray Sawchuck and he said sarcastically
Did he show you his abs?
And they giggled and said we touched his abs. Oh
No
Oh
He does like an app parade
Big part of his show the app parade you can have his autograph he can rub his abs and make a wish
Just do it just do a pencil. They come true a pencil rubbing a charcoal rubbing of his abs
Just you just push it against his abs and rub and get up
Like like going to the going to the the wall with the Vietnam Memorial Vietnam Memorial. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I get how it goes
That's crazy. Well
Yeah, you know, I don't know. I'm just really excited for it
I watched a couple reaction videos from many of the careers that I follow who are into action figures, of course
Primarily pixel Dan. I wanted to get pixel Dan's take because I've been following him for decades now. You like talking man
Pixel Dan is he wrote the book on he man
He literally has the full compendium of all the action figures and all that kind of thing
He did or every a review for every figure that came out in the classics line as I was collecting that line
So he's how I kept up with it and he's got two young boys now himself and they of course know him as a toy
Enthusiast his
Livelihood is going to toy shows talking about toys creating toy videos
So he drags them along to toy shops all the time
They themselves are not really into he man those two his two young boys, right?
Ah because that's dad's thing, you know, and that's been right things as he was kidding
however
When he showed them this trailer
Then they asked to get the castles out and they're playing he man again after seeing this trailer
Like you're right then like as an adult looking at singing is like derivative of Marvel
But in terms of like what kids are growing up on they're growing up on Marvel movies
So if it right if it feels like it scratches that it just probably to make kids more interested in seeing it
Absolutely, and you know he man is a superhero. This is what it's what it's about. It's about empowerment
That's what the whole superhero thing is about
it's about empowerment and that's you know, I mean Marvel is no less guilty of going to the
Lowest levels of marketing research to do, you know, I don't know if you're familiar with secret wars
You familiar secret wars. Yeah, so that all came from just marketing
Marketing meetings about what do kids like they love the word
They love secrets and they love Star Wars slash wars and so they go. Oh, let's just do see
Department of our government to the Department of War. Oh, yeah, that's what we love. That's what the kids love kids
Don't that war and now it's a secret war that's going on in broad daylight that we can't really talk about
So fun, so fun all these secret wars
Where's the fucking Beyonder to fix this shit? No, he started he started it all we did Adam Warlock. That's what we need
No, but that's the whole thing of
Where do you find that say that you have a right to carry a thing?
But they shoot you because you carry the thing. Do you have the right to carry the thing? I don't know
Colleges is like
It's a real head-scratcher there Jacob, yeah, yeah god damn it
Fuck anyway, that's a part of it too. This is coming out like a week later
So we should say like who knows what other atrocities have had. Oh god
Yeah, that's true. We are we are recording this is like a couple days earlier than we usually record it
So that is one of the two extra days
Right one other thing about the Masters Universe property and the movie it filled me with some hope
Which is something we're in desperate need of right now
It's something what cinema should be focusing on for sure he meant yeah, and he man is a bright spot
Masters Universe has been a big bright spot in my life and
You know, I love the mythology behind it and that's the thing
Like I said, they are adhering to the true lore and mythology. They're playing with it, but that's fine
That's what it has to you have to do that
You have to you know toy with it a bit
But I love the interpretation so far of like the vehicles that I'm seeing
And all that kind of thing like they've you know, it looks like rotons going through this guy
But you couldn't have a roton looking like a fucking roton if it looks stupid, but it looks cool. It looks really cool
What's the roton? What's the roton? The roton is the vehicle that you would push along and had a thing
It looked like it. Well, it looked like a spaceship with a giant. What is it in the trailer?
It's the spaceships that have like two a little orb being encircled by
Got you a spinny big says that because the toy that was the toy with the it was on wheels, right?
It had a wheel at the base and as you push the saw blade would rotate and it looked like it looks like a saw blade
Around a car. Yeah, right
Which as an adult, I recognize isn't terribly practical mark gates in the chat. Yes, you're exactly right
Roton is the stuff you put in queso dip. Yeah, get yourself a can of roton and
You are ready you are ready for some salsa
Yeah, did you see the Superman trailer before the super movie came out? What did you think of it then?
I did not watch the Superman trailer. I purposefully did not watch the Superman trailer to keep my
surprise that you were an advocate of watching the trailer because you are
Traditionally, I usually I know I know but this is so dear to my heart and I didn't want to get you couldn't help yourself
I didn't want to get inadvertently spoiled. I was like, I'm just gonna go and take it in and I was pleasantly surprised
You know, I'm just really I'm really enthused about the direction. I see so far. There's every possibility
It's a shit show. We haven't heard any dialogue
We haven't heard anything, you know who the fuck knows how the story is gonna play out, but it looks good
Having Marlena give that gravitas of like we hid you away so you wouldn't be killed by these like there's real threat there
I that's kind of cool
You gotta send your child to another planet in order to not have him kidnapped by an evil space dictator. That's kind of neat
That tells me that they're respecting the fact that adora was kidnapped in the past and that traumatized the fuck out of Marlena
So she sent her child to another planet. That's big. I
Don't know I
Since the last starfighter
Yeah, what'd you say Matt? Yeah, who are you gonna dress as when you go to see it in the theater? That's a good question
I've been thinking about it already what I'm gonna do. I'm just gonna put on, you know, my favorite he-man shirt
That's all I'll just put on my favorite Masters Universe shirt. You're just gonna show up as the OG
You're just gonna show up and be like I've been here since the beginning. Mm-hmm, and I'm still here. Yeah, I mean, I'm a big guy
I've always contemplated doing Ramman cosplay would go as orco thirsty scoop in the chat is right. I used to have
I used to have an orco outfit. It didn't look good though
It was one of those like hoodies that also had a mask and a silly hat. It was okay
It just didn't look right. I ended up losing that in the move, but
Yeah, an orco hasn't shown up yet. So that's another thing that could happen
But that could be another thing like they might just they might just be pausing that for now. Does that's another whole thing?
I'm gonna dress as an incredibly angry goose
Everybody go like oh Fisto. I get it
How fast I got that
It is terrible it says bad things about me as a human being how fast I got that
Pisto the goose. Oh
my
Yeah, so I don't know I'll go and then even
Scooper Dover girl was asking early in the chat about popcorn buckets. I'm like, oh shit. Who knows who knows what kind of pop?
Oh, yeah, they've had a collectible shit. You're gonna be oh, well, that's the whole thing
They've already solicited like ten new figures and you know, who knows how long that line already. It's gonna be broke
I'm already collecting three damn he-man lines as it is, you know
Calm everyone preaching fun calm to be on the street. Help me afford
Destitute please. He is gonna be on the street people is I need my plan teaching fun calm
I need my plastic man McPheeters home
What does it come out
June 5th. Oh
I believe so I'm so angry that it's not until June and we have to hear about this until June. No, no, no
No, no. No, this was gonna be
This is the big discussion. I wanted to have and again again
I just want to lay it out there that I'm very hopeful. I'm very pleased with what I saw so far
I am ready to shit on it if it turns out to be garbage, you know, I will you know, I hate I know
You know, I hated that latest Tron movie. I love the soundtrack, you know, there's
You know, I'm not I'm not partial to my IP. I'm not blind to the holes in my IP
But that's also you hate things that you love the beautiful thing about
Masters of the universe is that it really is a tool for imagination and exploration and
Back when I played with my figures most of my Lord came from what I'd read in the little mini comics
I I would ignore a lot of the
Filmation stuff. I loved hordak. I
Do not care for the filmation depiction of hordak at all. That is that's hashtag
Not my hordak with that and snorting like a pig half the time. No, thank you. That's not that's not me
That's just a weird that was a weird choice. So I said good day hordak. I do say good day hordak because he's a cool-looking villain
So we'll see
We'll see but I'm I can't wait. I teared up
You know movie got to me the preview got to me. So, you know, it doesn't take much
I'm on ice already. Well, the whole country's falling apart and then I see he man come hanging around. I'm like, oh
Yeah, there you go
Yeah, that's a really weird thing happened to me the other day. Uh-huh. What's that? I was walking down the strip and a
party bus like a big limo party bus
Which is not uncommon comes rolling down the strip right next to and I'm you know, I'm on Vegas Boulevard there
I'm on the sidewalk walking down the road and
that this bus has a
Roll down windows. It's all the windows are rolled down and the whole thing is just filled with what looks like
I don't know 13 year old girls 12 13 year old girls
young tween girls and
They are all leaned out the bus windows heading to the trunk. I'm the only I am the only person on the sidewalk
Okay, I'm the only person around
They are all leaned out the window and when they see me they all do the hand thing and yell six seven thing
Okay, yes, and they keep on driving and I believe that has triggered a full midlife crisis
They broke your brain I think they broke me I'm done god damn I am out
This has I I stood there for a minute
Just going I don't even know just dumbfounded, huh? Should I step into traffic should I?
Just it's a rap, huh? What should I do now?
And I'm walking like I am more than halfway through my life I really am
Like I I have lived more years already that I'm probably going to live
Yeah, that's that's probably true. Yeah
That's a that's a way that's a hell of a way to measure it with that with that kind of event happening to really clock
That but yeah, it's because those those children with their their Terminator vision, which they would have a reference
To you and said old man engaged six seven him six seven him
Also, I was like I wanted to go in and stop them and be like hey the six seven thing is out guys
That's done. I don't know where you guys have been but that's that is simply out. I know that it's weird that you don't
I'm so sorry Jacob. Thank you. Thank you
Continues to be dramatic if it's any dramatic if it's any consolation, I think you've lived at least two-thirds of your life, you know
See this is another thing Jacob
you know if you were like me and you were obsessed with a childhood toy property for the majority of your existence and
and and
You know even when there was lean times even when nobody was talking about the universe
You were in it in it to win it and now take that away from you
You know what I mean, but this is the thing back. I feel like Jacob think if they were making an Archie Manning video
Oh
Now I get it now I thank you Matt for clarifying that now I understand
That's what it that is what it does though. It does kind of give you the level of like a Bobby a bear documentary
The deep cut for you fucking Saints fans out there
Of
tweens on a bus yelling at me
To pass the time we took in a comedy special Eric Dillman recommended his friend Renan Hirschberg on YouTube
Okay, his newest specials called morbidly Jewish
And I won't try to do anything but you're too much from it
But the one thing really made me what lots of made me laugh really hard at it. But what was he goes, you know?
Harry Potter got in trouble for like, you know having you know
The people run in the bank or these like goblin people and they were like, oh, that's it. Yeah
the green gods and that's anti-semitic and he goes
Isn't watching made-up creatures and thinking they're Jewish stereotypes more anti-semitic than the green gods being anti-semitic
I put nothing path JK Rowling though. She's right intentions
Actually, you know, she meant all
Definitely if you have a chance to got morbidly Jewish on you, that sounds funny. Nice. What's his name again, Renan Hirschberg?
Ra a na n you say he's Jewish. I
Yes, okay
Let's do a little scooperty here we got a scooper here from Smitty scoop here like you know, I'm from New Jersey Paul, right?
Uh-huh. That's how you'll know that he's Jewish got it. Yeah
Because Matt Donnelly told you you got it
Gentlemen, well Matt won the first Smitty scooperty of 2026
But it may be a bit premature to declare that Matt has officially dethroned Paul and Jacob and reclaimed the Smitty scooperty crown
So I prepared another scooperty for your enjoyment to give Paul and Jacob a chance to redeem themselves. Here we go
The categories are winter Olympics geography sitcom spouses and hard
Shit. All right. Oh, I'll start with hard for 400. Here we go
Rachel what's for dinner? I'm married to Rachel Maddow
Now my giant brother still wants to fuck my wife. My mom and dad are mean. Oh boy
What sitcom was Paul talking about?
That has to be everybody loves Raymond, yes
Yeah, okay
That was so confusing Paul, that's a crazy quote
I'll try sitcom spouses for 1200
Okay
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Heaton for nine seasons on everybody loves Raymond? Oh my god
Oh
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Heaton for nine seasons on everybody loves Raymond
I'm really glad because when I was answering the last question
I did have to pause for a moment go like wait
Was it every was it everybody loves Raymond or everyone loves Raymond loves Raymond, but
The name of the wife I got to pass. I don't know
I love that Smitty scooperty is the one thing driving me to finally watch an episode of everyone loves Raymond, but
Does it pass to me? It does pass to you. Yeah, it's a pass for me. Jacob. Yeah, it's a pass for me as well
Deborah Barone
No way you would have a last name. No way. Oh, did she not take his last name?
Who cares
Does Colorado share a border with Idaho
Yes
Let's try yes
No, both Wyoming and Utah share a border with Colorado and Idaho, but Colorado and Idaho do not border each other. Damn it
Oh, I'm seeing in the chat. I'm seeing the chat. Barone was Raymond's last name in the show
He was Raymond Barone, oh, well, there you go. There you go. That's me. I'll try
I'll do winter Olympics for 400 daily double
Here we go what country is hosting the 2026 winter Olympics none country not gonna happen cancelled games
I mean, that's probably that's probably true
It is is it is it us I don't know yeah
U.s. It is I'll say us Italy. Ah, no, I didn't know
No, I didn't think I didn't think you were doing that there's no issues they're having issues that they might not have enough snow for
Oh
Yeah, they should come out to Pittsburgh
Winter Olympics in Indiana or fourth fourth
Paul, uh, I'll go with hard
For 800 what is the minimum number of darts that have to be thrown to win a single leg of double in double out?
501 darts 9
Is correct. It's called the 9 dart finish or 9 darter and it is considered to be on par with a 300 game in bowling
Hooray for me. Did you know that or did you guess it's a guess it was either 9 or 12. Oh
Matt you're up. Oh, yeah, cuz you'd have to hit the triple 20 you have to get just right every time until hitting the until
Hitting the double bulls. Yes. I guess you'd have to hit the bulls eye at one point. But yeah, whatever
Rock hard for 1200, please. Yeah
Including the pincer claws, how many legs does a crab have? Oh Matt, this is so up your alley
Yeah, eight ten twelve or fourteen
Including the pincer claws now, Matt
Usually you don't include the pincer claws
When you count crab legs this time make sure that you do I see the legs his legs and the claws his arms
That's the way I brought up right. I was taught my town. Yes. Yeah wonderful. See
Everyone's favorite claw full in the master's universe movie. Oh, of course having a big claw pincer arm. I
Hope so not at all like fisto
Who has an exact arm exactly like that? There was like there was three of those guys. There was claw full
There was fisto and there was jitsu. They all had fucked up hands. Oh
a eight
eight
I'm sorry, it's B
You forgot about the pincer claws
See them as arms
You will not go back on that Lindsay in the chat says she just wants some claws in her mouth
I'll close out hard for two thousand crab legs in my mouth
Is it possible while driving on an interstate highway to travel directly from Nevada to Utah?
without passing through another state
Via an interstate highway, I
Don't think it is I'm gonna say no, ah
Yes, but not on I-15 which passes through a small sliver of Arizona
Nevada and Utah share a 240 mile long border and I 80 crosses this border fucking I always forget about I 80
Matt doesn't count the pincer arms on the crabs and I don't count I 80. I said it was I 80 with that low
because I didn't know I 80 goes pretty low, but because it goes it goes from the
It goes from the Golden Gate Bridge to the George Washington Bridge
hmm
so I thought
That would not which are both in San Francisco. You're up. I 40 across the country
I will try sitcom spouses for 2,000 to get some money on the board. All right
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Richardson for eight seasons on home improvement?
my god
How dehumanized was that character?
Tim and
Was it Heather
Did he call her Heather did he call her Heather tool time Heather tool time
Samantha tool time Taylor her last his name named with Taylor. So she'd been
Angela
Matt Katrina, it's a pass for me, please
People throwing things on straight hints in the chat straight. Oh, all right. Yeah, what doesn't matter? I can't see him. Um, I
I boy I
Watched this show. I watched home improvement for at least a few seasons with my dad. Yeah
Yeah, I'll give you a hint I think it was
Okay, Jill is in my head
All right, so I'm gonna go Jill Jill Taylor
Did I know it's Tim the two men tool man Taylor and I think it was Jill. There you go
It is Jill Taylor Jill Taylor Jill the drill they called her
They call her Jack and Jill there's no ampersand in that name
I don't want to answer any of these Jacob
Fucking the Winter Olympics for 800
Let's see and what sport did
peer-man
Zabrigan
Tomba and Phil Meyer and
Just tell Andre Amant short and Petra Kronberger
Herman Mir
Whatever all these people won gold medals. What is it when you're making bobsled team?
Jacob the answer to every question in the Winter Olympics
Category should be who cares right? Is it skeleton? It's skeleton. It's always skeleton
herling
Skeleton
I'll
Paul wants answer. I'll pass. I'll pass Paul
For I don't remember. I think I think it's the little one. I'll guess skeleton
The skeleton of the Winter Olympics
Skeleton you betrayed me
Betrayed by a skeleton
At Lake Placid in 1980 Eric Haydn won five gold medals in what sport did he compete?
Haydn seek
He's a master now, I'm going to board for it. No, I'm gonna take determinism
As is the case than most of the Winter Olympics
Yeah, that's why that's why Jake Skellington won
Phil Luge you can't lose sure sure that's the only place Luge could win
Somewhere I don't know where it is Paul. What is it? I won the Luge you Luke can't lose for winning
Eric where you hide those gold medals
Yeah, that's
Let's see
Speed skating
Praying for the skeleton
President sweep wedding gold at all five distances
500 or 1,000 1500 5,000 and 10,000 meter speed skating speaking of praying for the skeleton
Uh-huh. Have you guys seen the fucking horror show that happened out here in the Pittsburgh area?
With this motherfucker digging up all the bodies
What? Oh?
There's a guy
He talked about a he bed for half hour and you're bringing this up now
this guy
He dug up so many bodies
He dug up babies he dug up old people wait does he go into cemeteries and doing this yes
It's in Philly, and so he's breaking into these mausoleums and these old
What do you call uh, you know with the?
Walls and all them. Yeah, you know ground stuff. Yeah, the Crips Crips
So he's breaking in all these Crips and shit, and this has been going on for years
He's been stealing all these bodies and keeping them at his house and selling some of the parts
And he's just into all this macabre shit. He's got a fucking
He's got a fucking storage unit with more skeletons
I'd buy that for a dollar the police went and raided his house right and the police chief came out like in tears
Like my men shouldn't have had to see this and all the stuff like there's body cam footage of the police in this house of
bodies and of bodies just lining the walls everything and one of the policeman is like is that a pacemaker like they're straight up
Skeletons with you can see. Oh, yeah, dude. My it's
Outrageous out
Fucking rages how many skeletons he stole and over Dover girl. He has some stored in his closet
He definitely did and they found um
They found him out by a couple of different methods
But one of the key ways that they traced him
He was leaving energy drinks at the scenes
Guess what energy drink he was drinking?
monster monster exactly right Matt
More those questions of this scooper day
Drinking monster energy drinks while he's stealing
Skeletons, it's the creepiest shit. You've ever seen. They're all like super desiccated and mummified most of them and
It is something else. So look he's not keeping them in good shape. I
Mean no, he's they're in their clothes and stuff
They're in their clothes and everything just sitting in his house, man. It's crazy
it's crazy like hundreds of people bought he he's on a million dollar bail and
We talked about Masters of the Universe for so long Paul. It's your turn winter Olympics geography your sitcom spouse
It all comes back to Skeletor. Let's go to Winter Olympics for 2000
Win
What is the only Winter Olympics sport in which women do not compete this sport is contested solely by men
skeleton
Skeleton if I yes if I get this with skeleton what's happening? I don't think you're gonna get it
Nordic combined. Oh shit
Country ski race that follows ski jumping the farthest jumpers get the largest head starts in the race
Let's race let women do it
Wait, how is that in the Olympics?
the it's like biathlon type shit, right I
Mean it sounds kind of like it, but that's even weirder
This sounds weirder than the biathlon not the other way. I mean chess is in the Olympics, right?
I don't care. I don't care. I don't care geography check it out. He's checking out the cold is getting to a border with, Oklahoma
Oklahoma
Paul's yelling Oklahoma
One of my favorite Saturday at live sketches with John love it's
He kept saying oh call wedgie fever was the game show and every time he got a question wrong
They would pull the wedgie tighter on your ass and he's getting pulled up by his underwear
He keeps guessing Oklahoma incorrectly for everything cuz he likes getting his underwear pulled
He keeps screaming Oklahoma, and then he gets one, right?
Matt does Colorado share a border with, Oklahoma
The frozen Indiana has broken Matt that is defeated
Yes
The frozen Indiana has done with that busload of girls did to me
Southeast Oklahoma shares a 34 mile border with the western panhandle of Oklahoma, which is what man was saying look at you Matt
Yeah, I'll try sitcom spouses for 800
What is the name of the character played by Gene Stapleton for nine seasons at all in the family?
I don't fucking know pass it to me. I know this one
Shit pass to me. I know it. I heard you the first time Paul
Shongs we're on your hit parade
Something played Oh, what is it? It's eat it stifle it there eat it
It's Edith bunker. I'm sorry Paul. It's Edith bunker
If I can take your last name, I don't want to be a bunker
Hitler got shot in a bunker. I don't want to get shot
Paul your turn will you stifle it you dingbat?
What city is the capital of Pennsylvania Oh
Harrisburg, let's try it. It's Harrisburg. Yeah, look at me. I'm winning
Freedom Bell
Geography for 1200
Name any five of the 26 countries that have five letter names when written in English Canada
Chad
Not your turn and wrong
Oh
France Iran, uh-huh. That's one
No, oh yeah, this is five letters no, is it no wait it doesn't it's six, right?
I was like, I know I can't spell but I can count
Palatins I pass
To me
Well this France clearly there's Canada
Chad
Let's see there's Egypt. Oh, yeah. There you go
Hmm a little bit no Columbia
Italy Italy nice. Sure. That's to war
Let's see France how many letters does France have Germany
Farsi Farsi sure Aruba. Yeah
Brazil no Hawaii pass Paul pass
Let's see been in Chile China Congo Egypt. Hey got one. Yeah, you got a Haiti India
Bunch of them. We didn't know there's 26 of them
No, I'm just looking at them real quick now
Five of them guitar in Spain guitar in Spain and Syria those are
Closing out the category and the game sitcom spouses for 400
What is the name of the character played by Florence Henderson for five seasons on the Brady Bunch?
Here's the story of a lovely lady whose name we refuse to reveal
and a man
Who has a last name but that is all we'll say. This is Brady
Here's some children
Yeah, they're hanging out
All right, so you had Marsha you had Jan Jan had little
Girl, of course, there was Opie
Opie Opie Cunningham Delilah
Skippy. Yeah my my my Delilah
Pass
Paul
What was the dad's name
Those that's not the question I know
Alice why are you trying to think about that because it was kind of like the pairing up of
Well, they called each other mr. Brady and mrs. Brady all the fucking time
Just throw you off. They were weirdies like that
Florence Henderson her name one Florence though. Oh
I'm sorry. That's time Matt the pass. Yes, Darrell
Carol, right. It was Carol
It is Carol Brady. Well nice
That is the game with that correct answer Matt launched himself into third place with negative 400 points
I'm in second place with zero points Paul wins with 800 points. That was a somewhat low-scoring
Smitty scooper II, but thank you Smitty scoop
You got positive points baby, look at you go for us Smitty scoops
That's incredible for me
If you want to send us a scooper II head over to hey scoops comm right there on the home page
You could send us any kind of jock versus nerd that we do here
You could also send us some email over to the scoop mail store head over there store. No just scoop mail. It's the scoop mail
Not a store
And yeah, we're always looking for interesting stuff I just heard my favorite murder there and they're asking for oh here we go
It slaps it is that is that is the shit right there, but my favorite murder gals
we're asking for people to write in their
Stories where people say oh, you've got to tell the story or someone asks you to tell that story about
It's a great prompt a great prompt that please if you have a
Like a really wild tale that your family recounts a good party story or something. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, we'd love to hear those from you guys. You know, we can always also send in your first BJ stories your first
Sex stories. We always love the they did what stories. Yeah, you know, it's kind of like terrible job stories
Something that happened to someone you grew up with a terrible job stories. We love to any of it
Andy all and the old poetry if you
Want me to just be happy just send in old high school poetry?
The mark in the chair the better mark in the chat is asking for first grave Doug story
Yeah, tell us about the first grave you robbed. How many?
Do you have in your closet? Oh my god
Don't watch those videos if you're squeamish. Honestly, it is do you fucking creep show it is deep show. All right
Thank you so much
Podcasts
Thanks, Ben. I've got some scoops to thank as well
We have a few a few more scoops to thank this month. Our list is all fucked up this month
Sorry about that. If we missed your name this month, we will do better next month
I want to thank though the man the myth the scoop the Chelsea's far Timothy Reed tipsy scoop
Tom Krieger Tom Mankerdy Travis Murray Tyler Tyler Tyler Bartlett Tyler scoop McDuck Virgil the verge
Walker Ryan Warren, bro, Wendy Bumgarner will breathe will Breeden will Kellner winter scoop Zelda Rae Skywalker and of course
Canadian scoop crystal. Mm-hmm. Thank you so much. Thank you so much
if you want to be thanked on air or get a
Myriad of other prizes and rewards head on over to preaching fun commas select a tier that works for your budget today
Or if you got broken by a busload of teenage girls this
Head over to farts in a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm
It takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month
You can help keep this show on the air
You know the whole drill head over there preaching fun comm farts in a bag dot biz. We'll love you for it
Mm-hmm. All right. Well, thanks for listening everybody stays if out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
Big thanks to all the scoops that hung out with us with a double episode day to day
So thank you all hanging in the chat and in the zoom
Love seeing your faces. It's lovely to have an audience and everybody out there on twitch
Peace and love y'all
Yeah