That's wrong.
How's that wrong?
Off to a fantastic start.
I should put my headphones on.
That's how it's fucking wrong.
I don't know how to do things.
It's an abomination your lack of headphones is disgusting to watch.
Hello!
I'd love to thank all you ice cream truck drivers out there.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Well these are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now I'd like to thank
Paul's Brother
Pyro
Richard Dunn
Sarah Boyle
Sax Guy
Jimmy D. Scoop
Scoop Brady
Scoop DuJour
Scoop Kata
Slurpee Ka-A Motherfucker
The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver
Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop
and Travis Jaguri
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I sure hope you do, PreachingFun.com is where you can go.
PreachingFun.com, go there, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
Here's the show!
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
We've got our friend Jonas Wolferton stopping by the churn today.
Paul created a profile on Patreon with the most ridiculous post ever.
We can finally announce, we can finally announce where we were.
Our mystery show that we were talking about.
It's time for Matt and Matt Hickley's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt. Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul. Sitting in Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
I want to start with an apology. I just blamed Paul for something that was Jacob's fault.
That was me, that was me.
Jacob took credit on it, which is great. I mean, eventually it will be my fault.
Yeah, yeah.
Very soon, I'm trying to...
I thought Paul had already done it, so I jumped on it the last second and did it.
This is for the Zoom hangout. I already told the people that were in the Zoom early, but yeah, that was my fuck up.
I thought Paul had already done it. Paul thought I had already done it, so I just jumped on it and did it real quick.
It didn't think about any problems that I was going to create in the future.
So I get all the Patreon emails and it just was like, "Wait, what? What's that? When? Where? What's going on?"
Yeah.
See, you get those and you were bothered by those. I get the Zoom email, so every time somebody tried to click through the link and go, "I was getting an email as well."
Oh, man.
We offered a new feature for Patreon off-air hangouts on Zoom. Paul was going to host the first one, and then we're going to be more detailed going forward.
I did, but we did get it cooking. Yeah, so I got to still chat with you, Matt, a little bit later about Patreon stuff getting in there.
And then I'm going to get myself all situated with the Zoom coordination stuff so I can actually send those out real soon.
So I'm going to do that, and then I'll talk to you, Matt, later this week about getting all that.
I'm busy.
But congratulations to Casey and Josh on their recent marriage.
Yes, that's great.
Such a lovely tag. And there was a surprise.
The reason why we did the Tierney show is because Paul and I were hired to go surprise a groom on his wedding by having his two favorite podcasters stop by and do improv on their rehearsal night dinner.
And we surprised Josh by pretending to call him on our way to another gig, and then we walked out of our car into the wedding venue.
And there's nothing more special as improv comedians to walk into a room where two people are very excited to see you and 50 people don't know what's going on.
But to their credit, they got on board real quick.
My son was like, how'd the show go? I go, well, no one was expecting to watch the show.
So the fact that they watched the show and participated was a real...
Why was everyone polite?
Imagine if I just came into your classroom with Paul and just did an improv show. That's the same feeling as everyone else at that dinner.
But they were down and they loved it. And the main thing, Josh was super surprised, really shocked, and Casey was very pleased that we got the desired effect out of him. So that was it.
No. And again, we say we have the best listeners in the world because we attract the nicest people. Sure enough, that wedding was filled with just amazingly awesome people who were very kind to us.
I was playing chess with their son. I was invited on the dance floor numerous times at the wedding. It was just a lot of good hanging. So, yes.
Incredibly delicious food, libations, games.
Oh, Paul, that actually brings up a sticky subject. I did get a note. You were only hired as the guest. You weren't actually supposed to eat anything. So I do have a bill.
It was an invoice.
They did send a bill over.
I get it. I had an extra ravioli or two. That's for sure.
That is noted on the invoice.
Extra ravioli or two.
Yeah. We should maybe address basically how this all snowballed in a way that made sure that Jacob wasn't there. I think maybe we should get into that as well.
Okay.
So originally I was called and I was emailed because I was a magician. And she said, I think my husband likes your podcast, but he likes magic. And so I think you did a duo. And she brought up Nick Paul. Nick Paul, who I just did the Magic Castle with.
Yeah, yeah.
I said, oh, so you want the magic show that Nick Paul and I did at the castle? And she's like, yes. And I said, great. So I called Nick Paul. Was he available? Yes. And then I basically on a follow-up email was like, so you guys saw us at the castle or whatever?
She goes, no, we've never been to the Magic Castle. And I said, so how did you find about the Nick Paul and I show? Because Nick Paul and I do shows together, but like at the castle and a few other places, but not often.
Right. And she was like, well, I just knew that my husband listens to the podcast. And then I started going like, uh oh. Nick Paul, Paul Mattingly, she might think she has the name right.
And I said, listen, right now, you have a magic show booked with myself and Nick Paul and Nick is available.
This is far enough away that maybe you want to, without giving anything away, figure out whether he wants you to show up with the magician that maybe your husband's never heard of or the podcast partner that she has heard of.
Which is really funny. If you show up at somebody's wedding with a magician that the groom has never heard of, it's great.
And he's like, Hey Matt, and hi sir. Hey pal, thanks for being away. What a surprise. I'm Josh.
And so like a month later, she's like, yeah, that, yep, you were right. I'm wrong. And we do not.
So I had to call Nick Paul to be like, Hey pal, you're no longer one. No one likes you.
You sure have a popular name. That's his name. Yeah.
So all that kerfuffle, you know, booking an improv show with Paul and I had it come earlier to my attention that just simply about ice cream social.
I might've said, do you also want Jacob there? But it was such a kerfuffle and a hubbub to pull it off that I totally, it wasn't until I was at the wedding and everyone was talking about how much they liked the podcast.
It was, we met another scoop that was there. Ryan, Ryan, who actually turned, uh, Josh on to us. Yeah. Way back in the day. Yes. Yeah. And he didn't make it to the rehearsal dinner and was so pissed when he found out we were surprised.
There I did a show. He's like, but anyways, it was, I really had a lot more fun at the wedding, knowing that Jacob probably should have been there too. And he wasn't. And that made me really feel great.
Well, I wasn't at the party. I was at home working on things. I will say, uh, not having any fun. It would have been nice to have Jacob there to deflect from the, uh, possibility of your early onset death.
Uh, he would have, he would have advised me, uh, or more to the point, he would have been in charge and knocking on your door and he would probably would just wouldn't have stopped knocking until you. Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
He would have said Matt, he would have said Matt and I would have heard a voice that wasn't housekeeping is what would have happened. I just knocked twice and assume you're dead. Yeah. In fairness, every time I do go to wake Matt up, I do impersonate a housekeeper.
Yeah. I don't always do the same accent. Sometimes I go Dutch. Sometimes I go Slavic. You know, it just depends on my mood. And then my instant boner wakes me up and I have to go like, all right, I'm up. That's right. That's right. But it was amazing. It was so wonderful.
Uh, we're going to bury that right now because we have our friend Jonas Wolverton here. Exactly. Speaking of instant boners.
He, uh, he, he headlined our, our, our variety show at Scoop Fest this year. The balls on him. Jonas, how you doing, pal?
Uh, my balls are doing well. Good. Good. We were worried. I could tell you. I could see the fear in your eyes. All good. Uh, hi. So you have a solo show coming up at the, um, uh, uh, it's not art square theater anymore. What's your biggest theater company? Yes.
Biggest theater company. Yeah. So I'm doing my solo Mack and fro show and Mack and fro is the bad boy of tennis who you guys saw at Scoops Fest. That's right. Uh, so you were a variety artist. You, you, uh, you juggle, you do a seer wheel. Uh, where did you end up, uh, coming up with the John Mack and fro idea?
I have always loved John Mack and roe. Yeah. No relation. Oh, interesting. If you're listening lawyers, no related. Nothing related. Did you play tennis in your youth? Um, very rarely. Okay. I was in New York city kid. I played baseball. All right. Um, thick ball, but, uh, no bad. Second base. Watch John. Uh, shortstop and third. Oh, come on. I call, I call infielder. He had infielder vibes. Yeah. Yeah. No, that's pretty good. Infielder vibes. Come on.
I feel pretty good. I still feel good about that one. Yeah. Yeah. So I grew up watching John Mack and roe have some serious, uh, blowouts. Oh yeah. Yeah. He is the most, uh, New Yorker of all of the tennis players from that time period for sure.
That's why I love him. He is the most likely for a New York kid to enjoy who doesn't play tennis. That, that, that, yeah, that's where New York kids are going to gravitate to is John Mack and roe. Exactly. Exactly. That and the 86 Mets who are all like high on cocaine.
Oh man, I got caught watching like a documentary on Dwight Gooden and, uh, uh, uh, Darrell strawberry. And, uh, it just kept getting like the clickety click of the roller coaster. All the heights are right at the very beginning.
And then it just goes down, down, down, down, down, down. And I was like, Jesus, will someone stop this documentary, please?
Somebody stopped this documentary before someone gets hurt. Get the present day. Get the present day. It's so dark. The whole thing. Oh my God.
These are my heroes when I'm, when I'm eight. Perfect. Perfect. Yeah. So I, I loved Mack and roe and, um, uh, I love the sort of performance art aspect.
I'm not really knowing what performance art was a kid, but later on from reflecting about it, I got a gig, uh, with world team tennis to, uh, do seer wheel, which is what you guys see in the back there.
And, uh, I was like, Hey, I've been thinking about this, doing this bad boy of tennis character kind of an homage to Mack and roe. Um, would you guys be cool with that? And they're like, yeah, absolutely.
So I got hired to do a gig. Um, I did a seer wheel act as him and also interacted with the crowd, um, and filmed the whole thing as a sort of, I didn't know what I was going to do with it. Make it like a documentary, a mockumentary or something.
Cause, cause Mack and roe, I mean, you know, for people of a certain age, he's, he's an iconic character, but like in the circus world, especially most people like sports, let alone famous tennis players. So like, was there any time where you were floating the idea of doing Mack and fro and just another circus guy was like, what the hell are you talking about? Please don't do this. What are you doing?
No, my world is the, the world of the clown. And so I, I, that's actually my first entrance into circus was through clown. I went to, I went to the clown conservatory in San Francisco. Yeah. And, uh, I did a whole year long program in clown.
And so my attraction to, um, the circus is originally through clown and through character. And I'm a theater kid at heart. And, uh, that's my, you know, my first passion. And so I wound up, um, there was no, like, and that's the cool thing about the clown is you can literally draw from anything in the world and, and find what's ridiculous about it and find what's funny about it and find the absurdity in it. Right.
How old are you when you go to the clown conservatory? Like where are you in your, in your life?
Uh, this would be in 2001, 2002. So I'm, I'm, I just graduated from college and in film and was working in film and was like, ah, man, I was making a documentary about a sideshow circus and wound up getting like literally ran away with the circus was like, this is so cool. I don't want to be making the film. I want to be the film.
So we actually had a stand up comedian. Come on. That happened with his documentarian as well.
Yeah.
Yeah. So, so you literally, here's the good news is like, if you turn to your parents, it's like, you know what? I don't want to do stuff in the film. They're like, Oh, thank God. But I do want to be a clown.
Shit.
Absolutely.
We failed as parents more than we thought we did.
We got monkey pod.
No more film bad news. I'm a clown in San Francisco.
Gift of the mad ride.
But they, but they were behind you in your choices.
Thousand percent.
That's great.
Yeah. Always, always, always. I mean, um, that's, that's, are they artists also?
Uh, no, not at all. Not at all. My mom like worked in book publishing. My dad's a, um, a political guy in Brazil.
A political guy in Brazil? That sounds like mafia. That sounds like mafia to me.
He's kind of like the fixer for the president.
This is not, you're not dissuading my, my conclusion.
I'm nailing it. Infielder, mafia dad. I'm nailing it left and right.
Yeah. Yeah. But, but for good, because he's actually a good president. He's, he's, he's on the side of the people.
So yeah, he's, he's not one of those assholes that's, you know, he's, he's very much against the current American regime.
So, you know, let's, let's get on this for the second year, but like, how do you keep up with all that?
Do you follow, uh, like, uh, Brazilian news and stuff?
Um, I am, I have Brazilian citizenship, so I try to keep like one eye open to what's happening in Brazil.
Also as an exit strategy for this, uh, country.
Oh, really? Are you, I didn't realize people were thinking about what other countries they could live in right now because of, uh,
It's just in the back pocket.
I, I wasn't immediately jealous of your Brazilian citizenship. I'll tell you right now.
Wait till you hear about my Canadian.
Fuck yourself.
I mean, I'm also a spy in addition to being a mafia.
So, uh, so that's, that's gotta be crazy to follow your dad's career a little bit. Yeah.
Yeah. And the thing is, my dad is actually the one who got me to circus. You can think about it. Like he, he was always into clowns, uh, growing up.
Uh, I hear stories about him, like, you know, back in Brazil in, in, in the, in the center of town, like the circus would still come through the town.
And they would, uh, do this thing. The clown would do this thing where the kid that would help the clown out to get all the other kids to come to the circus.
They'd put a little bit of ash like behind their ear so that when they showed up to the circus, they could like see the kids who had the ash behind the ear and they would get in for free.
Oh, that's, that's really romantic. I like that.
Yeah. So there's, I, I, and I was very small when I saw my first circus in Brazil. I was like five years old, I think. Um, I can't, it was either Ringling in New York or I was in this small, like rural circus in Brazil.
And, um, I just fell passionately in love with it. And so it's been, it's always been this idea of, of, of, oh, I really want to be involved in the circus in some ways, always been in my mind.
Um, and it, it just, it just came out after I went to college and, and got, had a film career and I was like, fuck it, circus. This is it. This is the new thing. We're going this way now.
As someone who works in a circus, I am always fascinated, fascinated by people who see that and go like, I gotta do this.
I, I'm, I'm someone who is in like, uh, uh, in that area, you know, mainstream kind of like show business and then saw variety arts. It's like, oh, wait, variety arts. You can work all the time. You don't have to try to chase fame or awards. You can just get work. And I think that's, I think that's what's really attractive.
It really is, but there is this thing of, cause it's so much of showbiz. What people, I, this is probably wrong because I'm in showbiz. And so I'm trying to picture what people who aren't in showbiz think about it.
But it seems like, you know, from the, from the movies and stories and everything, people are attracted to the kind of glitz and glamor of showbiz and circus has very little glitz or glamor.
Oh, hard to disagree. Hard to disagree.
When it has its own type. Sure. But it's not, it's not that red carpet.
I can't think of any more glamorous than Jonas wearing a giant Afro wig and a G string and having all these scoops Pelton with tennis balls. Name anything more glamorous than that.
I stand corrected.
Yeah. I mean, I've, I've, I've performed in, you know, um, like dirty rock clubs, like the Double Down.
You have done a show with the Double Down.
Yeah. Double Down.
The clowns, uh, wheel of misfortune.
What's it called? Wheel of Paul.
Just, you know, that, that club is not named after the KFC to fry chicken breast sandwich.
It was not going.
It's a happy accident.
No, I, I, I know about the Double Down.
I've been to the Double Down a time or two.
What's, uh, ass juice.
That's the, uh, the, the, that's the, the bartenders at the end of the night will take the trays where they catch all the.
Detritus and they will even, they will pour you shots of whatever is in there and you can.
And it's in a little toilet bowl too.
Yeah. There you go. It's a, it's a specialty of the house.
Yeah. I know me some Double Down.
A specialty.
But I've performed a Double Down, but I've also performed for the, uh, the spoltan of Oman.
Get out of here.
As a Double Down?
As Mac and Pro.
You've done the Mac and Pro?
No, not as Mac and Pro. Just, just generally over my career.
Okay. Nice.
So that's, that's a, that's a good spread for sure.
You started in clown, but you've learned other skills.
When, when do you like, when did you start figuring out like the seer wheel?
Like what, sometimes it's like, Hey, you're too athletic to just be a clown.
You should maybe do other things.
Yeah. I thought I was a clown, but I started, I was like, Oh, I'm old for the circus.
I'm like 25 or whatever.
And, uh, and then I saw Daniel seer, uh, he of the seer wheel.
Uh, the inventor.
The inventor of the wheel.
Yeah. He invented the wheel.
I didn't even realize it was that new.
Yeah. He, he premiered his, his, uh, act in Paris festival of,
Paris is one of the largest circus festivals in the world.
So we should say quickly that like for anyone, seer wheels, like a giant metal
hoop, you kind of say like a giant metal hula hoop or whatever.
That a person can fit inside.
Yeah. Yeah.
So the person kind of.
You can picture the, the, the Vichy, Vitruvian man.
Ah, yes. That's a great, yeah.
You're basically the spokes of a wheel and you are generating the, the,
the spin in the wheel.
Um, and you can roll and there's, and there's, um, you can manipulate it.
There's a whole bunch of like, uh, vocabulary that when I first started out
working with Daniel seer, um, yeah, which is, it's, it's a six foot tall.
Well, for me, it's my height.
So it's six foot tall ring that I get inside of and spin around.
Um, I started working with Danielle, uh, seer in Montreal in 2003.
He just won the, um, the silver medal, I believe at the Paris festival.
And he premiered a brand new circus discipline.
And so when I started out, there was four people.
And before that I saw him and what got me interested in it was I was in clown
school and we had to choose an apparatus.
We had to choose like juggling or, or, um, hand balancing or, you know,
whatever circus discipline or apparatus you wanted to choose.
And I, um, saw Daniel seer perform while I was in clown school right at the
beginning of it.
I was like, that's it.
It didn't even exist back then.
Right.
There was nobody had a ring.
Just kind of, right.
You know, it was just Danielle and I was like, he make his own, I guess he
had to.
Yeah.
He manufactured his own ring.
And then, uh, I, he, and then he's like, they're on Amazon.
They're not there.
Nope.
Yeah.
You can, you can get them online now.
They're, they're, they're more accessible and stuff.
And a lot of people, a lot more people are doing it now, but, um, I fell in
love with it.
I, the one thing that did exist that was kind of similar was a German wheel,
which has two rings.
Um, so I started training on German wheel and then, um, wound up creating an
act in German wheel, a clown act.
And then, um, audition for Daniel Sears company in Montreal circle was, and
got hired to, to create, be one of the creators, one of the creative artists
that originated the show called rain that toured the world.
Oh yeah.
Rain.
We should, we should actually put it like, you do love the sear wheel because
you, you, when we asked you to do school fest, you said yes.
And you said you had a version without a sear wheel, one with, and I said, okay,
what, what, what conditions do you need for the sear wheel?
And you laid out like three factors and we met none of them.
We asked for one thing.
It had to be a wooden stage and not carpeted.
We had a carpeted stage stage had to be very, very big.
Uh, our stage was very small.
And so it's the record.
That's the record.
Yeah.
I just kept saying, I kept saying, maybe do the version without the wheel.
And you just kept being like, I'm going to bring the wheel anyway.
I'm going to bring it just in case.
And we had, we had some rather messy acts before you.
Yes.
I was legit concerned.
We could not.
Oh, Paul was worried the entire time.
I was going to have your wheel at the end of the show.
All he was thinking about was your wheel at the end of the show.
I'm kicking banana husks and goop and pieces of lettuce and tomato off the
side of the stage.
I'm like, fuck.
You should have brought a sandwich onto the stage in the first place.
Banana, tomato, and lettuce.
You even added a criteria that would made it even more difficult for me to
perform. So thank you guys so much.
You literally did a banana peel.
What's funny?
Tell me one thing funnier.
That's exactly it.
I was, I was like, this is, this is, this is the shit show.
This is what it's going to be.
It's perfect for the world of Mack and fro.
Cause the world of Mack and fro he's, he's, he's on the, he's on the outs.
You know,
Yeah. If you're not, if you're not frustrated,
if you're not the butt of the joke, then it doesn't really work.
Great. Yeah.
Yeah.
The more obstacles you can put on in front of Mack and fro.
What is the seer wheel tiny stage record?
Do you know or do you have it?
I mean, really, did that to me? But I mean, seriously, is there anybody that performs seer wheel on a smaller space than eight feet? Do you I mean, talk, get a hold of Guinness are you asking Jonas is someone dumber than him? Is that what your eyes? No, it was fucking it was fucking fearless. It was producers less considerate than us. That's what Paul is asking. I know that I know the answer to that. I fucking know the answer to that. But it was great. And yeah, it was just so cool to see.
And I was legit worried, but it went off.
Though there is the world record for seer wheel performance does not currently have a smallest stage category.
Okay, however, oh, the minimal the minimum space generally required for a professional artist is 15 foot by 15 foot.
Look at that. You math wiz is out there might notice that that is bigger than eight. Yeah, I didn't know that we were actually the measure how professional we are, which is we are 56% professional.
Well, we've got that shit on video. You can just you can just send that into into Guinness and be done with it.
It is now that you've challenged me, I'm going to do it. I think about this all the time where I think my kids who want to go to college, I've said this on the on the podcast many times as like or I have said, or they can learn the seer wheel and just work the rest of their lives, right?
Training for the seer wheel. Do you do you accidentally at least once crush your fingers on the wheel?
Yes. Oh, I did it. Oh, that's the only thing that bothers me when I think about it all the time. I feel like it has to be more than once.
No, it's like Johnny dangerously one.
And then that's the lesson learned, huh?
And it's it's it's when you do the coin spin. So you're like, you're you're you're spinning like a coin. Yeah, and you're kind of kind of wobbling down to the ground. Yeah, yeah.
Back with your with your head like throwing down to the stage and coming back up and you're letting you pushing the wheel and you're grabbing and pulling it up and you're pushing it and pulling it up. And yes, that is the trick that everyone inevitably will crush their fingers on. That's the one I crushed my fingers on.
And then I learned, I learned how not to do that trick.
When you crush your fingers with it, is it is it just painful or does something usually break?
No, just, you know, just put a little ice on it. Just paint. OK, good. Yeah. Or just like, you know, slamming your finger in a car door. This isn't like the story of our all seer wheel artists don't have fingernails or something.
Because when I first watched that act, I always thought I thought, are there designs where there are handholds inside the wheel or anything? Or was that like an early on?
Some people do that, but it's very rare. I think it's it's just the simplicity of having a ring that's so
Right. You don't have to. Yeah, it makes it clear you don't need any any excess stuff. It's just like the the the focus is on the figures that you're creating with your body as opposed to
Your eye getting distracted by some kind of unnecessary thing. It's just like the German wheel that you mentioned earlier, like your hands are inside of two rings in the in the German wheel already. So there's already kind of an apparatus that does that anyway.
Yeah, it's it's it's very German and efficient in that way.
Like, this is Rebecca. Oh, Rebecca.
She got unmuted because she had to answer. We, we, it reminds me of contact. Remember the spaceship and the scientists decided that they had to have a seat in the spaceship, but didn't need a seat. So you're probably right. It makes it a much more elegant beast when it doesn't have the extra constructs in it. You're right.
That's exactly the the analogy I was going to use. And also the wheel I saw that had handholds on it. It shook so violently when the guy was using it.
I also have a theory in that in that that I spin left. So I'm spinning counterclockwise. Okay. And I'm getting I'm is that a choice.
It's just the way that Danielle spin when he taught me. He spun left. Some people spin right. But I spin left and I have I have a theory that that keeps me young.
Oh, you're Supermanning it.
Turning back time. Yeah, that's right. You're running the car reverse. Take the miles off. Taking that odometer back.
So your show you do two nights.
Yes. So I'm doing two nights November 21st and 22nd at the Vegas Theatre Company. It's called the Mac and fro show. And then I'm also doing the Mac and fro show in LA. Okay, at the legion theater, which is going to be December 3 at the legion.
It's a big hub for
Comedy. Also, the same exact show. It's going to be my debut in LA on December 3. No clown is huge right now in LA. Like it's very. Yeah, it's blowing up on the internet too. I follow like three or four very specific strange clowns on Instagram.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. And that's kind of the hub is at the legion. So I'm going to go I'm going to take my clown to go meet their clowns. Nice. Oh, that's going to be so fun. That's awesome.
Is there a website or anything that people can see the dates and times on and maybe buy tickets.
Yes, for Vegas. It's theater spelled in the British way T H E A T R E dot Vegas. And then for the legion theater. I believe it's a legion E L Y S I A N theater spelled the American way dot com.
Still, we fight over tea and how to spell theater. That's just the way it goes. Up with that. Let's just figure that out.
Also, we should decide right now. Should we should we just make this call right now. I always default to the British spelling. It looks more elegant. I also do R E. Matt, do you do R E or E R. Motherfucker.
And I just like jersey trash. I mean, I just had a petition of Toby Keith to the halftime show. The zombie body of Toby Keith. This happened to me this week. I'm bringing up a real thing. Yeah, that's real. They're going to AI him as the halftime.
No, there's a petition to make him be the halftime performer. Performers in American but has tan skin and speak Spanish. There's a legit petition to have Toby Keith instead. Yes, because the NFL is going to listen to a petition of 50,000 bigots. You have to you have to you have to say yes to that. You have to you have to look. I understand being a bigot. I don't understand spending your effort on the halftime show.
I don't understand burning these calories to be a more effective bigot. There's so many other companies that have DEI policies. Why are you going to the Super Bowl? There's so many ways to be a bigot where you're you'll affect a group of people. This case, you're only affecting bad buddy. And he's already doing very well. Yeah, exactly.
I went to Home Depot this week to get a piece of hose. I needed a piece of hose and it needed a very specific diameter for this hose. And I was like, I think it is a seven eights or I know I think it's a 7/16 rather. And so me and me and the guy we find 7/16 so we find a piece of 7/16 hose. I have a little piece of hose that I brought with me and I hold them up and they don't match.
The 7/16 is a little big. Let's drop down to 3/8. So we find a 3/8 hose. Paul, this is all math. Don't worry about it. I'm not worried. We find a 3/8 hose. And sure enough, it is a little small. So somewhere between these two 16th of an inch is where the hose that I have is. And I say to the to the guy, I go, maybe it's metric. Do you think it could be metric? And he gets the most offended look on his face.
Genuinely. He goes, well, because I told him it was for an ice maker. He goes, did you buy it in the United States? And I kind of chuckled a bit like, well, sure. He goes, well, then it shouldn't be metric. And I thought he was joking. And I kind of played along with it. They get these metric things and they bring them into the things in the United States. And yeah, I bought this thing in the U.S. but who knows where it was made. You get it.
And he, to my horror, he didn't get it. Was not joking and continued on that conversation and felt very strongly that something that was purchased in America should have freedom units. It shouldn't be in metric.
Your first mistake was Home Depot. I mean, we got to boycott that fucking place.
Scuba Diver girls, right. It's George Strait, not Toby Keith. I got, I got George Strait. He's been dead a lot longer. Either way. Just speak English. You know what I mean? That's all we're saying. I'm going to get the artist wrong.
Speak English. Don't use metric. It was metric, by the way. It was 10 millimeter. This is what I mean. This is what I mean is like, OK, we have known that we've had an undercurrent of racism as part of our culture in this country for a very long time.
No, this is the problem. We thought it was only an undercurrent. But now it's becoming an overcurrent. And the fact that like this person literally is spending their emotions, being upset about metric units for metric, dude, it's metric.
You have things in this store that are metric. Look, it's just there's ways to build stuff. And yes, fuck Home Depot. They're the option. Correct me if I'm wrong.
But from the jump, feet as a measurement started as being measured by the Royals foot length. So if you're sticking to feet, I thought it was a Roman thing.
No, it was the length of the length of the king's foot. So you're telling me that you're down a mile is something like a Roman thing, I think.
I don't know. But but I know with feet, it was and it changed from king to king. So you're just telling me your measurement system is so fucking crazy and it all depends on one dude's fucking feet.
So you're going to just bow down and kiss the foot. That's what you're telling me.
Literally in the chat is telling me that a mile is not the length of a king's foot. So sorry, sorry, Rich Scoop for clearing that up. Well, I mean enough inbreeding. You never know what you're going to get. Oh, I forgot I forgot my crown. Let me turn around.
No, no, no, no. Sideshow Bob to the extreme. Anti-royal anti-fascist metric system is actually the way to go. That's what I'm saying. Absolutely. Yeah, absolutely. It comes down to more democratic to use the metric. Far more democratic.
Actually, Paul and I saw Kirk Brattler do a bit to stand up about the way to convince Americans, like the metrics, the more is by start submitting our dick length in centimeters, then everyone's going to feel like a lot better.
Do you want a three inch dick? Or do you want an 18 centimeter cock? That was the bit is really good.
I'll tell you who else wants an 18 centimeter cock. And that's the following sponsor.
I'm sure that math is completely wrong. Don't convert Paul's math on that. Today's show is brought to you by Gregorius Griffin's Gardening Gadzookeries. That's right. That's from Danny Olwein in 2021. Gregorius Griffin's Gardening Gadzookeries.
Hey everyone, it's me, Gregorius Griffin. Are you here for gardening? Well, Gadzooks, I've got the gear. You go ahead and grab a garden weasel and get to scrubbing. Scrub out all them weeds, scrub them with your hands and your fists, twist it and pull it.
The gardening Gadzookeries will clear up and open ways and pathways for the seeds to take root, don't you know? Make sure that they're planted in rows. Rows are where it's at. And make sure you measure it with the metric system.
You don't want feet of crops. You want metrics of crops. Think about it.
Do you want a foot of cabbage or a meter of cabbage? Get right. Make your crops more metery.
Enter Hayes Group's checkout. Jonas, did you ever finish your documentary? Did you ever finish the doc that you were shooting?
No, I didn't. I wound up making a short doc on it.
But that's funny because the sideshow troupe is the Bindlesit Family Circus in New York City. If anybody out there in New York probably knows who those guys are. And they actually hired me 20 years later to do a gig for them.
Oh, funny.
After I left Cirque du Soleil, which I performed in Zumanity for 10 years, I've been freelancing since about 2019.
And nobody was like, hey, where's that doc, buddy? Where's that film?
They did ask for the footage, though. And I was like, you know what? I'm not going to make this into a film. But so you guys, please have this for your for your archive.
So they copied all the raw footage and everything. And back when we were shooting on tape. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Back in the day.
Now, Scott, was your gig for the Sultan one of the craziest gigs you've ever done?
Yes. So I was on that gig with Daniel Sear and one other performer, a woman by the name of Valerie. And it was in Oman. And we were treated like royalty from the get.
Like, I literally if I wanted to like a legit massage, I want to massage like any time of the day, I could have one.
I literally did two back to back 90 minute massages on the open of Oman's dimes.
Well, they got a lot of oil out there for the massages. That's the whole thing. That's that's it. It's all oil.
A lot of you were like Kobe beef by the time you went out there from the marble.
So it was the randomest thing. It was it was for a Toyota dealership opening, which I guess Toyota trucks are like big in in the middle East trucks, which is random.
But anyways, we're like, OK, we're opening this dealership. And they hired Sear Wheels. And and about an hour before the show, this massive sandstorm kicked up and like like biblical.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, no. And so we were on stage in these white, flowy outfits that were the giant sales.
While you're in your Sear Wheel. While we're in the Sear Wheel getting blown around, that's exactly what you didn't really have to do any effort to move.
You just kind of go with the wind. That made it much easier, much easier.
We were getting blown in one direction, like off the stage. And Sear literally got blown off the stage.
Oh, my God. Yeah. Were they OK? What happened? Not happy.
I know they're still they're still rolling. It's terrible. It's the worst thing that can happen to a Sear Wheel artist.
They know that's how they also disappear. And he just kind of like rolled away.
Yeah. But yeah, so like we get blown one way.
And then like I'm doing actually two people in one in one wheel with this woman, Valerie.
And we're spinning together and getting blown like towards as if we're getting blown off stage.
And we had to like find a way to maneuver ourselves to get back towards the center.
And you had more than eight feet to work with at that point still.
Thank goodness. Goodness sakes.
Yeah, there's at least nine feet on that stage. Wow. That is that's bananas.
Yeah, that was the wild one. That was the wild one.
So people were staying there in the sandstorm to watch the performance.
Yeah, but I didn't see them.
I really could not see the audience. I think they were there.
I was assured later that they very much enjoyed a full sand out.
Now, what's it like with the sand underneath? I mean, that's also a slippery kind of thing, right?
Was that even? Yeah, I mean, it was not it was not good.
It wasn't quite scoops level conditions, but sand, more grit than old tomato hunks.
OK, the sandstorm was not quite as bad as scoop vest. It was close.
Did they did they did the sound affect the performance, too?
Because I know when those things comes in, it's all that it did.
You can't you can't hear anything. Yeah. It's that it did.
He honestly waited longer to make that joke than I expected.
And thank you. Thank you. I'm I'm I'm nothing.
You're not patient. Start that song and then just like stop it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's how the town knows it's coming.
That's the seven air horn. Yes.
Yeah, you're just walking around all seizure.
What? What? Oh, no. Oh, no.
I'm going to get inside. Oh, shit.
Was that it? Oh, yeah, that's definitely coming.
And that song gets me pumped up. It's a great song.
It's a great song. You know, pumped up to hide from sandstorms.
We should we should write some lyrics to it on this.
I don't think I could do that. I don't think I could do that.
And you think that those are the lyrics.
I guess. That's it. Yeah, I love it. Sandstorm.
Yeah, sandstorm. And yeah, it's been just been
some crazy wheel gigs.
You know, I toured with the Dresden Dolls and, you know, that that band
from the 2000s. Yeah.
Sort of cabaret, punk duo.
And I performed in the on a U.S. tour with them.
So I had to clear out tire like rock venues, like the floor of the rock venue,
the pit area, and then I would do Sear Wheel in in in rock venues and stuff like that.
And that's always fun to do. I love I love rock clubs.
I performed at the Roundhouse in London with with them and cleared out the pit
and did Sear Wheel in there. That was fun.
So this is really taking you literally all over the world.
Yes. Yes. I have five continents.
That's so cool. I prefer five continents.
Yeah. Which one? Which two are you missing?
Australia. Australia.
That seems like an easy one to get. You should be able to get one of those.
Yeah. You know, I love I love Australia.
I was honestly before I before Cirque hired me to move to Vegas.
I was going to move to Australia and just overstay my visa and marry an Australian.
Just do that. No problem.
Yeah. That's just, you know, that's what you do when you're a vagabond circus
carny. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And then and then I say also France, even though it's not a continent,
France, the theaters in France always had like lovely cheeses,
like really stinky French cheeses laid out on the board of stinky French cheese.
And and France, I think I think I not only spent all my per diem,
I may have spent most of my salary on food in France.
That's fair. That's pretty fair.
That's fair. The food is better over there.
I hear good things. You should go theater re in France, too.
That's why Matt will not perform at those theaters.
Is that the best kind of pre sear wheel move to cheese up?
Is it does that help you?
Oh, yeah. You don't want to you don't want to be flowing free while you're spinning
around that sear wheel. You want to you want to clog that shit up.
I guess that's true. You want to be bound up like a cat in a cage before you hit that wheel.
One thing, the fun thing to do is to chug a bunch of water.
Oh, shit. And then do a coin spin and then just feel the water sloshing around in a circle.
Oh, you hate that. I honestly so much.
I honestly thought for a second you were going to tell me you pissed while you did it.
That would have been wild, like some kind of avant garde design that you make on like a canvas.
Do a sear wheel on a camera. Have you done it with paint?
Have you made like sear wheel art yet on a giant paint?
Now, let's skip over the urine, but let's go back to it.
Let's think about paint. We could we could use the wheel on a giant canvas.
I don't know. I don't know why Paul is naysaying my art here.
I have I have tried with with paint on the wheel.
It's a little slippery, so you can't really do very much.
You can create patterns of that.
I've also drank a glass of wine while spinning in the wheel, holding the wine at the same time.
The wine glass, you kind of have to tilt it ups because, you know, the the G force is taking it out.
So you can tilt the glass and drink it like that.
Well, that's fine. Drink a beer or two.
You know what you're spinning as well.
Since you've worked with Sear himself, does he have like pet peeves?
Has he seen people do stuff with the wheel that he considers an abomination or anything like that?
Oh, no, he's actually really just impressed.
And, you know, Sear is very impressed with the way the discipline has been expanded upon
and just completely taken to really wild, wild lengths,
doing things that we never could have imagined when we were first starting the discipline.
There's some things that the kids do nowadays.
And I'm like, yeah, that won't work on a scoop stage.
Does he have the market corner?
Does he have some merchandise yet? He needs some merch, right?
Does he not have a searing is believing T-shirt yet?
Because that's no, you've got to have it.
I know, I know. He's he's he's kind of like been in the shadows.
He kind of like made this thing, made his just circus discipline.
Yeah. And then kind of like just dropped in a couple.
Yeah. He kind of did the show that I was working on.
He did a couple. I did a Cirque show as well.
Corteo, he designed that act and then he kind of just like was like like like Homer Simpson.
Like my work here is done.
I have accomplished all that I need to.
Yeah, he was a wonderful, wonderful mentor.
And this is what what a what a right place, right time.
You know, honestly, like I just it's just when you hit it just reminds me like to whenever I'm kind of
need to make a choice on what I want to do on something, a creative project, whatever.
I'm just like, what is the what is the best possible scenario?
What what what what what's the thing when I have a vision or an inspiration hit me?
I really got to follow it to its to its conclusion because you never know what can come from that.
You know, literally, I have had a 22 year circus career based on one, seeing clowns in Cirque du Soleil,
Dralian, a clown troupe called Les Voila that inspired me.
It was like, oh, God, clowning. That's it. Yeah, of course.
Duh. I love Charlie Chaplin. I love Buster Keaton.
Like I'm going to I'm going to be a clown.
And then the second sort of lightning flash was seeing Daniel Sear perform and being like that Sear wheel.
Yeah, that's amazing. Like really to just hone in on my intuitive sense of like what's going to inspire me,
what's going to what's going to make me what's going to fulfill my soul?
You know, like what's going to what's what's the thing that's going to make me passionate to get out of bed in the morning and and or not sleep and travel, you know, halfway across the world and do a show.
John McEnroe, John McEnroe is the answer to that question.
Well, I I got a friend.
I got a friend in mime, no relation, Lauren Saul and Lauren got to work with Marceau before he passed.
And like, I feel like you've got kind of a similar thing here now that you are a direct line from Sear into this unique art form.
So have you already been approached by people?
Are you are you an instructor at this point in that way?
Are you are you leaning into that kind of bearing of the torch for this art form now?
I definitely can instruct.
I do private lessons for people that want to I'm really more into the creation side of it.
I've realized that I'm not really teaching for me is is it's cool, but I much rather make a one man show.
Sure. You know, a character based one man show.
That's where I like my I find my passion.
I mean, I am going to have you teach my children just so that just to save me on college money.
Just really don't want to go to college. At this point, it's as good an option as anything.
It really is. No, for real. Like, that's the thing is like you can like and you can go to circus college in Montreal.
They have the Ecole Nationale de Cirque, which is it's a university.
It's in Montreal. And if they are passionate about circus, kids who are 18 can audition.
Well, I'm one who's not passionate about anything, so I feel like I am going to be sending him to that school just because I find a passion there.
Yeah, for sure. Like it's such an amazing program.
I actually funny thing I auditioned for the National Circus School of Montreal the same week I auditioned for Cirque El Oise.
So I had two intense days of auditioning for the National Circus School of Montreal back in 2003.
And then also I had three intense days that turned into four because I got a callback for Cirque El Oise.
You grew up in New York, right? Yeah, originally in New York City.
Was anyone in the circus starts or anything like that when you were growing up?
No, we had we had Ringling Brothers, Barman Bailey Circus every year, which I would go see at Madison Square Garden and we had the Big Apple Circus.
Yeah. All right. But all these circus performers were like of circus families, right?
So everybody was they had generations of circus knowledge.
Our friend is ringmastering the Big Apple Circus right now.
That's right. Red Alters, Red Alters. So I just saw that.
That's amazing. Yeah. So happy him.
And so I figured out I didn't figure out that circus could be a possible thing that I could do.
I literally until I was 25 and I was like, oh, there's a clown program at that's amazing.
Like, let me let me let me audition for that.
And I think that's the whole movement of new circus. Right.
And and Cirque du Soleil is like you can have diverse you come from diverse backgrounds.
So a lot of the house troupe comes from gymnastics. Right.
You can have a soloist that comes from the dance world that then trained in circus.
Like, it's it's actually to your benefit to have an to have a new family history.
The contrary to popular belief. Yeah.
Yeah. No, it's like it's a it's a whole new world where you can train yourself in
in a year or two or maybe more, depending and really get to a high level of circus.
There is there is a whole new breed of circus artists out right now that are doing what he's talking about.
This is a brand new thing. It's really great.
Social media has done that. It's like it has to the magic world.
Right. Is the reason why magicians are finally a more diverse group of people.
We're not like going like what a woman doing a magic trick is.
I still say that. Come on.
But yeah, that's one of the one of the many positive aspects of the Internet is
one of the three positive aspects of the Internet.
It's more people are getting into circus arts.
That's pretty cool. Well, Jonas, we'll send people to theater Vegas.
The other Ari Vegas or the at least inside if you go see them in L.A.
What do people follow you in general?
Because you travel, obviously, you travel over the world, perform over the world.
Yeah, you can follow me on Instagram.
That's usually where I put all my shenanigans at Zoo Punk Cirque.
So it's spelled Z-U punk P-U-N-K Cirque C-I-R-Q-U-E.
OK, I'll put it in chat for anybody.
Yeah, we'll put in the bio of the episode as well.
OK, perfect. Yeah, that's Instagram is usually where you can find information about Mac and Fro Show.
I'm also in puppetry of the penis.
We didn't even get to that. Right. Oh, right.
Yeah, sure. That has its own.
There's literally puppetry of the penis as an ice cream cone.
Well, ice cream. Next Scoop Fest.
We I mean, we know we know a lot of puppetry of the penis people.
Like I'm buddies with Jamie and well, you know, Jamie, of course, too.
And you know, you know, he hired me.
Well, you know, tons of puppetry.
Well, we had the original, the guys that came out here.
Barry and Mike and Rich. Yes.
They did our first Scoop Fest.
Yep. And it was really funny because there was two hundred people laughing, applauding and one person
who just turned and looked at a wall during that performance.
It was awesome. It was amazing. Yeah, they couldn't.
It was a fascinating wall in my defense.
That paint was nearly dry.
I got to watch that paint just completely dry.
It was amazing.
I still remember because, you know, Scoop Fest, we just say like, hey, if you want to do a slot, do whatever.
We just want you to do it. You just tell us what you want to do.
And so they said yes to doing it.
And then I never clarified what they were going to do.
And so before the the show, I was like, I don't know what you guys want to do.
We guess if you guys feel comfortable where you're at or like how much longer of a slot do you want, blah, blah, blah.
They go, oh, we're ripping our dicks out.
I go, OK, OK, OK.
And that was the full conversation.
That was it. OK.
The most important question of today is how much space did they need to whip their dicks?
Yeah, see, it was 16 by 16 foot stage.
Yeah. Get us on the horn, folks.
They had so much room for activities.
Metric, Metric 16 by 16.
15 meter for all all you listeners out there that can't see this podcast.
I'm making the hamburger right now.
I like that you're like you saw I must do the clown.
You saw the sewer. I must do the cereal.
You saw the hamburger. I must make ships in the shape of my penis.
I must. I must do it.
It was already doing it, right?
And then I get paid, sure.
It's like every man's dream to get paid.
Now, how often do you do that show?
That's Thursday through Sunday in Vegas at the Erotic Heritage Museum.
OK. 8 o'clock show Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
OK. And then I'm also at the Wizard of Oz
doing this really cool immersive
experience after the after the movie at the Sphere.
I like right now there's some listeners who are like, yeah, whatever.
I'm just going to go see him play with his dick.
Like Wizard of Oz, sure, but I'm going to go to the dick thing, I think.
I mean, it's it's the last one of its kind.
Like they, you know, it's it's it's holding on as we're celebrating
10 years of puppetry of the penis in Vegas.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the Wizard of Oz at the Sphere.
Although I do have to make a couple of jokes about,
you know, in puppetry about Wizard of Oz, I'm like, well,
you know, you had all these choices in entertainment and you decided to come to
you could have went to the Wizard of Oz at the Sphere.
You chose this. That is it.
A different kind of flying monkey, that's all.
Choose your flying monkey.
Oh, you got to come up with a new a new cock and balls trick
called the flying monkey in honor of the Wizard of Oz.
Oh, I'm we got Halloween coming up.
I'm trying to like, yeah, this week, I figured out what the best trick would be.
Well, yeah, you guys do the batwing, right?
You could do batwing.
Yeah, I want to maybe the vampire.
Like I've got these teeth. He's going that are.
There you go.
I'm trying to I'm trying to work that into the show for the Halloween
for on Friday, the dick that sucks itself.
The vampire.
Healing. You can have it.
Take it. Take it.
I want that show to run forever.
I have news for you.
Paul's not going to do it. I'm not.
Although if you want me to open for cock, you could.
And some one of these that had to develop some kind of stand up bit.
Yeah, something I could just these guys are going to do the hamburger later on.
I can only do the slider.
I need to go back to my ventriloquist days.
I need to get a ventriloquist bit worked up.
That's what I need to do.
And honey, I need to move back to Vegas.
That's important work.
Yeah, I really got to go.
And yeah, I know we just repainted the house and we're loving our life out here.
Time for me to go play with my dick.
You'll support me, right?
As long as I don't have to.
OK, great, great, great.
Somebody said the Marilyn Manson trick.
Oh, I don't know. Is that for a dick trick?
Is that just sucking your own dick?
Oh, that's the way you cut your ribs out.
That that whole David Gahan from Preshmo.
Do that to the legend.
Yeah, urban legends. Yeah.
Well, we're about to descend into a bunch of Halloween bits,
so you're welcome to run away at this point if you want to go live your life.
I'll stick around because I'm going to practice my my vampire trick.
Oh, good, good, good.
I'll tell you who else is going to practice their new vampire
dick and balls trick while we wait.
And that's the following sponsor of today's show.
Men, men, this social is brought to you by Black Hole Baby Diapers
from Teddy Officer Scoop, also in twenty twenty one.
That's Black Hole Baby Diapers.
Hello, it's me, Carl Sagan.
I'm here from beyond the grave to tell you about the billions
and billions of infants shitting and pissing themselves throughout the nation.
The high time that you buy them the proper undergarments.
What I have is Black Hole Diapers.
What these will do is, of course, open a rift in space time
that we're not really certain what's on the other side of it.
But the piss and shit of the children will get instantly sucked into it,
spaghettified into the tiniest, smallest form that it can be
and thrown into some alternate dimension or whatever.
Again, it's all theoretical.
We don't know what lies on the other side.
However, we can, with some assurance, state that on the other side
of our black hole diapers, there's a great quantity of piss and shit.
Go ahead and buy these black hole diapers for your children.
Make sure that they don't sit directly on the hole.
That's the trick.
You don't want to spaghettify your babies or maybe some of you do.
I don't know this demon haunted world.
It's enveloping all of us.
Why not let it envelop your piss and shit from your children?
Do the environmentally sound thing and send all the piss and shit
from your babies into the nether regions of time and space.
That's Black Hole Diapers from Carl Sagan.
Enter hate scoops at checkout.
Well, let's see what. Oh, oh, oh, my.
My Uber Eats is here.
Hold on. I just have to go get my Uber Eats here.
It's oh, my Uber Eats driver.
It's vampire Bill Cosby.
Well, what do you know? What do you say?
How you doing? Hey, hey, hey, well, it's Bill Cosby.
I'm here to give you what you ordered from the store on some things.
Oh, thank you for sundries.
Oh, you have what you need.
Theo is dead.
Boo. He's a ghost this year.
Yeah, that's right. He came with me.
He's right here. This is my son.
Leo, who's a ghost now.
He's going to scare the fuck out of you.
That's what he does.
That's scaring you. Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
Was he scared?
Well, you should be good.
I'm glad you scared of my ghost son who died in the ocean
trying to save his baby, but he did.
And he did. Oh, boy, it's too bad.
It's a terrible thing.
I well, well, thanks for coming by.
Thanks for bringing my my groceries.
I'm never going to miss a chance to come and hang out during.
This is my favorite holiday.
It's all the holiday I get released.
It's not true. I'm free man now.
I can do whatever I want.
That's right. No.
No jail can hold the cause.
Oh, that part will cause me.
I'm so sorry I have to answer the story here.
Well, I'm going to turn into a bat then.
Poof. Goodbye. Flap, flap, flap.
I'm gone. Oh, that's too bad.
He would have really loved to have met our next guest.
It's actually Piff the Magic Dragon. Piff, come on in.
Right. I'm a magician, isn't it?
Hey, what do you want? We got some free candy for me, mate.
Oh, come on in. Where's your grub?
Give it over. I want some M.P.A.Y. days, right?
Yeah, I'm a dragon. Yeah, I mean, here's some candy.
Yeah, too. Right. I'm going to sit on a hoard of candy.
Uh, Piff, I just want to congratulate you.
Uh, your 10 year anniversary is coming up soon.
Ten years of being a Las Vegas headliner.
It's got to feel pretty good, huh, buddy?
That's right. It's a decade of decades for Mr. Piff the Magic Dragon.
What, what, what, what, what? I'll be entertaining everybody.
Can't nobody hold me down.
Hey, look, guess what I'm going to do?
I'm going to make all you bitches disappear.
Poof. Where'd Chris Angel go? Oh, fucking no, do I?
I'm taking over his spot. Yeah. That bitch is off. Done.
I'm the king. One king.
Are you still going to use the wind machines and blow garbage on people?
I mean, I wouldn't be much of a dragon if I didn't blow off people
with some fire and stuff. That's kind of what I'd do.
That's fair. That is fair. That's right.
And you're going to be touring next year with, with Penn doing Piff and Pop.
You say so.
No, I do say so. It's happening.
All right. I'll take you word out. Oh, no.
At least I got top billing, didn't I? What? Isn't it?
It sounds like you need some, maybe some, some legal advice
on how to deal with this tour coming up with, with Penn here.
I don't know. I don't think so.
I think, I think this whole sale, I got top billing.
That's all I need. Oh, somebody else here.
I'll bet. Runway. No, no, this is great.
Stick around and chat with.
This is our friend, the forgetful goldfish lawyer.
Maybe the forgetful goldfish lawyer can help you out a little bit.
What is it you need?
Piff wants to make sure that he understands he's protected
in this tour, that he's coming up with Ben Gillette.
OK, let me look into my briefcase here.
Well, it looks like all I've got in here is tetra flakes.
What were you asking me again?
You want to if you want to pick the magic dragon as a client.
Who's that now?
He's a magician in Las Vegas.
What's your name, sir?
Oh, I'm Matt. I'm the co-host of this podcast.
OK, let me go ahead and call somebody.
I've forgotten all the phone numbers.
Well, OK, well, OK, that's that's what goldfish do.
We just forget. I understand.
What you forgot something, I forgot to breathe for about a minute there.
Oh, no. Oh, gosh.
It happens. Yeah. Yeah.
But, you know, you don't have to make any calls now.
I just want to know that you're, you know.
I'll tell you what I don't want is this fucking idiot
representing me for anything.
It's a bullshit.
This is a great lawyer, Piff.
The fuck he is.
I'll tell you, I only think he's got in common with the law.
He's got the scales of justice. That's about it.
He can fend his way right out of here.
Go on swim away, you dumb bitch, isn't it?
Oh, the lawyer is leaving.
That is that is horrible.
He was upsetting.
It's hard to see. Oh, he just he ran into a light post.
Oh, my God. Oh, you're fucking idiot.
He is. I'm going to go chase him.
I will see you later, Piff.
Thanks. Thanks for coming by.
Bye, Piff. Happy holidays. Fuck all of you.
Wow. Jesus.
He's got really, really a cervic over these 10 years.
That was that was by far the most.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's changed. It's gone to his head.
All that all that success, all that instant ease.
All that all that gold and princesses.
It's really gone to his head.
You know, being a Las Vegas headliner is so easy.
It's all gone to his head. So easy.
Well, it's been a good week, everybody.
How do you guys have a good week?
I had a great week. Are you asking me?
I am. Sorry. Yes, I was asking you.
And then three notifications somehow popped up on my screen
all at the same time.
It really distracted me.
I got to rewatch Groundhog Day this week.
Oh, yeah. That's a Groundhog.
Yeah, it was on over and over again.
And it really struck me how much faster he accepted
that the day was happening over and over again to him
than I believe I would have in that situation.
Oh, he's just like the second day.
He's like, Oh, I guess this is happening.
Yeah, I've got it.
He really just kind of took it all in stride pretty well.
I watched on the plane. I watched Sinners.
Oh, yeah. How was that?
Love it. It's a vampire movie.
But I don't know if you I don't think anyone's talked about this.
There are some like racial undertones to it.
Oh, boy. I just I was very subtle.
I picked up on it.
Interesting.
You know, I saw some stuff in the trailer that made me think
that that might be part of what they were going to talk about.
But I but I couldn't really tell.
Yeah, I saw no seeds until I watched the movie.
I was like, wait a minute. So good.
I fucking love Sinners.
It's a great it's really good.
Michael B. Jordan is so good. He. Yeah.
What when they really kind of
really try to anchor the whiteness of the vampires,
they do it with specific kind of like Irish music.
And I felt like a little a little a little attacked then.
Not the white part, but the Irish part, the Irish part.
As you should. Wait a minute.
But yeah.
Oh, that is that is terrible.
Oh, gosh. Oh, oh, shit.
It's B. Arthur's candy cooter corn now with nuts.
That's a commercial, not a character.
I I agree.
These people are sneaking in extra commercials into our social media feed.
Picture it. Sicily, 1939.
My daughter's cooter is overflowing with waxy candy.
We should say that all these characters are submitted
by our listeners on all of our social media channels.
So these were all put on our Facebook and Instagram posts yesterday.
So if you're not following us on social media, we do the Halloween episode
and the Christmas episode where people stop by.
That's right. And we just pimp Paul all all episode.
That's right.
Who's next? Whoa, bring it says Paul.
Paul's like, wow, ring the bell, ring the bell, Jacob.
I could out of that cooter corn.
Holy shit, it's Ding Dong Mitch, the guy who doesn't understand
how to ding dong ditch.
Oh, hello. Hey, there, gotcha.
Hi, gotcha, gotcha.
What do you mean? What do you mean?
You answered the door.
Yeah, got you already.
Did you ring the doorbell again?
Might have been me. Got you.
We you. But what?
How did you get us? Yeah, I should.
Most people answer their doorbell. Hey, check, check this out. What's that?
Gotcha. No, I don't think that's how you get me, buddy.
We saw you ring it. I don't feel gotten.
Yeah. You understand? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, OK, OK. Like most.
There you go. Got you.
Because my doorbell works, is that how you got me?
Look, is there somebody at the door?
Yeah, you better go better go answer the door.
Hey, check it out. Hi.
Could be your other door.
OK, I'm going to check your other door.
Yeah, I'll go walk to my back.
Gotcha. It was this one.
It was this door.
Hey, hey, I hate this guy.
Still me, still me at your door.
Gotcha.
Gotcha. Ding dong, Mitch.
Basically, a force of nature over here.
Check it. All right.
Thank you. There you go.
OK, you're all right.
One more.
Gotcha. Bye.
I hate that guy. I'll see you in a little bit.
Mike in chat says he submitted characters on our Truth Social account.
Are you getting any? Are you reading from those, Jacob?
No, I've got I've got our Truth Social account pulled up here.
Yeah, I definitely I'm definitely reading all of those.
Oh, actually, from the Truth Social account, we have the woke truck driver.
Here he is.
Hey, God damn it.
Where's your pride flag?
Just they break down with the wind.
Oh, yeah. Oh, we got a little sun bleached.
Oh, I just I just didn't have time to put it up this year.
Well, eat shit.
Well, I was I was trying to.
Yeah, sure, sure, sure.
But I had to get to my my friends.
I'm going to my my friend's daughter's basketball game.
And so I wasn't able to get the flags up on time.
But I got to go right.
I'm sure your friend's daughter's basketball game, where I'm sure
they've talked a bunch of shit about trans athletes participating
and they haven't allowed some, isn't that right?
Outrageous behavior. Absolutely outrageous.
All right.
You know, trans rights are human rights, you piece of shit.
You know that, right?
Fuck you. OK.
Apparently, you don't know that.
Why don't you go eat your own shit, you non pride flag
having son of a bitch? Wow. OK.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
Well, apologize to my fucking fist when it goes to your head.
I will. Yeah, you better.
Do you want some candy?
Only if it's been made with LGBTQIA professionals.
OK, I want the gayest candy you can give me.
I have skills.
That is it. You win.
OK, all right. Back in.
Top of the day to you.
I'm going to taste the rainbow.
Sounds good. Have a good night.
Thank you. Thank you very much. You too.
Yeah. Thank you, both truck driver.
Yeah. Fuck y'all.
Oh, it's Truman Capote.
Truman, what brings you by?
Well, I'm just terribly excited and I was hoping there'd be some candy here.
Oh, that last guy just took the last of the Skittles.
That's all right.
Those don't feel nearly as good inside of me as a mounds bar does.
Sometimes you do feel like a nut.
I do every time.
Oh, that's all I'm enjoying. Sometimes you don't.
That's mounds. Fair enough.
Now, Truman is a movie out right now.
Springsteen was obsessed with the Nebraska, the murders of Nebraska.
You wrote the book In Cold Blood, right?
That's right. I did.
The Stark weather events, they were terrible tragedies,
but very American, if you know what I mean.
But ultimately, it's good that we're talking of this on Halloween
because it really comes down to the boy didn't get enough candy.
That's it. Oh, is that the that that was the root?
That's really the crux of it.
Yes. Stark weather was starved for some chocolate.
OK, well, that's a shame. That's good to know.
Yes. So, you know, is that something that could happen to future people
if they if they don't get enough Halloween candy?
Give your children lots of kisses.
Or they might murder people.
They might murder people.
Hershey it up every Halloween.
All right. Hashtag can't bury it up.
You had buried up, I should say.
You heard it from Trudeau.
Can't bury it up.
Did I can't bury the lead?
Now, Truman, did you get to see the Bruce Springsteen movie?
I certainly did see it was something.
What do you think? The boss is the boss.
Did you have a favorite moment in the in the film?
I enjoyed the credits rolling very much.
I like people to get their due.
My exit of the theater was lovely.
Yes, I appreciate seeing all the hard work that went into that mediocrity.
And it just reassures me that, you know, even when I'm working with Harper Lee,
you know, nothing's guaranteed.
Harper Lee, you know, I wrote that book, essentially.
OK, yes, what I was to say, thank you for coming by, Truman.
We appreciate it. You would say that.
Have a good night.
This is you did not see the Springsteen movie, is that correct?
I have not seen the Springsteen movie.
I'm actually going to watch it tomorrow.
OK, OK. We'll see if Paul and I did go see it together
the day of the day of the wedding and stuff.
I did get the re-release Nebraska album, though, that I've been listening to.
Oh, cool. And there's some gems on there. It's a fucking banger.
Yeah, no kidding around that re-release Nebraska.
I haven't listened because it's a multi album release.
And one of them is the him doing Nebraska at the Count Basie Theater.
Oh, I have that out myself.
Yeah. So it's really good.
I've listened to the to the 2025 remaster of it so far, and it is excellent.
I have a very exciting interview, actually, for you guys.
I haven't told you guys about it.
We're closing out the show with it.
The guests should be here any moment now.
This is really going to be exciting.
It could it could possibly be the last interview on Ice Cream
Social, depending on who is touched by who in this.
Oh, oh, good. They're here. They're here.
Ah, this is our guest for the end of the show here.
It is the death snail.
This is the snail that slowly crawls after all of us.
And if it touches us, we die. That's right.
So we have to we have to avoid being touched by this snail during this interview.
Thank you for coming by, snail.
I'm just going to start it walking towards your house last Thanksgiving.
Oh, well, I'm glad you could finally make it our way.
Are you aware that you were part of our
merchandise sales?
Our Kiss the Snail campaign is actually sold very well at our store.
Yes, I saw.
Boy, I hope I can one day afford a new shell.
Oh, sorry.
Is it a burden to kill everyone you touch?
Burden is a heavy word.
I do like my powers.
Oh, you like you kind of like being an arbiter of death.
When you're an incredibly slow moving mollusk,
you have few options in life.
But having the ability to kill things instantaneously
evens the odds a bit.
OK, I suppose it would.
I suppose it would.
Do you do you leave a traditional snail trail behind you after taking these lives?
It's somewhat traditional, but it has a design in it.
You know, that special S that people always make on their folders and things.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
That's what I leave behind me.
You leave the weird little S thing that looks the same, no matter how you look at it.
That's right, because I don't know if you're aware of this.
I'm also an automobile engineer.
I was not.
No, that's do you work for a specific dealership or anything?
No, I'm a self-employed.
I make my I'm kind of like, you know, make my own sort of deal.
You know, the tires have that S on it as well.
And, you know, that's to make the imprint very clear.
So when you drive one of my autos, everybody knows where your S car goes.
I want to thank Pinch, that's great.
This podcast, you see, I want to thank Jonas Overton for stopping by
and for staying around for this bullshit.
If we can't go out on an S car fun,
I don't know what we can do.
I look at that S car go.
I want to thank the following people.
All of these people crush their fingers just once.
Training on a serial.
That is Dan Dan 33.
Cup of Scoop, Chris Meyer, Cream City Scoop, Craig Little, Craig De Farmer,
Court Myers, Country Scoop, Councilor Matt, Corny Scoop, Coriann Ichimura,
Cone Photo Scoop Sector.
I think I said that right.
Colton Setmary, Colleen Fisher, Coffee Bean Scoop,
Coconut Time Travel, Coach Rat Bastard, Cloud in a Brothel,
Clayton Shoney and CJ Magnata.
The following people can hear a sandstorm coming from miles away.
Charles Dishecky, Charles Eaton, Cassie Rice, Carolyn Albert.
What are you doing with your tongue over there?
I can't. I can't keep up.
Captain James T.
Scoop, Canadian Scoop, Crystal, Cameron Hall.
Cali Ghost, Sea Wick, Buster Kamikaze, Brian Traves,
Brian McLeod, Brooks Lyle, Brian Richard, Brian Maddox,
aka an Arco Scoop, Brendan Allen, Brendan Light,
Brad Martin, Bobby Becerra and Bob.
The following people all got three hours of exotic
foreign massages with heavy oil and no happy ending. I promise.
Chronicler Scoop, Christy Salinas, Christopher Huff,
Christopher Heyworth, Christine Starr, Christine Elsesser,
Chris Melikon, Chris Kay, Chris Yorg, Chris Jackson,
Chris Fisher, Chris Ellis, Chris Bartzi, Chelsea Farr.
Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Charlie Thompson.
Thank you so much.
The following people have the same dreams as Jonas
to run off and join the three cock ring circus.
Bosen Scoop, Blue Line Scoop, Bill Beatty, Bike Scoop,
Big Sexy, the Digital Nomad, Big Loda Scoop,
Ben Sherman Scoop, Ben Smith, Ben Gow, Ben Dennis, Ben,
Belgian Triple Scoop, B.J.
Joyer, Bear Scoop and Bearded Scoop 3.
The following scoops all have giant penises
that are measured in the metric system.
That is B.B.
Hermit, Basecamp Scoops, Bart Vonk, Bad Pirate Scoop,
AWOL Scoop, Avin Zarls, Aramis Saar, Apple Scoop,
Anton Jernberg, Ant Foods, Angry Face Scoop, Angela Chan, Andy Cheek,
Andrew Ostrzok, Andrew Koenig, Andrew J. Hughes, Andrea Anderson,
Ameristat Scoop, All-Star Scoop, Alla Scoop 6666,
Akshay Mysore, A.J.B., Adam Stickney, Adam Goff,
Aaron Wintling, Aaron Boyd, Aaron, A Scoop of Root Canal,
a Ranch Slunk, One Small Scoop for Man, the Unbanned Scoop,
We All Scream for Mark McLean, Underscore for Shaping,
the Micro Scoop and Signature Curl Scoop.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do appreciate you.
If you want to be thanked on air or get a myriad of other offerings that we do,
find a tier that fits your budget and support us today over at preachingfun.com.
Or if you don't like your wheels, Siri, you like them German.
Head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com.
It does take you over to our Patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
If you think this show is worth more than zero dollars, fartsinabag.biz,
preachingfun.com.
Those are the websites that you need to go to help keep this show on the air.
Do it now. It's kind of awesome.
I actually bake my wheels at a low temperature over a long period,
and I just sear them at the last minute.
Smart, smart. You do a reverse sear wheel.
I do a reverse sear wheel.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Did you buy this in America?
It should have American measurements on it.
I thought he was kidding. He wasn't.
We are in for a metric ton of bullshit. That's a lie.
We sure are. We're preaching fun.
Like they're going to sell tape measures and they like won't have the centimeters
on the top side of the thing. They'll be like, they're just crossed out.
They just took a sharpie to it.
Sharpie just blacked out, just cheap, just blacked it all out.
You motherfuckers. It's still blacked out.
I can't do the conversion in my head.
I need that. I need it on the tape. Damn.
Love you, everybody. See you.