Well hello there, I am so happy that you're here because I'm gonna thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. I don't have a new list yet, it's a new month but we're gonna thank each and every one of you this month by name.
So right now I'd like to thank every single person out there who is an ice cream truck driver.
What is an ice cream truck driver, I'm glad you asked. These are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I hope you do, head over to preachingfun.com.
Preachingfun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
The lice you crave can be extracted with a comb.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
C-O-M-B coo?
No, C-O-M-B coo.
Yeah.
They're floating there, Paul.
Just like some comedians say.
There's a bit about language that I can't remember.
Gallagher, bitches.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social, sitting somewhere, that's Matt Donnelly, sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly.
Jacob the audio guy, I'm sitting in Las Vegas.
We're preachingfun.
That's the one that goes into the bomb, right?
Boom and bomb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like a little flip card thing.
Boom.
Yeah.
Man, I know he became a crazy, crazy twit, but I loved me some Gallagher when I was younger, man.
Oh, I loved Gallagher.
Yeah.
Back in the video store days, that was it.
You wanted to watch a comedian, you ran into Gallagher movies.
Yeah.
I got really lucky later on, running comedy clubs in Las Vegas.
I got to work several, like a two or three weeks, all total, with Gallagher as one of the headlining comedians.
And man, the conversations in the green room when Gallagher is on are really pretty great.
When he's not there to hear what people are saying about him?
No, no, no.
When he's in there.
I'm saying when he's in the green room, when he's back there like holding court and having the conversations.
The crazy, like the bat shit crazy shit that gets talked about is spectacular.
He really lost it towards the end there.
And he developed a rep in Vegas for being a kind of like crazy ass lunatic.
He was trying to like come up with his own version of like a slot machine or whatever.
And he was trying to pitch a version of gambling.
And he was a really, really angry, bitter guy.
But just stand up, man.
And also like while he was angry and bitter, also stayed super interesting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like he was angry and bitter, but he had his shit together.
He was a compelling person. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. And like, as we all know, just from I think watching three minutes of any version of Gallagher stand up, he sees the world differently than most people.
Yeah, yeah.
And hearing from those people is always just fascinating.
And of course, yeah, we think we've done this a bunch of times, but he taught his brother his act.
Then his brother, then he tried to stop his brother from doing his act.
His brother said, no, I'm going to keep doing it.
He sued his brother.
Gallagher's manager took the brother's side and left Gallagher.
Yes.
That's really the most insulting part.
And the brother got the right to perform as Gallagher too.
I think there's nothing worse than thinking like, I could franchise this, finding out you're right.
And then you want to be like, no, wait, don't do it.
Hold on.
No.
When that genie's out of the bottle, forget it.
If anything, you just should have doubled down and gotten more apprentices, right?
Yeah.
Right. He should have gotten Gallagher three, Gallagher four.
Yeah, yeah.
Release Gallagher four.
Fire.
Yeah.
Also, none of the others should have looked anything like him.
Gallaghy.
They never should have acknowledged it.
Well, they could all have just all you got to do is put on one of them duffer hats with a long wig done.
That's right.
Matt's halfway there.
I'll do it.
I keep switching careers.
I should start doing Gallagher's routines.
Just add a wig to one of your hats, Matt.
I will.
I've always said that when I cut my hair off at some day, that I'll just all attach it to the hat and just keep it around every now and then.
And I've sincerely thought about that, and it just seems like so much work to add it to my hat.
Yeah, if you're not having it done professionally.
That just seems like a lot of genuine work.
Also.
Sewing pieces of hair onto a hat.
You're going to select one hat that you're going to be stuck with for life.
You've got to sew it into a Velcro type mechanism so that it can be attached to multiple hats.
You don't make a bad point there.
It's a fairly good point.
My vision has always been that I would just walk out with the hat on and then take the hat off, and it would just be the "Oh, Jacob doesn't have any hair."
That's kind of fun.
Of course, when I picture it, I picture myself being like egghead, completely bald as well.
I can tell you, Paul, I'm completely impressed by the Velcro thing.
I was thinking of just honing up for hair for each hat that you had.
Oh, my God.
Are you crazy?
I know.
Who has the money for that?
Actual human hair?
Rockefeller Donnelly over here.
You just saved imaginary Jacob, bald Jacob, hundreds and hundreds of dollars.
Yes, at least.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Jeff Loomis makes a good point in the chat.
Tapeface tried to do the franchising thing, and it really did not work well for Tapeface at all.
But he didn't do it.
He was being very surreptitious about it.
But so was Gallagher.
I think that Tapeface did exactly what Gallagher did.
I think he just didn't get away with it, and he did it in a different time.
So people were talking about it on social media.
A time without social media where you can't just go, "Hey, that's not the real Gallagher."
Yeah.
I don't know.
Tapeface, we actually would probably get Tapeface to come on.
I probably could, yeah.
The problem is, when he started more, I think it was like Fringe Festival stuff,
he started more theatrically as the boy with tape on his face.
He considered it more of a show then.
I think the problem was that he did "America's Got Talent"
and then became a singular character in that moment
and changed it from the boy with tape on his face to Tapeface.
And then still, in his mind, saw it theatrically, and so he could have an understudy or whatever.
Yeah.
From what I heard, it seemed like he was looking at it as though he were putting an understudy into a show,
not that he was doing anything nefarious.
Right.
I mean, I'm all for it.
I would love to have that kind of problem.
We'll have him on, and we'll talk about it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's going to be awkward next week when Jacob comes on and you guys don't recognize him.
Me, me.
Paul, could you imagine trying to sell people right now?
You're like, "Don't worry, I handpicked this person to train them to be funny like me."
To just have a substitute me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hand-chosen.
I mean, there's more than a handful of podcasters who could probably do it.
No, but this is exactly what we're talking about.
This is an A-to-A analogy.
Right.
Sure.
But they're just simply not personally invested in someone else who's capable.
Agreed.
Yeah, it is a weird thing.
It is a weird time for all of life on Earth and the parasocial relationships,
which are the only things keeping us going day-to-day.
Let's see, so if we wanted to build a new Paul, obviously it would have to involve small, small barky dogs.
Mostly peanut butter.
Raisins to taste.
That's your base.
Raisins to taste, always.
The Lead Mill of Sunrise.
Yep.
Black T-shirts.
MLKennedy says, "Having tapers on the podcast like ventriloquism on the radio," right?
Grow up, MLKennedy.
Grow up.
And yes.
Those were the days, right?
To be a radio ventriloquist?
Oh my God, what a dream.
What a dream that would have been.
Ugh.
Hey, Bert, how you doing today?
Oh, I'd be great if your hand wasn't up my ass.
Oh, Bert, you crazy so-and-so.
But you don't even have to do that.
You're the crazy one.
He doesn't even see that.
You don't even have to do that.
I can't believe you have the audio right there to play that authentic clip from the old days.
I can't believe you just played that clip.
I know.
Gold.
Mortimer's nerd was a real perv.
What are you going to do?
MLKennedy, thank you in the chat, says that my mouth was not moving.
If anybody listening asks.
It was gold.
That was legitimate just, what do you call it?
Throwing my voice.
Yeah.
That's right, that's right.
MarbleTulipScoopy says he could learn to love Paul number two.
I watched the special the other day.
There's a special somewhere, I forget where, but it's on the Astroworld Festival.
The Travis Scott Astroworld Festival.
Yes.
That he did several times.
Where lots of people got hurt.
Lots of people got hurt.
The crowd rushed the stage.
There were multiple people that were kind of in charge of the safety of the festivals.
A lot of people didn't do their jobs.
Were there some deaths?
I believe there were some deaths, like crushing deaths and that kind of thing.
At one point, according to the special, there were four active CPRs going on.
Four people were actively receiving chest compressions and everything.
And that did not stop the show.
Oh, CountryScoop, thank you, in the chat says that 10 people end up dying in there.
Goodness.
This is from when?
Travis Scott's thing.
This is several years ago.
Oh, okay.
He used to do the festival every year at Astroworld to give back to Houston, where he's from.
And I was watching this thing and I'm watching, a lot of it was lack of communication.
A lot of it was not telling Travis Scott on stage that things were going on.
Arguably, he was told.
I don't know.
There were a lot of things going on.
There were large parts, though, of this documentary where I was watching horrible things happen
with all these thousands of people there in Astroworld and running around like crazy people.
And I was just looking at this going like, "Holy shit, this could happen to us.
Holy shit."
Like, we could just accidentally make something huge like this and then it just totally gets out of control.
And all of us look at it at the end going like, "I'm so sorry."
Again, these are the problems you want.
Paul and I are big enough that just the two of us falling over could crush 10 to 12 people.
Sure.
Yeah, it's true.
Just.
True.
All right.
We should not.
We shouldn't cross off the trampling.
No.
Trampling.
Jake, are you having second thoughts about putting this steel cage around every side
of the stage this year for Scoop Fest?
Oh, if anything, I'm more on board with it.
Really.
The chicken wire from Blues Brothers.
Oh, my God.
That is the best.
That scene.
Good Lord.
That makes me laugh so much.
They just keep throwing beer.
Just throwing beer bottles at the stage.
Smash.
God damn.
So funny.
And it's great too.
I'm going to ruin this scene for people who watch Blues Brothers right now, but if you
watch it, you can just watch all of the sugar glass bottles explode.
Yes.
As soon as they hit.
Yeah.
Like the thin little chicken wire.
But they still get all over everybody.
It's still a mess.
Yeah.
We have both kinds, country and western.
It's true.
Oh, man.
Raw hide.
I watched a little bit of Monday Night Raw a couple of weeks ago, Paul.
Take him home.
Before we go, I really do think the loser leaves town match we've set up for two people
with the name I want to scoop, baby.
We should really think twice about it now.
It's going to create some real friction.
Stampede.
Go ahead.
There will be crushing deaths, but in the good way.
Yeah.
Careful what you ask for.
Have you watched any Monday Night Raw, Paul?
Here's the thing.
I listen to podcasts about wrestling.
Okay.
I haven't watched a wrestling match in probably two years.
Now that it's on Netflix.
Yeah.
I keep getting ads for it popping up on Netflix.
So you decided to go ahead and watch one.
Yeah.
The other day, I'm home by myself.
I'm perusing.
I'm looking for an option to watch without SJ around because we watch a lot of things
together.
So I have to do the math of like, what is she not going to be mad at me for watching
without her around?
Wrestling definitely won't be mad at me about that.
Good math.
Yeah.
So I turned it on for a little while.
It seems to me, I haven't watched wrestling in, I don't know how many years, decades,
multiple decades.
Long time.
Yeah.
It seemed to me, and tell me if I'm wrong or not, it seemed to me that there was a
lot more talking than there used to be.
Yeah.
And that the talking is much more contrived than I remember it.
Yes.
Now, is that me?
Am I right?
Or is that just me, child versus adult, looking at this?
No, you're right.
And if you saw the South Park from a couple of years back, they really nailed it where
it's more about a theatrical thing than anything else.
The wrestling is secondary at this point, which is so silly.
Yeah.
It's funny that you mentioned this.
Just today, I deleted a couple of my wrestling podcasts because I'm like, this is...
Oh, you're falling off.
Well, I mean, yeah.
Yeah, because...
Tariffs?
Triple H was...
Oh, sorry.
Triple H was in the White House just a couple days ago.
Oh, is that right?
Triple H was in the White House.
Oh, right.
Because what's her name?
McMahon.
I mean, she's been there.
She's like the secretary of something.
She's not, you know, she's not really directly connected to the company.
Education, that's it.
Sure.
She's not really directly connected to the company anymore, legacy-wise for sure.
But to have Triple H...
Well, because Vince is out, right?
Yeah.
Well, so they say.
Okay.
But they might be...
Yeah, yeah.
I saw something he might be coming back.
I don't know.
Who fucking knows?
He was at a big party.
I was at a party with Vince, and he was making me pee on someone just the other night.
Yeah?
Okay.
Well, maybe he's on his comeback tour.
Yeah.
I'm telling you not to invite Vince McMahon to your pee-on-people parties, Matt.
No.
Because he turns into a shit-on-people party.
That does.
That's the problem.
Matt, you have to put Visqueen down.
You're going to ruin your hardwood floors.
This is so hard.
My wife knows I'm hanging out with them when Visqueen gets delivered to my front door on
Amazon.
Yeah, but I just, I think for my own, you know, sense of self, I'm just like, eh.
Like, okay.
Even, it's just been, it's really been these last like two months.
Shit's gotten, shit's gotten kind of sketched for me.
Again, and I'm, and I'm only just listening to stuff and hearing, you know, watching a
few little things on YouTube and whatnot, recaps, things like that.
And I don't know if you're familiar.
Oh, wait, there's ML Kennedy saying Linda McMahon just got hacked at an interview.
Someone got into the audio when she was talking about Department of Education stuff and somebody
played the clown song.
Hilarious.
Oh, the entry of the gladiators.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's amazing, ML Kennedy.
That's fantastic.
Yeah.
Cause that's, that's how she sounds and that's how the whole country sounds at this point.
Right.
But yeah, you know, they do this, it's become an annual thing now.
They have a big, uh, to do the crown jewel that they do over in, uh, Dubai.
Okay.
You know, uh, for the, in Saudi Arabia and that, you know, that's already kind of questionable.
Yeah, sure.
On a political note, but here, but the thing is, uh, CM Punk, when he was out of the WWE
for a while for years, he was giving those wrestlers unlimited shit.
Like he wrote a tweet, he wrote a tweet that said, go suck a blood soaked dick out in Saudi
Arabia.
You asshole.
Yeah.
Right.
So he was like coming for their throats over this, you know, there's given people shit,
but also CM Punk, I think you should talk to somebody, you know, but Jesus Christ, man,
it looked like he was taking a stand, but just last month, guess who's headlining crown
jewel.
Ah, got it.
It's, and then, you know, I, I watch, um, I watch botchamania all the time, which is
really funny.
And um, they did the old clip of Krusty the clown where it's like, oh, I'm so sorry.
They backed up a Brinks truck to my house.
I'm not made of stone, you know, like, of course, of course money talks, right.
But that's, it's endemic of everything going on in the whole world.
And the fact that these players from this, you know, wrestling corporation are becoming
statesmen, they're becoming statesmen.
That's glad Jacobs is a governor.
It's a Y or a, yeah, I don't, or a mayor.
I don't know.
It's just, it's too much for me to say Jesse the body Ventura.
I mean, he was the governor.
He was a governor.
Yeah.
It's just kinda, it's just a little too much at this point for me.
I don't know.
I just, Abe Lincoln was the president.
Yeah.
He wrestled.
Yeah, he did.
He was a boxer.
I think.
I think he was a wrestler.
Yeah.
The weird thing though on, on raw, not having anything to do with any of, of all those things
was, uh, the cameras.
They did, they do so much camera work now and they switch back, you know, they always
switch back and forth between different shots and everything during the wrestling matches.
Now they switch back and forth between different shots and the camera speeds on the different
cameras are different.
Like the frame rate is different on different cameras or something like that.
I'm not exactly sure what they're doing, but that's, that's what it looked like to me.
And so they would, they would move it and all of a sudden it would look like the two
wrestlers in the ring were moving faster than they were just a second before and then switch
back and it was, it's, it, whatever it was, it was definitely on purpose.
Yeah.
It definitely seemed to be something that they were trying to do to kind of add to the
action.
Yeah.
It was so odd.
Was it throwing you?
It was throwing me a little bit.
I was kind of hoping that you would heard something about it if they had said something
about it publicly or something.
I haven't.
Maybe not.
The only scuttlebutt of that is that they have professional camera crews now.
Oh, sure.
They have, you know, they've had some of their old camera crew.
Well, no, it's a, it's a huge step up because after the departure of Vince, Oh, did they
have like their own people before they had, they had Mr. Kevin Dunn.
Kevin Dunn had been there for a millennia and they finally got rid of him.
And now all of a sudden the production value has gone sky high.
They got these guys from ESPN, you know, the guys putting together the NFL best of stuff
and all that kind of thing.
Yeah.
So they're, they got some real high production value going forward right now.
It was a good looking product.
That's what I mean.
It's like the video wall in the ballet.
It was, it was a good looking product.
No, they have the production.
So John Cena, I guess is retiring and, uh, and him going through, like he's on a retirement
tour or something, I guess.
Yeah.
These are his last year's matches.
A pro wrestler going through and playing their greatest hits for an audience is so goddamn
funny.
Yeah.
And well, it's, it's a weird thing that they've done with him cause he went heel, you know?
Okay.
No, I don't.
He'd never turned heel his entire career.
Oh, so he's a bad guy now.
Yeah.
But now he's starting to regret it.
That's weird.
Like, like he is shoot regretting it.
Like he really is sad that he did it kind of thing because he never did it.
So that's kind of crazy.
Um, yeah, it's, it's something else.
What did you just said before that about, uh, Cena and, uh, I dunno, I can't watch him
do his retirement tour.
Yeah.
Interesting.
It, it's something else.
Uh, I don't know.
I just, I'll tell you who was really excited about seeing Cena too, though, coming out
next year.
And that's going to be the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Maddie's ice cream and social is brought to you by, I'm sorry
for the delay.
I just got some Bisque and delivered to my front door.
Oh, that's having a party shoeless Joe's bottomless Crocs.
That's from Anonymous in 2024 shoeless Joe's bottomless Crocs.
Hey, it's shoeless Joe here for the bottomless Crocs.
You may be asking yourself, how can I get bottomless Crocs?
Well, it's simple.
All you have to do is buy them from me.
Shoeless Joe, I have Crocs with no soul.
That's right.
Just the top of the Croc.
You slip it on just like a normal Croc.
Most people think you're wearing a Croc, but no, no, you are wearing a Croc with no soul.
You're walking around essentially barefoot.
Now that in a lot of places is gauche.
We don't want to come across as gauche, do we?
No, no.
Buy the topper, buy the Croc topper, put it on top of your foot.
No one will ever be the wiser that you are just hillbilly in it.
Go gauche, go broke.
That's what I say.
It's true.
Go gauche, go broke.
There's a lot of places.
He says it all the time.
I mean, many of you have probably gone into a convenience store and notice the little sign.
No shirt, no shoes, no service.
Yeah.
These Crocs let you skip that line, as it were, and go ahead and walk on in there proudly.
Even though you're technically barefoot, you have the clam shell of the Croc on top of
your foot, disguising your naked soul.
Hi, I was here.
I'm hoping to have sex with one of your slutty crocodiles.
Oh, okay.
Come into the back room.
Yeah, bottomless Crocs.
Yeah.
Get her hay scoops to check out.
Yeah, that's what really makes the money for us.
That naked soul turn was actually really poetic and beautiful, buddy.
That was actually a little too high brow for the...
Oh, you liked that?
Yeah, that was actually kind of poetic.
Poet didn't know it.
Yeah.
You know what's funny?
See, Matt recognized that it had gotten a little high brow for the show, and he commented
on it.
Matt just made a joke about having sex with a crocodile who was bottomless.
I think we both did the right thing.
This is where we live, right guys?
It's the same thing I used to talk about with Absinthe.
It's everything from the profane to the sublime.
We like to cover all bases.
We can get esoteric when we want to, but we can also tell you...
We should steal that line.
They're not using it.
They didn't take your...
They never used that because it was my line.
They should have used it, everything from the profane to the sublime.
Believe me, as someone who has given them a line, they will take it and use it.
They should have used it.
Matt Maddow's Ice Cream Social.
Everything from the...
What is it?
The profane to the sublime.
Get on board with our new fucking slogan.
Will you get it?
I'm on!
You know what?
You bring up the no shoes, no shirt, no service.
I don't see those signs that it needs to be...
As much?
Maybe they're done?
Maybe it's over?
No, I meant like, did that culture war win?
Do we now know we gotta wear shoes into the 7-Eleven?
We have to.
Do you know what I mean?
Or has footwear gone to the point of where it's like, "Well, technically, a toe ring
is footwear."
I don't know.
I think it's all just...
I think everybody is more aware that every business could just kick you out for any reason
that they want to now.
Yeah.
That's true.
If you come into a restaurant, or maybe not a restaurant, but like a 7-Eleven barefoot
and you're not being a jerk, they'll probably just serve you and you can leave.
Well, I had memories as a kid, going back and forth to the beach because I grew up on
the Jersey Shore.
Pinky's out in Monk County.
How come that's never come up before?
When my chauffeur would take us to the beach, no, my dad would take us to the beach.
We would go to 7-Eleven on the way home or something like that, right?
I would run in barefoot and feel like fun as in the store doing whatever.
My kids...
I really think the answer is Crocs.
Not anything but the fact that we've made...
Like slipping on a sock.
A very simple shoe.
Flip-flop was easy, too.
Flip-flop was easy, too, but I don't really ever see anything like proper flip-flops.
I'll see it in a proper sandal, more like an executive sandal style for a lady.
I feel like...I don't want to offend anybody, but I feel like people who wear flip-flops,
that's what they wear.
How dare you?
How fucking dare you use this platform to disparage people on that level?
Yeah.
I occasionally wear flip-flop, but rarely.
But anyhow...
For the most part, honestly, I just wear it when we have a churn.
I just wear it through the churn.
I just wear flip-flops through the churn.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm wrapping up my Magic Invention.
Huh?
You guys want to get into it?
It's pretty exciting stuff.
A Magic Invention?
Convention!
Oh, you're at a convention right now?
Well, I'm at my house right now, but Magic Live is happening at the Orleans Casino.
Oh!
They always dry run Scoopfest by doing a convention.
That's right.
They're always right ahead of us, right?
Yeah.
They do this convention for 5,000 people to see how it's going to go, and then everything's
road tested for us to bring in our hundreds of people.
That's right.
Well, we...
I mean, we can't help it that we have the better, more elite convention.
That's true.
This is how it is, man.
It's true.
I was involved in this convention.
Handsap has got a flip-flop.
Look out.
I've offended Handsap.
There you go.
I've offended Handsap, Handspap.
Sorry, Handspap.
Shrapnel.
You didn't realize.
That was a real bomb.
What do they call them?
Chooklas?
I wonder if there's another word people want to...
No.
Chooklas.
The thing you're talking about.
We all know what you're trying to say.
Chooklas.
Yeah, yeah.
They call them choncolas.
Thongs.
Yeah, yeah.
Choncolas.
Well, you know, people get really good at throwing those fucking things.
What?
You don't know about that?
I mean, people get good at throwing things that they throw.
No, but I mean...
No, no, no.
There's a...
Nolan Ryan started as a chocolist thrower.
I believe he's pronounced Chooklas, Matt.
A scoopa cabra saying Spanish grandmas.
Again, not to stereotype, not to get anybody upset, but there are lots of videos...
Too late.
...of elderly women taking off a flip-flop and fucking dead-ass nailing people in the
head with it.
Just...
Whoa!
I never had family members that would throw things.
I would have family members that would have taken off a flip-flop and just smacked you
with it.
Oh, that part, too.
I think we had throwers.
Spanish grandmas make a great name for a bowling team, just so we're clear.
Jeff Loomis, welcome to the part of the podcast where Paul introduces an obscure fact and
then acts borderline offended that no one else has heard of it.
It's not no one else.
Lots of people are saying it.
Listen to this guy.
But your introduction to that fact was terrible.
You didn't know the word and then you gave us no other word.
I said Chookla and I know it's wrong.
And then it was annoying that we didn't know it.
Okay.
Whatever.
Oh, man.
Oh, bossy says that the flip-flops are a weapon of granny's.
They're in the peninsula.
So there you go.
Oh, there you go.
I just I'm saying there is a sect of older ladies who have become very adept at flinging
their footwear.
A sect.
Jacob, hit the production meeting music.
Oh!
It's gone.
Production meeting.
Oh, God.
It's another button that I don't have on this pad.
Oh, shit.
Where the fuck?
This podcast is falling apart.
I know.
You're telling me.
Production meeting.
Okay.
If we're going to read a comment from the chat, we have to read the comment from the
chat.
Because for the listener at home, when you go, oh, yeah, so yeah, like, that's not a
good way to incorporate the chat into the podcast.
We've all been doing it.
So that's why I'm calling it out on a production meeting.
So if you're going to acknowledge the chat, fully acknowledge and fully read the chat
and then that's a good note.
And then we do it because otherwise I think people listening at home are going fucking
nuts.
OK.
All right.
Production meeting over.
No, that's not it.
That's the machine.
The machine.
Where the fuck is my production meeting?
It's just a machine now.
If we had a turn, this would never have happened.
We would know where their production meeting was.
It's true.
Possibly true.
It is possibly true.
So I was asked to host a show this year at Magic Live.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
And it became very clear very quickly that it was a mistake for all involved.
Who did it become very clear to very quickly?
No, no.
So here's the thing.
They always have a big showcase show and a big and a close up showcase.
Right.
And they always experiment with a third show.
And then the experimental third show is it medium, medium pace magic?
Is that what it is?
It is.
Yeah.
It is magic that starts like really far away, but finishes very up close.
Like you run.
Progressive magic.
Think of a card.
And then you run towards them and smack them in the face with a card.
Oh, God.
I was thinking of a confine of diamonds.
Oh, shit.
The most painful card to get hit with.
Oh.
I was on the bottom of his fucking flip flop.
So originally, the show is going to have no no host, and it was called the Experimental
Theater Concepts Show.
Yes.
OK.
Huh?
Who's not?
Everybody just I know everyone in the chest just rolls off the tongue.
Why couldn't I go?
I wish I was there.
I know.
It's a theater concept show, meaning you have to do like an avant-garde or unique trick.
Yes.
Yeah.
You have to experiment with the presentation of magic in some way.
I don't want to I don't want to steal your thunder here.
But when I think experimental and avant-garde magic trick, my first thought is Rudy Kobe.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, Rudy was around and Rudy was certainly someone who Rudy Kobe is certainly someone
who pushed the boundaries of magic and pushed magic in different directions.
And theatrically too.
Yes.
If you're going to make it about theatrics, his whole thing was theatrics.
Yeah.
No.
In fact, if you're familiar with Rudy Kobe, a lot of his stuff is on YouTube.
If you go look at look at his stuff, Lab Man is his alter ego.
Yeah, Lab Man is the is the is the bit and you really don't see too much like it.
And actually, that style of what he's doing is part of like an older vaudeville thing.
Yes.
But he made it so that it was completely felt modern and unique in its time.
It was.
It is great.
It's very, very cool stuff that he does.
Yeah.
I love the legs.
That's fine.
Yeah.
I said it's fine.
It's perfectly good.
So initially I was approached it was actually when I did my run at the Magic Castle, one
of the people ran the one of the people who runs the festival, my friend, Nick Lang, said,
you know, hey, this is going to be so experimental, we're thinking about having, you know, kind
of a host to kind of keep it all together and kind of have fun with it.
And the pitches are like, I'd be able to have fun doing like these different bits or whatever.
And it's the biggest and it's the biggest magic convention in North America.
Right.
It's, you know, it's, it's, it's, you know, obviously, I'm going to say yes to the opportunity
no matter what it was.
Right.
You've got to jump on it.
Yeah.
And when I showed up for rehearsal, like the bits were so avant garde that I was like, if
I'm trying to do like wacky bits in between, I, this isn't going to go well.
So the routines were just too out there to be made fun of or they were too, they were
too, yeah, they were, they were taking such a big swing that if I tried to make a joke
about it, it might look like I'm making fun of it.
Yes.
Was it like the end of my crock bit where I threw you off by being poetic and you were
like, Oh God, that was amazing, the way he moved that light across the stage, without
touching it.
I can't make fun of that.
Well, like when, yeah, even as that crock commercial, like I was like, why is this tear
running down the side of my face?
So example, like, I'll just go through the things that there, that there were like one
guy did like a completely AI thing where he sat down in the chair and a screen popped
up and did a complete AI head.
It was like Max Hedrum from the nineties.
Oh, wow.
But I didn't want to make a Max Hedrum joke to make fun of it.
Both did not date myself and I guess while you're looking at Rudy Covey's magic specials,
go ahead and look at Max Hedrum.
We're in the same time period.
Matt Fruer, everybody, Max Hedrum, catch the wave, k-k-k-k-koke.
Yeah, yeah.
And then, so, you know, another guy did a trick where he was talking, but then all of
a sudden he does this trick backwards and does the whole thing backwards.
And then another guy had a thing where everyone put on headphones, but it was like more of
like a theatrical piece.
And so you were not to be in the room.
And so they're supposed to make the room feel empty.
And this was like, it was, yeah.
And so all of us was very, I basically said that we've created a show that's very ketamine
friendly is what I was saying to my friends when I was like, what's the show like?
And I was like, it's very ketamine is the vibe.
Watch the show while sitting in a k-hole.
And so bringing a wacky improv comic was maybe not the best pairing for this.
No.
And especially like also like when it's like, you know, experimentation and technology stuff.
No, no, the funny thing is that we, I pitched an idea for this show.
I tried to get into the show as an entertainer and they were like, that's too out there.
Actually I was, we were told that it was not out there enough.
So I, cause I did this, you know, I did the, I'm going to be at the magic castle again,
August 20th through 24th, once again with my buddy Nick Paul and we did an improv bit where
we, where we, where we did magic, but took, made it like a genre roller coaster of a magic
trick.
That's a fun.
Yeah.
It's on my Instagram somewhere.
And so we pitched different versions of using improv games for magic.
So like we were going to do a card stab routine, having the audience members be our arms or
we would be the arms of audience members and do the trick and we're going to do an illusion
to it, to the song of anyone's choosing that you go through Spotify on one of our phones
and choose any song they wanted.
And we were going to, you know, explore doing an illusion twice to two totally different
pieces of music.
And that was considered not different, not different enough.
Now when I just described those pieces, I just described, you can see that like, yes,
I believe we were below the theatrical bar of what they were looking for.
But energy wise, they could have used it.
I think they could have used it just for a little, just to put a little pep in the room.
A little pep, a little kick up, yep, yep, yep.
And I had to like stall in between, but I wasn't going to do magic tricks in between
because the show was showcasing experimental magic.
So it wouldn't be good for them to do like road tested material in between to stall.
Did you err on the side of Cirque du Soleil?
Did you like wheel in a baby on a giant screen and be like, I'm the lonely baby who's sad?
Oh, were you there?
Paul, were you there?
That's exactly what I did.
That's what happened.
I mean, that's our kind of stuff's got to be laying around somewhere.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We're sitting around waiting for somebody that wants to print money, print money, print
monopoly money.
That's right.
That you can only spend at the Cosmopolitan buffet.
Zarkana and run.
They're both just sitting around waiting on somebody to pick those up and just run with
them.
Everything from the profane to the sublime.
Now what was your, what was your solution, man?
Jeff in the chat mentions, Jeff in the chat mentions that if you can go see a good magician
at the magic castle, it is an awesome time.
All right.
But you should also go August 20th to the 24th.
Oh, I didn't read Jeff's whole thing.
He said, if you can go see Matt at the magic castle, it's an awesome time.
I messed up.
It didn't read his whole post again.
No, you also is going to go see Matt at the magic castle.
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by stinky pants pants for babies.
That's right.
Stinky pants, pants for babies.
That's from a dead Laszlo in 2024.
Boo boo.
Wah wah.
I got a duty.
Boo boo.
Wah wah.
I got a duty.
Hi.
I'm a big dumb baby and I poop my duties all in my pants.
And I hate it because everyone says, hey, big dumb baby who smells like duties.
What's wrong with you?
And I'm like because I'm still pooping in my pants with my duties.
But turns out there's a solution.
All I need is these poopy pants for babies that come pre pooped and the poop smells like
bananas, so it's not bad.
So now I'm not big dumb baby who smells like poop.
I'm big dumb baby who smells like a pants full of bananas.
And nobody knows any better.
But don't ever take me on a field trip to the zoo or I'll get ate up by the gorillas.
Oh God.
I'm in the cage.
He got me.
No.
They shot him.
They shot him dead.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Poop, poop, poopy, poopy pants that smell like bananas.
Don't go to the zoo.
Enter HeyScoops at checkout.
Again, I was just laughing along with you, Paul, and then you made a Harambe reference
and tears flowing down my face.
Okay.
We learned last episode that if Paul's too gross and fast forwards the commercial.
That's right.
Do we think she fast forwarded that commercial or not?
I think she probably listened to that one.
It didn't get too gross.
Are you now that you know that fact, does it affect the way you make commercials?
Are you?
No, are you?
Not at all.
I'm not censoring myself for that woman.
No, she's been 20 years of uncensored bullshit for me.
She knows what's up.
No, but she also did say, because I talked to her about it the other day, she said, it's
not every commercial, just some of them.
What did Sam always in your corner was she won over by any of the Chinese bridge arguments
we had for our for your backyard?
I don't know.
I don't know that she's listened to that episode yet, because we got to talk about, you know,
maybe doing it and having the water flow of, you know, flowers underneath, but she could
be swayed.
She can be swayed.
I was contacted by one Ryre Appledorn who is apparently in the middle of constructing
a Chinese bridge for his own yard and with that same kind of flowery solution, I think.
So I said, hey, let's, you know, let's talk.
So he's already offered to build me a Chinese bridge.
So I'm going to see how it works and see what we do there.
Maybe maybe in a year or two, we can make that happen.
I write this summer, I'll always hire Ryre.
You hire Ryre.
I tell you, Ryre was a fantastic co-pilot with me and the dogs to get me all the way
across the country.
That was that was a very good thing that I didn't spill anything in the car or any.
Look, look, that's me.
That's my that's my issues coming out.
That was that's my weird I'm working on.
I'm working on new tricks and I had is I thought Ryre was so wrapped up with with brushwood
that I did not hire initially to make a prop for me.
And I had another company make a prop for me and not accomplish what I needed to accomplish.
And so I headed over to Ryre and a little bit like a little a little maybe jaded.
I just was like, hey, this company tried X, Y and Z and said it won't work.
I think that's bullshit.
I bet you could do it or whatever.
And he came back to me basically going, no, the problems that the company said that the
prop are correct.
But I've invented this new way to do it.
So Ryre came up with a totally new proprietary technology way to do the trick I want to do.
Amazing.
And I'm being cagey about the trick, not because I give a shit about that, only that I might
perform it at Scoopfest.
So I'm being cagey because I don't want to give it away.
Well, you should be cagey too, because you guys can patent those things at some point.
Oh, good idea.
Good idea.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know exactly how all that works with the magic community.
It's hard to make lock stuff.
Nobody does.
It's always very low key.
It's honor system, right?
People get along all the time.
No one ever fights about it ever.
That's the way it works in the magic community.
Magic and variety, have that in common.
Nobody's ever upset with anybody for stealing anything.
Nobody accuses anybody of theft.
Nobody is to say they've made it their own.
It never happens in the magic world.
Oh, and if you just want to get really mad about it, listen to burlesque people complain
about it.
Oh, I can't imagine, right?
Listening to burlesque people complain about people stealing bits is, I mean, listening
to magic people do it, listening to variety people do it.
That's already insane and annoying.
Let me tell you, honey.
Listen to burlesque people do it.
You're like, what are you actually talking about?
35 years ago, I was the first to reveal my left tit immediately as soon as the curtain
came up.
And those motherfucking bitches stole it and ran with it.
They call it the pirate eye.
That's right.
I had the first pirate eye move, left tit specifically.
And that fucking dungaree-wearing whore took that fucking bit from me.
Dungaree?
Yes.
That ragamuffin dungaree-wearing whore.
That's right.
This was 35 years ago when ladies didn't do such pantaloons.
It or he scoops at checkout, I don't know.
There was decorum.
Decorum.
There was fucking rules.
There were rules.
I was the first one to put castles on my kneecaps.
Dirty knees, look at these, we called them.
Dungaree-wearing whore is a scoop fest t-shirt, right?
That's about it.
Yeah.
And Brogan's always in the chat here.
Actually, Brogan, you're in Las Vegas right now, aren't you?
Do you want to unmute?
Yes, I am.
Because you're at a Star Trek convention?
Yes.
Because you're here to see, what is it, Dave Davies, Dan Davis?
I'm here to see Daniel Davis.
Daniel Davis.
Yeah.
From The Nanny.
The guy from The Nanny.
Yeah.
I ran into Jobeth last night at the bar.
Oh, God.
And you were talking about, because we had you on and we were talking about how Daniel
Davis was going to be at the Star Trek convention, that's why you were going.
So you're trying to get Paul to go because Daniel Davis is going to be there.
I did not understand the reference, obviously, in any capacity whatsoever.
But it turns out that Daniel Davis is not primarily a Star Trek person.
True.
And in fact, he himself, the actor, was debating whether or not to attend the Star Trek convention
because they're not that big of a character on there and they have a large acting resume
outside the Star Trek universe.
He's a Broadway star, yeah.
He's a Broadway star.
And then I understand Chris, the Microscrew, bought a cameo for you from Daniel Davis.
Is that right?
That is correct.
And then the result of that cameo was Daniel Davis saying, I was on the fence about doing
the convention, but now I've done this cameo for you and you're going to the convention,
I'll do the convention.
Is that right?
Oh, wow.
Brogan, while you're here, just because you brought it up privately and a topic that's
come up on the pod, you have come to the United States now three times or two times?
Twice, twice this year.
Twice this year.
Have you encountered any hassle or fracas coming to the country?
We've had scoops from other countries that they don't want to come to ScoopFest because
they're worried about things they post on social media, that kind of stuff, and there
are stories that's happening.
So I guess broadly then, have you experienced a difference in travel because you've come
here many times?
No.
I mean, don't get me wrong, it was genuinely terrifying the first time and even the second
time because I flew a different airline this time and I usually go from Edinburgh to London
to Vegas.
So Vegas is usually my first hit into the States.
This time I went from Edinburgh to New York to Vegas.
So passing through customs was at New York.
I have not had any problems.
No one has asked for my phone.
No one bothered at all.
Although I will say I got global entry, 100% do that because I got to New York and they
went to the little kiosk, took my picture, the guy looked at me and went, "Go through."
Did not stop me whatsoever.
Nobody asks for a goddamn thing.
That is genuinely more interaction than I usually have with anyone when I'm doing global
entry coming back in.
Into the country, like I said, from your Portugal stuff.
Yeah, like last week I came back in, like that was more interaction, what you just described
was more interaction than I had with anybody coming back in.
We came back in through Philadelphia.
Global entry.
Yeah, yeah.
Now Paul, I don't know if they could hear the bunnies on that one.
Yeah, global entry, when I was partying with Vince McMahon, global entry was very different.
Global entry, gobble, gobble global entry.
But yeah, like nobody asks to see your phone and don't get me wrong, I am very white and
I look like I'm 12 years old.
So you know, I look very non-threatening.
And because I am just a patinoid.
You bring up your race, I don't think anything race-based has happened with this administration.
Really?
I don't think anybody said anything about that.
I'm only mentioning it because I burn in the Vegas sun, but whatever, if you want to break
it racist, Matt, okay, whatever.
Logan was sunburned from sitting under the lights on the plane.
That was a joke last week.
Yeah, I was just curious, you know, whatever.
That's all fine.
I'm so excited.
My accent is getting a bit thick.
I think it's, I think.
What accent is that you're talking about?
What do you mean?
Shut the fuck up and let me get to my point.
There's no accent at all.
Bro, can you switch over to full Gaelic any second?
I've not detected the slightest change in your demeanor.
Wait, you're both from Kazakhstan?
That's right.
Kazakhstan represent engines to full, I canna hold her together, Kevin.
I'm at the table grabbing the bill first.
I canna restrain myself here at the table, going for my credit card as it were.
Someone ordered a pate.
Oh, we just, we just let him go.
We just wait until he stops.
Don't we?
Wait, you wind me up and I just goo, I just goo.
He wears himself out eventually.
At the table.
You want to fuck my crocodile?
It's really more of like a comedy tantrum, if anything, you know, you have to kind of
let it.
Palm addingly, a 50 year comedy tantrum.
That's my fucking biography.
The autobiography.
Yeah.
God damn right.
Let's do some scoop mail.
Message for you.
We got a scoop, a scoop mail from Sarah Boyle.
We got a physical scoop mail and I'm going to read you this letter that came with it.
Yes, Matt Donnelly.
She's right up there pointing to her.
Oh, I thought you were just like waving.
Uh, let's see.
This got left at my, at my house.
This was, I walked out of my front door and this was on my doorstep.
Creepy doing it, like I felt really intensely creepy, but I was like, I'm not going to pay
to ship this.
You live like three miles from me, like I could walk to your house with it.
And so I was just like, I know where you're not wearing like a FedEx uniform.
It's all good.
You know?
I don't know.
I, I think we're fine.
I think everything's fine.
I mean, everybody that's coming to the whiskey barbecue knows where Jacob.
That's right.
Yeah.
It's just my house, somewhat public information.
And yeah, so somebody at each other's houses anymore.
It's not like the eighties when you could just knock on the door.
You just left a box outside.
No, I didn't.
I think everything was fine.
And I love that hideous house.
You're trying to convince me to buy and I, I don't think anybody should buy that house
that doesn't want to spend another like hundred fifty thousand dollars on it.
No, no, no.
It's way too much.
But Steve and I literally like genuinely are considering buying a house that's in a different
cul-de-sac on Jacob Street.
If they drop the price a little and I'm like, is it, is it weird to move into his neighborhood?
Like you'd be, you wouldn't be the weirdest people in the neighborhood.
That is definitely true.
I've met a couple of your neighbors.
You wouldn't win that battle.
So there is that, uh, dear denizens of eventually a new churn bat scoop, and I recently got
back from 10 days of puffing, watching in the, uh, what is this a Westman Westman islands?
Yeah.
The Westman islands in Iceland.
Oh, that's great.
Uh, upon our return, there was a package of very degrees Fahrenheit the whole time we
were there and it was a hundred degrees Fahrenheit here.
And I was just like, I could, that's like half weeks.
Yeah.
Uh, let's see.
Upon our return, there was a package of very silly blood sport and merch.
Like the movie.
Like the John blood van Damme movie.
Great.
Have you, have you not looked in the box?
Uh, no, I haven't, uh, let's see, uh, though that you had pre-ordered a while back, uh,
I'm going to drop this box off of stuff at Jacob's house and try not to be super creepy
about it.
Uh, no, the letter is the only part of this that I've really dug into.
Because when I found a random box on my front porch, I opened it to see who had left it.
It has, well, I mean, it has my address on the side because it's in this still in the
shipping box.
Oh yeah.
Great.
But I wrote physical scoop mails if any do on it, just so you know what it was for.
So that's why I opened it.
I, I didn't explore any of the more, any of the outside.
I was fine with everything.
This was all good.
Uh, there is a, uh, what is that?
Oh, a kumite duffel bag.
Oh, that's great.
Uh, for each of you and Icelandic booze sampler for Matt and Jacob, uh, some coffee, a couple
of spare fancy Icelander, uh, travel bags, uh, Iceland air, the airline, Iceland air
travel bags.
And a while ago, Jacob and I discussed the, uh, random deal.
Sorry, my handwriting is dead in kosher.
There we go.
Yeah.
There's a random dead in kosher that someone bought me that might be, uh, it might be good
for SJ.
Oh yeah.
I pulled that out of the box and gave that to SJ.
She says, thank you very much.
I enjoy your no holds barred and so they were like, here's a t-shirt from this show.
You didn't go to of a band that you don't care about.
And I was like, why, why did you spend money on this?
Uh, see you next month for scoop fest.
You lied about that part.
I saw you today on this zoom call.
I wasn't sure if I was going to be able to be in one of the zoom calls, so I didn't.
Ah, thank you very much.
Sarah Boyle.
Thank you for dropping off some physical scooping house here.
Can't wait.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
They say kumite on them.
Fucking a yes.
Oh man.
That's awesome.
You'll see it very well.
Your background filters.
Hold on.
I'm turning off my background filter.
It's still cool.
Yeah.
Cool.
That's the pilot dead bodies behind the beep turns off.
It's true.
That's right.
Everybody's getting to see my, my, uh, my real background now because, uh, yeah, I, I just
have mirrors behind me, which is why I keep some kind of something.
It looks good.
It makes everything look bigger.
That's true.
It's true.
Uh, let's do a little chalk versus a nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for chalk versus nerd.
We got a scooper today coming out today from Hey scoop, get off my lawn.
Hello all.
I'm answering Jacob's call for some trivia with a scooper and an obelisk two for one.
Oh, that's, that's a great point.
Oh, some of you do send a multiple, uh, like scooper and obelisks all at the same time,
which is fantastic.
I love when you do that.
Do me a favor just to help my organization out.
Send them in two different emails.
Do one, one email per, uh, per game and that just makes it easier for me to keep up with
everything.
Uh, but this is fantastic.
And thank you so much for doing this.
Uh, let's see, uh, two for one, I have been out of commission for a while explaining my
absence from making these things.
So first a PSA don't get shingles, just don't do it people.
Let me tell you, that's the fucking truth.
I've had it twice.
My job has me lots of different places all the time, so there's no telling how this happened,
but I had chicken pox as a kid and now here we are.
I'm past the worst of it, but dealing with the nerve damage where it infected over my
mouth later, I got it on my face, my mouth, and in my inner and outer ear, including my
ear drum, 10 out of 10 do not recommend.
Oh my God.
I'm so sorry.
That happened to a friend of mine with his eyes.
He got it on the backs of his eyes and now his, like if he walks outside on like an overcast
cloudy day, he still has to wear sunglasses.
His eyes as a result are extraordinarily light sensitive.
I know in today's America, this may be an unpopular opinion, but do get the damn vaccinations
for single shingles.
I turned 50.
I'm under 50 and never really thought much about it, but this got my wife to immediately
go and get her first shot.
It picks a nerve branch and screws it up when you get it.
I caught mine in the first 48 hours and likely shorted the worst of it and still can't survive
without nerve blockers yet.
Just very fortunate it wasn't in my eye.
There you go.
I guess there's that.
Anyway, here's an obelisk and a scooperty.
Enjoy it more than the shooting pain, tingling, and hot and cold feelings that I randomly
get all the time in my face.
It's Chris, Hey Scoop, get off my lawn.
So let's see here.
We have a scooperty coming to us from Hey Scoop, get off my lawn.
I am stalling while I share it with everybody else so they can see it over here and we've
already played that, nevermind.
Let's see.
So this is why I need multiple emails.
Let's see if we've already played this obelisk as well.
Yeah we have, damn it.
But we didn't have the full read through of the email so that's good.
We had not had the full read through of the email.
That is true.
Yeah.
Give me one second.
I'm going to find us a different one from neck pubes.
Hey folks, I'm a proud patron and wish I could contribute more.
I just want to say to the people that aren't patron members, there is a lot you're missing
out on and it's worth a few extra bucks a month to have it.
The way I look at it, I can do gig economy work for about $20 an hour, I listen to podcasts
while I do that, 10 bucks can get me over 30 minutes of content so it pays for itself.
A question I have for the churn, does it help your numbers if we download the episodes from
a different app than Patreon?
I've picked auto download on three separate apps in case it does.
Anyway, love you guys, keep it real, neck pubes, and here is a scooperty that we're
going to look at in just a second to make sure that we haven't already played it.
But yes, good question neck pubes.
Yeah, I think it-
I mean the more the merrier, right?
If you set us the download on any app, it's going to help us out.
So when in doubt, set this show to download and it will be groovy.
And I have found a scooperty that we haven't played yet.
Let me just play the little production meeting.
Great.
That's the machine.
The categories are the first, the most, the last, and the least.
Paul, you're up first.
What you want?
I will take the last for $400.
Which of these three car brands was the last to produce cars?
Oldsmobile, Pontiac, or Saturn.
So this means, this question is asking who produced a car-
Who went out of business last.
Okay, that's what I was looking for.
I think it's Oldsmobile.
Let's try it.
Pontiac was 2010, Saturn was 2009, Oldsmobile was 2004.
And if you're keeping track, that means that Paul got it as wrong as he possibly could
have.
That's right.
I got it backwards wrong.
Let's see here.
I'm just going to mute that person who is not muted.
Great.
Moving on.
Matt Donnelly, what would you like?
I would like to take the first since I'm the second one going.
The first for $400.
Which of these platforms was released first, Twitter, TikTok, or YouTube?
Oh man, I'll go with YouTube.
YouTube is correct.
Twitter was 2006, TikTok was 2016, YouTube was 2005.
Well done, Matt Donnelly.
I'll try the most for $400.
Which of these sports leagues have the most teams named after birds?
Oh, the NFL, the MLB, or the NBA.
All right.
Bird time.
I think we had a version of this question before.
I'm pretty sure we have.
I don't think it's Major League Baseball.
I'm just going to kick them right out.
Oh, I think that's the one that it is, Jacob.
This is where Paul does his subtle hints to help.
I can't think of any bird named teams in baseball.
In baseball?
The Cardinals?
The Blue Jays?
Okay, other than those three though, I can't think of any bird teams in Major League Baseball.
The Reds?
The Reds are birds?
The New York Jets?
The Nickerbockers?
The Raptors?
Those are just pants.
And don't tell me the Raptors aren't birds because dinosaurs are birds.
Okay, I'll give you dinosaurs.
The Wizards?
The NBA has the Hawks, the Pelicans, the Raptors.
The NFL has the Cardinals, the Eagles, maybe it is baseball.
I think it is, but I can't remember.
They got three.
Is there another one in the NFL that I'm not thinking of?
We've got the Cardinals and the Eagles, the Ravens, so that's three for NFL.
The Murderbirds?
The Murderbirds.
The Hawks?
Is there a hawk team?
Yeah, that's NBA.
Atlanta Hawks.
The NBA has the Pelicans, the Hawks.
Shit, I've got three for baseball and three for football.
I've got to be missing one in there somewhere.
I'm going to say football.
I'll say the NFL.
It is the NFL, five.
Major League Baseball has three, so we named all of those.
Oh, and NBA has two, three if you chubby the Raptors.
Which we do.
We Raptors.
Paul.
Seahawks.
Oh, that's another good one.
Oh yeah, they're the Osprey.
I think that's the bird that the Seahawk refers to.
I'll take...
So that's four.
Who's the fifth one?
I'll take the last again.
The Dolphins.
That's it.
Chicken of the Sea.
Yep.
Boom, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Losing.
Which of these NFL players was the last to retire?
John Elway, Emmett Smith, or Deion Sanders?
Emmett Smith.
Emmett Smith is correct.
Retired in 2004.
Sanders retired in '01.
Elway retired in '99.
Yeah.
Matt.
I will do the last for 1,200.
The last...
Which Stooge was the first to die?
Last.
Larry Fine.
Last to die, sorry.
Larry Fine, Moe Howard, Curly Howard.
Pass.
Shit.
That's me.
I think Larry...
Oh, wait.
Did Larry die?
No, I think Moe died earlier.
Stooge to die.
I think Moe died earlier.
I think Curly.
I'm going to say Curly.
The last.
Shit!
God damn it.
It was Larry.
It was Larry, and I knew that too, and I was still thinking the first.
God damn it.
He was living in the Hollywood retirement home.
It's true.
He was the last of the Stooges to die.
Yeah, he famously lived in that Hollywood retirement home.
That's right.
Oh, that's me.
I guess I'll do the last for 2,000 since I just lost all those points.
Tom Bergeron has lots of stories about as a kid, he wrote letters to Larry Fine and
Moe Howard and actually ended up becoming like pen pals and talked to them and stuff.
We'll call them on the phone and stuff too.
Oh, nice.
Which retail chain was the last to close its final location?
Kmart, Sears, or Toys R Us?
That's a tough one.
I think there's still some Sears, aren't there?
I think Sears is gone.
Is it?
I think so.
I kind of think Kmart was the last to close up.
I don't know.
Because I think Toys R Us, when Toys R Us closed, they shut all of those down pretty
quick.
Yeah.
And I think it was very similar with Sears.
I'm going to say Kmart.
It is Kmart.
October 24.
Jesus Christ.
Sears, 22, and Toys R Us, 21.
I didn't even realize Sears was gone.
Yeah.
Sears has been gone for a little bit.
That's crazy.
That's because you never bought craftsman tools.
But I used to just go to Sears all the time.
I don't know what to tell you.
Paul.
All right.
It's gone, buddy.
The most, please.
The most for 800.
Which of these pie sells the most in the USA, apple, pecan, or pumpkin?
I mean, we say it's as American as apple pie.
I say that all the time.
But I got to believe pecan and pumpkin got a hotter business.
I'm going to go pumpkin.
OK.
It's apple.
29% of all pie sales.
Pumpkin number two, 23%.
Pecan coming up at the end, 9%.
I got to tell you, you people are missing out on some pecan pie.
I got October brain going on.
Yeah, you do.
I'm already in spooky season.
As soon as we flip to August, I'm like, ooh, ghosts and shit.
The last 400.
The least, I mean.
The least for 400.
Daily Double.
Yes.
Let's go.
This is where I strike.
Which of these three states has the least religious affiliation?
Vermont, New Hampshire, or Washington.
New Hampshire.
It's Vermont.
Only 63% of citizens claim religious affiliation.
New Hampshire is 64, and Washington 68.
Those heathens.
You were close.
Those dirty.
Those heathens.
Those Vermont heathens.
Those syrup-chugging heathens.
I'll try the least for 800.
Syrup-chugging heathens.
Which of these states has the least trees per square mile?
North Dakota, Iowa, Nebraska.
I mean, here's the thing.
I'm going to say Nebraska, and I'm going to tell you why.
Because they got all that farmland.
They got so much farm there.
Same thing with Iowa, though.
I agree.
But I'm going to go with Nebraska.
I feel like they've got more farmland per capita than Iowa does.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Nope.
I'm just wrong all around.
It's North Dakota.
North Dakota was the correct answer.
I was just out.
Paul.
I will take the most for 2,000.
Ooh.
Which of these celebrities is the tallest?
Alfred Hitchcock, Eminem, or Bob Villa?
Hitchcock.
Joke's on you.
I was just at a party with Hitchcock, Eminem, and Bob Villa the other day.
Same height.
Same height, precisely.
Bob Villa was the tallest.
5'9", Hitchcock, 5'7", Eminem, 5'8".
Man.
Burned by Bob Villa again.
How's that feel, Paul?
Will it never end?
Matt.
The most, 1,200, please.
Which of the countries read the most in a week per capita, Denmark, India, or the United
States?
No.
Oh, sorry.
United States right out.
No.
Yeah.
Isn't Denmark the one where they do the Christmas Eve, give each other a book, and you go hide
and read it all night?
Yeah.
Sure.
And then if you catch, if they find you in your reading spot, you have to hit them with
a sandal.
Right.
I'll pass.
Hit them with a sandal.
Passes to me.
Countries read.
I'll guess India.
India.
Let's try India.
They got a lot of people.
I know that's not per capita, but whatever.
India is the right answer, 10 hours, 42 minutes.
Denmark is still higher than the U.S.
Well, yes.
Yeah.
So you were correct about who had the least, Matt.
Great.
Yeah.
It's me.
I'll try the least for 1,200.
Which of these states has the least domestic pigs?
Now, wait a minute.
Does that mean the lowest amount of domestic pigs or the amount of pigs that are not well
domesticated?
I think it's the second one.
I think it's how many, which of them have the least domesticated pigs?
I like to wipe my ass on the couch.
Exactly.
I'm not very domesticated.
Rhode Island, Maine, or Delaware.
I'm the least domesticated pig you'll meet.
I mean, Rhode Island has to be a trick answer there, right?
Who knows?
Who can say with this game?
Rhode Island is a tiny little state, so you want me to pick Rhode Island because they
don't have the least domestic pigs because they're so small anyway.
Well, I'm not going to do it.
I am going to say Delaware, so go fuck yourself.
Delaware?
Delaware is the correct answer.
Oh, I just gamed your game.
Only 300,000.
Now, what do they mean by domestic pigs?
You know everything that I do, Paul.
It's your turn.
I'll go with the least.
For 2,000.
Which of these states has the least human limbs per capita?
Hint, it has the most amputees, Indiana, South Dakota, or Louisiana.
Oh, by the way, there is a player who is signed to an NFL team right now who has six fingers
on one hand, making the average amount of fingers that an NFL player has more than five.
Wow, which is exciting.
Jason Pierre-Paul, who only has nine fingers because he blew one of them off, I think,
in a fireworks accident, he's not currently in the NFL, so the fact that there is one
player with 11 fingers and everybody else has 10, the average is above 10 now, which
is wonderful.
Wow.
What do you think, Paul, Louisiana, Indiana, or South Dakota?
Indiana, please.
Indiana has the least limbs.
I'm sorry.
It's Louisiana.
Oh.
I have no data for any other states.
It's just something that Louisiana is proud of.
Well, they don't call it the big easy to lose your hands in for nothing.
That's right.
That is the full name.
Yeah.
Matt, you got the first for 800, 1,200 or 2,000, and let's see, you have zero points.
Perfect.
I have 2,800 points.
I am in the lead.
Paul is in a distant third place with negative 4,400.
So it's anyone's game.
Anyone's game.
Except Paul.
I'll go with the first for 2,000.
All right.
Which of these three movies came out first?
Lethal Weapon, RoboCop, Princess Bride.
Oh, man.
I'm right back in grade school for all of these.
I remember begging to see RoboCop with my older brothers.
Okay.
Because it was, because then Princess Bride, I definitely watched it in grade school.
Like that was, that was okay to watch in the school movie.
All right, man.
I don't these all feel like the same time.
I got nothing.
I'm going to pass.
I passed the me shit.
Princess Bride is 80s.
RoboCop is also 80s.
But Lethal Weapon is 80s.
So you see how I'm doing my math out loud.
I am aware of your mathematicals.
I think it's RoboCop.
I think RoboCop was early 80s.
I think Princess Bride is later.
Feels right to me.
I'm not sure when Lethal Weapon is, but I would guess like mid to late 80s.
So I'm going to say RoboCop.
It's Lethal Weapon.
Oh, shit.
No, this is wrong about all.
Oh, God damn it.
This is one of these.
They were all 1987.
Lethal Weapon was March, RoboCop was July, Princess Bride was October.
Wow.
They were close.
I have been played.
Can you imagine a year where we had those three movies in the same year ever happened?
Yeah.
1987.
Yes.
But like.
Yeah, it's easy.
Just imagine 1987.
I just didn't know.
Nothing like that happens now.
I don't know.
Let's see.
I'll try the first.
Oh, let's see.
Where am I here?
I have 800 points now.
So 800 is enough to get me there.
The first for 800 among these three countries, which was the first to learn about the good
news of our Lord and Savior, Jesus Christ, Ireland, Poland, India.
Let's see.
Brogan, did you hear about Jesus before Poland or India did?
Fuck you, Jacob.
Brogan, the self-hating Irishman.
Who was the first to hear about it?
Poland, India or Ireland?
I mean, Ireland is right there.
It's very close to several countries that really dug on Jesus Christ.
He got rid of them snakes.
That's right.
India.
I know I got to India.
I don't fucking know.
Paul, I'm passing.
I'll guess Ireland.
Let's try it.
It's India.
52 A.D. Ireland was 431 A.D. Poland was 966 A.D. Poland held out for a long time.
Paul, closing out the category and the game, the first for 1200.
Here I go.
Which of these three candy bars were released first, Baby Ruth, Three Musketeers or the
Milky Way?
Here's my math, all right?
Nougat is a scheme.
Why is it that all of Paul's math involves a nougat?
Because it's like they call it the nougat math.
I don't understand the nougat math with these kids today.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go with Baby Ruth.
OK, let's see it.
It is Baby Ruth, 1921, Milky Way was 1923, Three Musketeers 1932.
Paul got that question absolutely right, which pushes him all the way up to third place with
negative 4000 points.
Matt's in second place with a big old goose egg, that's zero points.
And I'm in first place with an impressive score of 800.
We crushed it.
We tow that scooperty up from the flow on up.
Thank you so much, neck pubes.
If you want to send us a scooperty or a price of Skrite Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jock
vs. Nerd or just send us some scoop mail over there, head over to HeyScoops.com right there
on the homepage.
You can send us some scoop mail.
We can do all those things.
HeyScoops.com.
Do it now.
We're on a low on a scoop on a scooperty's Jock vs. Nerds, all the Jock vs. Nerds.
We're just running a little low on them.
Head over there and do that little thing.
Thank you so much.
If you do, I want to thank all the scoops who got to join us today on today's zoom call.
I want to thank all the people who are watching us on Twitch.
And I want to thank all the people who support us over.
Oh, no, no.
What's happening?
You've been evaded.
What?
Look who's on the zoom.
It's Brian Brushwood.
Oh, I thought there was maybe somebody else.
I was really confused there for a second.
I'm sorry.
I'm taking client meetings here.
What can I what can I help you guys with?
I'm drawing charts and graphs and by God, how do you zoom?
People do this.
You just zoom all day.
It's not casting, but only one person's listening and then you don't get to run ads on it after
the fact.
I do in the class is the worst thing we've ever done.
You know what I got now?
Clients.
You know what I'm wearing right now?
A fucking white collared shirt.
The fuck is wrong with this world?
Sellout.
Yeah.
You know, it's even worse is you're about to get your ass handed to you at Scoop Fest
when we do the trivia battle.
So it's even harder day than you thought.
Hang your head in shame.
That is 100 percent the truth.
And everyone knows also, I can't help but notice the the room that Brian is sitting
in.
Brian is in my house.
Right.
It's on the other end of my house right now, which which only makes me a bigger asshole
for missing the bulk of the program because I'm sitting here like, oh, yes.
And this and well, the time we did it on the podcast, we did it like, ah, even more like
while you're racking up dick points, Brian, you were at the Orleans and did not text me.
Yeah.
You know, I was too busy getting cornered by Michael Weber, smirking his face off.
He has thoughts about because he's the fucking magic police and he's got opinions on what
is good to teach people.
Yes.
Sorry, I didn't text.
I was waiting for this moment, but client meetings pushed it.
I was working in my backyard yesterday and Brian gets back from from from doing all of
the all the things that Brian is doing in town.
He walks into the backyard in like slacks and a button down shirt.
And I didn't know what to do with myself.
Well, first of all, SJ yelled and I was and I made a joke.
I'm like, I'm just here to check the meter.
And then but the strangest thing happened because I walked in and obviously a lot of
landscaping was happening, a bunch of garden stuff.
And I see Jacob is edging the lawn.
And then I look over, I talk to SJ and then my eye drifts down to a patch of astroturf.
And then I follow the astroturf over and I see the feet that Jacob is standing on, on
the astroturf.
And I golden retriever my head a little bit as I try to consider why is he edging the
astroturf.
And then I realized that's not an edger.
He's pressure washing.
And we had a delightful conversation about pressure washers.
We did.
I had just gotten through pressure washing several tons of rock when when Brian came
outside.
Brian, because we I won't announce it on air, but off air, remind me to tell you that two
very high profile people got kicked out of Magic Live for wearing fake badges just to
go into the dealer's room.
That's OK.
I actually really that I'll tell you what, man.
This is one of those things where it's like if you become a high enough profile person,
you better get legit.
Because I used to I used to be a hacker, pirater and stuff swimming on all the pirate days.
And then I started hosting a show with Tom Barrett called Cord Killers about how to watch
what you want, when you want on streaming services.
And I realized how long, how long until somebody rings the hypocrite bell on this.
And so I had I had to give up all of that unsavory behavior.
Yeah.
These guys should have done the same.
And they're not.
You heard it first.
Penn and Teller kicked out of Magic Live, fake badges.
Apparently they were recognized.
No, no, no.
Actually, Pips the Magic Dragon kicked out of Magic Live with his fake badge and his
magic suit.
In a bit to make it totally hypocritical.
Well, one, Penn has no interest in going and Teller actually usually gets a VIP access
to the to the room before anyone else goes.
You just walk Teller in and walk him around.
They do the same thing.
Copperfield and Blaine.
I met David.
I met David Blaine this year.
Oh, that's nice.
Met is a strong word.
I greeted David Blaine this year.
But yeah, anyhow, super fun.
Brian, I'm so glad that this is the only way we're seeing each other while you're in.
No, I'm going to be here all week.
I insist that we meet up in person.
As a matter of fact, I'm going to go as soon as we're done here, I'm going to go to the
Orleans, but I guess you won't be around.
I won't.
My festival is over.
My convention is complete.
So there are on the Las Vegas strip billboards all over the place.
There's all of these new ads being run about reporting cybercrime.
There's all these things.
There's a Terminator cowboy on these electronic billboards like if you know of someone committing
cybercrime, scan this QR code and report them.
And we were standing outside last night looking at these billboards, trying to figure it out
and why these billboards were there.
And then I finally realized, wait, DEFCON is happening this week.
Yep.
And I was like, Brian is staying in my house because DEFCON is happening this week.
I should know this.
That QR code is suspicious because of that fact.
I was about to say, right?
Sure is.
I was talking about a honeypot there.
I will not be scanning any QR codes this week.
I would not be engaging my wifi anytime this week.
No.
Anywhere around that.
Sorry.
Thank you so much for everybody for hanging out with us today.
We don't have any new list.
We don't have a new list yet to thank new people, but we will thank everybody this month
before the month is over with.
We have had some changes to our Patreon, which is all very exciting.
So go on over there, check it out right over there@preachingfun.com.
Or if you got kicked out of a convention because you're wearing a fake badge and you are extremely
famous, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep
this show on the air.
Head on over there if you think this show is worth more than $0.
Also if you just want to piss off Brian Brushwood, listen to our show more and give us more money.
We sincerely appreciate every single one of you who donate, every single one of you who
listens.
We do.
Yeah.
We love every one of you guys.
Thank you guys so much.
And don't miss ScoopFest.
There is still time.
Do it.
Buy a ticket.
Fly your ass out to Vegas and have a blast.
That's right.
You can buy your ticket over there at scoopfest.com, you can just go to heyscoops.com right there
on the homepage.
There's a button.
Buy your ticket to ScoopFest.
Call the Orleans Hotel and Casino here in beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada.
Use the, or just tell them ScoopFest or use the offer code SupermanCatwomanFlash.
SCFI.
SCFI25C.
That's it.
Head on over there.
I used to have it written down in the turn, I need to write it down.
There it is.
It's coming through in clutch.
You invented it, Jacob.
I'm surprised you can't remember it.
I know.
Well, you know, it's so much joy and positivity that goes into creating those QR codes, those
custom codes for our discount people over there at the Orleans.
It's too much joy to hold onto, honestly.
But yeah, head on over there, get yourself a room at the Orleans.
Room visits at ScoopFest.
It'll be awesome.
I have some cyber crime to report.
I'll see you guys soon.
All right.
Take care of yourselves.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Oh, Myra in the chat is pointing out right now, SCF is for ScoopFest SCFI, I don't know
what the I is.
It's for September.
Oh, September.
That makes sense.
25.
Oh, yeah, that's that makes it makes a lot of sense.
That's that's just fair.