Oh hello there I didn't see you but I'm so happy you're here because I'd like
to thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers it's a new month we don't have a new list yet happy Labor Day by the
well belated I know but we will get to every single person on that ice cream
truck driver list and thank them at this part of the episode before this month is
over so if you want to be an ice cream truck driver help deliver that frickin
ice cream straight to people's frickin ear holes head over to hey scoops dot
com that's wrong head over to preaching fun dot com preaching fun dot com is
where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the
life you save may be your own a program hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice
cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
social sitting in Texas that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pennsylvania that's
automatically see the audio guy how's the weather in Texas Matt Donnelly it is
humid it's humid and kind of rainy and I'm back at the magic saloon here in
San Antonio and last time I was here scoops gave us Bucky's shot glasses and
there's one for each of you that forgot to bring home oh wow I'll bring you some
Bucky's glasses thank you yeah I think of Bucky's do you go to Bucky's while
you're in Texas I've been I haven't been I know it's like a statewide treasure I
know people yeah been to Bucky's love of Bucky's and it's it's I think it's
expanding or has expanded to Louisiana as well all I know is that when I was
performing as hillbill I put my baseball cards into a Bucky's bag and put that out
with a fishing pole and people really laughed at the Bucky's people love the
Bucky's bag yeah that makes sense that makes sense Bucky's for people who don't
know is the biggest truck stop you've ever seen in your life but it's not for
truckers it's just for you know regular Joe's driving their little Toyota Corolla's
up and down the street yeah so it's ridiculous yeah they've got smokers
they've got smoke shops you can go in there yeah it's all crazy I think there's
one supposed to open it near Las Vegas or like on the way to Las Vegas or
something like that a lot of day scoop in the chat right now is saying supposed
to be getting a Bucky's in Utah yeah maybe that's it yeah can't be Utah's
ahead of Nevada on the Bucky's list man but that hurts that hurts my feelings I
feel like you know we don't we don't have the the lottery we don't have
Bucky's I feel like 20 years from now we're gonna be dealing with Bucky's like
the Walmart situation like how there are no more gas stations there's just
Bucky's it's just Bucky's yeah mm-hmm yeah oh yeah no yeah for sure oh and
Leon Kasab is pointing out in the chat too that they are they're big Christian
no big Christian activists as well yeah it's it's tough it's tough no I guess
we'll just go to in and out or Domino's instead yeah you'll be fine we got we
got a sheet slash wah-wah locked down out here in PA so ain't nobody coming for
sheets and wah-wah I don't think holy sheets oh why the why the sheets not
that's their current catchphrase stop it no why the why the sheets not that's
hey hey you want to get 10 tacos for 699 why the sheets not that's terrible
that's what that's that's what they say and they're in their chicken nuggets are
called nuggets chicken nuggets are called schnuggets cuz that's fine but
yeah everything's why the schnuggets makes more sense than why the sheets not
schnuggets approved schnuggets approved no problem I'm fine with schnuggets you
gotta explain why the sheets not because they didn't want to go with eat my
sheets I sheets you not I sheets you not guaranteed to give you the sheets no
bullshit yeah that'd be good Laszlo I could give two sheets I got these are all
better than why the sheets not why does he's not because she's isn't substitute
for the word fuck now it's yeah why is this why the shit not it is not us is
not a phrase oh well I don't know you don't know look if you talk to my
bundled up GI that's every day it's a sheets not it's like a Rubik's Cube no
I'm never no I've never wanted to talk to your bowels I will tell you this one
thing I do not suffer from is constipation that has never been an issue
in my life ever ever Paul's Native American name is flowing river it's
absolutely it is mud Creek unstoppable maybe it's cuz you're getting too many
schnuggets I haven't eaten a long time haven't eaten it sheets a long time but
I will tell you this I was betrayed by value gentlemen oh yes so we went we
went last week to to Aldi do you guys have Aldi now in Vegas we just got it
yeah right I haven't been yet but we and I grew up I grew up with an all day
around me in Jersey okay so I really like Aldi our Aldi is good got some
really great stuff and brother the value just stacks so we're going long and I'm
grabbing some grub here and there picking out a few things and all these
one of these places where you can put in a quarter into the bass cart and get a
bass cart and rent the bass cart what it you just said bass cart three times what
the fuck is a bass cart so I grew up calling them carts yeah Buggies I see I
never call them Buggies they're called no I called them Buggies they call them
Buggies out here okay I always called them carts or baskets yeah that's fine
no they people out here don't know what the hell you're saying when you say
bass cart no and people like I think I have that with the sheets with that was
a snuggies independent film that came out in the 90s about that artist who
drew with like maple syrup on his placemat you know what he was great my
dad was a my dad was a grocery man I'm gonna say bass cart is probably insider
terminology that I inherited oh I bet you it is yeah gotta be I bet you
anything because he would you know I just I always called it a bass cart
anyway so actually when I go shopping I don't deal with any of that okay I get
on like a mechanic sled and I lie on my back and I walk around with like an
Easter basket on my belly and I just shopped that way I just reach I back
around I move around the store that's like that old Richard Simmons thing
right of like only search shop in certain spots in the grocery store and
this is the way to do it you get on your belly on the bound oh yeah only stuff
you can reach from your from laying down that's the only stuff that's safe to eat
anymore yeah so anyway I don't think I've ever heard the term bass cart
before well but yet regional term particularly used in the Pacific
Northwest and other areas for shopping cart or grocery cart I but it's for the
smaller one right you're talking about no this is just saying the the big one
the regular size was bass cart because I was accepting the notion that it was an
insider for a different kind of cart right so you get the regular shopping
carts and you get together get the bass carts too I know it's talking about say
in my brain I always just conflated it to being it's a cart that has a wire
basket on it mm-hmm right that was what that was why it was a bass cart that's
that's what it looks like here on the of the old Google yeah so anyway nobody out
here stealing carts or what about what about what about tiscots or tascots is
anyone stealing those out there yes the blue and yellow ones specifically are
gone you cannot what about my virtue someone stole it a long time ago and I've
been looking for it ever since you're not gonna find it you're not gonna find
it at Aldi pal what about my my pearls has anyone stole my pearls god damn you
know I think I'm gonna try and incorporate that bit but I think it's
gonna become more common because our power grid is gonna start failing a lot
more often so anyway you don't have to take a cart at Aldi ah bass cart
latter-day scoop we have a picture there it is shopping cart filled with bass
well done bass cart for sure good job so well done well you know you don't have
to bring a cart you can just bring your bag okay reusable bag and stick it in
there and then take that to the checkout line and stick it back in the bag which
what I usually do is I don't shop a ton of stuff very rarely do I use a cart you
can also just grab they leave boxes in the front so you just grab a box oh yeah
yeah from the product and throw stuff in a box check out and you're you know kind
of eco-friendly save some time it's nice I like it and also people forget their
quarter sometime and can't rent a cart so they just need to carry a box anyway
we're shopping around and I'm like ooh it's hot dog time there's hot dogs so I
grab some hot dogs and I'm looking at the hot dogs and they're like you know what
time it is it's hot dog time hot dogs are maybe maybe three bucks maybe all
right great good and then I look a fair price for a hot dog and right neck well
for eight hot dogs I look right next to these hot dogs and there's another pack
of hot dogs that aren't an Aldi in-house brand what how much how low would you go
on a pack you've already gone below the number that I would once I see $3 hot
dogs I go nope I'm done these these I believe the I believe the Aldi hot dogs
I believe they were priced at a point where if you took those up to the cash
year the cashier would turn around and give you three dollars along with the
pack of hot well they should have these these boys paper these boys were 89
cents so I was like Mike Neal said in the chat you guessed 99 cents you went
over my friend I was like you're out according to Price is Right rules I got
to try this I got to see what's up 89 cents let's go for how many any cheap any
cheek just yum eight wieners 89 cents so a dime and change per hot dog yeah I
swear to God I'm gonna get diarrhea listening to this Leon is sending the
right gift so uh poor Lindsey so he said sexy Barry White don't don't come in
with 11 cents like my 10 cents and change wasn't good enough math that's
it's a change so I or 11 cents I had those in the fridge for a while we hadn't
I hadn't gotten to crack them open yet and today yesterday it's the first of
the month time time for the doggies to get their medicine great and the doggies
like their medicine for the most part but one Billy Bones does not like his
heart tick flea worm combo and he only likes his heart-tickin fleas he only
takes it with hot dogs so we're like okay well I got these hot dogs what
better way to test them than with the doggies so I crack them open I put a
couple in the microwave and a sense vomit on it comes walk this way a smell
like we have never experienced comes filling filling that cost exactly 10
cents and change yeah and you put it in the microwave oh that's the only way I
cook my wieners that's so gross you are a monster you are a monster person the
only way I cook my hot dogs is microwave so the smell has infiltrated the home
it's really it's really rough scooper Nova girl and say you are eight years
old scooper Nova girl you are overestimate you're guessing hi so when
you when you bought those hot dogs they're like the savings come with their
own cost there was a monkey's paw yeah storm clouds rolled in as you got into
your car well when I did it and gave me a look was like okay and I found this
pack of hot dogs there were three dollars and something hot dogs oh my god
what are we gonna do the two dollars and eleven cents we saved from buying
regular hot dogs well and I'd say well about part of a comic book that's
basically it next to these three dollar packs of hot dogs though there was a man
he was his hair was all slicked back and he had on a beautiful black silk suit
and he said Paul he knew my name he said Paul wouldn't you like to save two
dollars and something since he was right and this is where we got old Tom Jacobi's
hot dogs did you say Tom Jacobi he died he died ten years ago Tom no I just saw
him today Matt you'll be happy to know that I did have my dogs I did hedge my
bets and on the way out I also picked up a pack of five straight-up fatty big old
what he called a bra grill dogs big bra okay you're right you don't do those in
the microwave do you oh yeah what the fuck their cheese infused
brats Matty cheese infused brats oh you are cheese infused brats I passed on the
chili infused ones it is like how did you how did you pass on the if you're
getting the cheese infused brats and putting them in the microwave Paul don't
pass on the chili infused ones I did I pass on some anyway we start cutting up
these wieners and I'm I have to get pieces between Bill and Ted basically
where they call me when Paul's done I'm gonna go hey I bought it yeah I start I
start pushing I have to push ah push the pill into the wiener meat to try and
disguise it and then I give I give one piece with pill into the dog's mouth and
quickly offer him a second piece no pill so that he'll wolf it all down cuz half
the time Bill is smart he will eat the wiener around the pill and spit out the
pill he's such a little fucker so I get his face Paul leave his face and I've
had Botox this is all right let me tell you so much emotion coming through Matt
Donnelly's face here's the problem through a chemical that numbs skin and
nerves bill spit out so many pieces that I had to go in for more hot dogs I had
to renew a couple more hot dogs is it possible that Bill also hates your
fucking new the second the second now he loves them this is the thing I was like
and these things think so bad that the dogs are gonna go crazy hot dogs it
makes me fart like makes that already gets it going yeah Matt Matt Matt
microwave hot dogs I mean do you boil water and boil them on the stove is that
your move grill them like a human being grill them where am I gonna grill a hot
oh like on a pan no that's a lot of stuff barbecue grill man that's a lot of
work no thank you nothing easier than grilling a barbecue I would argue putting
a putting a hot dog into the microwave for a minute is far easier Paul Paul let
me let me help you out here buddy let me help you out go to Walmart today get you
a George Foreman grill and just be done with life no these are gross I would
accept the George Foreman grill from you right now I'm not I'm not gonna accept
the hot dog in the microwave it's a meat skin issue yes what's it what you don't
like what happens on the tech you're seeing should be crispy well it gets
crispy sometimes no that's impossible in the microwave nope you're lying to
yourself but you're talking to a guy who loves the texture of pudding skin so
that's kind of what I've got with the microwave wiener if that's your level
of crunch I want to bite into a hot dog with crunch gross you're a Nathan's guy
huh yeah yeah no fuck that shit I don't like me yeah I pay a whole 389 at Aldi's
for a Nathan's hot dog you like you like you like a natural casing do you also
use lambskin condoms is that how you roll I only I only eat lambskin condoms
yeah but off you go grill you go to go to Aldi buy some lambskin condoms go to
IKEA and fill it with a bunch of meatballs and I empty all the meatballs
full of like a meatball I stuff stuff a brat into a lambskin condom and I double
grill yeah it's like that's how you get that extra crisp it's like a twice baked
potato yeah that'd be more like a jacketed potato right so so I get this
wiener and I'm breaking up the pieces of it and this is the second time it's been
in the microwave a sec in the chat for a scoop fest refund and is like and is
like dear God we had to turn the fan on on the window to blow air out of the
house because it was so stank it was awful and then so I've been I've been
cutting up and squishing all these wieners and this is this is how you know
it's bad wieners again this is how you know it's bad I threw away what was left
I threw away the other four wieners you threw away you threw a 44 cents worth of
wieners I never throw away food I don't throw away stuff I don't I rarely do
these were so bad I was like fuck this I can't I can't possibly but finally got
microwave his wieners maddingly found the bridge too far I finally got that
fucking gift from I think you should leave is so good so uh I finally got
bill to take all his pill finally got all of it done everybody ain't there at
what cost meat torturing your dog I'll tell you I'll tell you what the cost was
the cost was the unmistakable stench of a dead cows penis on my hands after four
washings it was still there it smelled like from under cheese at the circus it
was so fucking bad this thing I don't like the stink on my fingers would not
I put dawn soap on it I put all kinds of soft soap on it I I contemplated giving
my fingers an Epson salt bath because it was that how it permeated my flesh look
Paul do you guys buy sponges do you have sponges in your kitchen I do have
sponges yeah you get the sponges with the rough side on the back of it mm-hmm
get those put a little bit of dish soap on it and use that scrubby side to scrub
your hands I mean and you have to like you have to really scrub into it but
that's that's how I get like it would sit on your hands did you let the dawn
liquid sit on your hands did I let it sit on my hand oh did you soak your
hands and like dish wash oh remember remember the palm olive when you would
soak your hands in it remember that yeah who yeah that's that was a thing that
ladies did Paul I figured out who made your hot dogs who Al Qaeda Al Qaeda
made your hot dogs Al Qaeda Al Qaeda hot dogs everybody loves I'll have Al Qaeda
Al Qaeda hot dogs serve me up a wiener from Osama somewhere in a cave there are
people celebrating the victory of selling those hot dogs and getting the
permeate an American household here's the thing and my investigative journalist
wife and we're going to collapse them from within she quickly she quickly
while she sat on the couch many feet away from the kitchen smelling the
death end trails she went ahead and jumped online to find out what is going
on with these wieners and she found a reddit a reddit thread apparently they
changed the recipe on these just like two months ago all right everybody is
like dear god what is this this is not a hot dog this is the
smelling it is the nastiest thing people were like I've been buying these for a
long time now they're really disgusting we looked on the ingredients there were
all these weird our hot dogs will fly a plane right into your taste buds they
really did the secret ingredient is cat shit says fro-yog and he's right it was
nasty there's all like cumin and lots of powders and I don't I don't know like
for a while it was like chicken and beef for the top ingredients they're not
anymore oh god yes he looked at the ingredients after he was done yeah well
I didn't eat any well and dared me to eat a little bite night a little bite
it was so nasty when was the last time you purchased something from a grocery
store that your wife then had to dare you to eat or cause her to me they get
on reddit to figure out what was going on when I've been into it I chewed up a
little bit it was like it's like kind of like a falafel meat if it had been on a
New York sidewalk for a couple days like a gyro you mean yeah like a gyro but
like really like I'm like somebody stepped on this here gyro this big cut
like the gyros that would come with it would just be like the weird gray meat
you never you never quite knew where it came from yes yes yeah yeah yeah just a
rotating pile of something yeah so it was it was bad and and she was looking up
all these different people saying oh god these these hot dogs just are are the
nastiest thing I've ever eaten this is gross I don't know what's going on with
this and then the kicker was she looked on the on the bag to find out what the
branding and everything it's an all the in-house thing but she saw on the
packaging it says explicitly do not recycle this plastic I've seen labels
that says hey this plastic is not recyclable no but this one was like
warning what did it say why I can tell you my theory okay it's contaminated
there's something horribly wrong with it oh anyway it was really gross it was
really really bad oh I just did a search on our new Aldi hot dogs good is oh yeah
search that okay yeah one of the lines is people have had experience with bad
experiences with recent quality issues like the hot dogs being too greasy okay
too small okay or leaking what a horrible adjective leaking the hot dogs
are leaking people hot dogs al-qaeda hot dogs the leakiest wiener you can buy mom
well call the cops the hot dogs are leaking the hot dogs are leaking put your
thumb in it I mean this is sort of canary in the coal mine times though
guys we're on the front we're on the front lines of do not give those hot dogs
to any canary very very oh there's they're probably ten percent canary very
relaxed FDA guidelines at this point you know our food safety is gonna go rid of
red dye number five or whatever sure we are sure we are and replacing it with
important important asbestos from Russia pureed sea turtle yeah you know the
leaky hot dog lately that's the following sponsor today's show Matt and
Madeline's ice cream social is brought to you by Jacob's guide to taking notes
on how things are sexy but not sexual how young is too young and to make this
distinction this is Jacob's number one fan scoop
submitting this in 2024 what product is so the name is Jacob's number one fan
scoop that's who submitted this okay November of 2024 good it's Jacob's
guides to taking notes on how things are sexy but not sexual how young is too
young to make this distinction I don't know the last I don't the tagline to at
all hey listen no hundred percent this is what it is what it is is bananas
I'm talking about bananas now they're sexy right they're not sexual I mean you
could use them but I wouldn't but they're kind of sexy right but how young
is too young green green means too young if there's green on a manner don't play
ball that's all you gotta do that's that's simple rule just stay away from
green manners also leaky wieners stay away from green manners and leaky
winners mean to too young too young I mean I'm an old grandpappy pappy van
Winkleman so give me my old man on drinks I want my old all my drinks should
be named after very old gentleman mmm all I want in my mouth is elderly men
that's it I don't not gonna drink any young people elderly men slurp gulp let's
go Papa Van Winkle gentlemen Jack dusty old granddad's hat box fart McGee and
terrible terrible uncle Arthur those are my favorite one terrible uncle Arthur's
tantrums is the most fierce whiskey I've ever had terrible uncle Arthur's
tantrums I got I got a case of that shit oh they bottle it in Lithuania I found
out and they only sell it after it's been aged for 40 months in the open air
they don't have any they just leave it out in a bucket in a very thin very
shallow bucket terrible uncle Arthur's awful tantrums or something like that
it's called I can't remember exactly how phrased it uncle Arthur's terrible
tantrums whiskey go ahead and get some of that what it's basically they put it
on I get you some they they they age it in a bed pan open open face bed 100% it
check out you put those bananas lambskin condoms crispy I wouldn't saw the Wizard
of Oz at the sphere last night we should have been sled with that we
shouldn't talked about hot dogs for the a block you know what you know what I
just gave you 20 minutes of gold from a fucking rotten pig's asshole shut up
liquid fire shit gold is what you gave me make Wizard of Oz the a block but
then we fell into this pile of gold and I can tell you this Judy Garland doesn't
microwave up half as nice as an Aldi wiener that is true you take that she's
real stinky you take that back you'd have to spare as my Judy holy shit the
sphere is still amazing yeah the sphere remains amazing they I I think they
might have found their thing I think they might have found their thing that's
gonna make money every day when they don't have concerts in that building
just reboot movies all right specifically this one this is okay so
it's so weird so it's not the whole movie they have they have taken the
movie they have edited out big chunks of it so the whole thing is only like 70
minutes I think huh I think I think the whole movie about 70 minutes they've
used you know there's a ton of AI there's a ton of processing there's all
these things because basically they're taking all the scenes that are zoomed in
so like if you if you're zoomed in on any M for instance in one scene where
she's standing in a room talking to people you don't just see her zoomed in
you see the whole room of filled with filled with like whoever's in the room
that she's talking to got it so they they took things from the movie they
took implications from the movie and expanded those out and fleshed those
out it was really neat a lot of AI stuff a lot of a fit not a lot but a fair
amount of background characters I don't know how you guys are watching movie and
TV scenes with big groups of people I find myself always watching the extras I
think we've talked about this before Oh no I there are little people I only look
at the stars watch your watch your mouth there there please there no but little
people is the right thing to say yeah yeah guys eat all the hot dogs you
fuckers oh no no eat shit it's better for you that's it that's the new curse
all the hot dogs upon your house Oh God the worst thing your house will be
uninhabitable it'll smell too bad yeah no I look at background characters in
fact that's actually my kids will do that too and they actually did over
their own grandmother and numerous scenes because they realized that back
when my my mother-in-law was doing a bunch of background work all the time
right up in the background of some of their favorite shows and she'd forgotten
she'd done that show or something it's very yeah she had forgotten that she had
animated herself into spongebob squarepants she was an extra on it so
this is where they're using you know whatever AI technology CGI technology
to create you know larger groups that fill the whole screen and stuff like
that right that's right and they're making a whole new scenes and intro
scenes like when the when the house lands in Oz instead of just opening like
in the in the movie Dorothy opens the door to the to the house that just
landed and she walks out into Oz she walks out into Munchkin land in this
there's the whole storm scene and by the way they've got you know huge wind
machines and snow and all kinds of shit falls on you and the chairs vibrate and
it's the whole 4d experience but on a 20,000 seat scale instead of 100 seat
scale at the at the fair or whatever so it's really all this stuff they they
start the movie after Dorothy has already interacted with Mrs. Gulch with
the witch so like they start the movie a good 15 minutes in basically they start
the movie about two minutes before she's seeing somewhere over the rainbow mm-hmm
so I mean they just skipped through a lot of stuff but I mean it is it is neat
and there it was full 20,000 people in there or however many people they have
is their occupancy for the for the movie stuff well it's already it was like you
know it's it's doing the number one tourism thing which is people plan trips
around coming out to see it right and apparently we were talking to a buddy of
mine who's one of the people who run the show over there he was saying they've
already sold over 400,000 tickets geez Lord yeah so like they're just yeah I
mean cuz we went to the show last night that was their that's every Raiders
that's every Raiders game for the season 400,000 yeah close yeah close to right
right that ballpark yeah for sure well I'll tell you what's encouraging to me
is seeing is seeing so many of my local friends getting acting work inside yeah
the theater as extras and sort of like guests and hosts and all that kind of
thing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah bunch of people a bunch of people I
know are working yeah I was like wow like Marcus is there and yeah I saw a
picture I was like this is just like a who's who of people I've worked with in
the past this is cool yeah yeah so well it eliminates all these other shows and
jobs nice that they picked up our friends on the way which is good that's
right well I mean we did talk about that last night we talked about that with with
a friend of ours James last night he was like oh no one of the guys running the
show he was like all these great shows in town and we're just selling fuck tons
of tickets I know it's hurting the other shows in town yeah yeah I was like yeah
it's true but I mean it's also part of it you know it's it's Vegas goes through
changes and that's the song we all think of when we hear changes and you know
like every shows every every casino is never production show right right like
used to have some kind of big big show that had song song and dance and you'd
have five every song every casino hired 50 dancers and sure just went away they
dance on the deco the Titanic while it sank that's right that's when that last
the longest Jubilee right yeah but but everybody you know even the pen and
teller theater the Rio used to have a production show in there and that's why
it's like such a big backstage area for Penn and Teller it's because it always
used to be also they used to also split it with dance with a dance team yeah so
it's it's you know it is interesting that like you know Cirque du Soleil has
been open for you know 30 40 years right in this town right and and so you know
it's interesting that like a literal Death Star got built in the middle of
the strip and you're like oh no but that's a license they still haven't
gotten they still haven't been able to just make themselves into the Death Star
and this is when you're talking about the way you're talking about this very
experience this this was Star Trek this is Star Trek the experience oh yeah yeah
especially I mean the dome was what they built you in the I don't know you went
to that listen motherfucker they built the dome for the original Klingon
encounter which worked with the this the actual motion ride carts all right the
vehicles and then when they put in 4d only the ending of that was a theatrical
4d experience but it had seats that would poke you in the ass and squirt you
with water and shoot you with air and stuff oh dude I mean it didn't have the
dick-sucking alien like I would propose we're getting there we're getting there
eventually every day we're a little bit closer to that dick-sucking alien did you
see it happened at the corn concert did you see it see what specifically there
was a guy at a corn concert up in the up in the nosebleeds jacking it during going
at it during this is going whole hog turn the show and a bunch of people like
hey dude knock it off and he's like no I'm getting there like he went he went
to completion on him he didn't give a damn yeah so like the last corn that's
hurt is the second nastiest thing that's been discussed on this show today that is
horrible so I didn't know I didn't know Lucy K liked corn everybody likes corn
Matt all right they're hard to digest though okay so all right Vegas politics
and entertainment see change and all that stuff aside yes let's get it what's
getting the actual experience of going to see Wizard of Oz we get that they
open the doors I think 45 minutes early so we get there they have decked out
well they've added a whole bunch of stuff to the lobby so there's all new
LEDs and all there's a mini sphere in the lobby that people in the zoom chat
just saw a minute ago so they do all kinds of Wizard of Oz scenes on that
after the movie is over that's when they do a live performance they do they do
live performance afterwards you get to like interact with the wizard they've
got a huge hologram an interactive hologram of the wizard that that appears
out in the lobby and sorry Jacob breaking news we're getting updates in
the chat about the guy jerking off with the corn concert turns out people were
punching him in the back of the head and trying to turn to basically stop him
they were trying to stop him I don't think they stopped him what they didn't
realize was featuring out a bug to the guy jacket like he's like he loves a
good donkey punch he's like oh yeah no don't hit me no
please so much human contact certainly won't put me over the edge so was Darren
the the wizard when you were there Darren was not the wizard when I was
there but our friend James Simpson was oh he was the the guard the the you know
you can't see the wizard nobody sees the wizard not nobody I know how that James
is the used to work at 50 shades right yes yeah yeah yeah you know James yeah
he's good guy very good yeah we even got we even got a special little just us
picture with with James and the wizard in their costumes oh that's awesome yeah
it's on SJ's phone or I'd show it to you James will James knows everyone
everyone knows yes yes he is one of those work horses for Vegas that's right
in like every show yes that's right so we were there it is so what I want to
talk about it's so weird to watch a movie that assumes that everyone has not
only already seen that movie but that everyone is very familiar with it yeah
yeah yeah so like like I said earlier like the movie doesn't start with all
of the setup that the that the real movie starts with it doesn't start with
you're getting to know the characters it doesn't they're like you know these
characters we all know that you know these characters we're gonna skip over
this part we're not gonna have this 20 minutes in the movie where we get to
know Dorothy and Annie and Uncle Henry and all these people but you don't need
to know that you know who these people are we're going straight over the
rainbow she's gonna do the over the rainbow then pretty quickly after that
we're gonna see Gulch she's gonna be there trying to take the dog dogs gonna
get away and we're going to Oz so like 10 minutes in their defense we're there
you have done you have like 80 years to see the original version you know I'm
not really I'm not criticizing it but it is the first time I've ever seen
something that assumes that you already know the full story of the thing that
you're watching well the ruby slippers are still the number one most valuable
movie prop in existence oh they have to be they are I'd be I'd be surprised if
anything else was close to it well I think they might get usurped soon possibly
depends on what I just saw that by what Jacob what do you think is gonna get you
serpent go ahead oh okay I think it'll be the giant robot from Pacific Rim Luke
Skywalker's lightsaber handle yeah you're closer there Matt yeah it's an
original screen used Vader lightsaber that is going up for sale yeah Leon
Casab says that rosebud is the number two most expensive prop yes found in
the trash that that makes sense too yeah was we don't want to any spoilers for
Citizen Kane to anyone has not yet seen Citizen Kane go ahead fast forward about
15 seconds while we do all the spoilers for Citizen Kane yeah I think the the
next sphere show so make sure you bone up on it I think Leon absolutely no
kidding around go to the sphere to watch this again oh that'd be amazing actually
I'd do that today that'd be great maybe they'll get that that'd be really cool
it would be really good they could do a lot of crazy shit with Citizen Kane so
watching this movie with the assumption watching a watching a movie play that is
assuming that I don't need to get any information from the movie is a weird
experience already and then watching a movie that I have seen I mean who knows
how many times I've seen the Wizard of Oz in my life I mean probably hundreds
if not thousands of times back when we were kids it was on TV at least once a
course yeah and I would watch it all the time is a big on TV yeah I've embarrassed
my mom by saying this before but my mom did famously asked me one time a few
years ago when they colorized the the middle part of Wizard of Oz oh my and I
had to break it to her that they had not colorized it they that's how the movie
had been made it was the first part in sepia and second part in color she said
oh no no no when I was a little girl it was all in black and white mm-hmm and I
said mom no no no when she was watching it she was watching it at her home on a
black and white television exactly so it was all black and white just only for
her oh people who watch it on black and white TVs I was like now you were
watching at the black just you just be the family be carving up the recently
microwaved hot dog and they'd watch it watch it over at the old black and white
TV thanksgiving Matt they never had the luxury of microwaved hot dogs in the
50s I didn't know the joys of the pudding just give a mental spirit through
it and put two lighters on both ends they did do that shit they fucking would
fork it and cook it like that all crazy that crazy remember did you ever see
that one and cooked hot dog over a fire still sounds better than microwaved hot
dog sure did you ever see that hot dog cooker that you could put in your car
yes see that shit yeah it plugged into the fucking lighter and you could cook
hot dogs in your car like a monster now that's as good as the booze fridges
though the booze fridges that were built into the car boy oh boy those were the
days you get like the the refrigerator built into the glove compartment and
shit yeah oh so good this is where you keep your martini shaker while you're
in the car they had that they had booze fridges hot dog cookers yeah places
where you could shit and smoke prostitute prostitute dumpers old cars
had it all man well it was just the trunk yeah well I'll mean but it was
sold as a prostitute dumper nobody nobody carried trunks back then yeah they
didn't call it the trunk they called it the prostitute dumper yeah we call it
the trunk before I take it for a test drive how many gallons is this
prostitute dumper oh this is an 80 gallon prostitute dumper all right that's a lot
of prostitute dumper in there so I can get probably what three prostitutes in
there oh four four petite ones four petite prostitutes before I have to take
her in for servicing absolutely sir all right all right I'll take it good sir
you won't be you won't be disappointed and because you got it today just after
Labor Day I'm gonna throw in two prostitutes in the prostitute dumper free
of charge Wow prostitutes get the dumper start the hot dog machine and grab
yourself a cold seltzer oh I love seltzer well I have some cold seltzer in
my booze cabinet but only the seltzer is for the prostitutes toots don't get
booze no booze for toots no booze for toots no booze for toots
toots in the boot that's what the UK it's called the boots called the toot boot
oh I'll tell you who else has put prostitutes in the boot of the car not
in the trunk just in the prostitute dump and that's the following sponsor
today's show is brought to you by hey poops calm horse laxatives ha why poops
calm horse laxatives that's from rich scoop in 2024 hello I'm mr. ed I haven't
taken a good number two in a minute and what I really need a constitutional I
reach for hey poops the only laxative guaranteed to put a pep back in your
filly step oh good god Wilbur I'm tired of my trainers reaching in feet deep
with their gloved arms and grabbing at whatever remains inside my digestive
tract I've had full full bales of hay pulled undigested from my lower colon
and that's the game I don't want to play anymore no this old sway back needs
himself some help getting his sway back if you know what I mean so give me some
of that laxative that's maxitive give me some of that poop firing inspiring dump
building no killden fart producing lumpy horse juicing yeah I need me some of
that hey poops digest your shit hey hey poops it'll make you shit hey hey oh god
oh oh no oh I took a double dose and I've prolapsed oh no help me sir you
have to leave the studio now well come on let me stay my anus is hanging out
here like an Aldi hot dog yeah that is part of the reason I need you to leave
you smell almost as bad as a microwaved Aldi hot dog look I've got a bag for it
oh oh that's fine then I bring this I bring this bag and bass cart to tote
around my prolapsed anus
you know people come to me after listening to this show and they say how
do you guys come up with all this material you guys have writing meetings
and sit around and really really come up with different ideas and really workshop
them and everything I go no we actually come up with everything right there on
the fly we just we just go through and we talk about stuff and we have
conversations and sometimes it takes us to fun places like a horse a talking
horse with a prolapsed anus we don't we don't think about that at all before the
show starts that's just what comes up but it's all we'll think about after no
no still the second most disgusting thing said on this show today basically got a
radio flyer wagon designed specifically to carry my anus. How do you carry your anus?
I carry mine in a red radio flyer wagon. Thank you radio flyer. What I like about the
radio flyer is the color match the color match is pretty good for my anus. It turns out my anus is the exact shade of red as a radio flyer wagon.
It's fairly it's fairly unobtrusive and people who don't know wouldn't wouldn't
even know it's like I'm not wearing anything at all. It's very inconspicuous. Wizard of Oz thumbs up worth
going very expensive expensive but but a fun ticket and definitely a different
experience than anything I've seen I think anywhere before right yeah yeah
it's a crazy thing it's a crazy thing for sure so you thought you think they're
just gonna like well I mean I guess they're gonna keep cranking that one is
there is it an indefinite run I think so yeah yeah I think it'll run until people
stop buying thousands of tickets for it I actually know it's not even fully
finished that's true they're still adding they're still gonna be adding more
things to it yeah and they're selling stuff is there a merch thing associated oh
definitely oh I got a shirt I got a Wizard of Oz shirt for sure yeah you know
me and my merch laughs at me every time we go to a concert or something Jacob
will go by the merch is it a is it specifically sphere themed there's one
t-shirt where you it says you putting a pill into a hot dog meat for Toto mm-hmm
yeah that in there Oh Toto oh if you don't eat this pill you'll get fleas
and ticks I know it makes my hands smell like the underside of a hobo's rectum
but please just have it just the underside yes the underside of the
uncovered underside of the whole underside of a hobo's rectum yes it
smells like dandelions and her hey scoops check out yeah yeah not finished
winter scoop is it's what they're calling it's in its edging phase it's in
that's right the Wizard of Oz I also ran into a friend of mine we went to the
sphere with our cousins who were in town and they were laughing at us
actually the same thing that we were talking about with James earlier they
were like holy shit is it fun going out to entertainment things with Jacob and
SJ because we just see people that we know the entire time of course so one
of the people that we ran into was the artistic director from over at the new
area 15 Universal Horror Nights and yeah so she like they've just gotten opened
over there they're cranking it out I think they're still gonna make some
changes over there I don't think they're done just like the sphere so I mean it
is that that gives me a little bit of hope when we're talking about the the
entertainment jobs going away and yeah oh yeah there's all there's old stuff
that's that's getting hurt but there's always new stuff coming in as well so
it's it's always a fun thing it's funny that you mentioned that getting going
around getting recognized and being the gad about that she is and working in all
these coffee shops she is also becoming like well-renowned we went sure we went
to the Thai place for lunch yesterday she goes in the first time you up my
name's Anne the first person to see this is a former employee of hers and they're
having a nice sweet conversation the whole time and then as she's walking we're
walking us to a table a longtime customer says oh hey I thought that was
you and so she's just she's getting to know everybody in this Berg it's amazing
so it's really lovely it's really lovely somebody should know everybody in
Pittsburgh she's very popular she's very popular well she's in the Autobot
Society she is brother a member in good standing how much more popular do you
want to be you can't be much more popular I'll tell you what's gonna make
you very unpopular how badly you're gonna do with this jock versus nerd suck
eggs how long till I'll take those in I'll take the egg smell I'll take the
sucking egg smell over the
explosion of nuked meats I'm gonna tell you right now I had a whole other jock
versus nerd picked out today I changed it over to this one once we start talking
about the hot dogs okay this is from Leon Kassab good afternoon gentlemen
here is my brand new Mikey style quiz oh that I am entitled real or fake food
brands okay I was inspired by another podcast I listened to that will
occasionally cover press releases for new products from food change chains it
is an endless well of what the fuck I think it could be nicely modified into a
Mikey style quiz rules are simple is this food item real or fake I will
provide a description that has come directly out of a press release or news
story on the product or description that I made up you know how it works I'm
pretty proud of this one enjoy so as Leon and Leon is happy with this one so
I'm gonna give you a food description you're gonna tell me if it's real or
fake okay Pizza Hut the world's largest pizza company is bringing together two
of America's most popular treats Paul pizza and hot dogs in the form of its
all-new hot dog bites pizza the American rendition of the popular global pie
features 28 premium mini hot dog bites baked into the crust and is served with
a side of French's mustard is this real or fake it goes to me sure yeah it's
real Paul says real Matt I agree I agree it's real we are committed to
bringing more flavor and fun to the pizza category than anyone else and our
new hot dog bites pizza is an absolutely epic flavor mashup inspired by two of
America's favorite foods says Jared drink water vice president of marketing
at Pizza Hut last year Americans ate an estimated 150 million hot dogs over the
July 4th holiday we've taken the appropriate steps to notify the national
sausage and hot dog council that they will need to adjust their statistics for
2015 thanks to Pizza Hut's induction into hot dog bites pizza
that's horrible someone in the chats as they ate it and did not enjoy it really
interesting that's the person who didn't enjoy that first thing I think of when I
think of pizza is hot dog all right we got one to one tie right now Matt you're
up first on this one and oh good news Matt it's Starbucks somebody says hot dog
I say now that's Italian so as you saw from the first one these are from all
they're not necessarily present so the the hot dog pizza with hot dogs hot dogs
on the pizza possible he got a pretty good idea Jimmy why don't we try to Jimmy Matt is
Starbucks gravy latte real or fake description this holiday season Starbucks
is introducing the Thanksgiving latte a savory beverage combining rich turkey
breast broth with steamed milk top sage infused foam pair it with your favorite
pie slice for the ultimate festive and dull pie slice as you know I get the
fuck out of here as we know Starbucks sits around and just daydreams about
women in giant SUVs sitting at a drive-thru for 20 minutes and that's
right and pulling out something that has a specific color and so this fits
none of those categories and so I'm going to say false false fakeity fake I
will say they do some stupid shit in the name of capitalist chicanery that fucking
CEO that came in a while back and he knew a guy who knew a guy who had a fuck
ton of olive oil they started putting olive oil and some of the lattes like
that was a thing like anybody ever put this fucking stupid not a thing but they
actually actually rolled that out sold lattes with olive oil in it get the fuck
out of here but no there's no way there's gravy fucking coffee no they are
doing protein foam which is close to gravy I make some of that at home I make
my home protein foam double crisp double crisp the protein foam that means that
is fake it is still tied two to two the holiday special number three for you
Paul okay scoffee cup from KFC scoffee cup scoffee S C O F F E E cup from KFC
okay have you ever desired a sweet snack while you're drowning that morning coffee
on the run but really can't afford to use your other hand to hold it well
Kentucky Fried Chicken has a game-changer for you and the fast food
chain is pushing the limits of what we consider a beverage container with its
latest announcement it's called the scoffee cup an edible cup made out of a
wafer biscuit wrapped in sugar paper and lined with a heat resistant white
chocolate no phony baloney Paul says phony baloney Matt I sure baloney phony
let's go for it I would drink this the answer it's real
shut the fuck up what if our customers occasionally like to have their cake and
eat it why wouldn't we want them to have their cup and eat it instead that's from
KFC spokeswoman Jocelyn Boney maybe told the USA Today the cups also feature
aromas and come with the scents coconut sun cream and freshly cut grass the
those last few descriptions are disgusting but that is a lawsuit waiting
to happen I don't they've rolled it out nationally though I don't feel like I
think it's not I've never seen that in my neighborhood yeah I don't know I don't
know if that's a current thing or a past thing I think that thing failed
miserably well it's so Leon Casaba saying it's British he wrote this thing
so there you go but that makes sense now thinking about it as it's a scone cup
it's not scoffy that does make sense right it's pot scone pot cup in it it I
love me a cup I love me a scone why not eat the both of the same thing governor
give me scoff a scoffy it's probably pronounced scoffy oh did I mess you up
Paul I'm sorry tonight yes when you say scoffy I was like scoffing at their
customers no I don't Paul will continue this game of jock versus nerd under
protest I don't give up number four the nightmare King sandwich from Burger King
math is for you Burger King says its new sandwich is clinically proven to induce
nightmares in time for Halloween the fast foods change chains Nightmare King
is available through November 1st at participating locations nationwide this
spooky sandwich features a quarter pound of flame grilled meat a white meat
crispy chicken fillet melted American cheese thick cut bacon creamy mayonnaise
and onions on a glazed green sesame seed bun true Matt says true Paul what do you
think true it is true according to previous studies four percent of the
population experiences nightmares on any given night says dr. Bob the lead study
Bob and oh I guess they really did a study after eating the Nightmare King
the data obtained from the study indicated that the incidence of
nightmares increased by 3.5 times after eating that said I believe you I is the
nightmare diarrhea latter-day scoop yes is this always the nightmare is this
some fucking CIA shit what is going on here this is CIA shit yeah MK ultra yeah
no I checked it out it's MK ultra CIA shit okay that's what I needed
president galactic superstar peanut butter infused water from a combination
of Reese's and Dasani two of America's favorite brands have combined combined to
provide the new peanut butter infused water a first-of-its-kind hydration
experience combining the crisp purity of Dasani spring water with subtle creamy
peanut butter undertones of Reese's cups peanut butter designed to provide flavor
protein and hydration for your next workout well Dasani is the worst water
so I would put nothing beyond them okay they they will do anything they have no
all has a stand and he will take it I will say this is a legit thing I'll say
yes Paul says legit Matt false it is false I'm struck I'm up to baby I'm up
to you are oh you got me all choked up there Matt I'm so excited for your for
your lead Matt maple bacon glazed pop tarts Kellogg's pop tarts are getting
savory with maple bacon glaze of a flaky toaster pastry filled with smoky bacon
flavored filling and topped with a sweet maple flop frosting breakfast just got
bolder this sounds like breakfast for every hockey player in Canada to me so
I'm gonna say yes really yes it does sound well yeah I hope it happens it's
fake I'm sorry you can't keep you can't keep baking in the packets you can't
keep baked bacon won't last you can't you can't keep the bacon packed up nope
someone call horse someone call Tim Horton's I'd see Paul house wine and
cheese it box the limited edition product is a one part delicious box of
original cheese it's one part original red blend box of house wine offered in a
convenient package the innovative pairing highlights the cheesy crunchy
satisfaction packed into every cheese it cracker and couples it with the red
current aromas and juicy red fruit delivered in a house wines original red
blend a house wine and cheese it box is the perfect pairing to all of your
summer activities from music festivals to beach parties to picnics and family
barbecues this is Paul first this is what this is you first Paul who who makes
the wine it's a company called house wine according to this house line is
the is the brand interesting is there it is their red blend well I will say my
last shift at the old Tarjay we just unloaded a big old bunch of a new cheese
it that's being unleashed baconator flavor it's a Wendy's combo baconator
cheese it so cheese it is not above this I will say yes they are doing this this
is real all right showed his math and everything Matt I say it's real also it
is real we are thrilled to partner with house wine to combine their expertise and
America's favorite 100% real cheese snack into one portable box chef
delonis senior marketing director for Kellogg's US snacks division many of our
fans were already exploring pairing different wines with cheese it's just
like wine and cheese you can build you can compare real cheese inside each
cheese it flavor with the perfect wine complement and find a pair to enjoy all
summer long so these cheese it in this box wine company are trying to break
into the charcuterie board market I guess yeah man they're like they're
they're higher their upper crust class their executive class I guess even
seems in the chat brought up an image of it already there it is they're gonna be
selling that on the princess cruises it's a real deal I don't see we got let's
do one more here captain crunch delights from Taco Bell this item is Taco Bell's
first variation on Cinnabon delights a cream filled donut hole reminiscent of
Cinnabon's cinnamon rolls the new cat and crunch delights are a donut hole
version of a bowl of cat and crunch berry cereal with milk the pastry evokes
a giant crunch berry with the familiar flaming pink color not found in nature
the cream filling represents sweet cereal milk and the pastry is rolled in
a coating of crushed cat and crunch cereal yeah I know whatever it is it
sounds super healthy well I don't if this is this supposed to be ad copy or just
yeah that would be their ad copy or their their press release but they
wouldn't say they wouldn't say not found in nature I don't think oh interesting
that's my and my other thought is Cinnabon having the the name of that
stuff like they're not gonna share that with another company unless they're owned
by the same parent company which I don't know they could be because there's only
like four companies but I'm good is it my guess no it's Matt's guess okay but
you're doing great yeah Paul give me a lot of help there I'm gonna guess fake
yeah Paul I to say fake Matt you got you got Paul the answer is real oh shit I
should have called it I agree with Paul the rest of the way yeah the new
breakfast item went into test Tuesday at units in Bakersfield California and aims
to bring back sugary childhood memories of Captain Crunch's crunch berry cereal
it's a nostalgic throwback brand from when you were a kid said Amanda Clark
Taco Bell's senior director of marketing we feel like it will appeal to what we
call kiddults or the kid adults out there about what the hell what the hell kind of
person would that be what do they mean what could they possibly be talking
about kiddult that whatever whatever that sounds like some made-up bullshit
that sounds like some kiddult get the fuck the fuck you talking about that's
that's bullshit craziness we got two more to do here let's let's wrap them
up Gatorade pickle punch Paul oh god description hydration meets brine with
pickle punch a new limited edition Gatorade flavor formulated for athletes
who swear by pickle juice for cramps electrolytes combined with zesty dill in
this bold refreshment man Gatorade pickle punch being out here in the Berg
everything gets pickled up okay they have a fucking pickle festival
pickles Berg they call it pickles Berg sure everybody puts pickle on everything
everything is pickle nobody puts pickle in the corner limited edition Gatorade
pickle I must say I don't know that's gonna be nasty tasting I'm gonna say no
just cuz I think it's nasty and Paul thinks it's nasty so he thinks it
doesn't exist Matt true it is false now we got exciting now we're decked down to
a nail biter going only up by one right the last question last question this one
goes to Matt first tostinos salsa cereal there is no better snack duo on game day
tostinos chips and salsa appearing so beloved that even diehard football fans
are willing to take their eyes off the game to get the perfect bite but this
season tostinos and legendary wide receiver Julian Edelman are changing the
game and introducing the most creative way to snack tostinos salsa cereal for
those asking themselves what salsa cereal is it's exactly what it sounds
like eating chips and salsa with a bowl and a spoon it's a clever twist on the
classic chips and salsa pairing that has been a game day staple for decades but
makes it easier than ever for football fans to enjoy the game without ever
needing to miss a second of the action plus milk plus milk what the fuck
Matt you're up first false tostinos salsa cereal false in Matt's opinion Paul
I'll tell you what gamesmanship and the only other thing is they included the
name of a player that could just be nobody could have included the name of
an NFL player without it being real no I got a gamesmanship I gotta I gotta true
it are you going true I have to to games true on the salsa cereal because this is
me and Matt oh I guess you're right I guess that is the right games play to
make I have to he guessed false I gotta guess true that's true yeah yeah so it
is it is the right gameplay move to make and and real honestly the use of the
name of a player they don't you know there you go now they don't just throw
names you don't have players around like that like there's nothing that's true
that is true it's real Paul is right oh my god disgusting
horrific game day staples tostinos chips and salsa have always gone hand-in-hand
with watching football said Leslie Vesper vice president of marketing
PepsiCo foods North America salsa cereal is the latest way we're bringing fans
new experiences to enjoy the game and snacks to go with it no no god damn it
no not interested Leslie Vesper not interested that's horrific that is
horrific but I knew it as soon as they grabbed a player name barf doesn't make
sense that that logic doesn't make sense I mean you were correct and I'm wrong
but it's very easy to write a player's name into a fake thing but Matt we have
discussed this many many times I get to the right answer the wrong way all the
time oh Jesus there it is look see it's got his face in the chat
Julian Edelman's salsa cereal oh my gross that's gross how turned on I am by
it yeah see it's the corn concert don't hit me in the back of the head but
that's the big thing right now is having these players and people you know do
these big collabos yeah there was some person it's happening now to me to the
point where because I'm unloading all these boxes of shit and there's a some
cereal that's coming out with some music person I'm like I have never heard of
this person I am a thousand years old oh I discovered something this week
completely unrelated anything else I've discovered the thing that I think makes
me feel the oldest what is it you guys have anything that when you see it it
just it just immediately makes you feel old young people for working working
knees for me I believe it is the genre k-pop oh I see or hear a k-pop music I
just got fuck I'm old yeah yeah cuz I'll tell you cuz I like more j-pop I don't
really know anything about k-pop I know some j-pop k-pop besides black pink I'm
at a loss I like I see pop I see pops are delicious what's your favorite
flavor cherry for now until RFK jr. takes it away
it's coming after cherry it's going up to cherry next now the only flavor you're
gonna be able to get soon is just pickle pickle pops barf oh I'm a sucker for the
blue I want to thank pendulum for this podcast thanks Ben and I want to thank
all the people support us over on our patreon page it's a new month so we don't
ever thank you this yet this is normally where we thank people for supporting us
month and month out that's what we thank them for yeah yeah support and oh yo RFK
jr. looks like a microwave Mel Gibson but how's the smell being kind it smells like
hot dogs better than those dogs honestly if you have it within your hearts in
your wallets to support us please do so by heading over to preaching fun calm
today
or if you like your hot dogs to smell like death head on over to farts in a
bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm it takes you over to our
patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep
this show on the air head on over there if you think this show is worth more
than zero dollars sign up any level between three dollars and infinitely high
dollars those are the levels that you can sign up at you see we've gotten you
all these options from three dollars to infinity between those two goalposts
please someone select infinity we need infinity dollars if you can sign up for
infinity you'd be helping us out oh man it would make the world even even just
one month of infinity dollars would change our lives I wouldn't be in San
Antonio but yeah if you can help us out over there preaching fun calm farts in a
bag dot biz all these jokes about all the hot dogs they're not free people they
cost us a lot of money to come up with so if you could go over there and help
us out we'll come up with more classic bits like stinky Aldi microwave hot dog
I did read on one of the reddits some guy was like oh man I spent like $40 on
these the other day and now I'm gonna have to take them back and I'm like you
bought $40 worth of 80 packs of hot dogs more than 40 packs cuz it's not a full
dollar right it's probably like 45 packs oh winter saving for the winter gotta
save these parts up for the winter why these stinky dogs freeze up real good I
tell you what you know the smell it when you freeze it it holds the smell too
when you thought out it still has that smell that's how you know it's real
folks are still buying tickets to scoop fest so that's right this morning
welcome welcome that's work that's wonderful please keep buying tickets to
scoop fest you're gonna love it make it make the effort get out there it's gonna
be great interstate travel is coming to an end so hurry up you're right it'll be fine it's not like the
National Guard is being deployed in the States I hate the reality we live in everything's fine but you know we can also you know we
haven't played in a while was someone wrote me asking whatever happened to
store jingle so we also stuff for sale at our store and we can get there by
going to store jingle calm that's right you can get there by going to store
jingle calm what's that button can you get that I go in a store jingle calm
yeah all you have to do is go to store jingle calm all you need and that'll
take you right to the store jingle dot-com
door jingle door a big door song we got a store that's my WWE entrance music
right there oh Stephen Ames writes so says SJ every night I'm sure there's a
stinky hot dog in a canoe down here somewhere anyhow thanks listen everybody
Oh see ya