Now we're recording.
We're starting now?
Classic Jacob fakeouts, classic Jacob fakeouts, fake in your ass.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
It's the night before a scoop fest, and all through the house, Paul's already half-asleep,
and Jacob's falling apart.
Jacob's got a busted eye, everything's fine.
Paul, keep his eyes open.
I'm rolling.
Paul can't keep his eyes open if I don't bloodshot.
It's time for Matt and Matt in his ice cream social, sitting right across from me is Paul
Manley.
Right next to me is Mr. Matt Donnelly.
Over there on his own damn couch is Jacob the audio guy.
We're gonna go.
We're preaching fun.
Here we are!
And we brought in Mitzi here.
Mitzula's here!
Hello, hello, hello!
I had a couple of scoops reach out to be like, "There's no churn, right?"
I was like, "That is correct."
I didn't think it was right to invite people both to Jacob's house and Paul's bedroom to
record tonight.
Because those are the two places that we are right now.
It's a little much.
Yeah, I couldn't handle other people tonight.
I had to bribe Paul with noodles.
Paul is reclined.
Paul is supine.
We actually had to push to record because we were losing Paul before recording.
I mean, yeah.
You were falling asleep on that couch up there.
Well, it's midnight.
It's midnight, my time.
And I go to bed at nine now and that's late.
Yes.
I think I just might need you to sit up.
I think I might just have to have you sit up at some point.
You can ask.
Could I make a formal request that Paul Mattingly sits up?
You may file form B13.
I'm attorney for Paul.
File some forms.
I'm attorney for Paul Mattingly and your motion is denied.
There you go.
Sorry.
I was afraid of that.
I decline to incline.
Unrecline.
I will remain declined.
Supine.
And so fine.
Oh yeah.
Oh, lupine.
He's a werewolf.
Roux.
Je suis le loup garou as the French would say.
That means skin changer, ladies and gentlemen.
Loup garou.
Look, I don't want to change the mood too quickly here, but let's pour one out for Terry
Fader, shall we?
Oh, baby.
No, you know what?
It's so funny.
We were talking about this at the restaurant.
We went and got some noodles.
The effort you just put into sitting up was pretty amazing.
That entire sentence that you just heard, listening audience, was Paul sitting up.
That was like a 15 point K-turn with your body you were doing to just try to sit up.
There are so many elements.
You remember that scene from Boston Powers when he's turning the golf cart around in
the tunnel?
So many elements are on their way out in this apparatus.
And this is good hit, Paul.
Paul is pointing at various places on his body.
Hip is fine.
It's now shoulders.
Yeah, and he was on a plate.
Boy, are his shoulders tired.
Well, I was on a plate, but the shoulders are real bad now.
But whatever.
No, but we were talking about this Terry Fader, the famous ventriloquist.
Well, the first winner of America's Got Talent.
Yeah, winner of season one of America's Got Talent.
He's the one who made NBC learn that they had assigned those people to binding contracts
before they got famous, because it became much more difficult for them to negotiate
with Terry Fader after he signed a hundred million dollar deal at the Mirage.
That's why some people are saying, oh, really, I've never heard of him.
That's because America's Got Talent never brought him back.
That's right.
Never put him in a montage.
They didn't.
They don't mention it.
He does not come up.
He was the first winner.
He has never fainted from memory.
And what we think, what I think.
So it's a big news story in Las Vegas because it was abrupt.
He just was like, Oh, by the way, I've done my last show.
Right.
It came out earlier today that tonight was going to be his final performance.
He was in the theater at the Strat.
Paul has a theory.
It's not a theory.
I think it's legit.
Well, let's let's go ahead for legal sake, call it a theory anyway.
All right.
Allegedly, it's legit.
Does not make it so.
I'm pretty sure Terry Fader thought he was going to get raptured just like a rapture thing
happening right now.
OK, OK, I this was I've there's been numerous rapture, rapture rumors in my lifetime.
Yes.
Different religious apocalyptic.
Yeah.
Predict it in my mind.
One, the mind calendar.
We're not talking Debbie.
This was so late.
OK.
So it came on like a day before.
Yeah.
Tomorrow.
So so late to the party.
Pretty abrupt.
Next time there's a rapture.
OK, here's what we need to do or someone needs to do.
Mitzi, actually, you might be able to help us with this.
Someone needs to ahead of time figure out what sports teams will be most affected.
Oh, you should go around to every professional basketball team, every football team and figure
out how many real big Jesus Christians there are on each team and talk about who's going
to go in the rapture and how that will affect the team going forward if they don't have
them.
Right.
Over, under, number one, better.
So like for instance, like Baker Mayfield is probably the biggest heathen quarterback
we have.
Right.
OK.
I'm just saying I'm guessing.
OK, good.
I'm guessing just by his energy.
OK.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Correct me on this.
But I think be hilarious if I don't have any counterarguments, Baker Mayfield just looks
left and right.
Oh, shit.
I'm like one of three starting quarterbacks left in the league.
So Paul, don't tell me what you're telling me already.
I didn't know that any of this was happening.
So it is people doing it has come up real quick, but apparently through many different
channels within the social media forums and whatnot, people really think the shit's hitting
the fan.
If you go on Facebook Marketplace right now, it's a goddamn fire sale.
People are just putting everything and everyone up for sale because they think they're about
to get rapture.
People are selling their houses.
You want to know why?
I do.
Yes.
They think they're.
What is it?
They're going to get rapture.
Yeah.
Tylenol.
Tylenol is what's causing people to believe they're going to get rapture.
It might be.
Or is Tylenol causing people to get rapture?
Is it possible that Tylenol has both created a god and has made that god rapture?
Guys, I bought a pill from Dr. Oz that makes me rapture proof, so it's okay.
They're like, "If Kimmel's coming back on air, get me off this planet."
Maybe.
Jesus, take me away.
They're afraid this is the second coming.
Like, "Shit, that's what I meant the whole time."
It was three days.
You know what?
It could have been deeper than we even think.
You know, old Orangey Borgie had a little trouble getting the words out the other day
during the Tylenol debacle.
I won't hear it.
He's sharp as a tack.
Well, he may have actually had something going on.
You are saying that this Tylenol could be responsible for rapture-type stuff?
He might have actually been trying to say, "A-send-a-med-a-fin."
Oh.
Send-a-med-a-fin?
Send-a-med-a-fin.
Yeah.
There you go.
Not a-see-da-med-a-fin.
A-send-a-med-a-fin.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's ascend together.
It is.
Yeah.
I feel like that's all the funny that our listeners can handle today.
It's more than they fucking deserve.
Eat all my ass all day.
Wow.
Yeah.
What?
Yes, we heard it.
I think he means Trump, not our listeners.
Yeah.
Oh.
I thought you were talking to our listeners, and so did some of our listeners.
Well, some of them too.
They know who they are.
You know who you are.
Well, it's easier to do the Jack vs. Nerd today.
Fine.
Paul, I'll leave.
You don't have to be out.
That's right.
I just wanted to be a little...
You don't have to yell into that mic.
Come on, Mitzi.
We can do the Christian...
We can find out how many Christian athletes are on each team, right?
No, you're doing great.
But, yeah, definitely we can find out how many Christian athletes there are on these
teams.
We just have to be on top of it next time.
Are we talking...
Yeah.
It's the only way I want to discuss the Rapture.
Did you hear anything?
I did.
I heard about the Rapture this morning...
Performative Rapture.
That people were, you know, thinking about that the Rapture might happen.
And I saw like an atheist TikTok.
I was like, "Great."
Exactly.
But Paul was saying like people were leaving notes and stuff for their neighbors.
And I was like, "These people think their neighbors are just heathens.
Are they going to get Raptured?"
All of my neighbors...
Are you kidding?
My whole neighborhood is like, "Guys, I'm surprised we didn't just have a bunch of keys
in our mailbox."
That's exactly it.
These jabronis are like, "Oh, yeah, here's the instructions to how to get into my basement
and how to...
Here's my key...
Two gay pride flags on our little sign in the front yard."
They're going to be feeding so many of their pets.
Yeah.
Oh, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
We have to take care of so many animals.
All of us are going to be left here just raising dogs.
Yeah.
I guess, you know, we've been, you know, joking around.
I guess we should say wholeheartedly, that's fucking nuts.
That's really fucking crazy.
But it's just...
That's really crazy.
That is one stance that we could take.
And I agree that that is a viable stance that we could take.
A different stance, though, that we could take is give us your shit.
Par for the fucking question.
You're going to get... because you know we're not going to get raptured.
Literally, the second word in the description of this podcast is godless.
Yes, godless.
Well, that's the other fucking...
We're not getting raptured.
Leave us your shit.
Yeah.
Just give it to us.
That's the fucked up thing.
There's straight up preachers who got their flock to give them everything.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
And they are in Barbados.
They are all left.
They did get raptured.
Wait.
So straight up religious cons?
Yeah.
Straight up con jobs.
There have been a lot of con jobs happening.
Is this job a side effect or the actual inspiration for this?
Side effect.
Because from what I understand, again...
So how did this rapture ever get started?
Exactly.
Everybody's laced up right here.
We can't pin this one on the Mayans.
I heard this was one fucking guy.
One guy on the TikTok somewhere started this up, and everybody just started going, "Oh,
okay.
That sounds right."
One guy couldn't have started this.
Oh, no?
No, no.
I've got it right here.
And then you undertake one religious rapture, and then you have them give him stuff.
Nah, it doesn't work out.
Jacob.
The math doesn't check out.
I think you'll find that one guy did change a lot of things.
He had some pretty far out ideas about where we go after we pass on.
We're long hair, you know, walked everywhere, had a lot of people following him, had a lot
of people hating him.
Huh?
Yeah.
It's like an evolution.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That guy?
Yeah.
Just pretend.
Fuck you all.
Fuck you all in the face and mouth forever.
Bullshit fairy tale that someone pulled out of their dick hole.
No, no, no.
He was a beautifully pasty white Middle Eastern.
Sure.
You're right.
Golden-haired Middle Eastern.
Golden-haired blue-eyed.
Shredded.
White guy.
Yeah.
Super shredded.
And if you don't believe Jesus.
If you don't believe Jesus was beautiful and white, then I've had it.
What has happened to this country?
Every crucified Catholic Christ has five-minute abs for days.
Just fucking washboard.
In fucking Belize a couple of months ago, we went into a church from the 1800s and they
had a painted Christ on the wall there, literally painted on like bright blue eyes.
And there's like stone relief coming out of this, this thing from the middle or like early
1800s.
I think it was like 1813 or something.
It was just all so fucking stupid.
And now we see it.
If you want to sell a religion, you got to have some sex appeal.
We're seeing it all writ large here in our own country where it's all like fuck history,
fuck truth.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the sex appeals thing.
Oh, that too.
Well, people do draw this president in like all kinds of heroic handsome poses all the
time.
People sure do that.
They sure do.
Definitely not for any reason other than truth.
But this goes, this goes back to when we, you know, we went a little, we got a little,
a little heavy, real, a little heavy in our last episode.
And maybe you did like that moment of silence was Paul searching for remembering the last
episode.
I know.
I remember a second ago, it was great because I got to watch him in the eyes, decide whether
or not to just say Jesus was fake or to name another long haired celebrity person that
he could have been talking about.
I was going to say something real dumb and I was trying to think of nothing's funny to
joke about.
I was ready for Axl Rose.
I was ready for Axl Rose, but who am I going to throw into the bus?
I was saying that was a good joke.
I was saying.
I was ready for it.
Who am I going to even throw into the bus at this point?
Who am I going to say like, I don't know, the lead singer of Mr. Big?
It can't be Axl Rose because he's on that steel horse.
He was the lead singer of Mr. Big.
All right.
That's pretty good.
That should have been the one I went with.
Jim Morrison.
More than words.
Could have been Jim Morrison.
Jim Morrison.
Long time ago, there was another guy who chose to go a different route if you know what I
mean.
You know, shake things up a little bit, move to the beat of his own drummer, a little left
of center.
He beat up his own drummer?
He beat up his own drummer.
I mean, probably.
I mean, that's how you get into the top of the industry.
That guy was Peter Gabriel and he got into a big fucking fight with Phil Collins and left
Genesis.
And that was the Genesis.
That was the Genesis of the Book of Genesis.
That's right.
Yeah.
Sledgehammer.
I know it was old, but I didn't know it was as old as Phil Collins.
That also explains why the drummer had to, the gorilla was the drummer.
That's right.
Yeah.
Because they got into a fight and the drummer couldn't go.
There it is.
Yup.
This is how things go.
My right eye is filled with blood.
Yeah.
We're all, we're all old hobbling into the scoop.
Jacob, nothing has been stressing you lately, has it?
Old damaged men.
I literally had this thought multiple times, Sucre, I was like, "Churnouts are just easier."
Churnouts are just easier.
I was like, "Go somewhere else."
Holy shit, are they?
Do it for a day.
All right.
Everybody enjoy the last Scoop Fest.
Hope you had a good one.
No, no, no, no.
See you at Churnout.
We love doing Scoop Fest, but it is just so hard.
And when it's over, it feels so much cooler to pull off than at Churnout.
Yeah.
Oh, certainly.
Oh no, it's so much more rewarding.
Totally.
Everyone.
We can actually, what a great, terrible segue, but we actually can announce something pretty
cool that's happening.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah.
So for people who missed out on Scoop Fest, I had this event that's happening in New York,
and so I asked Paul if he wanted to join me just for fun.
This is a total coincidence, but we're doing just a, I'm calling it random comedy night
for no reason.
But Paul is going to come out to Tierney's.
Yep.
Paul and I are going to do a show at Tierney's.
This will be great.
Recreate the magic of the first pre-Scoop Fest, Scoop Fest.
Yes.
October 23rd, we're going to be out there.
And part of it is because my buddy, Kurt Braunler, who also performed at one of the Scoop Fests,
he got hired by The Tonight Show.
Oh, good for him.
And The Tonight Show doesn't film on Fridays.
So Kurt Braunler, I said, when he told me he's moving back to Jersey, I said, "I'm so jealous."
I said, "But I'm going to come back to Jersey, we're going to do a show at Tierney's."
He's like, "Yes."
So Kurt's going to do Stand Up.
Great.
Fantastic.
Paul and I are going to do Improv.
Perfect.
I'm going to do a little magic.
And I reached out to my buddy, Dion Flynn, who plays Barack Obama and other characters
on The Tonight Show.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Because he told me he moved to Montclair.
I said, "Well, Kurt and I and my buddy Paul are going to come out to the thing."
And he goes, "I'm in."
Yeah.
I go, "This is hilarious."
Fucking A.
So I have Dion Flynn.
This is a no-joke phase.
This is a real thing.
So then I reached out to my buddies from Possible Side Effects to live in Jersey.
And I said, "Just so you know, I'm doing the thing with Kurt and Dion, and Paul's coming
out."
I said, "I'm mad I'm not going."
Why aren't you?
So now, Digery Douche and Pat Shepard from Redbaker are all coming out.
Because all there was before was you and Matt going and hanging out in tyrannies for a night.
And that seems like a lot of money for me to throw away to just go hang out in tyrannies
for a night.
Here's the thing.
Here's the thing, Jacob.
You should just want to hang out with me and Matt to start with, and then your dick wouldn't
be caught in a wringer like it is now.
So if you go to...
Hopefully this is in the notes, but if you go to HeyScoops.com/ComedyNight, you will
find tickets available for it.
There's just a-
Not for long, motherfuckers.
There you go.
Probably not.
It's not a huge venue.
Get on that shit.
It's coming up.
It's soon.
We're charging 20 bucks.
30 bucks if you want a guaranteed seat because it's tyrannies and there's like four tables.
Sorry, I just bought them all.
They're now $50 on the secondary.
No.
On the secondary market.
BintzyTix.com.
So it's a total random tyrannies comedy night, October 23rd, Thursday.
Yes.
It's like I'd be losing money, not going.
We're just, yeah, I'm just picking up Paul at the airport and we're going to head over
to Montclair.
It's easy.
This is hilarious.
Yeah.
So it is-
It's hilarious how much it's blown up.
I know.
It's like exploded.
There's actually another name of a person I want to reach out to.
I won't say it now because I think someone might say yes if I reach out to them.
I think they will.
Is it Letterman?
It's Letterman.
Well, I mean, no.
It's David Letterman.
It's already lining up, so yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like that.
Frankie Valli?
Frankie Valli.
It's Frankie Valli.
God damn you, Bintzy.
I told you.
I'm not going to do it.
Sorry.
That was Tony Coven and Dan.
I feel like we could make Frankie Valli happen.
Danny DeVito.
Buzz Aldrin.
I think I can get Buzz Aldrin to stop by.
Okay.
If you get Buzz to come, I'm at it.
It's like, "God damn it.
I could have hung out with Buzz Aldrin."
I could have punched people with Buzz Aldrin.
If I could have hung out with Buzz Aldrin.
If I could have just gotten drunk with Buzz Aldrin, I'll be so mad.
I may be a mannequin who can't sing.
I forgot what Bitt Paul's doing.
I'm standing barely still.
He's Frankie Valli.
I'm almost motionless.
Can't someone put a mirror near my nose?
To see if I'm breathing.
Hey, man.
He's someone who keeps one of our listeners kind of employed.
We've got to be careful with our Frankie.
I've got nothing but love for Frankie Valli.
They're coming out with a new movie, Weekend at Frankie's.
No one doubts that being true.
It's true.
No one's like, I have time to get shoelaces.
They should just as my shoelaces right now.
They should just call it Jersey Boys 2 and steal the plot of Weekend at Bernie's.
That would be a hilarious thing to film for just the cast.
They should get Kenny's with a direct that one too.
Yes.
I've swallowed my body out and fucking Teddy Ruxpin'd me.
For that one would they also ignore the fact that they're a movie?
I've got a cassette tape in my belly and I just play the hits.
I'm the fucking Teddy Ruxpin.
Frankie Valli Ruxpin.
Then the tape gets caught.
You wouldn't.
I went to Sam's Club today.
You liar.
To buy some stuff for Scoop Fest.
How deep are we at?
Should we do an ad?
Oh, sure.
Before your transition.
Yeah, let's do an ad.
Not to be.
A following sponsor.
Today's show.
It's going to be a long week, folks.
If you had two eyes you would have nailed that.
That's right.
Today's show is brought to you by PP Vijayjay's Toilet Hole Lubricant.
Get rid of the stick.
That's right.
That's PP Vijayjay's Toilet Hole Lubricant.
Get rid of the stick.
That's right.
Everybody love it.
It's a party when the confetti spaghetti come out.
It's always al dente when I crash into the wall.
You're right.
I drive pretty good.
I make a joke.
But it's no joke when you're hungry for colorful pasta shapes and you want something to fill
your belly.
Go ahead and order up a big plate of Yeti and Andretti's confetti spaghetti.
Put 10 minutes in the pot and mom, you're going to love how it tastes and dad, you're
going to love how it feels.
And babies and kids, they're going to love how it looks because it's colors like a rainbow.
You're right, Yeti.
I forgot to mention it's loaded with protein and low in saturated fat now.
So go ahead and eat your pasta confidently, Yeti and Andretti's confetti spaghetti.
Come and get it before it goes cold.
And red number five.
Thank you.
Hey, scoops, a checkout chat.
GPT can't find any credible evidence that Terry fader quit his Las Vegas show because
of the rapture.
He gave no reasons, though, no, it didn't return phone calls.
No, it's the rapture because he had been raptured.
No, it's just for Vegas style, like typical Las Vegas stuff is that usually you want to
get a last minute boost to announce that you want to announce the show is closed and get
a little bit of that last minute that final wave.
Yeah, here's the here's the thing.
It wasn't him, but he's in those circles.
His fans were getting raptured.
He was worried he was going to have tickets, maybe not famous, but possibly family.
You know, could have been like Terry, I'm getting ready to go meet the Lord.
It's like, well, I better go down to go see Grandma one more time because she's going
to be jumping off the roof.
No, the rapture is on the twenty sixth to twenty seven.
I think he thought I think if anything, I think it's more credible that he thought he
was going to be rapture two days today and tomorrow.
Yeah, right.
So he wouldn't have like quit the show just to go visit somebody who was going to go get
raptured.
Maybe.
Maybe he did.
No, no, maybe he did because he knows down in his heart he's a sinner and he's not going
to go because remember, he got caught up in some shit.
So you think he he quit his show because he's a sinner and isn't going to get raptured?
Maybe because he's like, I bet so he better clean it up.
Maybe he's going to take this in the course of the last thirty eight minutes.
Yeah, he's going to go on from he quit his show because he's getting raptured to he quit
his show because he is not going to get raptured.
But others.
But I'm sorry, Paul, did I answer that question?
I'm his attorney.
I like that.
I like that question.
Stricken from the record.
Your client, I said to be fair, I'm pretty sure I got past his first issue.
I said at the top, I said he quit the show because of the rapture point and Matt.
So I think I honestly do think like I bet, you know, because I all the religious shit
is about guilt.
If it comes out that Terry Fader considered the rapture in any way when quitting this
show.
Yes.
How much money?
I think you're just right.
OK, I think I think Paul, a hundred percent correct.
All right.
If he even consider for a moment that the rapture might might play into a part of this,
I I'm very I'm very happy with this theory only because the other answer is only that
like this Vegas entertainment is becoming a hellscape and that all of these things that
we know and love are going to go away.
I hope you can program LED lights.
Right.
Exactly.
I hope you can work with an AI program.
By the way, Dorothy appear huge.
I just did with Paul's my favorite bits.
I think it's so funny.
I love when on television or movies, lawyers yell, don't answer that.
I was doing a show in San Antonio and I forgot to put bullshit in one of my pockets, so I
went to do a bit.
I was like, oh, shit, there's nothing in my pockets.
And I had an audience member on stage and go, quick stall, I got to put things in my
pockets.
And I ran off stage and that thunder you just heard as she's car starting things sound like
thunder thunder.
And I was like, what the fucking hell?
That was that.
And it's speakers.
I'm sorry.
S.J. Can you hear my air quotes?
It's an electric.
Vivian.
I mean, S.J.'s car.
It's an electric and it makes that startup noise.
That's so funny.
It's just from the speakers.
It's just it's got a Tesla coil in it, just fucking rattled.
So he I go, be funny.
Tell a joke or something.
And I left and I went on stage and I put stuff in my pockets were small venues.
So the stage is right there and I just put some of my pockets and he got comfortable.
Like he said a couple of things and got a laugh.
And then he just started talking and someone yelled a question at him and he was like starting
to feel himself or whatever.
And I go, do not answer that.
Do not answer that question.
And I went on with a bit like that.
But yelling, do not answer that.
You don't have to answer that.
Yes.
From any from anywhere across the room.
It's a good bit.
My favorite bit of your still always be my pearls.
My pearls.
Yeah.
If the lights go out anywhere, my pearls, my pearls, the best, it's a it's a good bit.
The best.
Yeah.
I haven't had an opportunity to do it because lights never go out.
We talk about Paul.
You lose power all the time in Pittsburgh.
Yeah.
But it's just me and the dogs.
The dogs don't laugh at the my pearls bit.
They don't think they roll their eyes and they go, no, they hate it.
They hate it.
They all pee instantly.
They're like, fuck you, dude.
That's fucking cheesy.
They're like, you got pearl money and we're still feeding us this shit.
Yeah.
What do you do?
What?
I just ate a Caesar's dinner for the umpteenth billionth.
They love Caesar's so much.
God, they love those little Caesar's dinners.
You don't.
This is make dog dinners.
Caesar's is a brand of dog food made by the bars company.
I thought the little Caesar's pizza company as well.
No, because the Starbucks has those weird like lippy lick cups.
They have like the dog cup thing.
No, these are.
These are pup cups.
No.
Pup cups gross me out, man.
It's just a, it's just a cup full of whipped cream.
They're ordering them.
I mean, it tastes so good.
You don't have dogs.
I just look so disgusting when I watch myself eat it.
The boys love them.
So he just gets them every time.
He's just covering your beard.
Did I get three pup cups?
You got a dog?
No.
He got a big old white spot on his nose.
What do you have to have a dog?
Yeah.
To order a pup cup.
Don't answer that.
Nazi Germany?
I live as a dog.
Not sure you can tell me I can't order off the kid's menu because I don't have a kid.
My pronouns are bow wow.
They do tell me I can't order off the kid's menu.
So I actually, I ordered the kids at Chinese.
I do the kids.
Oh yeah.
The canes.
Two fingers is plenty.
Not a Chinese guy.
Do you see the Japanese guy who lives as a dog?
Have I?
Yeah.
No.
He has.
Listeners, you'll notice that I had to do it that way or as Paul would just repeat that
five times.
He has a custom made multiple thousand dollar fursuit that makes him look like Lassie.
For real?
And it looks so real.
Okay.
It will scare you.
He lives as a person.
He does this as a bit.
He lives as this dog.
Okay.
As much as he can.
He has people take him to parks.
Oh my God.
And be like I'm their dog.
And he'll play with kids and shit and have other people come up.
No he will not.
Have people come up and pet him.
No he will not actually.
Oh yeah.
It's kids birthday party entertainment.
Dad went to the park and this guy just like a dog started playing with us.
Don't ever go to that park ever again.
We are moving.
Today.
You remember what it was like when you were playing games on.
It's better if I kill you now.
You were playing games on the PlayStation.
That's him?
Sorry, Mitsy just showed me a photo and I'm seeing a picture of a dog.
That's him.
Dude, that's what I'm saying.
From that distance you won't be able to tell.
Oh wow.
That's what I'm saying.
It does look like that.
When you see it in motion.
It's like you're playing a PlayStation game.
Like an original PlayStation game.
The graphics are right.
The internal skeleton is off.
The mocap is fucked somehow.
It's just.
Just a little off.
It's uncanny valley to an nth degree.
But for dogs.
For one fucking guy.
Paul.
You have to surprise Ann by getting this guy to be your fifth dog.
Poor Ann.
He doesn't have a corgi costume.
She.
There is a Patreon level scoops if you want to be Paul's fifth dog.
No, seriously.
I think it's like a $20,000 outfit.
Anyway.
Sorry.
Right now.
Go fund me.
It's above that.
Yeah.
Go fund me.
Well, poor Ann.
I mean, it's already.
Today's her first day alone.
Did you get any calls from Ann about anything going on in the basement or anything?
Oh fuck.
I got a squirrel in the basement again.
You do not.
I think I do.
What did Ann call and tell you?
She told me there's a bunch of stuff falling off my shelves.
I'm like, no, that's, that's a squirrel.
Yeah.
But you.
But Ann is.
And it's clearly going to go down into the basement and take care of this squirrel problem,
right?
No.
I'm going to come on here.
I just got off the phone with Ann.
She said some DVDs and some figures and got knocked off a shelf.
The squirrel's back.
She said she's going to leave it down there until I get back, so I'll have to deal with
it.
Well, it's got to get, it's getting your time.
They got to come back inside.
You had a guy.
Didn't you?
Didn't you call a guy?
No, I did it all myself.
Did you consider dressing up as a squirrel?
I called people, but they were like, oh, I can't really do anything.
Good luck.
That's what they say.
But you, the last time you had a hole in the wall.
We still do.
Okay.
Maybe that's the culprit.
What?
No shit.
Oh, bad.
That hole is structural.
No, this is.
Now we call that hole off limits.
We're getting the house.
There's a sign with a no squirrel, a big no strike through it.
They can't figure it out.
The house is going to get repaired in like three weeks.
They're coming out to fix the book.
Okay.
But of course, three weeks and here comes another fucking score because it was raining
so hard now and thinks possibly the sump pump kicked on and it was enough vibration to shake
stuff loose.
But we know, we know that's not true.
It's maybe that sub pump vibration.
It's maybe, but I, I don't know.
I don't think so.
Nope.
Squirrel.
I guess we'll see.
Is it possible that this squirrel only wants to be on this podcast?
This is not the same squirrel.
We thought that.
I do.
We caught that squirrel.
We drove him five miles away.
This is how long it took him to get five miles.
No way.
A squirrel could travel five miles.
Yeah.
You might be right.
I don't know.
Do you think it's a Japanese guy dressed up like a squirrel?
If it is, I got, I got a very sexy night ahead of me when I get back home.
Exactly.
Speaking of sexy nights and problems that Paul can't solve.
It's time for Jock Versus Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock Versus Nerd.
Explosion.
Rapture Teens.
Rapture Teens?
Teens, yeah.
That's the only fancy account that has SJ's face on it.
Oh, shit.
RaptureTeens.org/rapture.
Sorry, guys.
I can't do this.
I've got to go check a website out real quick.
At your computer.
Mitzi is here.
We were going to have him come on Zoom, but he's here in person because he's been touting
this version of Price is Right to us for quite some time.
Yes, that's right.
He, and he learned what everyone else learns, which is like, just do it, and we'll say yes.
I saw, this is not hard.
This is borrowed from Dropout TV on the internet.
Shout out Dropout TV.
Great.
They had an episode and it was very tilting and fun to watch.
Dropout TV is, Emily Gillette called me and was like, "You have to get these shows on
Dropout TV.
They're layups for you and Paul would crush on them."
And I was like, "Emily, we're old."
I was like, "Dropout TV is for young people."
20 years ago, it would have been perfect for you.
Yeah.
Young people were on that.
Young people at the UCB Theater were on it.
So they have ...
My students who became teachers taught, those students became teachers and those teachers
taught the people who were on Dropout TV.
Right.
So you're like the great, great, great grandfather of Dropout TV.
Look, you know, when Ben Schwartz was like, "Yeah, I mean, you guys really paved the way,"
and put me in a generation above him comedically, but I was like, "You would sit in on my show
all the time.
Why am I old?"
We graduated together.
And then I was like, "Oh, I guess he's right."
Yeah.
I looked back and I was like, "Wait, he's right."
Sometimes they're just right.
We still have a fun podcast.
Paul, thank you for waking up in time to say that.
All right.
So this is second closest scooperty.
The point is not awarded to who gets the answer correct.
The point is awarded to who gets second closest to the actual answer.
Okay.
More importantly, there's no price is right rules.
There is no price is right rules.
The only time that factors is if two people are equally wrong, the person that's lower
gets the tie break.
Gotcha.
Okay.
So if you're both five off, if Matt's five over, Paul's five under.
I'm so happy.
I've never been happier with a game already.
There is.
I did add a wrinkle.
If somebody gets it exactly right, second closest gets a bonus point.
Oh.
Hilarious.
That's really funny.
I like that rule.
Yep.
I like it.
All right.
So these are all numbers.
Even when they're exactly right, second closest is still right.
Yeah.
So even if you're right.
It's still going to be numbers.
Yes.
Everything is going to be a number.
Great.
Maybe.
I could find a way.
I mean, you could find a way, but it's going to be really hard to input into the spreadsheet.
All of these numbers are based off of a Google AI, so we can trust that source.
As of getting warmed up.
Paul's just yelling out numbers.
I thought he was just yelling numbers.
Yeah.
I'm just yelling out some numbers.
You were right.
He's yelling out numbers.
Starting with the first question.
Jacob, you are first on the list.
All right.
So you'll go first.
All three of you will give your answers and then I'll give you the right result.
You're not the boss of me.
How many hotel rooms are there in the Las Vegas Valley?
Las Vegas Valley.
So all of Las Vegas area.
Yeah.
Not just the strip.
For a hint, according to Google, there's 50,000 on the strip.
Yeah.
I think it's like 200.
I'll say 225,000.
225,000.
Some people would say that differently.
Some people might.
Matt.
Those people have two not bloody eyes.
225,000.
I will go with 175,000.
Interesting.
Some people would have said that differently.
175,000.
Paul?
300,000.
Wow.
I'm trying numbers.
All right.
The actual answer.
Thank you very much.
Nailed it.
150,000.
859.
Which makes Matt our closest guess.
One point.
Nope.
That's not right.
159, which makes Matt our closest guess one point.
Nope.
That's not one point to Matt.
No, it's one point to Jacob.
Jacob, our second closest.
Yes.
Damn it.
All right.
One second.
I'm great at this game.
One of my equations got broken.
He's already having a hard time with it, but I'm great at it.
Okay.
150,000.
I'm locked in now.
I've got it.
Yeah.
Sorry.
One second.
I have never been more angry that we're not on video for a show.
We're not on video for how many shows in a row, and we're not on for this one.
Paul is just a face and a sea of comfort around him.
Keeping it in Vegas parking and weather related, going with Matt first on this one.
How many jets, blasters, and nozzles are there in the Bellagio fountains?
Oh, fuck.
What counts as a jet, a blaster, or a nozzle?
Well, the jets is a gang.
Nozzles are time travelers.
When you're a nozzle, you're a nozzle all the way.
Nozzles are just, you know, idiots.
Muggles.
Nozzles is what we call the people watching the show.
So it's totally not just jets.
It's jets.
Nozzles.
Everything.
Nozzles in Aries.
Nozzles.
Nozzles squirt water up in the area.
800.
Matt guesses 800.
Paul?
I'm going to need about 350.
How is it that Paul isn't drunk?
I'm going to say, uh, 801.
801.
All right.
There are 1,214 jets, which means Jacob would be closest.
So Matt gets the point.
I thought it was going to be like seven something or six something.
I love it.
It's already the much better version of Price is Right.
I love this.
I gotta fix this because I just realized there was one little error in my equations.
You're cooking, buddy.
All right.
How many pounds of ice cream, we're starting with Paul this time.
How many pounds of ice cream were used for the world's largest ice cream sundae made
in 1988 by Palm Dairy?
Ten pounds.
Ten pounds of ice cream is the world's largest ice cream sundae.
All right, Jacob.
Wait, what?
This way?
Beat it.
Beat that.
Is that right?
Paul?
Good luck.
Good luck being better than second best on that.
I'm going to say...
How much?
More than 30.
Oh, really?
More than 30?
I only said 10.
Oh, I don't know what you said.
I said 10.
800 pounds.
800.
Oh my God.
That's insane.
And Matt?
Eleven.
Oh, you sneaky fuck.
The correct answer is 44687.
Jacob would have been closest, but due to math, Matt is second now.
I played it right.
He gamesmanshiped it properly there by knowing that Paul was so far off that you could be
one better than him and be correct.
That's it.
I was close.
This might give an even bigger advantage to the person who goes third.
That's true.
Well, I mean, it depends on genuine answer or not.
Right.
All right.
Next up.
That's a genuine answer.
This one we are starting with Jacob.
We're back to the top.
As of May 19th, 2025...
Ask something about ghosts.
How many episodes of The Simpsons have aired?
Something about ghosts.
I asked for a ghost question.
Oh, Simpsons episodes?
How many have been?
As of when?
As of May 19th, the most recent airing of their most recent episode.
So there have been 532 episodes.
532, Matt?
What episode?
530.
All right.
There have been 790 episodes.
Locked in.
Yes!
No.
Locked in.
Wait, what did I say?
You said 532.
I got it.
I said 532?
Paul said 530.
So he's second closer.
Oh, in my mind I said 522.
I don't even know what I said anymore.
All right.
Starting with Matt.
Going in the middle is really tricky.
It really is.
Just say 10.
How many minutes is the combined runtime of all 21 official studio albums by Bruce Springsteen?
Oh.
Wait, what?
Question about ghosts.
How many minutes...
It's spooky season.
...is the runtime of all of 21 of Bruce Springsteen's studio albums?
Wow.
1,800.
Paul?
It's hard to game this one.
Yeah.
1,801.
Ooh.
Jacob.
It'll be weird when Paul gets it on the nose.
Which way is wrong?
Right, right.
So this is the thing, right?
So now you have to figure out what your right answer is in your mind.
Right.
That's it.
And then figure out where you want to be.
So now I have a 50/50 chance.
Well, if Matt is closer to the answer than you are right now...
Not possible.
If Matt is closer to the answer than you are, then you get a point.
If you're closer to the answer than Matt is, then Matt gets a point.
Wait.
No.
But you have to guess and that'll change it all.
Right.
But you said right now.
So I was answering...
Oh, I guess you're right.
I was answering the question that you asked.
Something about ghosts, please.
There's not a lot of ghost math.
Sorry.
Man.
What were the two answers?
1,800.
1,800 from Matt and 1,801 from Paul.
1,802.
Whoa.
All right.
The correct...
All I was between 1,802 and 1,799.
Right.
I'm getting this one locked in.
The correct answer is 1,178 minutes.
Oh, shit.
Paul gets the point.
Oh, yes.
You're the second closest.
Matt was closest with 1,800.
Paul was second with 1,801.
Oh, yes.
So by sandwiching Paul.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I meant through the other...
Yeah, yeah.
Never mind.
But you couldn't have sandwiched yourself in between us.
Right.
That's the move.
Okay.
This is fascinating.
I wanted it between you.
But you couldn't.
But I couldn't that time.
Right.
That's right.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, that is a different...
Because I'm using ghost math.
That's right.
In September.
Okay.
I like this.
Spooky.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think we found a new tactic.
I like this.
That's true.
We definitely found a new tactic.
How many distilleries are currently operating in the United States of America?
Do they count Guam and Taiwan?
Matt.
We are starting with Paul.
It is 2025.
Of course not.
Distillery means makes rum.
Makes alcohol.
Just booze.
Yeah.
Distilleries.
Although it just makes distilled spirits.
So St. Croix counts with Cruz and Rum.
So I'm going to guess there's probably, probably, I'm going to rough guess, let's say a hundred,
no, probably 200 per state.
Per state?
Per state.
Oh!
So 200 times 50?
Do you want us to just tell you now that that's wrong?
Not all states are like Kentucky.
Thank the fuck God.
And the fuck God is my favorite.
Yes.
He's the good one.
Hello.
I am the god of fuck.
Fuck God!
Wait.
Are you done answering?
No.
200 per state is 10,000.
200 per state is not right, so using ghost math.
If this is your first episode of listening to Matt Madley's ice cream social, I'm sorry.
Just stop now.
Just bail.
I really thought he was just relying on Mitzi to do the math, like 200 per state, go for
it.
Whatever you think that might be, Mitzi.
No, no.
We're running with it, buddy.
You got the number in front of you.
Just put me close to it.
Yeah.
No.
Okay.
Well, let's do.
Is this the first guest on this question?
Yes.
5,000.
Okay.
Jacob.
4,999.
Okay.
Now we're playing for shit.
So I get the gamesmanship, right?
Because then if I go somewhere more realistic.
If you go realistic, then you give me the point.
If you go unrealistic, you give Paul the point.
No.
Yes.
You went forward, didn't you?
No.
I went one under you.
He went one below.
So Matt can't get between us.
So he either has to go under or over.
But if he goes over, then that's going to be a point to me.
That's what I just said.
And you followed that up with saying no and then said the same thing.
Basically, I'm in a position to either give Jacob or you a point.
That's the only thing I can do.
That's exactly it.
So the question is, do you think the numbers are less than their numbers?
Or you could get it exactly right and give us two points.
That is true.
That is an opportunity.
Matt, get it exactly right.
All right.
For the sake of getting it exactly right.
Here we go.
Daddy's rolling the dice.
1,321.
Ghost math.
All right.
Matt's answer is two thousand two hundred and thirty, meaning Jacob is second closest.
So Paul was closest.
Yes.
Have you gone over?
No.
No, I was close.
That was closest.
I was way over.
You both are way over.
There's only two thousand places making booze.
Yeah.
Can you imagine?
That's why there's such a shortage.
That's why you can't find booze anywhere.
I'm realizing right now, like, holy shit, why can't I remember any of these answers?
It's because I never have to.
I usually have the computer screen in front of me.
Next up, we've got a fun one.
This is one of my favorite ones.
This is about ghosts.
Are you keeping track of the points?
Yeah.
What have we got?
It is currently a three way tie at two points apiece.
But who has the second most points?
Me.
I am currently winning with the second most points in this game.
How many more questions do you have?
I have four plus a couple of backups.
So a lot of questions.
I got two more.
Two more sounds great.
Then we'll keep going if we want to keep going.
How many college football teams are currently playing football in the Big Ten?
We are starting with Jacob on this.
The Big Ten.
For you non-sportsball fans, this is actually a very good question.
I think like four.
Four is Jacob's guess.
Matt, how many teams are currently playing in the Big Ten?
Ten.
That's a solid guess.
Paul?
Five.
So you're thinking of the Pac-12, which has two teams and not the Big 12, which has 16
teams.
Because you don't math.
Right.
The Big Ten obviously has 18 football teams, which makes Matt the closest guess and Paul
the second closest guess with five.
No, I'm using ghost math.
So currently ghost math is winning the game.
Come at me.
Casper is running this thing.
How many days were there between the groundbreaking and the grand opening of the Fountain Blue
Las Vegas?
Oh Jesus.
Holy shit.
That was a boondoggle.
How many days?
Come on, Paul's doing Kentucky math.
With ghosts.
Who goes first?
This one starts with.
I think I went first last time.
Matt, you start first.
Oh yeah, because I said four on the last one.
1,400.
1,400 days.
Paul, how many days between the groundbreaking to the grand opening?
1,401.
1,400, 1,401, fuck.
So again, like I just decide, I decide who to use it to know who you want to give two
points to.
You're going for it.
I get it.
You did not nail this.
Let's see, 365 times 17.
Oh, you think they did it on the actual anniversary?
No, no, no, but like, oh, but you're just doing that.
It was roughly 17 years.
Was it?
Yeah.
17 years.
It was a fuck ton of time.
Um, so let's see if I go high, Matt gets a point.
If I go low, Paul gets a point, right?
Not 17 years.
Paul has the lead.
Matt has 1,400 guests.
Paul has 1,401.
Ah, okay.
So if you go high, I get a point.
Right.
You go high and I get a point.
Oh, wait, wait.
You say the fountain blue?
Yes.
Oh, one day.
One day.
Yeah, yeah.
One day, Wink.
That's right.
It was one day.
All right.
Well, Jacob was close.
It was, uh, I didn't could find the official day of the groundbreaking, but I found an
article on February 2nd of 2007.
Okay.
And it opened December 13th, 2023.
Yeah.
So 6,158 days.
That was a lot of time.
Five ownership groups, I believe, and multiple other things that happened in that time.
I think a couple of court orders to tear down what had already been constructed.
Yeah.
That means I get the point, right?
Yes.
It does.
Which means right now, Matt and Paul are tied at three, which means Jacob has the second
most points.
And it's a cat's game.
When Matt and Paul are tied and Jack versus nerd, Jacob wins.
Second most points win the game?
Eh, we could do that if we really want to.
That's really funny.
Second most points wins the game.
Oh, that adds a whole nother layer of strategy.
I have three, I have four more questions.
We can play for second, second, second if we want.
No.
Let's wrap it up.
No, that's good.
One more, but this has been fun.
Is it about ghosts?
All right.
This is, this is one less.
I don't have it.
He doesn't have any about ghosts.
Well, not with that attitude.
All right.
We're going to go with this one.
I have two that I'm trying to between.
What is the current cost to join the Las Vegas A's season ticket holder priority list in American
dollars?
Oh, I was going to say your pride, but that doesn't.
Starting with Jacob.
Oh shit.
God damn it.
Why does it start with me?
Um, $472 Matt, this is just to get on the list.
This is the, this is the down payment to put your secure, your spot for the A's season
tickets.
What did you say?
$472, $473.
All right, Paul.
It is definitely more than that.
But I'm going to say 470.
What'd you say, Jacob?
Two.
That's a four 72, four 72 50.
This is actually the only time you can technically get in there with a middle number or it gets
even better guys.
The current price to join the A's season ticket list is $19 a one cent.
Oh shit.
I got that right.
I still won.
No, I knew you got the point.
Yeah.
I thought it was like a hundred bucks.
So here's the thing.
Paul got the point, which now gives Paul four points, which means Matt wins the game cause
he has three points and Jacob loses with two.
We did it guys.
Wouldn't that make me the first runner up?
First runner up.
I like it.
Excellent new game, Missoula.
Have fun programming that one.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
I, well, here's the thing.
If you were to host a live again, I think the way to do it would be, um, for all of
us to-
You would write your answer down and then show it so that we can't do it this way.
Yeah.
So you can't do gamesmanship.
Oh.
So even if we did on zoom, we could, we could, we could private message you.
Yeah.
Our guesses without you.
Right.
That's something that we can, or, or we can-
Or we can just write it down.
Or just write it down and hold it and hold it.
Yeah.
We can figure it out.
We could write it down and just be able to hold it to the camera.
Normally I'm like the lowest tech guy.
I can't even think of a lower tech solution.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Matt's like, just make all the answers below 10 and we can just use our fingers.
Perfect.
You know what?
That's actually better.
Just flash our answers.
For one of them, for one of them is not a bad idea.
This game is all within 10 to one to 10, feel free to sign your answers to me at any time.
We don't have anyone else to thank right now because we are in the, the back and I've done
a bad job at prepping for this show.
That's we're going to do a lot.
We got a lot going on.
We got a lot of thanking.
We got a lot of jiggering with our Patreon for something by with a brand new course.
Thanks for having me gentlemen.
Or an updated version of the game, a fun, a fun version.
Yes.
And thank you to everybody who supports us over on Patreon.
You are the reason that we're able to do this show.
You are the reason that we are able to do things like Scoop Fest this week, which is
the reason that you're getting an insane show right now.
There's a lot of reasons and they're all for you.
Congratulations.
Yeah.
For anybody who has left a bunch of money by their unraptured neighbors, you can send
that our way.
Yep.
I was all ready for it.
It is so weird hearing these sound clips not at one and a half feet.
And if you want more questions about ghosts, go to FartsInTheBag.biz.
Bring it.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts, farts in a bag.
Next.
Second closest.
Just ghosts.
Oops.
All ghosts.
That's FartsInTheBag.biz along with PreachingFun.com.
It takes you to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can upkeep this
show on the air.
Like I said, the Patreons are the reason that we are able to do this show twice a week each
and every week, no matter what is going on in life like this week.
So here you go.
Enjoy.
Take care.
Thanks.
Thanks, everybody.
I was going to ask Paul, did you like the video I made for the bucket show this week
with their pop-up guys?
Yes.
I really thought they were going to kiss at the end.
I was disappointed.
There's a lot of sexual tension between those two dolls.
I know.
It was really heavy.
Thanks a lot for this, everybody.
Take care of yourselves out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
I did like it.
I liked it.
It's funny though.
It's just somewhere in the middle.
That's all.
There's a bunch of Christians who aren't Christian at all right now.
There's a bunch of other Christians who are diving way too in on this Rapture stuff.
But that's me in the middle.
But those aren't Christians either.
That's not what Christianity is not about going up into space.
Wait, whose Rapture is that Christian?
It is a weird small sect thing that came up in like the 20s.
It's not truly Christian.
It's evangelical at best.
There's not a way to buy yourself out of it.
So it's definitely not from the Catholic Church.
Exactly.
It's a hoohah.
If it can't be cured with a plenary indulgence, I don't want to hear about it tomorrow.