Oh hello there, I am so glad you are here because I want to thank you, the ice cream truck driver.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
These are the folks that deliver that ice cream straight to your ear holes.
Right now I'd like to thank Travis Jagre, Thunder, Cougar Falcon, Scoop, the lost ice cream truck driver,
Slurpee Caillet motherfucker, Scoop Cotta, Scoop Dijor, Scoop Brady, and Sax Guy, Jimmy D. Scoop.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
Here's a show.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Scoopfest coming up at the end of the month.
We won't talk about it the whole episode, but I'm going to say it now.
Scoopfest.com, head over there, join us here in beautiful Las Vegas at the end of September.
It's going to be awesome.
So soon.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly.
Also sitting in Las Vegas is me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
Hey everybody.
That's a nice hat tonight, Jacob.
Thank you, thank you.
I like that one.
Paul, you were asleep, so we had our first Scoopfest crisis, but you were asleep, so we didn't bother you.
Yeah.
I appreciate that.
What happened?
Well, that lineup subject to change asterisk is really coming into play this time.
Okay.
Yeah.
The asterisk has changed.
All right.
Just one thing.
Just one of them.
Right, but we already had some stuff made up that's going to have to just be like, well-
Oh no, we've already gotten-
Lanyards and stuff.
Yeah.
No, we've already gotten sub people in, and yeah, we're all good.
Oh.
Yes.
So lanyards weren't printed with the old info yet?
Oh, no, the lanyards are printed.
The schedule on the lanyards-
We're fucked on lanyards.
We're fucked.
That's fine.
There's one event on the lanyard that's going to be a different name than what's on the lanyard.
That's okay.
That's the way it goes.
Yeah.
In the same time slot.
No problem.
I appreciate you guys letting me sleep.
I, again, like I said, been fighting a cold.
You can hear it in my chest.
My head is really hurting today, and I slept in because I was off today, and Ann didn't
go in until late, so she was handling the little dogs.
Man, I was out.
I was in bed till 11, so yeah, and it was-
P.M.
11 a.m.
Slept all day.
Yeah, I slept all day.
No, no, no.
That's fine.
Now, does Ann factor in your sickness when she hates you for being a wuss, for not going
into work because you weren't scheduled?
Smart.
I'll have you know that that all got resolved, so my non-schedule had two-
Ranch Slunk in the chat is already blaming the microwave hot dogs for your illness, Paul.
Two components.
No.
I agree.
Ranch Slunk, by the way, is correct.
I didn't have any microwave hot dogs yesterday.
We had pizza.
Ann and I ordered pizza.
Fire it up the oven?
No, we got Domino's.
We got Domino's.
It was great fun.
We were having one of those nights.
We were really being fun with each other.
We love just hanging out on the couch being catty bitches.
We watch this show right now called, oh, what is it called, Stewart's Crossing?
It's not Stewart's Crossing.
Sullivan's Crossing.
Have you guys heard of this show?
I've heard of it.
I've not seen it.
Canadian Scoop Crystals is pumping her fist.
Yeah, it's a Canuck production.
It is heavily Canadian, this show.
They got-
Sponsored by Tim Artins.
They got some folks in the show who you would refer to in Canada as Native characters, like
Native Americans, Native North Americans, so they got some of that.
It's sort of like Northern Exposure, but not funny and-
Oh, so just like Northern Exposure.
No, it's not funny.
Stay down, Northern Exposure.
And it leans pretty heavy into stereotypical, romance-y dumb stuff.
First Nations, first people, yes.
So they have this guy.
It's the guy from Gilmore Girls who was Luke, who I can't remember.
The romantic lead in Gilmore Girls.
Does that give you a-
Luke from Gilmore Girls?
Listen, buddy.
I've watched that series as well.
These are the shows that I watch with the wife.
If you just want like a timeout, Paul, and get all your facts together, we can do that.
We can figure out something.
I'm just saying.
You keep asking us for things that definitely Jacob and I have never come close to watching.
You've never seen Gilmore Girls.
Stop yelling at me.
No, that's a snappy dialogue.
Good show.
That's a good show.
Snappy dialogue?
See you later, guys.
I have to go stream the Gilmore Girls.
Matt has left the Zoom chat.
Matt will be back on the show after he's watched the Gilmore Girls.
Hey guys, I'm back.
I just want a preview.
I can't believe the snappiness.
So much snappiness.
Anyway, it's a good little show.
But this Sullivan's Crossing is cray-cray, cray-cray.
The guy is basically just an unlikable character.
He's just an old curmudgeon who runs a camp.
He's got this Sullivan's Crossing.
He goes by "call me Sully, bleh I'm Sully."
Name a Sullivan who wasn't called Sully.
That's what I know.
Who was like, "call me Van."
Right.
No, he's just Sully.
"Call me Van."
Van's Crossing.
His daughter...
There's one of them out there that I just call Goose Killer now.
Wait, does that mean the whole time it's been Sullivan, Sully Van Halen?
Is that the way we should be?
Oh my gosh, it should have been Sully Van Halen.
Maybe it's Sylvanian Van Halen.
Sylvanian Halen.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to our show.
We are Sullivan Halen.
We are the number one tribute rock band.
We celebrate Van Halen and Sullivan's Crossings.
Sullivan Morrison.
It is the best two things.
Sullivan Halen.
Here we are.
Sullivan Morrison.
If I had anything to reference Sullivan's Crossings, I would do so right now for the
sake of the joke.
His estranged daughter comes back to Sullivan's Crossing.
She's gone on to be a brain surgeon.
She's a literal...
Supposed to be a brain surgeon.
Now, Matt, how many years of education...
You know, I've got a bad dare.
I even reach her.
You know, I've got the hots.
Yeah, I've got the hots for a teacher.
That's it.
Matt.
You gotta talk to your boys.
I know what I was going to say.
Right now.
They gotta do a couple Van Halen covers.
Yup.
Don't say anything else, Paul.
I'm done.
It's on our WhatsApp thread.
Yup.
It'll be on there.
I've got shoes burning down the avenue.
I'm hot for teacher.
What do you say?
What do you know?
I'm hot for teacher.
Eruption is what I was just thinking of.
Which one?
Yeah.
Eruption.
Just the guitar solo.
On accordion or harpsichord?
Yeah.
That's it.
Good Lord.
That's...
Panama.
I've never been to Panama.
I've never been.
I'll never go.
Panama.
The country's quite large.
I'm stuck here.
Are there any pubs in Panama?
You know what his son was named?
Wolfgang.
Wolfgang Sullivan Halen.
I love to skip and dance.
No.
So the girl comes back and she's a neurosurgeon.
After all of that.
I'm so sorry.
She's a neurosurgeon.
How many years would you think would take to become a neurosurgeon?
Eight.
Study.
At least eight.
Yeah.
So we're experimenting around 24 tops.
Okay.
So we're already starting to do ramp jumps of logic.
Canadian Dookie Houser for those making a temporary reference.
Not even.
But she's not with it.
She misses everything.
Everything.
Her dad's a former alcoholic, recovering alcoholic.
She just misses everything.
Everything.
One of the things that happened in this last episode that we watched, he gets hospitalized
with a heart condition, had a heart something go on.
And he's in the hospital and around all of this is the looming possibility that he's
going to lose this Sullivan's Crossing campground because he can't pay the bills.
And Anne and I just looked at each other and like, he had a heart attack and was hospitalized.
If this was America, the show is over.
He has gone into full on forever debt.
He can't even do bankruptcy with medical debt.
He's done.
We were just like, this is amazing to see this from a Canadian perspective.
And he also got belligerent in the hospital and pushed a doctor and stuff.
And we're like, there would have been a security officer there shooting him in the head if
this was the States.
This is not, it's just so crazy to watch with a non-Canadian eye.
Oh, that's true.
Scoop Jesus in the chat is pointing out that Breaking Bad, just the concept of the show
of Breaking Bad does not work in Canada.
Right.
Because the whole impetus for the show is that he gets sick and can't afford the cancer
treatment.
Right.
That's number one.
That was everyone's number one takeaway from Breaking Bad and that's why you saw so much
medical reform.
That's right.
Instead of medical reform, we have pizzas on roofs.
It is crazy that when you really see what we have on roofs and blue math, you look at
any hit drama, exactly what we got any hit drama that we've had of like the last 20 years.
Yeah.
None of it.
None of it works outside of the States because of the bullshit that we have integrated into
our society.
Well, so many movies and then you get into like the dated stuff.
So many movies in the States, you got the healthcare stuff and then like the older movies,
the plot goes away if anybody has a cell phone.
Right.
All these things.
It's great.
Like the whole movie goes away if things just aren't terrible.
Yeah.
Well, I mean the show, The Wire, is one of the most celebrated shows we've made.
We don't need wires anymore.
Right.
The Wire, we don't need a wire.
Every season, that's it.
That whole show is just built on, every season was a different systematic failure of our
government bureaucracy.
Yeah.
It's just wild.
And then you get into the show that kind of started all of those back in the day on HBO,
you had Oz.
And it's just about like if you have any prison reform or if you have decent, like a decent
justice system, you don't have that show.
Right.
No, that show is about hot prison sex and I'm here for it.
Oh, man.
Well, I'm not saying they're not great shows or that they don't have the amount of prison
sex that I need to get through the day.
I'm just saying they don't work outside of the US.
I'm happy with every other part of them.
But we're just, we're just watching that show and just mocking it at every turn and having
a good laugh here and there.
And really enjoys it though.
And it is kind of a nice relaxing show.
And I mean, it's honestly, it's like, it's fantasy for us.
We're like, Oh man, you imagine living somewhere where people could talk to their neighbors
and then you could go and get taken care of when you had a heart attack and not lose your
fucking place of business.
Oh God.
Not free enough.
Oh yeah.
You're right.
Totally not free.
Not free enough to suffer.
Where is your freedom to pay?
Oh, well, it's a weird topic to bring up on a comedy show, but we were on the air the
other day during the Charlie Kirk stuff.
Oh no.
We can't talk about that.
We're not talking about it at all.
All I want to talk about with that is that it fucked me up for the day.
Well, sure.
Yeah.
Getting, getting, uh, getting news that someone just got killed for being on shows, voicing
opinions like it fucked me up for the whole.
I made a point to go to my comic book store, even though it was late in the day and I needed,
I needed just, I just picked up a few, oh, but here's okay.
So to shift topics completely, do it, do it because we, we were on the air when it came
out and then the, and then the show came out and everything, it feels weird to not say
something about it, but that's, that's kind of what happened right when we were on.
And then, and then, yes, the last couple of days have been not so weird.
Not so weird.
Yeah.
Uh, bad news, Matt, guys, guys, I got it.
I was reading up on, on, uh, Israel and Gaza.
Should we just go there?
Should we?
No, no, no.
Let's just, let's shift over to a fun topic at, uh, at the comic book shop.
I got to pick this up.
It's a brand new arc, brand new start of a new run of powers.
Oh, Matt's kids are going to be so, so I'm so sorry.
That your son is probably going to find more of these books now and just go to Whackety
Jackety town for everybody on Twitch, uh, just open up the centerfold, show everybody
the centerfold.
Let's see.
Let's see what the centerfold is.
Don't do it on Twitch.
Look at the next issue.
Oh my goodness.
Oh wow.
That's just, that's just, uh, jizz.
Yeah.
I don't know what's going on there.
It's not even drawn on there.
Paul just showed us his jisms now on a comic book.
I will show you.
That's just him.
Speaking of those laminated, speaking of snapping dialogue, this is Bendis dialogue right here.
That's what, that, that's what Bendis is known for.
Just talkie talkie talkie talkie talkie talkie talkie.
His comments.
If you can't see the video, Paul just held up a comic book to the camera.
It was a full panel.
Just chuck a block with a word.
It looked like a lot of speech bubbles.
Lot of word balloons.
Yes.
Uh, that's some, that's a, that's a Bendis hallmark right there.
And I'm pleased to see that again.
I'm looking forward to reading this new arc and seeing where it goes.
So yay.
New powers is out everybody.
New powers.
Yeah.
Dead last celebrating as well.
That's good.
And what else?
Oh, and then, uh, and then I got this too.
This is for those other super nerds out there, Transformers issue 24.
This is, uh, the culmination of the two year arc done by Daniel Warren Johnson, uh, and
uh, Jorge Corona, uh, this is the end of this story and this book has been incredibly successful.
Um, what's his name?
Kirkman from walking dead.
This is one of his side project things he's taking over the main writing.
So that's going to be really interesting.
I would love to see the possibility of a Kirkman Transformers storyline that could be made
television or film thing.
Preach.
Right.
Are you think, you know, are you, do you know what Kirkman would add to that, to that comic
Paul?
What would he, what would he add?
Snappy dialogue.
He's my dad.
He's the guy behind you would open, you would open the comic and it would snap right back
close.
He doesn't have some pretty good dialogue.
I mean, he's, he's the guy behind walking dead.
He's the guy behind, uh, invincible he, and I would love to see an invincible style cartoon
helmed by Robert Kirkman for transformers.
I think that'd be awesome.
Are you watching any of the peacemaker Paul peacemaker peacemaker.
Oh, I haven't watched the new season yet.
It's yeah.
I haven't either.
The first season was so good.
I really liked the first season.
So funny.
Is it good?
Okay.
Yes.
How many episodes are we in now?
I think three.
I watched two, but I think, I think I have one on the hopper.
Yeah.
Scoop Jesus in the chat.
You're I'm, I'm with you.
We're, we're letting it get a little ahead and then we'll probably, that's kind of my
thing.
Yeah.
I always want to.
That's what I'm doing with task.
Oh, oh, we tried, we tried to watch it, but I'm not trying it yet.
I'm waiting to the four or five episodes to watch it yesterday during all the, you know,
we're watching it and, and Anne's like, I'm already just like a bundle of nerves and nothing's
even happened in this thing.
Like nothing is, nothing happens in the first 20 minutes or so that we watched.
And she's just like, and I was like, fine, I'll turn it off.
And she's like, and I'm like, we just watched that evil lives here, latest episode with
that horrible kid that ended up going crazy, killed his mom, all that nutty stuff.
And she's like, yeah, but that's true.
This is made up.
Let's just watch.
What's already actually happened.
Why do you have to keep making up horrible stuff like, okay, you're right.
You're right.
This is on the reality of the horror show that is existent and not the fictional horror
show.
Also, we are going to talk about Gaza.
Oh my God, it's just outrageous.
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one.
I stopped watching.
Did you ever get into nerd core rap?
MC Chris.
Um, yes, I love MC Chris and, uh, who's the other one that I like?
Well, there's a couple, but, um, there's another guy that used to do, uh, packs every year.
He was a, uh, mainstay, but yeah, but MC Chris is still my nerd core rap guy.
Why?
What's that?
I turned out.
I liked a band that was nerd core rap without me knowing it was nerd core rap.
I just said when I looked them up recently, I was literally on the plane and I was like,
I want to listen to something.
I basically get, uh, like, I'm like, why?
I would say I have nothing to listen to and I used to listen to a ton of music and I'm
always like at a loss of what to listen to.
I'd do the same things, right?
Uh huh.
Um, I'll go into David Bowie or Tom Waits, Jag or something like that.
And then it's predictable.
Um, I'm on a good music kick right now.
I'll tell you about it when you're done.
Was it?
So I was like, Oh, there was this band that crushed, uh, I saw them multiple times because
they just were always in lineups.
They were never the headliner.
They're always in lineups.
A band called Two Skinny Jays.
Are you familiar with them?
I have heard of them.
I am not familiar with their oeuvre.
They have a, they have one major album called Volumizer.
Okay.
And I put it on and I was like, I thought I was going to basically put it on, like maybe
be embarrassed or just nostalgic.
Uh huh.
It is still a really good album.
It's a bang, huh?
Crazy, well-written lyrics.
Yeah.
Really good hooks.
They're very good musicians.
Um, it's really, it's not, um, you know, constructed hooks.
It's th they were a live band.
They rushed at, uh, the year and a half in college, somebody saw them twice in concert
and two different locations based out in the East coast somewhere.
Yeah.
That's why Matt didn't finish college.
He was stupid.
He followed around the Two Skinny Jays.
Like, here's another person I saw too much of without being like a huge fan, uh, G love
and the special sauce.
Have you, do you have the special sauce?
Yes.
I remember.
Oh, they had a couple of hits.
Yeah.
They're more mainstream than Two Skinny Jays.
They actually had, they had a couple of legit hits.
They were out of Philadelphia and lyrically, it's, it's inescapable that they are from
Philadelphia.
I say that as a Springsteen fan, um, he never sings about Jersey, but, um, what is, what's
one of the jams that Two Skinny Jays does that's, uh, grown up is a good one to, to,
to, I think I may know these, this song that you've rattled something in my head from way
back.
Yeah.
Um, and I was just growing up is grownups is the, uh, the movie that they wrote starring
Adam Sandler.
That's right.
Theme song.
Yep.
Um, yeah.
Uh, the opening song of Horns of Destruction is really great.
A Horns of Destruction is really, really funny.
Uh, Lemon Drop is a good one.
Uh, but yeah, I was just going through it and I was like really like, oh man, I'm usually
embarrassed about my music taste and, and, uh, there was actually one band I thought
of it.
I cannot go back, but I laughed when I thought of their name.
Okay.
So I won't even go back and listen to it.
It's too embarrassing.
Oh no.
I remember cause I remember her at this really, really cringy incident of when I was on this,
the team bus for the basketball team.
Okay.
And our team, our team was, uh, basically half white and half black at my, at my JV
squad, uh, when I was playing basketball and, um, spoiler alert, um, the black guys were
better at basketball.
Uh, and, um, uh, Oh, that's where that rumor started.
And so they would, the, the, the cooler, honestly, the cooler black kids would go sit in the
back of the bus.
Like that's the way it works.
Right.
And they would all be, you know, hit, hit, hitting, uh, you know, put their headphones
on listening to different discs and their disc bands and I got turned into like one
song by a rapper called me fi me.
Okay.
I can't even, I won't, if I listen to them now, I'll just vomit, uh, uh, out of embarrassment.
No, I had me fi me on and I was like, Oh, I might know a really awesome rapper that
maybe they're not familiar with.
And so I remember like bobbing my head and like really showing that you were doing some
hip hopping.
Yeah.
I remember telling that you were, that you were enjoying the hip hop cooler black kids
to know that I'm listening to hip hop and they're going to ask me who, and I'm going
to say me fi me and they're going to go, what?
And that's exactly what happened with the exception of the positive reaction.
Okay.
They were like, get that trash out of here.
They're like, I never heard of it.
I was like, yeah, I heard one.
He's got one trick.
That's okay.
And then the guy was like, oh, I'm like, well, that's all right.
That's a start.
And then they just made fun of me for being into it.
They're like, but you were really into it.
Oh man.
See, it's not least worst nightmare.
This is, this is our worst nightmare.
This is our difference in age.
This is our difference in age showing.
And I was just lucky.
I was just lucky because I was a few years ahead of you and in the hip hop stuff, which
I'm just going to argue was a golden age of hip hop that came up in.
And so you would talk about someone who never gets embarrassed.
I don't get embarrassed.
I don't give a shit.
I have, I have always put my freak flag very high and not giving a fuck what people think
I would be in the back of the bus with my boom box on field trips and my two deck cassette
player and I would vacillate between body count, public enemy fear of a black planet
and the Disney afternoon soundtrack and they might be giants.
I mean, what all over the place, crazy shit.
You know what I mean?
I, I didn't give a fuck.
I was playing all the hits, all the hits, all over the place and then I really lucked
out.
I really scored some points at governor's college.
Yes.
Paul definitely had the over the shoulder boom box program.
Don't think anything else for a moment.
No, it was too wide for, I mean, you could, it was, but it had a hand.
Yeah.
It was a governor's college program.
We had a field trip out to a mall one day, Paul put that double decker right in his lap,
like a villain with a cat.
That's exactly how I rocked it.
What I did have was a 60 cassette case that I had over my ammunition belt.
I was a straight up, no, not an amp, but it was a padded case, a bandolier, a padded case
that helps 30, 30 cassettes, one was like a movie poster for commando with just cassette
decks all over them.
Just Chewbacca with, with tapes on my, on my bandolier.
I was ready at any time, whatever the, whatever the thing I had, I had everything, man.
I had it all.
Scoop Jesus says you look like John Popper.
I had, I had Pantera, I had fucking, um, uh, what's his name?
The Harry Connick dude.
I had it all.
I would go between Pantera and Harry Connick in the drop of a hat.
But at governor's scholars, we went to this mall field trip and we bought some stuff and
I bought, um, tribe called quest low end theory album.
It had just come out, it came out that week.
And so getting on the bus, uh, some of the other kids and, uh, some of the other hip
pop heads were like, Oh, let's listen to that.
And so they played it on the bus speakers.
So the whole bus was listening to low end theory on the ride.
Thanks to my purchasing, uh, finesse of making sure that I got that new tribe album, which
was just fed.
That's just a fantastic album.
That's a masterpiece.
So you're welcome, everyone that's hero.
And Scoop is showing exactly how Spock would have handled me, uh, but, uh, it was a different
time before the rise of headphones like that.
Yep.
You know who else listened to a whole bunch of Mattingly's cassettes at the back of a
school bus?
Mattingly didn't know they were there though.
That's the following sponsor.
I would have been bopping my head so hard.
Yeah.
I know you were.
Um, uh, today's show is brought to you by women brought to you by Tom Cruise.
That's from MLK in 2025.
Today's sponsor is women brought to you by Tom Cruise.
Hey everybody.
It's me, Tom Cruise.
I'd like to present women.
I'd like to, but I can't.
Yeah.
Oh, I gotta run.
I gotta run to my next next.
Shoot.
Oh boy.
I'd also have trouble presenting women because my good friend David Miscavige misplaces his
and we don't try to find them.
And that's just how it goes.
Allegedly.
Who knows?
I don't know.
Yeah.
I was thinking about Tom Cruise this morning and then everyone makes fun of him for running
and he always likes to run in his films and he always runs full speed.
And then I was like, Oh, I, I couldn't do that.
Like if I booked a part and they're like, this is where you run full speed to the airport
for like 30 seconds.
I'd be like, Oh, this is going to look terrible.
I don't think anybody makes fun of Tom Cruise though.
Like we don't make fun of his running because he's an older gentleman and is bad at running.
We make fun of it because he does it so often.
Well, he writes, I don't think there's any question that Tom Cruise is in great shape
for a man of his age.
Yeah.
It's not like he's like, Oh, I have to do this.
He's coming to the producers to be like, can I dangle from a plane?
This is the part where I run.
Yeah.
He's making it happen.
Matt.
Don't feel bad that way.
You're going to be fine.
In today's modern age, what sense does it make not to be on roller skates or some sort
of ambulatory device that could make you go even faster than running?
I was thinking there was like, they'd have to write in like an electric scooter for me
to be like, and I was like, Oh, that'd be really fun just to actually see electric scooter
chase.
Yeah.
Like really fucking like born identity level, like, but just pushing that little thumb button.
It'd be funny.
Yeah.
Man, I am a sucker for those.
I treated myself in San Antonio.
I always go try to get my steps in, right?
So I try to get my 10,000 steps in.
And so I kept telling myself that I'd rather those electric scooters, but every time I
just had, I'd always, it was hot, so I just had to get my steps in close at night, close
to midnight or whatever.
But the last night I go, Oh, I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to walk.
I only had to walk for like 15 minutes.
I go, I'm going to walk 15 minutes straight out of town.
Okay.
Find one of those scooters and ride it back.
Yeah.
And that's what I did my last night.
And man, I just, I know it's so dumb.
They go like whatever 15 miles an hour, but bopping and zipping through the streets at
night.
And you're just going all over it because it was a Sunday night, right?
The whole, that whole week, whenever I'm there, it's like a show because the river walks the
center of attention and it builds during the week and then it's crazy in the weekends.
And then Sunday, it's like, you feel like it's great.
Like receding.
It's probably busier than Vegas right now.
Probably.
Although I guess the reports coming from people who worked with that company are that tourism
is down in a lot of places, not just Vegas.
No.
Yeah.
Sure.
What?
Yeah.
Probably unrelated to anything else.
In the United States of America?
Yeah.
The land of dreams.
I mean, the rivers flow with milk and honey because if people pick up the news, it's nothing
but sunshine and rainbows here.
Right.
This is just like the Garden of Eden out here.
On the good ship, lollipop.
But so no, so Sunday night it was dead.
And so I basically had the streets of San Antonio to myself.
That's right.
I want to say it very romantically like that.
I just zipped around.
I was loving it.
I probably look like a big idiot, but I had loved it.
I had my Mi Fi Mi on my headphones and.
Great.
I was going to say, were you listening to Streets of Philadelphia and replacing it?
San Antonio.
I was just singing that loudly to myself.
The streets of San Antonio.
It almost fits the meter.
It means red stick, I'd yell as I drove down the street.
That's right.
Did you, have you had a show since, since you've modified your language yet?
No, not yet.
Not yet.
My next magic show will be at Scoop Fest.
Okay.
Where I'm only doing things they haven't seen.
Sweet.
New, new stuff.
Bunch of a, bunch of feet stuff.
Yeah.
A lot of feet stuff.
A lot of feet.
A lot of bare feet.
Magic.
Yeah.
Borrowed, borrowed and returned feet.
Oh my God.
Foot to impossible location.
Matt.
You know.
Foot tip.
Foot tip in this trick.
You know, we have yet to actually implement with PNT the magic that is magic Wanda.
That's true.
How about we have magic Wanda and your bare foot with googly eyes on it.
Yeah.
And we call him Presto.
Presto.
Magic Wanda and Presto.
Huh, huh?
Is somebody just laying underneath the curtain with their foot up in the air?
Dude, that's a YouTube channel if I've ever heard one right there.
I know.
That's gold.
It's also in 12 years the best idea that Paul has come up with and he's like, pitch this
to Penn, Matt.
They did sled a foot.
This is my foot.
Did they?
Three seasons ago.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Okay.
That was one where I helped work on that trick and I gave Penn a button on it where after
the whole thing was over, he says like, oh, you can put those cards back together or whatever.
And then she, the volunteer goes to do it and I go, no, with your feet.
And they like that.
And that was always there.
They're out.
I was at a record of Penn Sunday School and Penn said, Matt, you are a genius.
And then Teller wrote me an email saying, you are a genius.
Wow.
And I didn't know why.
And then Penn told me at Penn Sunday School is that basically like this very hammered
girl came up to do a sleight of feet.
And when they yell, no, with your feet, she was like, okay.
And she just flipped herself upside down and started moving with her feet.
And she wasn't wearing any underwear.
So she just was flashing Penn and Teller.
Yeah.
And they just sat there with a private show and they were like, what a great profession
we have.
What an odd job we have chosen for ourselves.
Yeah.
So they both wrote me privately to let me know I was a genius.
Great job, buddy.
Oh, I got to tell you my music thing.
I've been on a kick lately, full albums.
So all I do when I run through an album now is I do a Google search or a chat GPT search,
whatever search engine I've got kind of most handy.
And I ask like, what is the best album from and I just pick a random decade or year or
whatever.
And then I listen to that full album.
But it's always an album that was made to be a complete album.
So like this week I've listened to Elton John, Yellow Brick Road.
And yesterday I just finished Purple Rain.
I just finished the Purple Rain album.
And holy fuck, Prince is really good.
What?
Breaking news?
Yeah.
Prince is really good at this.
I knew what he was doing.
Like when doves cry, go listen to when doves cry, do yourself a favor, listen to when doves
cry and it is like it's a perfect song.
The reason it's so ubiquitous is just fucking perfect.
Yeah, he's really, really good.
It is one of those things where it is worth a re-listen for those things.
And you're right, Jacob.
I will take you up on that because he was so popular that like you understood music
to be that like, for instance, that my kids started listening to Michael Jackson's music,
which is just a no inner conflict there.
But the thing is like, you're like, oh, he really just had like, his voice honestly is
like, it's unique and it's okay.
It's not amazing, right?
But he had two superpowers that he could dance his face off, really believe in dancing, and
his ear for sounds, like is just the actual composition of sounds and music is that.
So I think like, I got distracted because someone put my website in the chat.
I don't know why.
Oh, that was me.
Sorry.
In the chat, somebody was asking where they could find dates for your show, so I put your
website up.
Oh yeah.
I haven't updated it.
You got to go to my Instagram for the updated dates, but I got to update it.
My next dates are, and this is really important, Scoopfest, then we're going on a bunch of
cruise ships, and then I'm going to be in Sparta, New Jersey.
Sparta.
On October 17th, doing two shows there, and then yeah, and then after that there'll be
a special show in October that we haven't announced yet, but I'll announce after Scoopfest.
Yes.
Because it evolves palmatically.
And um, what else?
I think, I think, I'm not doing, I'm about to enter cruise ship season, which is why
I'm being, this is, I'm going to do a bunch of cruise ships through the holidays.
Cruise ships through the holidays?
I'll be back in San Antonio, November 3rd through the 8th.
But the big thing, I'll be making a big stick, because then come the turn of the year, Jokers
of Magic is going back on tour, when all those dates are locked in, that's going to be at
the start of the new year.
There'll be two different tours, one in January and one in March, and we'll be all over the
place and I'll be pumping those dates a ton.
That's good to hear.
Because that's the show I want to be doing.
Right.
Yes.
That show is awesome.
If you didn't get to see the first run, it is such a fun show.
Anyhow, I want to go back and listen to those Prince albums because I actually want to understand
that these sounds didn't really exist.
Right.
Yeah, because I grew up with those being music and so you're like, "Yeah, it's pretty good."
But I think it's so cool to go back and really hear the sounds and the tones of the instrumentation
of those songs.
Yeah.
So I'm listening to the Purple Rain album and Darling Nikki is one of the songs on there
and it's all about just like a woman masturbating in a hotel lobby and then has a woman who
has sex with her and then she invites him to come back and it's all this stuff.
See Shakespeare, right?
You find the core stories of the American dream.
It was revolutionary at the time because it was very female forward, very woman empowered.
She's taking control of her own sexuality.
She has him come up for a one night stand.
Oh yeah.
No, she's in charge.
And the song, she is fully in charge.
She rocks him with everything in the book.
She's got the whips, the chains, the whole secret room thing.
And then she's out the door before he's even awake and just leaves a note, "Kissy, kissy,
you want to do it again sometime?
Let me know."
"Hit me up next time you want to grind."
Yeah.
And she's just like, she's out.
So it was very female forward and very empowering.
The end of that song has some of the backwards stuff on there.
So if you listen to Darling Nikki, at the end of it, it is something being played in reverse
on the track.
So I was out walking listening to Darling Nikki and I texted a buddy of mine, Andy,
who is previously the president of the official Prince fan club.
He has every piece of music that Prince has ever released and then every piece of music
that he can get his hands on, bootlegs, all that kind of stuff.
So I texted him and said, "Hey, I'm listening to Purple Rain, listening to Darling Nikki.
What is the backwards part at the end of Darling Nikki?"
Because I knew he would just, I was like, "Andy will just know this.
He'll know it at the top of his head.
He won't even have to look it up."
So he texts me back.
I have this in my head.
You know what?
What is it, Paul?
Do you know what it is?
It's something to the effect of, "Thank you friends for listening to this.
We hope you enjoyed the song," kind of thing.
It's weirder than that.
What does it say?
It is, "Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine because I know the Lord is coming soon."
Oh, Lord.
"Coming soon."
Oh, no.
Well, he was deep into that.
Because remember, Prince was super religious as well.
Yeah.
There's a ton of stuff at the end of a bunch of these songs, including Purple Rain, When
Doves Cry, all this stuff.
There's a lot of really Jesus-y stuff in there too, and it's a little weird, but it's also
kind of like a glimpse into Prince, and I'm kind of enjoying that part as well.
I wish we could have gotten that Kevin Smith documentary.
Yeah.
And then the other one is on the shelf too.
There's another one that anyone who's seen this is amazing, but it got held up by the
dumbest legal technicality.
Right.
Yeah.
They said they were going to make a six ... They signed the contracts for a six-episode documentary,
and the guy who made it said, "No, it needs a seventh episode."
And because I went to a seventh episode, the Prince part of the production team got to
say, "You broke contract.
No one gets to see it."
Awful.
Yeah.
That's amazing.
That's it.
Well, this would be my recommendation, Matt, for you, MC Chris Friends.
Okay.
It's an EP, so it's a quick listen, and it's all Batman and Robin.
So I think you'll like it.
All right.
I will give it a listen.
Cool.
You know who else found out today that Prince was a pretty good musician?
It's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Pacific Rim 3, The Ultimate Rimming.
That's from 2025 Nesticle Scoop.
That's Pacific Rim 3, The Ultimate Rimming.
Hello there, my friends.
It is me, Guillermo del Toro.
I have tried my best to make an Evangelion live action film, but of course, many things
got in the way of my production, not the least of which just trying to make giant robots.
It's tough.
So what I decided to do, take a much of the pre-production material from that and go ahead
and make my own Kaiju film, and I did, and what I have created is the Pacific Rim.
But now I have the two of the films under the belt.
I had the guy doing the thing from the Lost in the Gang of Mean People, Dangerous People
show.
Lost in the Gang of Mean People, yeah, Dangerous People.
So I got the Gang of Dangerous People show, man, who do the movie.
I'm like, "Ah, that's okay."
But now I realize the money is in the pornography.
So I say, "Okay, let's go."
And I want to do this the right way.
So I am bringing Yenna Yemisin out of retirement, yes?
And Yenna Yemisin.
Who?
Yenna Yemisin.
No, it's all right.
Who?
Her name is Yenna Yemisin.
You say Yenna?
Yenna Yemisin.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
I hear, "Yes, I am a saint."
Is that what you hear?
Hold on, hold on.
Let me look this up.
Oh, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I have a pronunciation all messed up.
I may have to say, "Belladonna."
So Belladonna is going to do this new movie, and she is going to do what is going to be
called "Specific Rim."
It's one specific rim that she wants to get her tongue on.
And it's the Charlie Man from the "I Got the Gang of Bean People" movie.
And so, the whole movie about her in a haunted house trying to find one specific rim.
And you see, no robots.
Oh, there's a robot, double-headed robot.
Well, okay.
Tell me what I did.
I guess some of these new dildos do have AI.
That has to be true, right?
There have to be sex toys with AI by now, right?
But I guess, technically, you can't call it a dildo if it has technical parts, right?
I think so.
Yes.
Yes, Mr. Del Toro.
I believe that is true.
Look, I'm no dildo expert.
It seems like you are.
Wink.
No, no.
My name's Jacob.
I am, of course, a dildo expert.
Benicio Del Toro.
I mean, look at that.
Guillermo Del Toro.
Look up the definition of Guillermo Del Toro.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry.
Guillermo.
Benicio Del Toro.
Not that hack.
Not that dildo expert.
Scoop Jesus's artificial intelligence.
Yes.
The AI inside.
Guillermo Del Toro's dead last love.
Say it again?
He's selling a bunch of his old movie props.
Is he really?
Yes.
I don't know if it's an existential thing or he's just trying to make some room for
stuff because he's got a lot of shit.
Right.
Have you seen anything that you want?
Oh, my God.
I mean, not really because horror collectibles aren't my thing, but one or two pieces would
be kind of cool.
No, I mean, I'm really happy.
I actually already bought something from his.
Oh, really?
What did you get?
Yeah.
I got a case of snappy dialogue.
Oh.
It's so snappy.
Yeah.
Guillermo Del Toro.
I tried to open up the case and it was snap, snap, snap.
Too snappy.
You know, is there a horror memorabilia thing that either of you would really want from
old horror films or either of you old horror hits?
I'd want the giant pot of boiling water from sleepaway camp.
That's what I would guess.
Oh, really?
Oh.
They got the big fat guy?
They got the big fat guy and he holds up his burning arms.
Yeah.
The camera, the whole shot.
It's all jellied out?
Yeah.
Oh.
That movie's something else.
There was a time when I was a teenager, I was probably like 15, 16 years old, where I
was so over horror movies.
I was just a kid.
I was like, "Fucking horror movies.
They're not scary at all," but I would go see them because they would have naked teenagers
in them.
Oh, yeah.
And like after the first, what, half hour of the movie, I'd be like, "Well, there probably
aren't going to be any more naked teenagers.
I'm kind of done with this movie."
But yes.
I mean, that's sort of the formula, right?
Yeah.
But I was not interested in watching the horror movie part at all.
It was just, like the horror movie part, which to me, was just boring and stupid.
Jacob, have you seen any of the "Terrifier" films?
I saw the first one.
Okay.
Yeah.
I watched it with Matt's kids.
I was going to say, I still want to do a "Terrifier 3" with Matt's kids.
They loved it.
"Terrifier 3" with Matt's kids would be like a big Patreon level.
I just bid on eBay for a cracked sidewalk that was the path of death's design.
So when it was cracking through the streets, I got that crack there.
Someone has to have Freddy Krueger's glove, right?
Oh, that has to be.
Yeah.
There's a couple of those because they did it different for a couple of the movies, right?
That series went on long enough that there's a Freddy Krueger, and I bet Robert Englund
has one in his personal collection.
Probably a few.
But the classic stuff, like Freddy Krueger's stuff-
I'm talking like he's collecting all the "Hammer Horror" stuff.
He's got like old "Wolf Man" and "Bella Lugosi" shit.
I would love any of that stuff.
Like the classic horror stuff, any of that stuff would ... I'd display that very happily
in my house.
Like the pinhead stuff, "Hellraiser," I was a big "Hellraiser" fan of those early movies
and everything.
Yeah.
There's probably some stuff that I'd like.
They had a replica-
That's actually when you watch Penn and Teller do needles, it's actually pulling the pins
from Pinhead out of Teller's mouth.
Oh, God.
Oh, it is though.
I've always wondered.
Those are Pinhead's own pins?
Yeah.
Oh, good old Pinhead.
That's right.
Teller didn't ... because he takes the needles out and puts them in like a ... I think I
might be conflating Teller's version of this with a bunch of other people's versions of
this.
But does he take the needles out and put them in like a lemon or something, or-
He takes them out of an apple to start.
Like a pincushion?
That's what it is.
It's an apple.
Yeah.
He eats them from the apple and then he pulls them out on his mouth.
So he could have like a little ... instead of an apple, he could just have a little Pinhead
prop and he could just be taking the needles out of Pinhead's head, I guess.
That'd be pretty funny.
That would be, yeah.
That's nice.
I'm going to send him a DM right now.
Teller, I have a note on needles for you.
What's that thing called?
I have a note on your oldest, best, whatever.
What's the name of the puzzle box for the Hellraiser?
It's got a name.
Oh, it does.
The Nepronomicon?
It's something like the Painacron or something like that.
The Lament Configuration.
Thank you, Steve Jasper.
Teller's street show, by the way, I don't think he's performed a trick more than needles.
Has to be.
His most performed trick.
He had a little mat and he says, "The show will begin when all the needles are in the
apple."
And he put out his mat and his little table and he just started sticking needles into
an apple and that's how people would gather around him when he's a street performer.
That was his crowd gathering?
Yeah.
Just who's this guy putting needles into an apple and what's about to happen here?
Yes.
Andy Cheek asking if I have any movie props.
I don't have any official movie props.
I've got a lightsaber, but it's not a real lightsaber exactly.
I would like to have a real lightsaber.
Do you have any?
Director's cut.
So you do have some actual screen used movie props?
Yeah.
That's cool.
Somewhere.
Yeah.
Stuff from commercials I've been in.
That's cool.
Shoes.
It counts.
Oh, some big stuff.
I know I've got some stuff around here somewhere.
I just don't know what I have.
I don't know.
I have Judy Gau's ruby slippers.
Oh, that's nice.
I think I have in my house somewhere, I think I have a cane that FDR used.
That's probably my best prop is that.
That's definitely your best one.
It's right where it is.
FDR's cane.
I can even show it to people on the Twitch.
Yeah.
And for people who don't know, Matt does actually have a cane that FDR used.
After it was in a show in the episodes where we joked that it was FDR's cane, we found
out after the fact that it was FDR's cane, but that's a really weird series of events.
And it was used in the show as FDR's cane.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's some weird shit.
It was an old cane from "Grandma Ruby's House."
That's the funniest thing.
We just talked about this for what?
Five minutes?
Yeah.
I'm grounded by Ruby Keeler stuff.
Of course.
Yeah.
You've got tons of film use props.
I'm lousy with Ruby Keeler stuff, so yeah.
Hollywood Walk of Fame on your wife's family tree.
Yeah.
Do you guys know what happened to that giant typewriter she danced on?
No.
Oh, I've got that.
I'm using it right now.
That is something I ... I should have pitched this to the people who work behind the scenes
at Spiegel World, because they put these different events and shows together, but I thought that
Spiegel World should get Sean and John together with my wife and reenact the tap dancing on
the typewriter bit.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
That typewriter prop was ... If you don't know what we're talking about, you can YouTube
Ruby Keeler dancing on a typewriter, and it's a famous movie musical bit.
It's from the movie, the 1937 film Ready, Willing, and Able.
After its use in the film, the typewriter became part of the film's production design
and is now considered a piece of movie memorabilia, even though its current location is not known.
Yeah.
I bet that just got-
I mean, back in those days, it was-
I'm assuming it got taken apart in these programs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even just recently, even through the '90s, stuff just got trashed, man.
Oh, yeah.
A lot of stuff gets reused, broken down and reused for different things.
Right.
Sometimes, yeah, but-
Yeah, if you can reuse it, they're breaking it down and reusing it for the next thing.
A lot of times, people just throw shit away, man.
Especially in the movie, the studio era.
Yes.
Is it true, or is it false that the Falkor is the animal skin from Dumb and Dumber?
That was a rumor.
I don't know if that was actually true.
I don't think that was actually the- but they might have repurposed part of him for the
mutthut truck.
Yeah.
That's what I kept hearing as a rumor.
It might have been.
It might have been repurposed and-
I don't think it was.
It feels too good to be true.
Yeah.
It's not quite the same fur either.
Right.
Yeah.
Google says no, not used there.
Okay.
Yeah.
But yeah, it was a good thing.
When it was- because it wasn't close in time, was it?
The never ending story-
No, it was a long way off.
The first movie was much earlier, right?
And in fact, I do believe, I remember just a couple years ago, someone actually still
has Falkor in their barn somewhere, kind of rotting away, half rotting.
Oh.
Yeah.
Slower ball.
That's too sexy.
Yeah.
Falkor, have you seen those fucking Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle heads from the Henson
designs?
Oh, yeah.
Nowadays?
Yes.
They look-
I have a friend who worked on the construction of those.
Oh, wow.
They look crazy now because they're rotting away.
Oh, yeah.
They're insane.
NECA made a line of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles cross universal monsters because they had both
those licenses.
This was like two years ago.
They made figures of the turtles as monsters.
They had like Leo as Frankenstein and I think Raphael was a vampire.
They made Michelangelo a mummy, right?
Okay.
And they based his head sculpt design off of the rotting mask of the one that was used
in the movies.
Oh, jeez.
It looks very much like, it's really cool.
It's really cool.
It looks kind of skeletal.
It's wild.
If you look up rotten Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle head-
The people on the Zoom, we're about to see it right now.
Yeah.
No, I know.
I remember talking with a puppeteer, Tim Lagasse, who is big in the puppet world.
He's the one who taught that puppet workshop to my kids and he basically says that all
the material that goes into puppets eventually rots.
Yes.
Right.
Even like sponge and stuff like that.
Like sponge will just dry out and become dust.
Exactly.
Yep.
And then you have to update stuff.
And Jacob just showed me some pictures that looked horrible.
That looks really scary.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh no, the heads are just rotting away and then you have the teeth in there and they
don't rot away.
And if you look up Neckah Michelangelo mummy figure-
My search history is already weird enough, I'm fine.
It's basically that same head.
Also, leading up to Scoop Fest, boy do my Amazon recommendations get weird fast.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're on Amazon for Scoop Fest, my recommendations get real weird real quick.
But most of the time you're just searching on the site Jackable.com, right?
That's right.
Cookies engaged.
Turn them cookies on.
Time to jack it.
Speaking of jacking it, it's time for Jock vs. Nerd, winner gets the jacket.
Right here on Twitch.
Jock vs. Nerd action.
Who am I?
Oh boy.
It's exactly, it's exactly the same.
On the hunt for balls.
No, we're rotting Michelangelo.
We've got a scooper today from Scoopy Logic.
Scoopy Logic sent this one in a couple of years ago.
I've gone back into the old Wayback machine here and found this scooper, a scooper that
Scoopy Logic sent in I think in 2023.
Anyway, the categories are not only a fruit, deals of a lifetime, TMNT, very coincidental
there, and hodgepodge.
Oh neat.
I love it.
I'm up first.
We've got some TMNT.
I'll try TMNT for 200.
Let's see.
This actor voiced Shredder in the original cartoon series will accept his best known
role.
Oh cool.
Oh, I have zero idea.
I have to pass, Matt.
This is Philip Seymour Hoffman.
No.
Famously, Philip Seymour Hoffman.
Paul, who is it?
It's the guy who played Uncle Phil on The Fresh Prince.
Oh, interesting.
That's right.
I did know that.
James Avery.
Yes.
Matt.
If that's the $200 question, forget about it.
I know, right?
I'll do not only a fruit for 200.
A berry.
This tropical fruit naturally grows in bundles.
It's better than naturally growing in bindles.
Right, right, right.
Only hobos eat this berry.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul.
Bananas.
It's a banana.
Technically a berry.
That's right.
Paul is technically in the lead.
Paul, you're up.
TMNT, please.
For 400.
The multicolored masks were established in the original cartoon.
What color did they all wear previously in the comics?
Red.
Damn it.
I knew that one.
Red.
I should have done.
I should have gone there.
Paul out with a commanding lead right now.
800 to 0 to 0.
Baton Rouge.
Baton Red.
I'm just getting the basics, though.
We got, you know, just getting the simple questions.
All right.
You have to smack talk with your lead, buddy.
Yeah.
We'll see.
I'll try TMNT.
Try to steal one for Paul for 600.
Here we go.
This TV producer is credited with writing the classic theme song.
I don't fucking know.
Matt.
God damn it.
Stevie Wonder.
No.
I don't know.
Stevie Wonder.
Paul.
Fred Wolfe.
Chuck Lorre.
Oh, Chuck Lorre.
OK.
Chuck Lorre.
That's anyone's game.
And Paul's points are gone.
Matt.
I've got 200.
Hodgepodge.
James Bond creator Ian Fleming wrote this book that in 1968 was turned into a children's
movie starring Dick Van Dyke.
Hmm.
Deep Throat.
Go--
Would you say Mary Poppins was starring Dick Van Dyke?
Probably not.
It was.
I mean, he was the--
Yeah.
He was one of the leads in that.
It feels like the actual time frame.
Yeah.
That's not it, though.
I don't think.
I'll pass.
I think I know.
All right.
Passes to Paul.
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang.
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang is correct.
Cool.
Chitty Chitty Bad Bad.
Paul.
TMNT, please.
For 800.
According to Internet Conspiracy, what band was created after touring in a live action
TMNT concert series?
Oh, man.
I don't know.
But I do know--
Come on, Paul.
You know this one.
Michael Ian Black was part of the promo team for the Turtles way back in the day.
I feel of great kinship with him doing costume work.
I'll pass.
I don't know.
You don't know about the Turtles?
What band would you guess?
It's probably a boy band.
Probably--
No, it's the Turtles.
No.
It's me, I bet.
I have no idea.
I'm passing.
Matt.
I bet the guess is New Kids.
Black Eyed Peas.
Oh, wow.
The Black Eyed Peas.
Tonight's going to be a good fight, was the original lyric.
Oh, yeah.
Mm.
Let's get some pizza in here.
Let's get some pizza.
I'll try not only a fruit, a gourd.
The season is almost upon us.
Prepare for the all-factory overload.
Ah, yes.
Wait, what-- oh, is it pumpkin or pumpkin spice or, yeah, all those things.
Yeah, pumpkin.
It's pumpkin, pumpkin.
I don't know anything, huh?
Let's go--
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself.
You know some things.
Let's go with Hodgepodge for $400.
This American actor accidentally killed two people while driving in Ireland in 1987.
Huh.
This definitely tickles something in my brain.
I think it's in there somewhere.
I know.
I'm trying to think.
Is it Robert Downey Jr.?
He got in a lot of trouble.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul. his name is flying out of my head right now.
And into two people walking.
No, it's fucking Ferris Bueller.
Matthew-- Matthew--
Damon.
Fuck.
What is his name?
Matthew--
Sully.
No.
Matthew-- oh, Sullivan's Crossing.
Matthew-- fuck, why can't I get his name?
It's going to be really funny if Paul's just doing a gamesmanship here and trying to get
me to say his name.
No.
I can't get his name.
I can't-- it won't come to me.
Matthew-- shit.
Harry.
No, pass.
I can't get his name.
Matthew Broderick, Paul?
There you go.
That's it.
Yeah.
I'll try Matthew Broderick.
I could not get it.
It is Matthew Broderick.
No.
You could not get his name.
Paul.
Hodgepodge for $600, please.
Children's book author Roald Dahl wrote the screenplay for which James Bond movie?
Oh, boy.
James and the Giant Spy.
That's it.
I'll pass.
I don't know.
Passes to me.
I'm trying to think of like, what are the weirder James Bond movies?
Like Octopussy is a weird one.
That one's all set with like a circus troupe and stuff.
Yeah.
Uh, there are some weird ones out there.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt.
That is James Bond, of course, Sleeping Foot to Face.
I bet it was Dr. No.
Four people to a bed.
I don't know.
I don't know at all.
Dr. No was the first Bond movie.
You only live twice.
I think that's the one where I think you only live twice is the Sean Connery one where he
does it in, where he does Yellow Face.
Yes.
I think he dresses up as a Japanese man in that movie.
It's me.
I'll try Deals of a Lifetime.
200.
It's a B.
In 2007, this creative team negotiated for 50% of all digital rights for their show and
have made almost $1 billion since.
Wow.
This creative team negotiated for 50% of all digital rights of their show.
What was this category?
Deal of a Lifetime.
Oh.
So these are smart people who made a really smart deal.
Yeah.
Uh, I, I have no idea.
I guess I'll pass.
Uh, Matt.
I think this is, uh, Trey Parker and Matt Stone.
Oh, that would make sense.
Good call.
It is Trey Parker and Matt Stone.
Well done.
Matt.
I knew a thing.
Um.
Where did you go?
Boy, they must be.
They are cleaning up, clearly.
Yeah.
You heard it here first, folks.
Trey Parker and Matt Stone doing fine.
Uh, the references, I don't know if you've watched them.
They're funny.
They are.
Uh, Deals of a Lifetime.
400, please.
Outside of the small pittance of merchandising and sequel rights, how much was George Lucas
paid to direct the Star Wars, uh, the original Star Wars film within $50,000?
Everyone knows he was paid with candy.
That's right.
Um.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul.
I think.
How much was George Lucas paid?
I don't.
It wasn't.
I don't even know if it was $100,000.
I'll pass.
I don't remember.
Yeah.
I mean, he can't have been paid much.
Uh.
Do I need to guess?
Oh, no.
I'm in the lead.
I don't want to guess.
Pass.
$150,000.
Whoa.
Paul would have gotten points if he had said $100,000.
I would direct Star Wars now for that money, just so you know.
Oh, okay.
Mm.
Nah.
I need $160,000 minimum.
I'm going to stand fast on that.
All right.
Paul.
Uh.
I'll close out Hodgepodge.
Freight Hundo.
Daily Double.
Here we go.
We finally found one.
Turn it around.
Real deal.
Volkswagen's top selling product is not a vehicle, but iconically German food.
Wolf, wolf brand chili.
Ooh.
Well, it's either a pretzel or a bratwurst.
Two bits.
Okay.
I'll go pretzel.
A pretzel?
A currywurst sausage.
Oh.
Who would have accepted bratwurst?
Would we have?
If you had said currywurst, I would have accepted currywurst.
Yeah.
Currywurst.
I might have even accepted sausage.
All right.
It's me.
I'll try Deals of a Lifetime 600.
We've got four questions left.
One Daily Double left.
In 1986 anti-trust lawsuit, in a 1986 anti-trust lawsuit, the USFL Donald Trump successfully
sued the NFL winning how much money?
Hint, pick a number, one through 10.
I don't remember.
Pass.
Matt.
A dollar.
$1.
Yeah.
Shoot.
$3.
I was ready to guess a dollar too.
I watched the documentary.
They presented him with the check.
This is back when he wasn't who he is now, and so it was a very embarrassing moment.
Later on, he would go on to prove that he wasn't capable of embarrassment.
Yes.
So there you go.
But very capable of vengeance, it turns out.
Yes.
Holds a grudge for a while.
I'll go with deals of a lifetime to close it out.
Oh no, it's Matt's turn.
Great.
It's Matt's turn.
I need to make up some ground here, so I will steal Paul's question and do deals of a lifetime
for $800.
Daily Double.
There you go.
Now you got it, Matt.
Paul with the gamesmanship, retired in 2001, this former NY Met receives a little over
$1 million annually for every July 1st until 2035.
Bobby Bonilla, baby.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
How did he do this?
Bobby Bonilla.
I have friends, my Mets friends, the day that it pays, they go, "It's happy Bobby Bonilla
Day," and it's the day that Bobby Bonilla is still being paid by the Mets.
What happened?
So basically, they gave him a crazy contract to play baseball, which happens at baseball
more than any other sport, and then he ended up being so terrible, they wanted him to stop
playing, and there was no rules yet on stretch provisions, and so they basically, to not
hurt their salary cap or not hurt their bottom line or whatever, they asked if they could
stretch his contract out for whatever it was, like 27 years or something like that.
And even when he got paid now, it's not even considered ridiculous, but back then it was
a ridiculous amount of money to play horribly for the Mets.
It's a ridiculous amount of money to not do anything.
Well, ask Kawhi Leonard.
Who's that?
He's a man who's getting paid a ridiculous amount of money right now for not doing anything.
Made a really, really good ... If we did old school Jock vs. Nerd, this would have been
the question of the week for sure, but Kawhi Leonard was paid $28 million to not show up
or do anything for this company that was a sponsor of the LA Clippers.
Oh, this was the way they got his ... It was like phantom salary.
Yes.
It was to get around the salary cap, to give him an extra bonus money inside the salary
cap.
At least that's being investigated right now.
It's just blowing up now, right?
But it was supposed to be an environmental company, worried about reducing people's carbon
footprint, and so the joke is that Kawhi Leonard never even tweeted or did anything, but what
is Kawhi's stance on people's carbon footprints?
Is he even passionate about it?
Who knows?
It's a weird, weird thing.
That's really funny.
It was first exposed nationally by Pablo Torre, which has a great podcast, Pablo Torre Explains
It All.
Yes.
Mark Cuban, I guess current part owner, but former majority owner of Mavericks, started
hitting up on Twitter.
He said, "Why don't you come on my show?"
They debated about who's at fault for this for two and a half hours.
They put an hour and 10 of it on air, and there's two people passionately arguing about
something, and there's no name calling.
No one gets called Hitler.
No one gets called a child molester.
No one is insulted.
It was an earnest debate where people kept their cool.
It's worth listening to just for that miracle, just because I didn't think people could still
do that.
Just to be clear, you mean they edited all that stuff out, and that's in the full version,
but not in the part that they aired version, right?
They wouldn't have done all that arguing without calling each other Hitler and child molesters.
I know.
It's against the rules of basic conversation these days.
That's right.
I'm glad you didn't disagree with me right there, because I would have had to call you
Hitler.
Here's the craziest thing.
We've done so much crazy shit because of bullshit child molestation rumors that aren't true.
It's all because calling someone Hitler stopped working.
That used to be the worst thing you could do, and someone figured out that calling someone
a child molester is worse than Hitler, and then that took over, and that really has created
a bunch of extra conspiracy theories that wouldn't have been otherwise.
Do you think that if it were released today, like if new evidence came out today that Hitler
himself was a child molester, do you think the pendulum would swing back to just calling
people Hitlers again?
Then I'd be like, "Life is a herald.
That's a perfect third beat of conspiracy theories."
That would be it right there.
Paul, you've got not only a fruit for 600 or 800.
You have negative 400 points.
Matt has 400 points.
You have 800 points.
It's a very high-scoring game.
I'll try 800, please.
Not only a fruit for 800, according to the U.S. Supreme Court, Nix v. Headon in 1993,
it's a vegetable.
1893.
Sorry, 1893.
Tomato.
So the U.S. Supreme Court ruled that a tomato is a vegetable?
That's it.
It is.
It's a tax case.
Vegetables are not a botanical classification.
It's technically a fruit.
Yeah, you're technically a fruit, Hitler.
I'm not technically a fruit.
I'm just a fruit.
La-dee-dah.
I'm closing out the category and the game.
Not only a fruit for 600, a composite fruit.
This misnamed fruit actually consists of many tiny individual fruits embedded in a fleshy
receptacle.
Oh.
Your mom.
I like me a composite fruit.
Let's go.
I like me a fleshy receptacle.
A composite fruit.
This misnamed fruit actually consists of many tiny individual fruits embedded in a fleshy
receptacle.
Fleshy receptacle is really just not where I want to be in the day.
We are different people.
That was my high school band.
Different people.
That was our number one single.
We open for the meat puppets.
And I mean that literally.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt, you can win with this.
Man, I don't even know if I have a guess for what a fleshy receptacle would be.
Fleshy receptacle, do do do do.
I have a guess.
I'll pass to Paul.
Pass to Paul.
Pomegranate.
Pomegranate?
Oh.
I bet you're right.
There we go.
Oh.
No, it's a strawberry.
Strawberry, raspberry, or blackberry.
Boo.
Boo earns.
I thought about strawberry, but I didn't think fleshy receptacle.
Fleshy receptacle threw me off.
That's the game I win today with 800 points.
Matt has 400.
Paul has a negative 200 after his fleshy receptacle mishap, and that is a scooperty from Scoopy
Logic.
Thank you, Scoopy Logic.
Like I said, Scoopy Logic sent that to us a couple of years ago, so if you want to send
us a scooperty, send us a Price is Scryte Jock versus Nerd, send us an Obelisk Jock
versus Nerd, send us some scoop mail.
You can do all those things over there at HeyScoops.com, and today is evidence.
If I don't get to your scooperty when you send it in at first, I'll probably get to
it later.
Eventually.
I want to thank my favorite fleshy receptacle, Penn Jillette, for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Penn.
Of course, I want to thank all the people that make this show possible who support us
on our Patreon.
These people all are writing on the new Powers comic book coming out next year.
Fantastic.
Circles and circles.
Signature curl scoop, the micro scoop for shaping.
We all scream for Mark McLean, unbanned scoop, one small scoop for man, a ranch slunk, a
scoop of root canal.
Aaron, Aaron Boyd, Aaron Wendling, Adam Goff, Adam Stickney, AJB, Akshay Mysore, Alla Scoop
6666, All-Star Scoop, Amera Scott Scoop, Andrea Anderson, and Andrew J Hughes.
The following individuals all bobbed their heads vigorously while they listened to the
podcast in the hopes that someone will inquire as to what it might be that's causing them
the jam so hard and they try and get a successful obelisk off of it.
Bearded Scoop 3, Bear Scoop, BJ Joyer, Belgian Triple Scoop, Ben, Ben Dennis, Ben Gao, Ben
Smith, Ben Sherman Scoop, Big Lodo Scoop, Big Sexy Digital Nomad, Bike Scoop, Bill Beatty,
Blue Line Scoop, Boss Wayne Scoop, B.O.B., Bobby Becerra, Brad Martin, Brendan Light,
Brendan Allen, and Brian Maddox aka Anarcho Scoop.
The following people can be seen dancing in the video "Jigging with the Devil" by Sella
Van Halen.
That would be Andrew Koenig, Andrew Ossichuk, Andy Cheek, Angela Chan, Angry Face Scoop,
Ant Foods, Anton Jernberg, Apple Scoop, Ameris Saar, Avin Zarlez, AWOL Scoop, Bad Pirate
Scoop, Bertie, Bert Vonk, Base Camp Scoops, and BB Hermit.
Sorry, yeah, I did, I said Boats and Scoop wrong again.
So Boats and Scoop, thank you Boats and Scoop.
Also, all of these people have realized, "Hey, Prince was incredibly good at what he did."
Brian Richard, Brooks Lyle, Brian McLeod, Brian Traves, Buster Kamikaze, C. Wick, Kali
Ghost, Cameron Hall, Canadian Scoop, Crystal, Captain James T. Scoop, Cargo Van Killa, Carolyn
Albert, Cassie Rice, Charles Eaton, and Charles Jachecky.
And the following scoops were all featured in several Roald Dahl books.
That is Charlie Thompson, Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Chelsea Farr, Chris Barsky, Chris Ellis,
Chris Fisher, Chris Jackson, Chris George, Chris Kay, Chris Meloncon, Christine Alsasser,
Christine Starr, Christopher Hayworth, Christopher Huff, Christy Salinas, Chronicler Scoop,
CJ Magnetta, Clayton Shoney, Clown in a Brothel, Coach Rat Bastard, Coconut Time Travel, Coffee
Bean Scoop, Colleen Fisher, Colton Stettenberry, Cone's Photorescoopter, Corianna Jemora, Corny
Scoop, Counselor Matt, Country Scoop, Court Myers, Craig DeFarmer, Craig Little, Cream
City Scoop, Chris Baer, Cup a Scoop, and Dan, Dan Thirsty III.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do love you and appreciate you.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air, if you want to be invited out to our Zoom episodes, Twitch
Farts, get yourself over to PreachingFun.com, sign up today.
Or if you, like me, are surprised that we got through an episode today without me having
a weird bathroom story, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are here because of you Patreon supporters, so we thank you so much every show, because
we couldn't do the show without you.
So if you want to be one of those Patreon supporters, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz,
those are the places that you can go over to and sign up, honestly, just be part of
the family.
We're just one big happy group here.
We all have so much fun doing this show all the time.
It's all about the family.
That's right, Bing.
Fast and furious family.
All of his Bing Crosby impersonation are just perfect.
We're doing a heist just to show how much family matters to us.
That's how much family matters.
We rob people for the love of family.
That's right, come on out.
Look, ScoopFest is two weeks away, we've got room for you.
You can still make that choice.
We do.
Go to scoopfest.com and buy yourself some space tickets.
We're selling tickets every day right now, so yeah, we definitely have space for you.
Come on out.
It's going to be awesome.
Yeah, it's going to be really fun.
We just added a thing that's going to make people very happy.
It is.
Make a road trip of it.
Do what you got to do.
I don't know if you guys saw this in the chat of our Scoop Group stuff, but we had a pair
of Scoops who are coming to ScoopFest who ran into a little financial hiccup as far
as return tickets went for their flights back out of Vegas.
Our community stepped up and already helped them out, got them some GoFundMe coin to get
them a flight back home, so I mean, I'm telling you, we got the best listeners on the freaking
planet.
I love every one of you guys and it just makes my heart swell every time I come to this podcast
to record and see all your lovely faces and people that message me.
I don't get mean messages.
I just get nice stuff.
The occasional, "Paul, you didn't get this right thing," but that's about it, but that's
about it.
Most of the time, I get, "Paul was right," so I like that too.
I hardly ever get mean messages, but when I do, several people make sure to forward them
to me, so I do have that going for me.
Yes, Winterscoop pointing out that only my heart is swollen when I come.
Yes, that's what happens.
Just my heart swells.
It's a condition.
Yeah, yeah.
I saw it in the comic.
It depicted like a circle in a circle.
Hey.
Yeah, that's right.
Some people out there might be looking for another podcast.
You can participate in our obelisk scheme by selecting one person and one person only
to check out our podcast.
I say, promise them all the snappy dialogue.
That's a lot of snappy dialogue.
God damn it.
Very snappy.
Snapped on.
Snapped on for my Gilmore appreciation, but the dialogue, it's so snappy.
Tell them we are the Gilmore girls of dudes podcasting.
I'm sure we tackle a lot of the same issues.
Thanks for this, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Paul is Jesse from the Gilmore girls.
Jesse?
Yeah.
Jesse is a character in the Gilmore girls, I think.
Marble Tulip Scooby Tree over at Twitch is Team Jesse for life.
Oh, oh yes.
Jesse is Luke's son.
So Rory, the daughter, is torn.
Oh Paul, Paul.
I didn't care.
Oh no, but she's torn between Jesse.
And this rich kid.
What's his name?
Logan Huntsberger.
I happen to be Team Logan Huntsberger.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the stage, Logan Huntsberger.
He calls her ace.
It's the cutest thing in the world and she should have stuck with him, but she was convinced
that she was going to be the ace.
So we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her.
So we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little
bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and
then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have
a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with
her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going
to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat
with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going
to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a
chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then
we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little
bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and
then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have
a little bit of a chat with her, and then we're going to have a little bit of a chat with