yeah oh hello there I am so happy to see you because I'd like to thank you the
ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers it is a new
month we don't have a new list yet but we will thank each and every ice cream
truck driver before this month is through if you want to be an ice cream
truck driver and I sure hope you do share this fucking ice cream straight to
people's fucking ear holes head over to preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is
where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life
you save may be your own
oh it's a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love
to great let's go I had a weird night last night I had a weird weekend I've
had a weird life who am I fooling it's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream
social sitting over there in Las Vegas it's Matt Donnelly sitting over there in
Pittsburgh it's Paul Mattingly sitting here in Las Vegas it's me Jacob the
other guy we're preaching fun we're preaching fun hey everybody yeah we're
doing you uh everybody having a good day I don't care here's a production meeting
blammo is right right out of nowhere boom I just scared the shit out of my
cat with that blammo oh it was so much blammo oh man really woke her up poor
kitty we are our company gentlemen is restructuring we are restructuring our
company okay through somebody quit it our oldest our oldest friend and I
suppose employee although that feels weird it feels we paid very little but
yes but Annie is Annie is moving on from us our dear friend Annie is moving on
with us from us she has been with us since the beginning of patreon at the
very least we launched our patreon and then immediately expressed how
overwhelmed we are by our own creation yep yep and she emailed us and said I
will help organize this for you and then continue to do so for I guess I don't
even know how long I mean I have I mean I mean we probably did patreon on our own
for like a month before she swooped in and was like yeah here let me just let
me just take care of you sweet sweet children lost in the woods it's very
important to note you know and I think I really think is just Annie being
respectful like I think she's just a first-class person started finish it's
simply that like when we started we had like seven tears we had a bunch of bonus
rewards for people who were on for more than three months right we had all kinds
of different deliverables that we were thought you know that we could do if we
had all the time in the world and then quickly realized that we don't have all
the time in the world but Annie kept all of these things organized for us all the
time and more importantly fielded emails from patreon yes I ordered what is
happen I ordered all you can eat video whatever hands-free eating video and so
long ago when we were first figuring out what our patreon was going to look like
this is great we're just gonna go down memory lane now that we're talking about
any when we first figured out what our patreon was gonna look like we just
threw so many ideas at the wall and I think Paul I think Paul said the hands
free eating yeah yes I'm sure I did and Matt and I just went both of us like Paul
explained to us what he was thinking he said well we'll make a video where we go
to a restaurant we will order food and then we'll eat that food without using
our hands and and Matt and I just said like oh yeah yeah that is something we
should do yeah no problem and no issue just right on there because our early
patron was like hey let's pay for our gas and a meal once in a while that was
our goal for the patreon and so yeah no I mean it was ridiculous and you know
all the things we've learned we've talked to other people who start a
patreon or sort of you know it's interesting and then now we've really
simplified things here on a picture more than ever most because we kind of
discovered that we're such a community that like watching us do stuff or
making us do stuff it seems to be less interesting to our listeners than
making sure that we all hang out or create social opportunities for each
other like all you have to do to get us to do a hands-free eating video now is
convince us that it's gonna be funny and we'll probably just do it if we can if
you want a hands-free video for me I need a skateboard and a stick a ramp of
food that can go down towards my mouth a new competitor entering the arena
between team slide and team swing skateboarding skateboard with a skateboard
catapult yeah oh the whispers to your oh something else if we hit a goal we
actually came close this month to hitting a bonus goal for the first time
in a long time we felt everyone just short which would be no means a bonus
episode and just before we got on there we even brainstorming new ways to do
bonus episodes and what about some we're in good shape to work I think we had a
good idea we're in good shape without any to deliver a brand new bonus
episode should we get there so please don't let this reorganization hold you
back for support we still need you and by need you I mean we are completely
reliant on you but yeah I mean you know yes we gave her a stipend but it was a
charitable stipend and so I mean it really was just her helping us out for a
decade and so she will be I feel like she wrote off the time that she worked
for us as a charity donation on her time yeah and that'd be fair we would back
that up at the IRS yeah I was sure I don't think any court would convict her
no we're basically when it comes to us running a company we're basically make a
wish I just got a random link texted to me from a random phone number wanting me
to reset my Instagram password I got that from Google today too yeah I think I
don't know you know I think maybe yeah maybe the line the US infrastructure
might be hanging by a thread I think we're probably fine thank you Annie you
have been our champion for years we are going to miss you in ways that we don't
understand yet so so thank you so much we're gonna run into issues over the
next weeks and months and we're gonna be like fuck Annie was just taking care of
this and we didn't realize it I know that's going to happen so thank you so
much Annie we very much appreciate you and everything you have done for us and
for this community over the years she was a huge part of making this the
success that it is yeah and always will be Annie Annie will henceforth be always
welcome at any ice cream social event yeah anything that we ever do for all
time Annie is forever welcome yeah and it's just in yarn and sticks is saying I
hope Annie gets free membership for life I think we can yes Annie has whatever
she wants get her she might be sick of us guys so it's not it's easy up on the
rewards but she wants to stay away from us I get that too well I don't think
we're you know I think she has access to the patreon stuff to a degree I don't
think we're taking that away so we're not we're not scouring to reset all the
passwords I haven't been resetting the door codes this morning I'll need your
keys in your badge Annie yeah and if you're badgered your gun give me your
gun give me a gun I don't care hand me any gun any gun any badge any gun broken
is right and he's probably the only one who remembers the passwords that's
absolutely that is true she has not received the last email or phone call
from us that's for sure my last email to her was expressing thank yous and all
the stuff and like and maybe could you just put a list together
thank you so much Eddie that was so wonderfully appreciated yeah so I had a
weird week I went to um went downtown the other night went downtown on Monday
night we're not starting there I tell you where we're starting okay you went
to a football game with with pod therapy is where we're starting I did I went on
Sunday I went to a football game with pod there this is where football why
football rules like like when you look at American sports like football is just
in its own fucking category in terms of success you I would say I three three
other friends JD who directed is directing the hey scoops movie sure my
friend Alice who has the offensive crayon purposely offensive crayons all
went to this game and I went to bust balls with everyone I think so maybe JD
after the fact during the game because you were at what I would think is the
dumbest football game on earth so if you don't follow sports it's the last week
of the season okay the Raiders were already the most terrible team number
one draft yes locked up they're bringing but at the beginning of the day we
didn't know that we thought the only thing that was going to matter on the
day was that the Raiders needed to lose to lock up the number one draft pick and
then right before the game started they come over the PA in the stadium they're
like hey the Giants just upset the cow or just lost to the Cowboys or upset the
Cowboys or beat the cow whichever one they did yeah Giants just beat the
Cowboys which solidifies the Raiders getting that number one draft pick now
that's not even on the table and that's like another table the Chiefs come to
town there's no Mahomes he's injured Patrick Mahomes is injured he's out
now he's a probably the last game did they come to the game there yeah yeah
he was at the game I'm out there wasn't he I don't know I thought he was there I
thought somebody told me he was there I don't fucking know I don't watch your
breaks you asked us then Jacob and I were clarifying with each other can you
just give us a second I thought he was there I thought somebody told me that he
was there because it was probably Kelsey's last game yeah both teams
started yes yeah Kelsey might retire he's probably retiring Travis Kelsey yeah
he's my age he's old he's also married to the gajillionaire that Brady it's
true that is true yeah but second most money and it but somebody made the
second most amount of money in his marriage and that did not stop him I
don't know because he hated his family he had to go back to my kids anybody
hiring Giselle is a way I'll spend time in Tampa Giselle is a certified which
careful she also knows a black belt buddy she'll kick your ass I ain't saying
anything negative about it I was wondering how powerful which Taylor
Swift is in comparison I wonder I guess pretty powerful wonder as well either way
I feel like Travis Kelsey's gonna land on his feet somewhere I'm saying there's
absolutely nothing on the line Raiders absolute worst team they're playing they
are the worst both teams played multiple not one but multiple backup
quarterbacks oh so many quarterbacks and no one could score a touchdown no and it
was just a field goal festival for the first half and I'm texting you and I'm
texting house and I'm busting balls like all right happy field goals yeah like
basically like why are you at this game it's so dumb that sounds like an old
that sounds like a Steelers game playing the whole game with nothing on the line
it comes down to a field goal and the Raiders win drill it 14 to 12 they
scored 14 points with no touchdowns which is a miracle they have scored a
safety at some point scored a safety in there and people went fucking wild like
it was great and all of my ball busting fell on deaf ears because it was like
whatever that was fucking amazing and I was like this is why football wins like
that is by far the dumbest game like right now it's a Brooklyn Nets beat the
Wizards on a last second shot right like like when when the NBA has futility it
is futility yes when you are watching the backup of backups play against each
other to win by a field goal kick and everyone is like it's like what what
this is what football has won this football has won I mean we went in large
part because it was a meaningless game of course the tickets she bought tickets
that morning yeah yeah we were on the 13th row on the on the 40 yard line so
we had killer seats right and yeah we just had we went to we went knowing it
was a meaningless game knowing that neither team was gonna really care the
backups were gonna be the ones that care they are the guys they're playing for
jobs they care and of course everybody's professional so I mean they're they're
still going out there and doing the thing and yeah it was it was so much fun
it was the most relaxed sporting event I've ever been to there were there were
Kansas City Chiefs fans sitting directly in front of us we were just having nice
conversations the whole game and would like razz each other with that when our
team did well of their team didn't do well just everybody was just having a
good time just a quick check in with our listeners here Jeff Loomis in the chat
says I'm so disconnected from the NBA this is the first time I heard the Nets
are now in Brooklyn and not New Jersey Jeff they moved there before I moved to
Las Vegas I used to be a Nets fan you are behind on that I used to be a Nets
fan and they and they moved to Brooklyn and I'm such a Jersey guy that I was
pissed because there was a superior deal offered to them for them to play in New
ark yeah and they took this really shady real estate deal so this guy Bruce
Ratner could basically own all the property around the stadium and Bruce
Ratner moved the team to Brooklyn and immediately sold the team and kept the
rights to the land and everything around it it was such a fucking it was such a
fucking piece of shit deal I mean I know it moved them out of New Jersey but have
you ever heard of a more New Jersey deal than that come on they finished in style
as they say but yeah Jeff it's been at least before 2008 I don't know what year
but it's been a minute I always think that they moved just so they could
rename their dance team you know the name of the dance team for the
Brooklyn Nets right I don't it's the Brooklyn Nets Brooklyn Nets
you guys win you guys just good job yeah that's wonderful all right dance teams
for all the football teams let's go for it let's go all right well the Raiders I
just saw them the other day they're the Raiderets they're there that works
they're just like Brooklyn I know the Saints I know the Saints ones they are
the St. Seychens so they've done this a lot all right oh bangles bangles yeah
right the Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders that's just Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders
but they're a dance team as well right the Chargers are called a charger the
subtitle guys hate them are the Packers what are they the Packers fudge Packers
okay that's it the fudgies the dancing fudgies for the Packers the the bears
the cubs yeah the cubs oh are they the cubs it's a bunch of it's a bunch of
young dudes so they dance the cubs and the Twinks not to be confused with the
Dolphins they have the seals how awesome would it be to be the football game is
it you know time out and they're like all right making way the field give it
up for the Twinks it'd be great right that's good tons of cartwheels a lot of
backflips yeah yeah oh bear you have honey bears says we just do oh honey
bears is solid honey bears is nice yeah I'll tell you who else likes a good a
honey bear just cut this off before we get to the commanders and mark today's
show is brought to you by al dente for its book three Al dente escapes the
tickle hut that's al dente for its book three al dente escapes the tickle hut
that's from Dungeon Scoop in 2024 deep in the heart of the tickle hut and then
they tied up and it cannot move you see he got a feather somebody got a feather
on his feet and he feeling it but everything is a dark so he don't know who
it is give him a tickle so he have to struggle and wiggle like a worm until he
find a wall and then he were up against a wall and then he's he feel a door jam
and he squirm up to the door jam and he put his mouth under the door knob and he
lick it open and then there's still no light but he go through the door and he
wiggle wiggle wiggle even more someone still tickling his feet all the way he's
so scared there's Cheerios on the floor he can feel them his body crunching up
against the Cheerios and he hears a crying baby in the background then
shards of glass that he wiggles on shards of glass and broken Cheerios he
realizes he will never escape the tickle house or will he? Read my book! I tried to get out of the tickle house!
Who knows what's gonna happen?
Who can say?
Enter Haste Scoops to check out
You know the difference between a door jam and a door jelly right?
What's that?
I don't
I don't either
Okay
Monday night we uh we went downtown SJ and I we go downtown we had a rare night off together
and so my wife and I said oh we're gonna go out and and hit the town we'll go
find some dinner we called a couple of friends and said hey we're gonna go
down to Fremont Street and walk around maybe find a little music find a little
food see what see what the night brings us so we went down downtown we went
downtown head down to Fremont Street what we say gentlemen would we say this
is version 5 version 6 of Fremont at this point it's a resting version 5 it's
a it's a slightly slightly adjusted improved like you know they do like the
point the decimal points on different versions of stuff but it's okay I'd say
I'd say we're like 5.5 of that makes sense okay I think so Jeff Loomis you
are not completely wrong I am I am in a small minority of Las Vegas locals that
goes and does stuff on the strip in downtown that's true mainly I mean the
strip part is because my my work takes me there it's rare that we go to the
strip without work taking us there but downtown is a different animal but yeah
so we head down we we listen to a little bit of music there's a band that SJ
might work with a little bit and we wouldn't listen to them a little bit
which was nice and and then we see we did a very Las Vegas tourist thing we
saw a billboard for a special at one of the steak houses at the I should give a
shout out here the Fremont the Fremont Casino down on Fremont Street they had a
special starting at 9 p.m. 1799 for a steak and lobster dinner hey that is
that's a nice old-school Vegas touch right there can't beat that with a stick
so we said you can't be that they're trying to be old Vegas and we talked
that we've talked about like Vegas a lot on the obviously and there's a hearing
this week local businesses are trying to stop Las Vegas the town from raising
parking prices and expanding paid parking and they're basically their
argument is their argument is like the fuck I follow of course our good buddy
Troy heard who is one of the key motivators down there in the Arts
District yeah with with the theater and majestic doing his thing and his you
know his feed has just been so sad to keep up with they are just trying to
fuck the Arts District yeah and they're just trying it's just nickel and diamond
it's just the worst kind of nickel and diamond and it is being done with it
seemed it sure seems like from an outside point of view it's being done
with zero for thought not only zero for thought Jacob it seems with some level
of malicious intent as there are now security guards parking security guards
out there who are former police and they are carrying guns like what's one thing
to have a meter made on duty it's another thing to have an armed guard
patrolling your parking spaces just me getting pistol whipped as my as my chip
won't scan on the parking meter right exactly it's like it's like I just came
down here to watch my kid in a new version of Cinderella I hear what you're
shut I hear what you're saying dance I hear what you're saying and I appreciate
what you're saying I don't see that as a change
lost Las Vegas security guards it is easy to have the to have the license here to
be an armed security guard and also it's an open carry state so like having more
having more guns around is what while I don't love it it's not a surprise but do
you do either of you recall running into that on the regular in the arts district
I arts district is so new relatively okay but I mean but like I I oh no no
it's definitely changing I don't I'm saying I never saw armed guards parking
lots down in the arts district ever you know that that's I mean the argument
likely isn't like I guess I want to be able to fucking pull heat on some you
know scoff laws it's that right if you're gonna send me downtown working
late at night I would like to be armed is what they're doing because it yeah
outside I'd like to be armed everywhere I go but that's not good
are you with that well I mean I'm just taking a quick vote and nope nobody
wants Paul to be armed I've got my adamantium claws that retract and you
know so I can we're actually gonna take those away from you oh no I'm not I'm
not comfortable with you having those grafted to my bones nope sorry we're
taking them is on fire in the chat today Jeff insists you know what raising
parking prices means that this might be a spot available and I'm willing to pay
a premium for it Jeff if you lived here I'd tell you to move but you don't even
live here oh shut up and get lost and Jeff I'll tell you the the downtown
parking situation I don't think again just looking at from an outsider point
of view it sure doesn't seem like it has been affected the business side of it
has been affected by these parking rate changes yeah it's the look like this is
that are saying let they want locals to come on down there breeze in grab right
eat see you see a show go home no problem and that should be the way our
arts district work it's us it's locals it's for us also we are like our taxes
already paid for the fucking streets why I'm having to pay again to park on my
street yes we're Jacob you're ready Jacob in this country it's insane yeah
there is a meeting happening today we're not gonna be able to go to it but there
is a community meeting happening in my neighborhood today about a new church
that is wanting to be built nearby people are up in arms
right argument it should be I hope they did fuck off get the fuck out how close
to your house pretty close okay like other side of kind of the the block and
everything from me but like as the crow flies should this should this go through
and get squirrely in your neighborhood how much of a possibility is there for
us as ICS to try and file for church status at that point trying to try and
solve some things I mean it would it would automatically lessen our tax
burden which I mean we would definitely get away with it at least through the
current administration until the IRS gets beefed back up yeah you're right
we'd have three good years of skating so I would have minimum three good years
probably more like ten so yeah let's let's fucking go I mean this is fucking
also like the way your neighborhood is set up right like you have the wall
there and stuff you can put whatever st. Annick sculpture you want like right
there yeah yeah just have like we could do anything I got I was genuinely I have
trees and I have some palm trees in front of my house and I have been
genuinely considering hiring somebody to come carve tiki figures into the living
palm trees ooh can that is that safe for the palm tree I'm told that it is
really I would I would look into that a little more before doing it for sure I'm
not this is this is an idea that I'm playing with I'm just saying it to say
that I just put ridiculous things out in front of my house you can carve six six
six into the trunks of those no problem right in there it won't be too damaging
all right not a cult ish correct so we head downtown we enjoy our $18 steak and
lobster which by the way was delicious was it not was it like crawdad times or
was it lobster tail nice nice lobster tail a little cup of the drawn butter
which I mean who doesn't love a nice cup of drawn butter that's right he yeah a
little ghee for you I actually I poured water I poured butter into this can
that's I'm drinking right now good slicks your slicks up your blood vessel
walls make sure to make your blood move quicker keeps the vocal cords nice and
lubed perhaps blue ribbon butter Jeff Loomis says in the in the chat cost more
than 17 bucks to buy a decent quality steak at the grocery store that is true
this steak costs less than $17 at the grocery store but I would put it I would
put it on par with an outback not terrible at all like a street mugging
kind of steak sounds thin nice thick steak nice thick steak is that a full
measurement you put up with the screen is it also that big round as well it's
and a half right yeah that's that's girth girth and with oh they said oh we
asked the waiter said what does it come with he goes oh it's steak lobster and a
baked potato so no great what's the big potato come with he goes butter and
sour cream said anyway you can uh can do anything else with that anything else
you can add to the baked potato he goes well I can load it up for you go oh
that'd be great load it up for me you didn't ask how much the loading would
cost didn't ask how much the loading cost but it came out you know food came
out and the load up was some shredded cheese and some bacon bits right in
caviar yeah caviar no problem that was five bucks I was gonna say don't you do
it man that was the only weird the only weird cost it was five bucks the drinks
were cheap we both ordered cocktails there were like eight dollars for a for
a drink it's like good job Fremont Street casino down here doing doing
this yeah so that's nice we we walk out of there we listen to a little more
music a couple of our friends come down and and meet us so now we're all we're
all hanging out and moving around and they say oh let's go check out this new
bar downtown I'd shout him out right now if I remember what it was I'll find it
here in a minute Jacob I know so we went down we check out this new bar it's a
Japanese bar downtown in the Arts District they're really nice it is
called Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi Pachi it was lovely I had
Happy Days themed bar it was not it was not Paul oh I'm thinking of Potsy Potsy
that's right that's a different bar different bar different bar yeah yeah
the jukebox is cheap though you know how to work Potsy Potsy you gotta order the
Ralph mouth there you go so we hang out there we we have some cocktails our
friends have a little bit of food we pick off their food a little bit the
food was really good the cocktails were delicious oh I had a wagyu washed old
fashion and just fine just fine now what's that mean oh so they just with the old-fashioned they wipe a steak in the in the that's it
they just dip a steak down in there in the it just they put a steak those
drink shakers they just put a chunk of steak in there whip it up this is I am
also washed I've replaced my soap with wagyu beef now when I shower just just
just take wagyu beef across all my extremities and butter with you Matt
you're really gleaming yeah yeah I just the only person doesn't like this new
look is my cardiologist the only man who knows my secret my cardiologist he's
like I'm drinking butter I'm washing myself with beef what do you want for me
doc I don't want you to do either of those things name one thing I can do
differently
you're right pass next new solution you got me that's not gonna work for me doc
so you were at the Fremont enjoying this meal so we went to the Fremont enjoyed
this meal and then we go over to this to this new establishment called Pachi
Pachi reference to Fremont it is a walk from Fremont but just a walk it's just a
few minutes off of Fremont in the kind of on the edge of the Arts District
between kind of the Fremont Street experience and the Las Vegas Arts
District there's like where the Griffin is and all those spots on that end but
just a little bit past that and one walk over there's always fancy little spots
popping up over there yeah exactly over by like Carson kitchen area all that
yeah it's offensive to charge for parking it's that's why we walked for us
to clearly build for locals just pull in there have a good time and get out of
there yeah yep that's true so we were in there we're hanging out with our with
our friends there are four of us in there and we are at the end of the
evening we are the only people left in there with the exception of one group of
three guys that's over by the bar okay and so we we finish up and we're gonna
we're gonna head out we're gonna go you'll probably find something else and
maybe a maybe a nightcap before we call it a night and so we stand up we're
gathered up our things and one of the guys from the group across the room
breaks off and comes over to us and says you know you guys you guys enjoy your
night thank you so much for coming by and our friend goes you are you
associated with this establishment because oh yeah I'm one of the owners I
just want to come over and thank you for for coming in a lovely guy we had a nice
chat and he says hey I know you guys are getting ready to leave before you head
out for the night would you be interested in having one more cocktail mmm and we
all do the thing where the four of us just do the do the look at each other
and check in and we go yes let's have another cocktail this will this will be
nice and we all start to kind of shift towards the bar in the in the place and
he goes great hold on just a second and he calls over to the bartender says hey
I'm gonna take these folks over to forever I'll be back in a little while
what whoa oh we're going somewhere else never go to a second location Jacob
never go to a second location never go to a second location we're gonna go to
my apartment never go to a second location this is awful so we go oh we're
going somewhere else he goes yeah yeah it's just a it's just a little walk it's
a couple doors down go all right great we're in and so we we head down we walk
down the block it's clothing optional so you can leave your clothes here or check
out when you get into the place whatever you want to do they have lockers I think
it's fine don't worry about it lockers here so if you want to leave your clothes
here that's cheaper $2 over there I'm scared for you I'm really scared now oh
no no it's not that kind of story so we go over it turns out the bar that we go
to is a new bar in an old location the old location of this bar is a bar that
SJ and I used to go into all the time when we first moved here so that was
kind of exciting so we were we head into this new bar the the owner from the from
the Pachi Pachi he comes in and he says yeah these are my new friends just met
them down at down at my spot and we're all great in the world we all meet we
all we all shake hands sweet Nova girls asking did he ever prove that he was the
owner that is a fine question because what happened at that point after he
introduced us to everyone what do you think he did after we walked in he said
oh let's go let's go have a nightcap a couple doors down we walked down to the
other bar we walk in he introduces us to the the staff and everybody who's there
yeah what do you think he does at that point we haven't ordered anything we
just walked in we've met everyone it's a finger wag in the air for everyone
drinks for everyone finger wag that's what I think happens next Paul's on it
he just goes well I gotta get back over to my bar thanks for coming in guys
is this the game that they're playing they're just shifting customers to each
other's spot and we all look to each other we're like I weren't well we have
you know yeah right this is gonna you invited us here yeah these are my new
friends you I don't want to talk to you time right we were leaving his
establishment when this happened so that was trying to be slick and kick you out
of his his place so we could close no that I was like maybe you wanted to
close but that doesn't make sense because we were leaving we were like we
were up and putting our coats on leaving that's bizarre didn't make a single bit
of sense driver taking you to a specific strip club right I guess but I don't
think anybody got anything out of that I mean the bar that we went to got us to
buy another drink there I mean it was great we had a good time there we did
have I mean he left and we did just order a couple of rounds drinks there and
had a nice time there so the recommendation was awesome this is
bizarre this is bizarre also because I don't have a single bad part of this
story it was just the weirdest fucking thing I've ever seen in my life but the
weirdness matters right because like how how quickly are you gonna go to Hotsie
Totsie again I mean I don't think it's affected our opinion of that place at
all here's the thing you went down for your bargain steak steak steak bisque
the plate and lobster tail that's right and decided to dial it up by going to
Hotsie Totsie uh-huh and what probably would have ended as just a really fun
night out downtown and now next time you have like friends in town or whatever
and they're still doing the the surf and turf special whatever you're not gonna
do it again right you're not gonna just go like oh we should go do this and
bingo bing bang boom it's a really fun night downtown right well the surf and
turf special and the and the Hotsie Totsie aren't connected right they were
just they were just a walk from each other right so the surf and turf was
just earlier and then Hotsie Totsie like I know what you mean though it is a it
is a weird nightcap on the end of your experience at Hotsie Totsie in other
words like if you like a friend came down like is there any old Vegas left on
this town and you would be like oh buckle up I'm taking you down to the
Fremont we're gonna go yeah it don't don't get your don't get your potato
loaded and other and follow my lead yeah then down there you might be like hey
there's also like a little bar if you guys want to get off the strip we can go
around the town like you know me like you're very lucky like replay that
scenario but you're very much less likely to be like now to be like hey you
want to go to this bar where the guy weirded me out like you're just not
gonna do it you're just not gonna you might be right you might be right you
know like you're just simply not gonna be inclined to treat someone else to
that experience again because you're like this owner is weird there's just a
weird story and it's a it is like I say not a single bad thing not a single bad
thing at any part of the story including the recommendation the
recommendation was great no and we had a before how flawed this person's logic is
like we yes we can't find all of the spaces on the board game of decision
making on this person's right and and I and I didn't even tell you about the
full-length conversation that we had at his bar before leaving there we stood
there and all chatted and laughed and had a good time for easily for ten
minutes before he suggested that we go to the other bar we all stood around and
laughed and had a good time for about ten minutes but he specifically said you
guys want to stay for one more he saw you leaving and said let's do one more
came over when we were leaving we stood up we're putting our coats on he came
over and engaged us in conversation at that point we had a nice long
conversation we all had a nice time and as that conversation seemed to be
naturally getting to a point where we could either you know sit down and
continue it or move on with our evenings he said I know you guys are leaving
would you like to have one more cocktail right and that implies one the
cocktail happens in that location and or at least that he's gonna have it with us
and to that he's paying or that's a free round sure the paying part I was less I
was less weirded out by the paying part it is weird to escort someone to a bar
and not by the first round that's just weird agreed no matter who you are or
not if I rally a group to move one location and go to be location especially
if I'm gonna ditch them which he did that's really odd at least at least if
he says get them whatever they want on me listen I owe you back to my bar but I
wanted you guys to check out this place this rounds on me now you're doing some
hospitality work and now you know whatever but he just like shoved you into
somewhere else make buy things over here you're welcome is not it's a weird move
it is and you know what I really wanted to do you know an hour later we were
leaving the second bar yeah but I really want to do was go back to the first bar
and see well see if it was still open if it is just if it is just vanished see if
it was still there there's not even a building yeah right exactly oh there used
to be a building here years ago exactly you familiar with the hot seat hot seat
building and there's a painting of a guy and it's like 1958 fuck that was the guy
that's the guy total ghost how long was the walk between the bars oh good
question around 90 seconds it was right there yeah right now I'm not not out of
the way at all really a couple of doors down and in the in the same area in an
area we were familiar with there wasn't there was not a single moment in this
story where any of us were uncomfortable at all because not to put too fine of a
point on it but by making you go to another bar and get another drink in
which you didn't pay for you also to pay for another hour of parking that you
were about to save by leaving the bar in the first place that would have been
true that would be true for for other people we had we had parked with our
friends at the at the valet down at the Golden Gate Casino and you have friends
there and we have friends there they take care of there also connected but
it's also it's also old-school Vegas so it's all it's free valet for anyone if
you can get in the hard part there is get again because it's small it fills up
that's Jeff Loomis she charged $50 a car than anyone who really wanted to pay
could do it yeah I mean look at the capitalist Jeff Loomis over here
capitalism will solve all our problems right Jeff yeah I tell you who else
thinks capitalism will solve their problems and that's the following
sponsor old money guns Jeff Loomis today's show is brought to you by creepy
best-by guys part-time job as a professional wrestling trainer that's
from bear scoop in 2025 it's creepy best-by guy part-time job as a
professional wrestling trainer hey it's it's getting the ring it's just go a
couple see we can do here okay yeah all right now first thing you want to do is
you want to put your arms together with the other person's arms and you know
hold hold on to them so specific type of holds like what do you mean by which
holds start touching see what you see what you touch but like is there a
technique to the hole that I should be using you've been you've been punching
rice like I've asked you punching rice yeah I asked you to punch rice that was
part of the training yeah yeah big old bucket of rice he just yeah punch in
that rice yeah and it gets your grip strength growing right yeah okay yeah I
used cooked rice though so it was much easier it was very nice okay I'm gonna
call you Panda Express okay enter Hayes groups and check I don't think I think
that would very much defeat the purpose well unless you cooked it and then
refrigerated and let it reset in there then maybe I don't know maybe be sticky
enough that's why I remember I worked with this guy who's the nicest guy in
the Virgin Islands and he was a former army ranger and he said that they would
jab their hands into buckets of sand to build up their callus and strength and
then you added rocks after your house is built up after a while and then you
added broken glass when the rocks didn't do anything to your hand you just kept
jabbing them over and over again into hands the sands or whatever and he's
like that way that if you only get two fingers on someone you can still and he
literally put two fingers on my neck and I was like Jesus those are strong
he's basically saying that you just that way you still needed two fingers free to
kill someone who was trying to kill you and I was like thank you for your
service my pants what was his army ranger there's an army ranger yeah yeah
we I had friends like that a couple of Ranger friends back in the day and yeah
they I didn't fuck with him a whole lot hardly ever in fact hardly ever we have
an update on a previous story a few weeks ago fellow went to the old what was
what was the establishment went to the the haunted thing at the John Wick the
John we're on the way the John Wick experience over at area 15 fella showed
up there with a real sex doll companion and wanted to take himself and his real
sex doll companion through the experience and at one point shenanigans
occurred but professor big scoop in the chat with us here in the in the room
with us here in the zoom where it happened if you will was there so you
professor tell us your tell us your tale if you have seen the video I am the tall
guy standing to the screen right of the guy playing the manager what's it we had
we have friends send to our Instagram the actual security footage of the
events that took place yeah oh yeah so you're working there currently yes bigs
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean you know friends of ice cream social you know
sure Nicole Unger and Brenna Folger Oh lovely Brenna Folger is no friend of
ice cream so those names have nothing to do with who may have sent us those
videos so give us the skinny bigs what what what happens from your POV all
right so we've got we got the word that this is going to be happening like like
two days before really that part advance oh yeah okay that's polite or is it
polite or has he done this before with lots of places and finally realized oh I
gotta give the answer to both of those questions very well be very well be he
asked permission for the doll to be armed and we said this is an open carry
state go ahead you can strap heat under the under the torso of the real doll my
doll is coming straight from her job as a parking meter and force so so we knew
way ahead of time and and of course all of the records Chris Brown normally
plays the manager and the and the others but I was like oh come on I I was
getting ready to bump him in because I was also playing the manager and I was
like all right I I need to go in there and just kind of be his his muscle right
be the be as you know the guy standing behind him yeah and he was fine with it
and the guy came in very nice guy apparently been spending you know about
an hour or two beforehand out in the bar having conversations yeah with her and
patrons that would patrons that would come up and say oh yeah phone so I
really likes the decor here blah blah blah and the whole time he said he said
now here's the thing I'm not as weird as you guys may think I know she's fake
but I've had some really bad relationships is just makes me
comfortable makes me not crazy hard to argue with that logic who can argue
yeah and and again middle-aged guy would say it I would say probably 50 plus you
know well he's got that top of the line Vag doll model money that oh my lordy
that shit ain't cheap and he he didn't even want the whole thing he went with
the you have the huge tracks of land model as well it was yeah you lose it
over the side of a boat you wanted to be able to float guys I'm just so
psychologically damaged from all of my relationships with humans decided to
find my own holy shit now I didn't see them but everyone but some other people
said it made me took them off when once they got out of the bar apparently she
had elf ears as well okay okay yeah that is why she was rolling for
that go before going to each room exactly nice Auburn haired young lady in a blue
dress so he comes in so this thing is apparently they prefer sex workers yeah
it's heavy right it's a horse yeah it's I would I would estimate it is closing in
on 100 back somewhere between somewhere between 50 and 100 how is Jacob speaking
point with real women think you can't how's he currently transporting the
thing so he has a truck that has a lift on the back great she rides in the lift
stop it he just carries her yeah I'm like is that Paul he was just carrying
her around I'm not to be I mean I'm not as crazy as I was I just hired this
vehicle that normally transports aquatic animals if you know if you think you
recognize this swing this is the one that SeaWorld used to use you've
probably seen this thing before got a deal got a real deal it it was actually
like like a some sort of a chair one okay all right yeah so so we're in there
and we get the word all right he's coming through blah blah blah so he comes in
and because this thing is so heavy he he's got it up under the armpits and
he's kind of waddling in you know Oh Supernova girl is saying roller skates
and and somebody needs to get through to this guy and get him a pair of roller
skates no but roller skates with I just what boom she'd be on her ass every five
seconds he'd be doing like that's a real problem he'd be doing like those weird
like Scott dances with her you know just like to the legs and up and around you
get a tripod maybe we can talk roller skates what'd you call me yeah you heard
it so he comes in he puts her behind a chair he tries to be apparently she's
got wires or some kind of armature in the fingers and he tries to get her to
grip the back of the chair is this the side the grip was apparently not good
enough and you guys have seen the security footage yeah Paul it's a ride
backwards just both eyes just pop right out of the head like champagne corks it's just like it's like a cartoon oh they just they just
fly I don't with another way I christen what other guys in the room now this is
indeed where he is not as crazy as I think he is because if he was crazy
thing he was he would start weeping and he actually did just kind of start
laughing and he was like okay and this one guy went to kind of help him and he
was like no no so he went let me be the one that touches this don't do that sir
don't help some things can't be undone sir back away they're supposed to be the
the sockets are those sockets god this is this is worse the sockets kind of
packed with cotton or something yeah just one of the little cotton balls also
popped out and so he gets her he gets her back up she's there staring at the
manager and she's got no oh and and of course I'm sitting there I'm you know
it's not my show it's it's Chris's show and I'm just like all of my years of
improv just failed me I had no idea what to do in this surreal I believe I would
have literally fallen to the ground I believe I wouldn't be on the ground just
right next to her my eyeballs might pop out as well I don't know yeah this has to
be a huge curveball because you've already volunteered to do something
maybe above and beyond at work and you've you said to basically you decide
to hop on the social grenade so to speak you will be the front and back
depending on how you're operating the room muscle to basically keep awkward
bad conversations from happening right that's that's kind of like your your
your MO yeah yeah I'm just gonna drop must have thrown you for a loop I just
wanted I just wanted to be in the room standing back in the corner looking
stern you know all right are you people are you gonna you know get my boss here
you know it didn't go through a lot even weirder was it was in like a general
admission everyone else knows that that looks like fun and they started
throwing themselves on their backs hoping their eyes would pop out of their
heads and we're just like seven people died that day it's like the 80s movie
moment I'll make sure this person fits in I think I think Chris got
a line of dialogue out before the thing and then he was just like cuz Chris do
you guys know Chris Brown local Las Vegas actors work with oh I don't know
if we know Chris I'm not sure thank you it works with Rihanna is that right no
different Chris Brown ball okay okay so he was just I know you know waiting for
things to get back to some semblance of normal and then he did probably the
quickest version of that show right you have to this show resets like every 20
minutes right like you can just run people through the show just resets you
do the same show like many many many times and during the day it's got to be
weird to do the show right after that show like you have to like yeah there
must be like a weird thing where you're just watching yourself perform because
you're like I shouldn't be just doing another show I should be talking to a
counselor you have suffered a traumatic event I will I will contact the eyes
exploding out of the robots and counselor for you and oh my god and so we
sit the group accidents all the time here's my card and again it's the end of
Chris's ship so I was in there just bump him out oh it's the end of his and he
was just like he's just like oh my god the eyes they pop and we just we're both
just like what were we supposed to did he find the eyes oh yeah yeah they were
you know they're white carpet they were yeah I mean you can actually see him in
that in that security video any and he just picked him up and pocketed him yeah
he didn't worry about putting them back in her head at that point what do you
know is this a video that we can reasonably post on our patreon do you
think I don't think we can like reasonably share it I don't like that's
for sure yeah I don't think we put on a butter goes the patreon yeah I probably
know we've had the same conversation over I'm sure it's like you guys have
to decide favorite nations make sure you split whatever money you make off of
selling that video so yeah so yeah it was it was just like in yeah yeah
just tell you now scoops scoops you know we owe you high fives when we see you in
person I have access to the video okay so we're gonna video and we'll figure it
out from there that's exactly it here I just I just sold tickets of Jokers of
Magic for people just cuz they're like yeah I wasn't I wasn't gonna Wabash
Indiana but now let's go let's let's hit it we gotta see this video no that's so
hilarious there you have it January 23rd lucky day at the old House I'll be there
holy smokes well thank you so much for sharing your inside scoop with us for
sure did you have like a like a company debriefing about this event everyone
kept their underwear on at all times Matt no but I mean like you might have
been like as a company worth checking in you know that's that's the only thing
I'm like are you saying post you say oh post no no we just I mean there wasn't a
whole lot to do except I mean the guy apparently had a great time you know he
went through was there any worry about the other people who went in the
experience with him uh they I don't know if they were friends or not but they
they thought it was interesting featured on a bug for the ticket value I will say
those people probably got a much different show than than than most
people right I know that the guy at the end playing the unseen it goes alright
everybody let's move you pick up that sex doll let's go the characters have to
talk to the doll like it was a person he yeah and he would do things like like
yeah this is the blah blah blah oh she says I'm about tired of you speaking for
safety you sir have disqualified yourself as a proper custodian for this maiden
custodian ship on her this instant oh my god demand satisfaction preposterous
preposterous whatever Britney Spears dad's thing was with her that's what I've
got with that doll now I'm gonna take care of her I can give her a better life
what's the shame now is simply that you've peaked right like this is it
there's there's no other story coming down the pipe that's going to be like
and then this other time like you're you're done now with stories from work
yeah yeah that's that's that is that's true you have to go to the other ones
first and just keep hanging that one back until someone really I just can't
get over him fucking carrying the damn thing I put in a wheelchair that that I
mean the eyes popping out was just oh my god what do we do him hoisting her up
and then wobbling back and forth between her that that almost broke me right
there those doors close those doors now I find the writing to be the Herculean
effort here I don't sure you waddle around a hundred pound weight it is the
constant fabricating of dialogue in your head that you were translating to
everyone else in the room that to me feels exhausting doing some work man
doing some work yeah and like I said the gentleman was not a young man so I'm
guess he's getting his young man can't afford those things that's true too
that's true too young man only can only afford the torso did you get a whiff of
any thing whatever do you mean ball did it smell like anything just been fucked
a bunch of times say that then what else could you be asking did he like to shoot
down his throat like what are you talking about
it smells like soup I'm calling the authorities that that doll is that doll
is clearly leaking cream of mushroom get the cops in here right now this is
disgusting oh my god would it be too much if she's leaking cream of mushroom
down her leg and he's like up menses what are you gonna do oh I don't like
having professor bigs on here anymore it's her time of the month but my time
in the mouth as he slurps it up it's his shirt her he's basically a walking
lunchable he clearly has not been cooked he keeps his snacks in there that is
clearly raw cream of mushroom soup sir look that it's human grade where can
people hear more stories from you they can hear them on the fabulous geek shock
podcast or just geek shock we actually were able to finally get the just took a
decade a little more than a decade finally got it all cleaned up anything
worth doing is worth taking ten years to do it yeah well somebody was sitting on
is what the deal was we were talking about it and we just on a spur of the
moment I wonder if that guy's still sitting hey guys it's free click nice
nice yeah I have a friend is sitting a guy sitting on a great eyeballs of fire
is just sitting there and I can't wait for them to just sell it to me at a
decent price I got someone sitting on cream of mushroom cooch and I don't know
what I'm gonna do until I get it and it is leaking out no it's not the episode
title cream of mushroom cooch is not the episode title oh and Paul you'll be
happy to know that I have been carrying on the legacy of our own versions of
situational aware I think I think we all got something at the experience that
just occasionally gets us that's all there is to it yeah well thanks professor
big to see you man thanks for coming on yeah you guys thank you yeah yeah thanks
buddy good lord all right let's do a little jock
first his nerd of cream of mushroom soup
call the cops I'm just upset now we got a scooper to come and do is the day from
Swedish scoop the categories are retro dances phone numbers penile slang and
Beatles Paul you're up first what you won't give me that 2,000 penile slang
please I'll give you that 2,000 penile slang for show a British term for a
stupid or contemptible person this is really just the tip a knob end a knob
end a bell in come on aren't you a bell in oh my god oh I got smacked it's me
I'll do retro dances for 400 choppy checker taught us to do this dance
before doing it again the very next year believe that was the twist it was the
twist let's do it again did it again like you did last summer that's twist
again I need a song I want to penile slang for 400 oh I'd love to be an
Oscar Mayer this mascot wiener truck driver wiener Paul penile slang for 1200
sure why not gallus dominescus is one of the most common and most domesticus is
one of the most common and most tasty birds in the world the male is often
called this a cock it's a cock cock is right rock copy the walk out cock of the
block I'll do penile slang for 800 I swear it isn't short it is slightly
above schlaverage you could even say it is this that's a good one oh well I
shlong that's a good one I do like that one long it's long nicely done with the
wordplay on that one Matt you're up slag you dick well make something up I'll do
retro dances 800 domo oregano as you do this stilted dance a subgenre of popping
the robot that's the robot a classic beetles for 400 this beetle supposedly
died in 1966 and was replaced with a look-alike with the band dropping clues
in later releases well it's pull don't you know
it's me phone numbers 400 now for 1200 Tommy two-tone told us to call Jenny at
this number eight six seven five three oh nine that's right yeah fun fact is a lot
of people maybe of our generation and older will use that as their supermarket
codes things like that so I want to go with a real phone number if you're
traveling oh if you're traveling discount just in my desk in the
supermarket you can use that number huh just put in the local area code number
yeah huh all right Matt you're up what a valuable tip please
yeah I'll do be the beetles for 800 please Ringo star replaced this original
drummer in 1962 Tommy smothers that mother's what was his name I've got that
is the question I know I know literally the question oh man fuck both my
eyeballs what is the name Todd glass Pete best Pete best yeah that's it
Pete best Pete best shout out to Robbie for the clues in the chat oh nice Paul
you're up I will go phone numbers for 2000 I'm shooting the moon oh no sir makes
a lot told us if the butt is round and you want a triple X throwdown dial this
and kick them nasty thoughts 100 makes a lot believe that was the $2,000
oh my god someone someone call the cops the moon just got shot fuck the moon
I'll drop phone numbers for 1200 call Whitehall 1212 if you need the London
Metropolitan Police better known by this name it's also the location of its
headquarters mmm the what are they called Scotland yarders or pocket just
give you the answer thank you for the hit Paul Scotland yard I was trying to
get the Bobby's and then figure out Scotland yard from there I was still two
steps away from Scotland yard whatever if Paul's playing life flight I'm in
let's go I want to retro dances for 1200 daily double now it's for 2000 this hip
hop dance shares a name with a hugely popular 80s doll Paul what is it well
it grows in a garden okay the carrot grows in the Sun you get real stiff and
orange this would be the cabbage patch there it is the cabbage patch absolutely
yeah oh Beatles for 2000 shoot the moon we're gonna do the Beatles for 2000
nobody helped Paul Paul can't get any clues at all fine I'm the cover of Abbey
Abbey Road this beetle is the first in line and wearing a white suit it's got
to be John John is correct you know I'm going across the road first I didn't
want to get hit by a car he was always safety conscious that closed the road we
just met took the picture you know oh let's see score check with three
questions left Matt is winning with 4,000 Paul and I are both on his heels with
3600 it is anyone's game and Beatles I guess I'm gonna go retro dances and get
the $2,000 question nervous about it I'm shooting the moon this 60s dance
popularized by James Brown is more than a gravy soaked Thanksgiving side
dressing do the dressing is of course the dressing and you might put it in
clothes and turning to the side and look at yourself in the mirror that's I did
the sweet potato he did the other sweet potato stuffing the corned hash the green
casserole as everyone knows I can casserole I'm gonna do the pumpkin pie
here we go if you soak your pumpkin pie and gravy we gonna have words oh so good
we'll have so good words nasty nasty makes everything better permission I got
permission to take a gravy covered pumpkin pie to the John wick experience
don't drop it the gravy's gonna know what's gonna pop out of that thing oh
Jesus potato do the mash potato I don't know what is the move though what's the
actual move of the mash potato where you you got two fists and you pump them up
and down I only know that because of the the scene in the Blues Brothers at the
Oh Ray Charles's Ray Charles's song yeah at the music store they land in that
yeah Matt well yeah phone numbers or Beatles I need both questions to catch
you so I will take both questions please oh boy good call Beatles phone numbers
art rat is Paul McCartney's phone number damnit I will do eight six seven five
three oh nine Beatles 200 to two to two this TV presenter introduced the band
and they're really big shoe at Shea Stadium after they appeared on his long
running TV show a year earlier that would be chubby checker no checker dick
Clark's rocking Stadium concert dick Clark's rockin Stadium Eve it would be
and that would be Ed Sullivan and Sullivan of course and Paul closing out
the category and the game phone numbers for 800 call 588 2300 to reach this
company if you want to lay down some carpet Empire Empire carpet is correct
and that is the game oh shit I win with 5600 points with 5200 I definitely wasn't
looking at that the whole time man with 5200 balls that third with 4400 that's
from the sweetest scoop thank you sweetest scoop that was a very fine
scoop we haven't done that well collectively on a scooper T in a while
I even lost a 2,000-point question and still came up in the pluses yeah right
that's crazy if you want to send us a scooper to your price is right jock
versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd head on over to hey scoops calm
hey scoops right calm right there on the home page you can send us any of those
jock versus nerds you can send us some scoop mail you can do everything right
there at he scoops calm check it out I want to thank Annie for all of our years
of helping us out on this podcast thank you Annie we love you you've just you've
helped us out so much over the years I truly don't think we would we definitely
wouldn't be what we are and we would not be anything close to what we do on the
patreon side without having had any in our lives for all these years that's so
I thank you so much I want to thank Penn July for creating this podcast Penn
you've done far less than Annie in terms of doing this pod I mean really just not
pulling your weight I think we might have done less for this pod than Annie
now that I'm thinking about about it I want to thank all the people who support
us on our patreon page it is indeed a new month or did you send us a new it's
a new month and we're trying to figure out who's gonna do Annie's job so we
don't have the list guys we just don't have it we just don't have it I do have
a text here from FedEx my cat food is coming that's not gonna help this
podcast at all I want to thank all the people who do support us on our patreon
page at all the different tiers we really appreciate it this is normally a
part we thank people at a certain tier and higher by name or by scoop name if
you want to be one of those people then head over to preachingfun.com and sign
up today
or if you never want to hear the words cream of mushroom soup coming out of
Paul's mouth again go over to farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching
fun calm it does take you over to our patreon page where for as little as
three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air we are dependent on
our patreon supporters so please if you think this show is worth more than zero
dollars farts in a bag dot biz preaching fun calm that's where you can go to show
it you can do monthly subscriptions you can do yearly subscriptions and save a
little bit of money and you can gift subscriptions to other people I still
really like the idea of obelisking people via gifting them a patreon
subscription they don't even have to ever know that they're a patreon if you
could just sign up your email that's fine who cares you know but it really
does make a huge difference for us in our bottom line and look how close we
are to bonus episode territory we could get that in February if we just have a
few more people joining us to the obelisk scheme remember if you don't have
the current funds or availability to that's right jump on our patreon right
now you can participate in the obelisk scheme it's as easy as one two three
look around the room find someone who you think shares your sensibilities or
might find this podcast in the least bit entertaining and educational or funny
and point them to our URLs get them listening to ice cream social just one
person though just one it's not a pyramid scheme it is an obelisk scheme
so just find one person and again I've said it before I will say it once more
if everyone within the sound of my voice right now would simply get one more
person to listen to this podcast we could almost double our audience that's
just math math all right my dreaded and sworn enemy thanks for listening
everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
hey you guys want to go over to this other podcast over here and hang out
with them for a little while sounds good leave us immediately after you left us
see you later oh you asshole oh well this is actually fun I like this
podcast this new one is nice by started another news side podcast