Oh hello there I am so glad that you're here I want to take this opportunity to
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you ice cream truck drivers I
right now I'm sorry I got confused because I fucked something else up it
doesn't matter right now I'd like to thank Dr. Scoop Little, Elk and Magic
Scoop, Fifi, Frankie Sticky Scoop, Galactic President Scooper Star McScoopsalot, Ice
Blue Scoop, I Wanna Scoop Baby, Jacob Dinklage and Jake Schneider if you want
to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks head over to
preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice
cream truck driver and who knows the life you save may be your own that's
right I forgot to hit record on the zoom in case we have zoom people talk so now
I'm gonna hit record on the zoom now we're recording on zoom whoo here we go
hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's
go
it's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social sitting in Pittsburgh that's Paul
Mattingly sitting in Los Angeles that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Las Vegas it's
me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun hey guys very exciting very exciting
stuff guys yeah happened I'm being sarcastic but no I'm in LA doing a
little run at the Magic Castle nice nice have you already started that or
is that coming up soon no I started it did Wednesday night and Thursday night so
far and what room are you in the Peller theater okay which is funny because the
theater that features duos so people think Peller is a combination of pen
and teller but it's not true just by coincidence the guy who pwned it up the
the cash to make it happen was a guy named Albert Peller got the theater
named after him and yeah it's but you know the interesting thing about Albert
right did you know Albert no I don't know if you knew Albert or not but he
actually changed his name to represent Penn and Teller he was such a big fan of
Penn and Teller that he changed his name to celebrate Penn and Teller and then by
coincidence that theater was named after him originally his his last name was
Angel Field and but then he he found more magic people that to change his
name to so
but yeah and so I'm playing with my buddy Nick Paul a very funny guy and one bit
we always do in the show is we say we have an improv background and so we do
improv during a magic trick where I basically just try to mess with him
while he does I love I still haven't seen this idea live I love this idea it's
really fun it's really fun and so yeah last night I was messing with him and
actually messed up the trick good you got into it so you're playing the bit
too hard exactly I'm honestly not interested in you fucking with him
during the set if you've never fully messed up a trick while small fucking
with him no and I had this I just I did this bit during my magic live show so
when I messed up and he really had to reset I go don't worry I can handle this
I'm an improv guy a master of crowd work sure I mostly work cruise ships but
crowd work is universal hands up who's celebrating their 50th wedding
anniversary crowd work is the same no matter where you go quick where are my
people who are turning a hundred right now
hey there they are there's always a group of them no matter where Arthur
Peller 110 there he is yeah yeah yeah how old is he he dead little is known
about him little is known about he's an enigma is that right it depends on how
wide you want the scope to go no one of this show knows no one no one playing
the pillar theater this week knows that's what I know yeah but we're doing
the show I have a new bit I put a new bit in the show with with Ryar Ryar
Applethorne's fine craftsmanship again oh nice but I'm not gonna give too much
away because I'm gonna perform it at scoop fest so okay I will talk about it
after I'm sure we'll be talking about it after scoop fest so there you go but
look at us we're talking about it now but super fun it's a super fun bit yeah
it's been a great run so far it's always fun to be back out here nice yeah I've
had a comic booky week mm-hmm you've got exposed to radiation and now you can
turn green at will well I told you guys I saw Thunderbolts yeah oh yeah didn't
really like it I just saw Superman which would better what did you get the soup
or the man I stuck with the soup I don't regret it
waiter there's a man in my suit Superman
has that been done before I know it's my brain was in the same exact thing it's
like wait that's a good joke that's just a simple turn that has to be done before
but it's really I have to have been done before by somebody yeah yeah yeah that's
Superman oh it's all right it's okay I'm not I'm a Marvel guy not a DC guy I was
gonna say that thing people are some people are finding it very emotional
seeing that movie really yeah the the last the last couple minutes the old
James Gunn heartstring machine oh that's right it is a James Gunn one isn't it it
fires up on full cylinders in the last couple moments but so I feel the movie
there's like a baby raccoon that they're torturing brother crying it's a it is he
throws baby's dog squirrels everything your emotions throws everything at the
fucking screen he hates automatically the motions no no no it's fine with your
school and chat with a bold opinion that this man was a lot better than the
Snyder one wow the famously bad Snyder Superman I'm gonna say so is so is
everything yeah telling you about Superman Jesus so bad but yes is all
right you know but no I don't know I don't see I don't see how they're gonna
build the franchise off all this but we'll see now we'll see I yeah I don't
care about that though James Gunn's in charge of making new DC films fact this
yes this supposed you know the Superman has to be responsible for every single
movie that's going to come out after this I think it's just not something that
has to happen okay all right I think the DC is fucking up timing wise bigger than
bigger than just will they be able to do a sequel or universe around this I think
everybody is ready to take a break from superhero movies I think that I think
yes the majority of people around are ready to just be done with superhero
movies for a little while I know which which I know leads me to why DC is such
a terrible company the best movie they've made recently is just too little
too late yeah it is like a good superhero movie everybody's tired of
watching superhero movies shit and it it really is a matter of timing like you
say Jacob and I think it's more to the point of at least for me my personal
self not only am I a little bit done with the whole onslaught of superhero
there's a lot but I think more more for me I feel like I can't even I can't even
believe in this shit at all at this point because no one's stepping up to do
shit when did you believe in the end the Superman oh I don't believe in the
Superman I believe in the spider-man but just leave sticky webs everywhere
everywhere that you go but I don't know it's just it's just hard to to get your
gumption up for that you know truth and justice stuff when truth and justice is
under such direct attack name one place that it's not the way you think the
fucking Smithsonian yeah I mean it's it's preposterous that's the thing and I
just kind of like well this podcast know that I was trying for a while to have a
no sarcasm rule when I was talking about yes and it's just too overwhelming I
can't agreed I can't read 100% agreed I can't know we went all the time people
you don't want to hear us speaking earnestly about this yeah and I don't
want I don't want to speak earnestly about it at this point but I want to I
want to make my opinion known to a point but I mean yeah hold on I'm gonna take a
moment and just speak earnestly about it you know burn I'm really tired of the
Smithsonian getting changed around to show what other people are that's right
burn I'm super tired of it I'm gonna say over Christmas and go to jail burn I
went to the convenience food mart the other day and they done changed it up
they called the Supergulp the big sipper and they're racing our history burn
anyone young listen to our podcast just did a very good Jim Varney pull there
Jacob I like that yes Ernest goes to camp was a thing yeah and then Ernest
does anything became a thing where he got electrical superpowers Ernest goes
to Camp Crocodile that's the new one I remember watching Ernest goes to camp we
would have different different different families would step up sometimes take
care of take care of us you know give my dad a break when he was just a single
dad and I remember being at the Chadwicks they were lovely family that
would take care of my little brother and I for a weekend and they had a daughter
who was like eight years older than us she was look out she was gorgeous and
taste of like you know whatever and so you were all in love with her yeah
exactly and everybody was in love with the daughter and we're sitting there at
you know 11 and 12 being like what I wanted to hang and I remember I remember
torturing her as me loving and pointing out every single joke I loved and Ernest
goes to camp to her like she was trying to like just for minutes on him be like
wait wait wait watch exactly yeah she was trying to leave the room and I was
like no no the golf cart came back that's the same ghost golf cart from the
beginning amazing that's amazing that daughter name was Sarah low name was
Saint Mother Teresa I mean all she's thinking is like these poor kids with
their dead mom I guess I can sit here listen to the fucking breakdown of
earnest goes to camp this way dead moms do to kids brain I can turn them onto
this Jim Varney Christ he got mushed out in the head real quick either
volunteered as well boy soup kitchen or I guess listen to this drivel for an hour
let's damn it well Saturday keeping on my comic book theme my local guy he's
moving soon and he's having a he's having a big sale on a bunch of his
dollar books and what what have you and so he's got his cheap bins and then he
made him all his dollar books he sold him for a dime a piece for this one day
sale yeah that's less than a dollar I got a hundred and sixty some books like
sixteen bucks it was amazing that's awesome so yeah I had a real good sweep
there got a bunch of X-Men and X-Force and a bunch of little knicky knacks all
kinds of weird stuff some somebody swooped in before me you got all the
spider-man but that's alright I've got a lot enough spider-man but yeah so it's
been very very comic book heavy week for me here which is nice and then I went to
and let me go to another comic book shop we went together out at the Pittsburgh
Mills the Pittsburgh Mills have I told you guys about the fucking Pittsburgh
Mills no baseball team so the Pittsburgh Mills is an almost abandoned mall okay
they've got it's a dead mall but it's got like three stores still left in it
and currently it has a spirit Halloween a Macy's and a giant comic book shop and
that's about what it's good then and I say giant comic book shop I mean giant
comic book shop it is huge takes up like five storefronts ginormous anyway when
because there's also a lot of eateries right there around the Pittsburgh Mills
mall that's where we go to Chili's sometimes if you were gonna go if you do
a Google search for the Pittsburgh Mills mall the first thing that comes up is
why did the Pittsburgh Mills mall close yeah and it's and it exactly this mall
is closed go ahead and look up Pittsburgh Mills mall potholes because
as soon as I suggested let's drive out to the mills and Anne agreed I said I'll
drive if you're not gonna give me guff about the potholes and she's like I'll
drive because there are god-sized cracks in the earth that await await your
vehicle and Anne just can't she's like anytime I hit one the wrong way it's
like forget it she will drive around the whole parking lot so the the the place
closed quote-unquote the mills closed and everything's in this weird litigation
space right and it comes down to the stores that are renting they're quick
timeout aren't just clear you said I'll go if you don't complain about the
potholes and her answer was I'll drive yes so yes and was like no no I'm going
to complain about the puddle so I guess I should drive that's it like yeah she's
like I'll just I'll just drive you know you can't put that on the table I would
veto that right away if I don't complain about the potholes I suppose I'll do the
drive that's what she said and I'm like okay fine now no I heard that I heard
that conversation happen I accepted it and I moved on because I have been a
part of that conversation word-for-word absolutely and to to her credit she's
been having to go from store to store all around this district right yeah so
she goes there's a cup there's a store out by the mills that she goes to so she
knows these streets so she knows where the killer potholes are so she has some
sense of the navigation of the streets and I don't knows the streets and don't
ever question I like it don't ever question that Anne McPheeters knows the
street it was like I think it's called like a harbor pilot or whatever but
basically oh yeah when you bring big ships into ports they take a small boat
they shepherd out a guy who knows how to navigate yeah the tugboat that gets you
away from the rock yeah I like that they could fucking use that out there and as
the harbor pilot of potholes getting to this thing like no no we're gonna look
we're gonna go sideways here we're gonna drift for a while the Pittsburgh Mills
mall is currently experiencing a significant pothole problem with a
recent lawsuits filed by the mall's owners and even by neighbor neighboring
businesses due to the poor condition of the roads on the private property yes it
is terrible we we finally got and went long ways around to go to the Chili's
and then when we finally got out of the Chili's we we had our dinner and then
we're heading out of the Chili's she waited for traffic to stop to be done
they were still in the the mall complex she pulled out into the wrong side of
the street drove down the wrong road side of the road for about 90 feet I know
these I know these streets like the back of my hand she's just like she's like
we're not even I'm not even playing that game today and the dance we have to do
all around it's insane you know like it was like they'll tell like some of you
know if someone's as late with their their pregnancy like that like that like
they're nine months and it's just so oh no they'll tell you to go getting on a
rough road I'm saying we should we should monetize this on the rough road
they say going like a hay wagon ride you're right the Pittsburgh Mills
pregnancy popper call it the labor maker labor maker the labor maker tour the
Pittsburgh Mills pothole baby bringer tour the baby popper router my god I can
only imagine driving around writing in a wagon being pulled in that parking lot
yeah you would you would injure your spine yeah I would not come out of that
without serious injuries yeah you know who else is willing to rattle babies out
of mothers and that is the following sponsor today's show man manly's ice
cream social is brought to you by roll dolls guide to writing about abnormally
large objects that's right that's from Boson scoop pronounced Boson scoop in
2023 that's when he gave it to us this is raw roll dolls guide to writing about
abnormally large objects hello it is I famed children's author and a rock on
tour roll doll you may remember me from such wonderful child's tales as James
and the giant peach well that was my final draft after I experimented with
several other large objects before I landed on James of the giant peach there
was Kevin and the gargantuan grapes there was also Stephen and the abnormally
rotunda orange I also wrote one called Bethany and the big old snowball and
Catherine finds a fucking huge quarter that last one turned out to just be a
silver dollar the dumb lady she was just a dumb person she was a dumb person I
went on to write more dumb stories later but finally of course I landed on James
and the giant peach yes now if you want to come up with your own person and the
large thing story I encourage you to do so but don't you dare use the name James
don't you dare use the adjective giant don't you dare use peaches those are my
intellectual properties hi I'm Jimmy the large nectarine and I would like to tell
you guys a sort of tale go ahead Jim I Jimmy the large nectarine yes that's
right I feel you may be dangerously encroaching upon my IP in what way in
what way rolls how do I say well I saw how do I say your name say it how you
want I'll see you in court listen you're what you've done is you've you've gone
around my idea of having an individual involved with a large object yeah no I
have become the personification of the object yeah so you have anthropomorphize
that would be like me having a book called James the giant peach I'm just
hearing dollar signs that's all I'm hearing that's absurd and you are you
profit the giant nectar that's right
originally it was me and the giant nectarine but but the the book not to
spoil it is about us fighting a device that combined us into the giant object
you see before you like the fly yes like like the modern adaptation of the fly
yeah so you're Brendan Jimmy yeah yes oh I like this say would you like to come
to my writing cottage oh I have out in the back of my house sure but just you
know there's a lot of odd things to being a giant nectarine that maybe your
house is not prepared for what do you mean I every time I sit down I squeeze
juice everywhere oh yeah do go on oh that seems like a feature of the book do
you ralt oh oh oh we're about to have some sweet sweet times I think you and
I James mr. Jim mind if I dip a finger in that peach pin of yours my gosh my
gosh sure he scoops a check out mine if I put a finger in your navel orange that's
just upsetting yeah just upsetting nectarines I went to a music gig the
other night and there was a fan there there was a woman who is a fan of this
music group and I guess follows them around from different gigs and had made
them all baked goods and made the entire band baked goods the fan cake says the
fan cakes if piff likes but I mean brought them a veritable buffet of baked
desserts it was so much like it was so many cookies there was a cake it was all
this stuff and yeah I was like that I am a little jealous of this right now there
is there's a fan of this band who brought in enough baked goods for at
least ten people oh wow dedication yeah well what were the things did you eat it
what's going on oh I eat something for sure I definitely ate something you know
me I eat the fan cakes you know I know but there wasn't you you there were
cookies jealous there were brownies I can be jealous I can be jealous of what I
want to be jealous of you got the benefit it was like lemon bars it was
really good oh yeah good lemon bar oh yeah real good lemon bar can be great we
got the Wagner's market right up the street from us right on an unrelated
note my stomach is completely pregnant now oh no swallowing so much sperm I got
a I got only pancakes oh god only pancakes well you know what we got to do
Jacob we gotta get you on a wagon we got to get you on a wagon in the
Pittsburgh Mills parking lot real quick get that get that cake baby out of you
that same night I discovered that several of the Fremont Street performers
are now trying you know when they when they shut all the lights down on Fremont
Street and they do the shows on the canopy they do like the video shows on
the canopy above there right so I guess several of the street performers have
now instead of taking a break while the canopy does its thing they try to dance
along to it okay because I guess they're not allowed to do their act while the
canopy is playing but they can just dance along to the canopy and so they
stop doing several people stop doing whatever act they're doing on Fremont
Street and just start awkwardly dancing along with whatever is happening on the
big Fremont Street canopy and they expect people to continue tipping them
and or stay at their location to watch the show restart after the canopy stops
doing its thing that's like y'all have the wrong idea on what to do with this
situation this I appreciate y'all trying something this isn't it my heart goes
out to those poor motherfuckers oh my god that is the worst gig on planet Earth I
think I didn't stop yesterday and watch a street magician though on my on my
stroll of the strip yesterday there was a street magician in front of Bellagio
and so I saw that guy oh maybe he yeah he made my faith in humanity disappear
he wasn't that bad no no no no no I'm just saying in the general that the poor
performers had to be out there oh huskin and buskin oh man oh Jeff Lumis points
out but the top five Fremont Street performers pull in some bank there is
sure there is a real cottage industry that happens in Las Vegas with the
street performers especially down at Fremont Street yeah we don't know whether
the guy used to get paid 20 bucks get kicked in the balls we don't know whether
he stopped that for medical reasons or whether he's now retired to a lavish
island we don't know yeah I think or they did some kind of ordinance on it I
think they actually I think that guy that Matt's talking about died oh we all
the nut kicking guy from a nut kick I someone kicked his nuts into outer space
just fucking Thanos did just ah the legend of moon nuts your testicles are
like planets boom no I think I don't I don't I don't know I don't remember
anything about him dying but I did think that I think they stopped him doing that
yeah oh you think they probably died because he had because he stopped that
was the only thing keeping his balls from growing out of his heart every time
let's see it was the only way he could keep his balls from becoming so big that
they would keep him in his house they found him in his house he woke up one
morning like Kafka and he couldn't get him like he's like Gregor Samsa and he's
like oh shit it happened the balls got too big I can't get out the door and I
left my phone in the kitchen like what would you do if your balls were too big
to get through the door yeah and you left your phone in the kitchen you're
dead yeah yeah you're over you're not gonna what are you gonna pull your balls
off Jacob no no you're right I'm dead sure but if I make a living kicking men
in the nuts I'm a sex worker quote unquote right well someone was a savior
for that man to keep his balls in check because otherwise the they were gonna
just keep going yeah oh according to chat GPT the the guy
on Fremont Street who got kicked in the balls has indeed passed away Wow oh no
yeah but we don't know what from what I don't know what from yeah yeah particular
torsion that's it I passed away after hospitalization according to a social
media claim no mainstream this is a good time to mention the zoom chat if you are
a patreon supporter of this show you are eligible to come join us in the zoom
chat for this show you could be in here with us people have the chat going all
the whole time and people have something to say they can say something in the
chat and we'll bring them on to the show and they'll say it those people are all
patreon's they support us over at preachy fun calm and you can too
thanks Jacob cloud on a brothel and the chat is pointing this out now I can't
let's see it either he was really thrown because your Las Vegas hat if you look
at it differently that logo the LV can look like a 47 and he thought you were
wearing a Donald Trump oh yeah totally it totally can look like a 47 it really
does I don't see it at all so look where the L and the V connect that can be the
four and then the that's a four outer crop of the V cover up be a seven up
the far side of your of your set of your V okay her about the far side of your V
there you go you see the four okay oh yeah yeah see the four okay yeah and then
he said if you let that go you see that one's got the little thing of this so it
looks like a seven oh and that looks like a seven it kind of does look like a 47
another reason to be in the zoom chat I can't unsee it now that's really fun who
said that first got cloud in a brothel who is the person that I'm angry at man
I like this how to all you got to do is black out that little dot at the top of
the V all I've got to do is put a piece of tape over the hat not wear it ever
again all I've got to do set this cap on fire easy peasy living squeezy nothing
nothing that kerosene in a match can't fix no shit you know show up and ruin
things that I previously liked and that's the following sponsor today show
met madly as ice cream social is brought to you by Cory the camels bail bonds from
James T scoop in 2021 that's Cory the camels jail bonds hey everybody it's
Cory the camel hey hey girls hey guys hey everyone so I know a lot of you are
going to jail now cuz you're doing stupid stuff like not being born here or
you know doing other dumb things like saying no to people with in authority
well okay fine do it do what you want to do I don't care it's fine it's free
country sort of so anyway all you got to do is pay me money and I'll get you out
of jail that's right Cory's bail bonds it's here to help are you in a pinch are
you serving time in the old clink huh you in the old four-bar hospital the old
yeah the other nicknames for the jail the the the slammer yes what else they
call it the the crossbar motel huh the the the stinky place where you go when
you're in jail what's the other nicknames for the jail dr. Hassan
Pfeffer's fart box you know those classic classic nicknames oh I am going
to dr. Hassan Pfeffer's fart box oh well then you're in need of my services I am
if you end up in dr. Hart in a house and peppers firebox all you got to do call
me and I'll get you out lickety-split oh I don't like it out oh you want to go in
there you've been trying to get into dr. Hassan Pfeffer's fart box for a while I
love the smell yeah a lot of people do it's the hottest club in town I can
vouch for I can vouch for the bail bondsman Corey here I thank you I was
true story I wrapped up in a Las Vegas sexting rig and as an Israeli citizen I
got bailed out and then just got in a plane and flew the country all right and
that was shortly before he became president of Israel another success
story everybody but last week in Las Vegas wait a minute all right commercial
over also dr. Hassan Pfeffer's fart box that's a great costume idea is that's
open to interpretation has to be a Dutch oven costume on Amazon no there was a
child sex ring arrest they rested like eight people in connection with a child
sex ring here in Las Vegas there's a big children eight people eight it wasn't
ice kids are still running the streets yeah but yeah so one of them was an
Israeli citizen and they put his bond at like yeah I don't know I don't know the
amount but it was a low amount so he just paid it he just paid it and went to
the airport got on a plane and just left the country okay you know he probably
didn't realize that he wasn't technically allowed so there's a bit of a
dust-up over you know with all the people involved like how the hell did
you let that happen controversial story here local is saying this was not just
an Israeli citizen but a government official ah so that makes it a little
more sticky and I don't guess we have any kind of extradition deal there oh
you know if anything Israel does it's played by the rules so holy an Israel
government official was arrested in Las Vegas earlier this month on charges of
luring a child for sex yeah like full-on yeah like with a straight-up fish and
pole yeah candy bar a bobber and everything Wow know what I mean bird
never make bobber jokes it was Lake Mead we a lot of people stock their ponds with
fresh fish we we stock Lake Mead with children hungry children let's see oh he
had a $10,000 bail yet a $10,000 bail he posted that that standard amount for the
charge didn't appear before the judge was not required to surrender his
passport and returned to Israel two days later on a pre-scheduled flight they
could have just the chat flights he already had scheduled the chat is
filling in the mad details here winter scoop says we do have an extradition
treaty with Israel they're claiming he wasn't the right guy they're claiming and
and then Newman comes in and says this is an earnest Lexington Kentucky native
well this guy was from Kentucky oh this is really government official but he's
from Kentucky he's originally from Kentucky apparently well that's what
Newman's saying yeah right well I trust Newman I you know if it comes if it's a
Kentucky history thing Newman knows it that's what we know that is true well I
mean we know how to fish for children right
speaking of children it's a good segue right so I was recently haunted with what
what you know nature versus nurture genetics versus whatever as one of my
children one of my children started wearing a gold chain around his neck huh
oh you took the kids out of Jersey but you can't take the Jersey out of the
kids I liked I bit my tongue because I want to be like oh my god you look so
Jersey right now you you fucking t-neck reject if you shit off of you have you
seen the South Park where one of the boys finds out he's originally from New
Jersey and the mother goes full New Jersey for him oh my god I was doing a
show last night and I brought up San Antonio and the crowd all cheered for
San Antonio and I said are you all from San Antonio and they go no or whatever
like they're just for cheering whatever just a nice place next girl gets up she
says she's from Jersey and no one applauds at all not not a single clap one
boo from the back I was like wow we just love hearing the word San Antonio that
we just burst into applause but you know Jersey just kills it kills the mood I
get our rule I get it there are rules and then my other child this is really
daunting wait younger younger worse than a oh you're still a gold chain oldest
where the gold now wait oh yeah what chain great what else is there anything
on the gold chain no that's that's what makes it simple and elegant yeah slow
your role I got questions I got quite am I going to start giving gold chains to
Matt's older son yes I am has he been watching the a team no he's just been
watching I rock Z for furbishing videos on YouTube okay well he's coming by at
natural you know this one has the tea tops on a lot of people don't like the
tea tops on it I tell those people don't fuck yourself that's what I tell people
if they tell me they don't like the rock with the tea top on it you go fuck
yourself right now come down to the shore say you don't like the tea top no
okay so if that channel doesn't already exist somebody hates money oh I'm sure
it does is this situation from Jersey Shore is not doing I rock Z restore
videos on YouTube then the situation hates money let's go let's go down let's
take a drive out here to the dump okay let's go to the dump and let's see what
we can get on our I rock mission hey look at this piece of shit over here it
looks like a flattened piece of garbage looks like your mom's boys I gotta do
but what do you know it's an old I rock that's been to the crusher but we can
dig some gold out of these here hills look at here friend look at that oh we
got ourselves a volume knob factory I rock volume knob I'm sorry I'm sorry
weren't you on the Jersey Shore was I ever I am the fucking Jersey Shore yeah
I wrote I wrote Shambod on Snooki yeah how about that about that I still got
the other name I couldn't think of all I can think of is the situation I still
got basically a shroud of Turin on my belly from where that lady went to town
on me I got the snooki shroud of Turin on my fupa I got the snooki shroud of Turin
emblazing on my fupa forever from a fake tan juice Matt yes is this the
beginning is this is this the end is this this it or is it now I got to get a
bracelet now I got to get a earring now is this just are we the waters what's
happening his ears pierced he wants he wants to sleeve tattoos wait on what do
you has he asked for a tattoo no I wouldn't put it past him but no
tanning lotion though what I need a bunch of self tanning lotion latter-day
scoop found the fucking shroud of the story that's exactly what it looked
like do you think what do you think his tattoo request might be he would
probably get a spider-man tattoo or okay something with with the band or
something like that he's really in the music all right drumming the spider-man
is the way to go that's eternal yeah all right the naked lady mudflaps the the
silhouette naked lady on the mudflaps he wanted three different tribal symbols
on his lower back for peace tranquility and and money but from different but
from different tribes three different tribes the mud flap that eliminated the
that that area of tattoo right like you don't get tattoos in your lower back
anymore right like that calling it tramp stamp eliminated I think the tramp stamp
is out yeah yeah the cleave sleeve is what's coming the cleave sleeve is in
for sure yes I see a lot of cleave sleeves but I don't see a lot of tramp stamps
yeah yeah yeah yeah I've also started seeing a lot of a lot of ladies here in
Las Vegas walking around in the in the very short dresses with the with the leg
tattoos like the leg sleeve Oh leg sleeves showing off the leg what do you
call the leg sleeve tattoo is there a name for that somebody in the chat tell
me if there's a name for that but it's where they do the whole leg just like
you do like the sleeve of the arm hot the game glam winter scoop just says
milk leg that's the milk leg pant leg the ink leg leg I like ink leg ink or
just leggings
Gamm Glam actually the answer sob Gamm Glam that's it okay Gamm Glam Glam Gamm Gamm Gamm Gamm Gamm Gamm yeah yeah yeah a mistake the mistake and my youngest son we have
like this is you know this is gonna sound a little bougie guys but we have we
have okay we have toaster tongs do you know toaster talk yeah they're like
basic wooden to take your thing out of your toes yeah like wooden like little
wooden tongs they're smaller than like classic tongs they're wooden yeah they're
almost like like people who can't use chopsticks you know use fake I got you
it looks like it's like I got you wouldn't but why would they go with wood
does it doesn't for a hot thing doesn't conduct electricity yeah so if you jam
stick that all the way down the toaster and not kill yourself yeah I see yeah
okay and there's two because I one time used it to get food out of some other
object and my wife got angry that I used the toaster tongs on another food object
on the improper thing so I was never in the toaster and a bit of like you know
20% rage 50% sarcasm bought a second pair of toaster tongs good okay to be
like I'll use these however I please and my son spontaneously grabbed both
toaster tongs and started moving around my kitchen like a crab oh no and I was
like it was like I saw a ghost I was like what what do you have you if you've
never done that for no right he does not know my my that I was the crab at
Starbucks when I went to Starbucks I used to move around the whole store and
cower into a corner with the two pastry times nurture versus nature that that
memory straight up came out of your boss that's just yeah it's science your tongue
yeah it is science well you know they're finding out more and more of that crazy
shit how much yeah how much DNA memory there is and how much and I mean you
know cuz like like with with women they're born with easy now we're gonna
be in a Sarah Ross clip right now we're three guys talking about women right
right right right how about female presenting individual okay go for it
okay representing individuals see our are are born with stop the even me and
microphones ovum that that you know that's from there you know they have
them in the womb all right I mean yeah like as the as the zygote develops yeah
yeah no zygote develop into babies into a fetus yeah like early on you've got
that genetic material that's gonna make the next generation and they're
discovering more and more that events that occur during pregnancy to the
mother can translate genetic information habits different stuff like like they
did a study on like groups of people who are experiencing famine and how their
progeny were affected by that and not even that first generation that second
generation sometimes - I don't know it's interesting it is interesting I mean I'm
always blown away by animals learning behavior right or like also all these
animals like no like crows in a certain region all know how to like navigate
traffic lights and things like that right or like all right yeah things with
it and the light over them that but by the way that's how they navigate the
traffic lights that yeah yeah whereas crows of the past would just slide right
into them right right they've evolved but did you did you see not they are
evolving now Jacob did you hear about they are I'm being stupid but I know
it's actually happening too no no no no did you did you read this article Matt
about the the crows that have all gone mute no yeah so there's this whole
region of crows that have gone completely mute and the scientists are
looking for the cause I killed Jacob I killed Jacob everyone I'm sorry I'm
sorry there's just sad emojis coming in just depression let's just go live
feedback in the chat you got some LOL some laughing faces you got but you get
one sigh what Andy said I murdered that one so thank you and you have three sad
faces this is looking like a 60% hit of a joke we've got it we've got to see you
at the cone which which hey man I'll take 60% any day that joke is for the
birds yes I'm raving about it to my wife see now we're rolling now we got it
going oh mr. head scoop thought that it was a real fact coming through yeah mr.
head scoop that is your fault I hate to blame the victim on this but that is
your fault Brogan says 60% of the time I'm funny every time yeah that's generous
thank you Brogan that's generous I I don't give a flock at any rate I will
submit my my youngest son for genetic studies for comedy good oh my god that's
so crazy I've never been a prouder dad I've never been a prouder dad that's
pretty amazing that's pretty amazing yeah has all of the the strife about you
you getting the wrong thing out of the with the toaster tongs is all that been
settled or is there still tension in the house I don't know I never see my wife I
don't know I don't know oh I saw yesterday she was she was mad about
something I couldn't tell what but she was hot about something but yeah yeah
yeah you should do Cisco's the tong song oh tong to tong tong tong yeah yeah oh
someone already memed you Paul slaking fool it's not a murder of crows on the
list there's probable cause there you go oh slaking classic now I'm mad at you
too now I'm mad at you so one of my kids is now a middle school ah they start
middle school at 7 a.m. because they hate you that's it wait a minute they say
they say cuz the bus schedule so like grade school starts at 9 a.m. and middle
school starts at 7 a.m. they say it's now busing this is this is something
where I legit have beef with the way they do it because there are tons of
studies that say this is terribly detrimental and it's especially
detrimental to children in that age range I know what beef is I have had beef
experience I know adolescence need more sleep they've proven that man it's
fucked up oh I I agree it's a real I know you do I know it's not on you it's
a real game changer I would be so awkward if this is where Paul found out
that Matt was the one who set that rule up the one son of a bus never forgive
you this podcast is finished was even worse she was over there not looking at
her kids is middle school they had signups for cross-country and so my
sign up for cross-country and it is a hundred and five degrees out right now
yeah and so I figured they can't be they must have them inside of the gym or they
must like you know take it easy or do something different and I go to pick up
my kid from after cross-country and his face is just bright red like a tomato
like absolutely no your son is a fair skin young man yes also anyway yeah he
is porcelain skin yeah and it was a bright red tomato and I was like I said
is that sunburn or from exhaustion of running and he says ice combo he says I
don't know that I don't I honestly don't know probably is the answer probably oh
this is like I don't know why I look like I'm a tomato right now that's
horrible I said why are they having you run what is above a hundred and five
degrees they said oh cuz you know we're part of the national program and so we
have to we have to compare what we're doing to all the other schools who are
doing it and most schools don't are in a hot area like ours and so it's like a
false sport on the national oh I got you I said that's not a good enough answer
for me just so you're just so we're clear I don't care how I don't care how
you fair nationally my child I don't care yeah I don't care how you fair
nationally in this thing that I already don't care about I don't care about
children's cross-country running so why would I care about how you line up
against other kids from Milwaukee yeah I just I was like what are we doing and
even my youngest son was like we did recess indoors because the principal
said we won't we won't go do recess outdoors if it's if it's a hundred and
two or above and I saw somebody at the school has figured it out but I said a
hundred and two who gave that two-degree variance to like I was thinking a
hundred degrees easy that's the official number math that's the number that you
want to pay attention to is the 102 and that's really crazy
amateurs pay attention to a hundred professionals pay attention to 102 it's
it's a hundred one boys roll out the soccer balls let's go yeah I got an eye
on the thermometer if it takes up to 103 we're heading inside and it's madness I
mean there are the soccer practices start next week and I'm like it is still
August why are we pretending like it's not August in Las Vegas why are we like
why are we doing this yeah cargo cults of education programs it's still October
it can still be October in Las Vegas and be that hot oh my god that's all yeah it
is it is ridiculous that that is why when I joined the cross-country bear
jamboree aha I didn't fuck around I just I just did the the animatronic junk band
you signed up to become a robot high school guitar player I was I was an
animatronic jug band fat bear that sat down I was like can I just sign up for
cross-country bear bear jamboree Paul ran cross-country a couple of times in
the suit it didn't end well no that was awful yeah I have an update for some of
the scoops who told me basically there's a there's a k-pop Disney show where they
do k-pop versions of different Disney songs and stuff because my kids have
ever since they went to that concert I've not stopped listening just cannot
stop listening to the soundtrack to zombies and descendants movies oh so
you're trying to switch it up on them so they said some people said the music
from the k-pop ones actually pretty good and so I try to turn my kids onto that
and they saw it coming a mile away and they were like no no no thanks have you
tried black pink I was like hey I heard this like a k-pop show in Disney maybe
we should watch that tonight and they're like no nice try narc concert footage on
YouTube and stuff I bet they'll like that all right yes I think killers of
the age where I think black pink will turn his head yeah black pink is good
he'll be like and they are and they are legit good music too yeah yeah you'll
like they are they're really all right I'll do my best I'll do anything to stop
listening to throw on black pink and throw on some fucking babymetal dude
like it's a babymetal concert footage is awesome as you know early in the summer
you know we took him to MJ the musical so Michael Jackson was pretty prominent
and the thing now we have mixed emotions about Michael Jackson's legacy but
separating artists I don't mind some Michael Jackson music in my car his pro
profile from Michael Jackson Michael Jackson no longer played at all alive no
longer alive but also no longer play to my car and I guess I can't complain it
like I what happened I want my kids listen to Michael Jackson I can't really
can't really can't really pound that no chaotic clumsy if Jacob could wear a
47 hat you can listen to Michael Jackson what has this podcast so man that does
just look like a four
god fucking damn it Jacob are you like now retroactively looking back at a
couple weird thumbs up you've gotten walking to Caesars you know walking a
lot of people just yelling things about like January 6th peaceful protests am I
right high five yeah oh shit let the protesters out of jail a lot of people
say that to me fuck the Smithsonian oh yeah yeah that's come up a lot and wait
make sense now wait like okay here's what that's like seriously we've lost
the plot we cannot yeah can not care about a Cracker Barrel logo we just can't
no you just can't we can't we can't right away how weird was it that I
called this weeks ago when I was in Mesa Arizona I made a joke that it was gonna
be just called barrel after yeah and and I predicted a dust-up with with MAGA and
and crack the barrel of course just just of course the Simpsons we predict
everything they're trying they're looking for anything to distract from a
certain dead pedophile
like it wasn't even like they changed the name to something like it you know
like General Mills and the answer my mind all other stuff like they changed
they changed stuff they just took off the weird guy that you couldn't really
see that kind of looked like a shotgun but kind of look like a person leaning
against so here's the thing it just says that yeah with that logo as a kid I
always thought that that was a big strapping man man spreading you thought
he was straddling a barrel I thought he was straddling side straddling a barrel
yeah only in my later years I really looked at it he's got it's it's not it's
not one leg it's both his legs and they're withered they look like it looks
like you straddling my god you're right I always saw him as a straddler yeah yeah
no he's he's he's an old grandpa he's a withery old grandpa with both his legs
on one side and so taking right taking away the weird old white dude you can't
quite see just going with the actual name of the company created chaos I
mean they lost as it should the company lost hundreds of millions of dollars
shit really yeah yeah and people are just mad but you know what but you know
what also that shit is just fucking straight-up stock manipulation yeah yeah
when you get right down to it all this shit is just they're just playing these
games okay I work for a certain company that has several concentric circles
around it that the head of that company just stepped down yeah oh right this the
CEO just step oh that's right yeah yeah but but he didn't leave the company he's
gonna pull works for the Olympics several circles yeah he works for he
works he still works there he's just in a different role so it's all just optics
and games man it ain't nobody lose enough exactly I got over that woman was
like we the viral clip with woman saying look you got a lot more in common with
these immigrants being picked up off the street that you do with the billionaires
causing this mess oh hey baby that's the goddamn I'm stepping down you won't hear
me anymore I'm gonna be right over there that's why guys so you cannot talk to me
I'm gonna be look yeah I've been doing this role shitily for 11 years I'll take
my golden parachute now thank you very much and continue to work here that's
just trying to make what two bucks off of Brogan that's it yeah yeah yeah yeah
five yeah thank you we get I do I get the PayPal emails you play spawn and
broken PayPal's us and then I get the I get the emails anyway all right let's
get into some scoop mail or something let's do it let's do a little scoop mail
we don't have any physical mail we just have regular scoop mail from Valerie
good morrow churn denizens I haven't written in a while as life has gotten in
the way the last thing I wrote was about the lady wanting a CSI team to
investigate the mysterious shit in her shed toilet I'm a little behind in on
episode 1234 there was a proposal to add see what the cone as a sign-off this
reminded me that I hadn't actually written in to propose an alternative use
of cone my partner's work life doesn't allow him to be a scoop however he's
very supportive enjoys the bits and stories from ICS that I curate for him
and he knows a few of the running gags what do you mean your partner's work
life doesn't allow him to be a wait a minute what's going on what's the
conflict of interest we present we pose your partner's work doesn't allow your
partner to listen to podcasts well I don't know what's going on there yeah he
also enjoys meeting scoops everyone will be known for known or met thus far has
been amazing kind and fun as my partner supportive and scoop adjacent I have
taken to referring to him as my cone in a few of the scoop gatherings that we
have been a part of I would like to pose the cone be used for a non scoop
supportive partner and that the new sign off be one of the following see you in
the parlor wink and tap on nose optional or see you at the soda fountain jerk
optional handshake like pulling a soda fuck you in the face that's about the
fountain jerk I like to see at the set of fountain jerk it's good yeah I like
that I think there's room for all of these things and I love that you've got
I've already gone ahead and just started calling your supportive partner your
comb let's hope they don't waffle look at that broken just coming through five
dollars coaching Brogan's the best oh we got one from Andy hide sure it's just a
short one today I wanted to write to ask for a trophy or statuette or merit badge
or whatever it is that you give out to improvisers for a chanting outstanding
achievement in improvisation here's the scenario my wife and I had been married
for a little while now and we have been meaning to update our wheels I came home
one day Kevin carrying heavy grocery shopping bags and walked straight past
her into the kitchen to dump them on the table my wife followed me into the
kitchen and from behind said in a bright and proud voice hey honey I got my new
will signed off and finished so now you will get everything before she could
even finish her sentence I turned on her and used a piece of produce to pretend
to stab my wife directly in the heart somehow she didn't see the funny side of
this and I was sleeping on the couch that's Andy oh no Andy good bit good bit
that was a good that was a good bit good timing like you're fast - I think she's
mad at your ass yeah well was it a banana oh maybe a cucumber celery
don't bend the type of produce the type of produce of raw chicken or the poultry
just no produce a flatly old chicken I challenge you to a duel and you smack
them with chicken breast I just saw that episode of the Simpsons the other day
where Homer goes around slapping people and challenging them to a duel gets in a
gunfight well that's what we used to do on this show now we just do jock vs.
nerd oh yeah
Oh chicken breasts that will slap you whoa oh we got a price of sprite today
let's see Matt Matt the Magnum scoop us wrote this price of sprite for us said
that they know that Matt really hated all of the jock vs. nerds where there
were the infinite wrong answers so we made the price of sprites apparently
Magnum scoop has made this price of sprite specifically so that Matt would
hate price of sprite by the end of this game as well Wow Wow let's see what
happens this is some fucking saw shit right here yeah what number is the fourth
law of thermodynamics it isn't for what do you I'm first I don't even know what
this question means what number is the fourth law of thermodynamics hint it
isn't for yeah I don't even know what that means means it's not number four
gotta be number five yeah I mean I'm gonna guess number five Paul what's your
guess I'll guess number three all right Matt four let's try it zero oh well shit
huh all right oh we were all over at what temperature in Kelvin does all
motion stop I mean absolutely stop Paul you're first absolute zero absolute zero
Matt neck negative one oh that might win I'll say one it's zero Paul got two
points hey a blank day is a vulnerability in software or hardware that is
typically unknown to the vendor and for which no patch or other fix is available
Matt you're up first zero zero a zero day oh zero day that's pretty good right
I think you're right that's a jack reciter I'm going one Paul what are you
going not to Matt do you hate this yet it's zero man got two points it's all
zero that's the that's the bit oh yeah yeah we got it - okay this year predates
the birth of Jesus which is one AD or one CT etc and is used for astronomical
calculations I'm first I'm gonna guess zero Paul uh I'll guess well no it's uh
oh what was it no what was the BC what did it go I don't know I know what you're
talking about but I don't know I'll guess 230 230 Chinese dentists please
one one good guess good guess Jacob was exactly right zero two points oh all
right Jacob what's the scores down oh we're all tied at two and there is the
fifth question Paul is first on this one this numerical nickname was given to
school-aged Samuel Joel M well before his Tony Award-winning performances Oh
zero mustel right great zero zero Matt's gonna guess one stands for mustel Paul
was exactly right zero 38 be 17 be 29 spitfire mosquito these are all well
known WW2 aircraft of the Allies but what is the most famous Japanese aircraft
Matt zero that's the zero I'm gonna guess one Paul's gonna guess two and Matt
was exactly right and pulp fiction the rapey pawn shop guy had a chopper with
his name on the keychain his name can sometimes mean a number in British
English what was his name if it was a number hilarious that's the best
question in this in this price is right right there
his name was Zed which is zero Paul's gonna guess one Matt's gonna guess two
and Jacob was right it's time for the bonus round we all have four points each
it's me first I'm gonna wager all four I'm gonna do a high-powered spin if you
can hear my dogs barking it's because the yard guys are here Oh yard guys
yard guy oh yard guys and I lost the wager oh my god Jacob what a cat I'm
down to zero points Paul what are you bet I'll wager it all bill wager no
it's Jacob my name is all right let's go mid mid spin oh Paul is a medium pace
kind of spinner we all know that I wager all my points betting it all low
please a low pace a nice a nice lackadaisical spin a lazy spin and Matt
gets four points you know what that means Matt and Paul are tied eight
points apiece Jacob wins oh no traditional scoopity rules that was a
price is right sit in by Magnum scoop as if you want to send in a price is
right or a jock versus nerd of any kind head over to hey scoops calm hey scoops
calm right there on the home page send us in a jock versus nerd send us in
some on screen what is happening do all the things over there at a scoops calm
also buy yourself some tickets to scoop fest do yourself a favor come visit us
here in September in beautiful Las Vegas Nevada head over there hey scoops calm
or you can just go to scoop fest calm and hey you can get a discount to your
tickets at scoop fest by being a patreon you go over you sign up on the lowest
tier three dollars a month sign up to be a patreon you get a discount for scoop
fest that is more than three dollars a month it's more than three dollars you
can make us look silly go to patreon.com/hey scoops no no that's too
complicated go over there to preaching fun dot com I'm stretching this out
because I can't remember where the button is. There it is. And if you want to go
I don't know slap people with chicken breasts go to fartsinabag.biz
that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun dot com it takes you
to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can help
keep this show on the air that's right not only does it get you tickets to
scoop fest or the cheaper tickets to scoop fest it gets you the knowledge
that you personally are keeping this show rolling that's right all of that
crow humor from earlier wouldn't be possible without you yeah all right I
want to thank the following people who all carry on distinct memories from
their parents sperm that'd be scoop Lindsey scoop Jesus scoop is your door
scooper real good scoop Emily scoop Dave ill scoop Chang the Beijing bugle scoop
Bucky scoop Brady scabby the rat scoop sax guy Jimmy D Sarah Boyle Sonya
Petrovich Sam Reed Saltlick scoop second mingle Ryre Appledorn Ryan Hayward Rose
Ron Heck and Roger Edge big thanks to these people who may not be from Jersey
but do love to rock a gold chain pick it up pick it up pick it up Philip
Guyton Phil Tomlinson Phil Renly petty officer scoop Peter
sanzone Peter McDougal Peter Heinz Peter Buford Pete bougie Pete Romano P back
scoop PE scoop poly gone Paula Paul's brother Paul Helzer scoop Luxton one
fell scoop oaky scoop Nikki Benoit Nicole Levin Nicole Burson back and
Nicholas petty and I want to thank the following people who all recently got a
pothole named after them in Pittsburgh that'd be erotimus scoop robots ahoy
Robert Paulson Richard Hill Richard graffiti Richard fast not Richard done
Reverend Nick Dingman of the church the spaghetti Church of the Flying Spaghetti
Monster scoop scoop Getty well that's a long one Reverend Nick Dingman of the
Church of the Flying Scoop Getty Monster remember the Alamode refrigerated Perry
scoop Randy Glenn Randy Ralph Barrett raggedy girl radioactive scoop quite
quiet scoop and pyro plus proto scoop and proper scoop big thanks to these
folks who get paid for getting kicked in the nuts and may or may not have died
because of it nesticle scoop Neil Fleish Neapolitan neck pubes Nathan Hootin
Nathan Clay miss Johnny Australia mr. head scoop Motor City Smitty
Monica day monad knock scoop Mohan there mitzulah Mississippi churning scoop
Mississippi churning scoop milk leg scoop Mike wins and Mike six thank you
and the following scoops are just like me and really scared one of their
gardeners just now just by sitting in their chair and the gardener just walked
past the glass door to my office looked inside and looked very frightened to see
me those are Mike federally Mike Michelle Yaser Michael Shaw Michael
Martin Michael Calder Michael Melissa Archiga Malia McTits Max the ginger scoop
Max Mackenzie Matt Lackie Matt aka Stormageddon Matt scoop a fail much ice
cream sundae Mary Norbury Glazer Mark Wilson Mark Matson Mark Gates Mark Cohen
Mario Rosa Mark Sadowiski marble tulip scooby tree maple raisin scoop mama
ninja scoop macho scoop Randy Sprinkles em hurts Luke Mellon Lauren Grinsey
Linda Brandmeier little red Leon Kasab Leon Cox Lee Forrest Lee Drummond Laurie
Ellsworth latter day scoop Larry Goodale Lance Amon LAJ and Max Shnor thank you so
much everybody yeah so much by the way I just checked her email zero PayPal tips
for me taking off my shirt just to be clear words the amount that we expected
so far so far yes thank you all for tuning in stay safe out there we love
you and we'll see you soon do love you guys
[Music]
we sure are see ya