Oh
Hello there I am so glad you are here because I want to thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Who are the ice cream truck drivers? These are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
It's a brand new month right now. It's actually Halloween as we're recording this, but it's a brand new month for us
So I don't have new lists yet
But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver at this part of the show this month
Yeah, we'll thank all of you every single one of you if you're an ice cream truck driver
You'll hear your name at this part of the show of this month
That's right
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver preaching fun commas ring go preaching fun comm head over there sign up to be
An ice cream truck driver and who knows
The life you save
May be your own
Maybe
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
Pittsburgh is Paul Mattingly also sitting in Vegas. It's me Jacob the audio guy
Yeah, see even your kids think you die all the time Matt does one Jacob impersonation his entire family thinks he's dying
That's right. That's right
We get it
We're about to set up our trick-and-treat
Deal as soon as we wrap here. We'll be going outside the city of our house here. Yeah, same here and
I
Well, we did a test run last night basically Ryre Applethorne built me a
Disguised jack-in-the-box giant jack-in-the-box. Yeah, uh-huh. And so yesterday was trunk or treat
Over at the school. And so everybody had these ornate
You know trunk design set up their car trunk designs
Yeah, they do like full-on decorations on their cars and everything right? Yes a trunk look like a monster mouth or all kind of stuff
Like that. Yeah, and my wife signed signed me up for it. But we
We've been crazy busy. And so I basically had
30 minutes to run home and put stuff in my car to make trunk or treat happen and then back to the school
I had the Halloween parade and I had to teach a theater workshop to the kids there and then trunk or treat was right after
And so I rolled up in my Corolla
Yeah
put down a blanket the skeleton a couple a couple skeletons and
then I gave the controls over to my youngest son who scared the shit out of everybody with a jump scare and
With with
With with with basically no decorations. We got third place in the trunk or treat because we were scared
Yes
Ryre Appledorn coming through baby. Well poor Ryre Appledorn. I have to get him on the phone
The prop did not hold up to the stress test of a repeated truck or treat thing. Oh really?
How many how many reps did the prop get last night I mean
50 60 reps. Yeah, you know, I don't normally perform that trick 60 times in an hour
Interesting interesting
Will that my now my son to his content is the the front door broke off completely and okay
then the fish that the clown was holding snapped out of his hand and then the finger got of the one clown got caught and
Something on one of the reloads and snapped a finger
It was a real
It was a day news a day and I was also relying on that tonight today
so I'm gonna get my neighbor Gary to see if we can fix the front door on the on the
Clown now the clown with a snap finger and a couple of broken things doesn't hurt that doesn't hurt the bit at all
the vibe is still there for the scare. Yeah and
To Ryre's credit he I for no reason he added two giant loud horns to the prop when I didn't ask for that at all
And it absolutely makes it and my son was way on top of it
Just blasting people with the horn on the jump scare and just really good really crushing it. And so perfect
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but yes, this is indeed
I gotta I'm gonna see if I can put it to put it back together for the for the for the
Tonight the don't leave the property reading. Yeah. Yeah
Oh
Paul you're already dressed for trick-or-treat. You got your you got your Ninja Turtles hat on there
This is actually a winter to that. I just sport when it gets cold. I was outside doing some chores today
It's freezing out here. It's in the 40s. You're full on Ninja Turtles hat. I'm sorry. It's not a costume
It's just your regular hat. Yeah, it's just a regular hat. I wear my phone. Yeah, of course
I mean I wore Ninja Turtle pants on the airplane for years. That's how that's how I roll. I'll give shit
Yeah
No, somebody was just asking me if I would open up my own comic book store at some point
I don't think I want the hassle. It's too much hassle my guy. My guy is in a new location now and
It's just been challenge after challenge for him getting it all squared away
It's a great new space, but just brick-and-mortar retail is thriving like no other time in history
Right now, you know what comic shops are actually doing better this year than they have in a long time. I
Think they're up something like 30 sure. No, seriously. It's a believe you but I'm
That's a not a great comparison to what comic book shops a few years ago weren't doing well at all, right? Uh
Yeah, I mean, yeah, they've certainly had their ebbs and flows. Yeah, that's all I mean, but they're yeah, I guess that's true
I mean, there are a lot of them in town now that you're right there. I've seen a lot of them just pop up
Anecdotally across Vegas. Yeah coming up coming up from the bottom, but it's a it's a you know, relatively inexpensive form of of
entertainment and
Every comic book shop has always been a labor of love. There's nobody for sure
That is nobody open the comic book shop being like and then and then I'll buy my island
More the more to the point when did comic book shops become the collectible shops as well late?
Seven when we were kids they were they were just comic book shops, right?
Or were they were they already not late seventies as far as we mean like when it became
About collectibles about the collectibles. I've got like all that all like the toys and gimmicks
Yeah, the toys from the different things and there aren't the collectible toys and the and the Pokemon cards and all the things
Don't make me start listing things. I just sound like an old man
There are still some comic shops that are very purist and really hold mostly
Books and there are the other things that those like those toys and things have a good
Margin on them. So yeah, everybody kind of thought fair as it out. Yeah
I'm holding the mug from the wedding the wedding favorite mug of the people who nice. Oh nice
Yeah, I just got out of there. You went you gotta get it. Yeah. Yeah, I have they sent me this one
They sent me this non-descript plastic cup that I'm drinking out of. Yeah
but yeah, we went and
Anne and I had a
Day to go and just kind of do a few little things together
she's been working like crazy and
so we went to get some food at Applebee's and then we went to the comic book store and
then we went to try out this new ice cream spot that we have in town and
It was great. This new ice cream store is great. And yeah, it's called
Crispy cone and what's your what's your go-to order at an ice cream shop. I'm usually chocolate
You're just a scoop of chocolate usually but this time the way they do it
I usually just rob them. They just say give me all the money in the register
Smart smart. It's very different
This this place very fancy crunk. Oh, he's out there got ice cream shops working for him
My default is probably chocolate chip cookie dough. That's Anne's that's what Anne likes
Yep, that's my go-to order is a shake
Okay, shake. Yeah, I want to I want a no labor. No labor for you. Just went down get it done
No, no, I want to I want to take it. I want to I want to be able to walk and sip
Enjoy my shake shakes are so good
And then I feel so terrible with myself after I have them and I don't know why
Big one. I I see people order like the huge ones that everything I'm going to you are a crazy person. That's me
I love me a big big chocolate milkshake. I just want I want a little like hand-sized
You know just a little little shake little little chocolate shake or maybe a vanilla or something like that
I don't have restraint if I get a shake. It's gone. It's gone
I yeah, it is it is a it is a two-minute treat and then it is I'm with you on that
I I have no ability to like casually take a come you do have to pace yourself on the old shakes a little bit
not me
Now take it take it down
That not only will not pace himself on the shakes, but they I got one that was
What he caught cheesecake, oh
Yeah, so they put chunks of cheesecake all on the sides of it and then drizzled strawberry syrup all over it
Really really fucking good. It sounds like a mess
It was it was really hard to get home and it was really tricky to juggle
But it was delicious. You must have been an Anne's car. No, we were in mind. I
Thought that you would have taken that into your own car. I
Know I was like, uh, I had well, here's here's what happened
Paul does not like taking food into his car. I don't we're in we're in the ice cream shop and
I start to get gurgle belly
And I and I know
That time is of the essence
The clock has started and we we not only got we each got an ice cream and we got hot chocolates
So I'm sipping a little bit of hot chocolate eat a little bit of ice cream
Mixing temperature should really help really help suit that belly. Well
Got a big pot of coffee. I get in the car Edward and as soon as we're driving I'm like and I
Got a bucket of prunes. I got some stuff going on things are things are happening and she's like you're gonna make you're gonna make it
I'm like, I think so she says is are you gonna shit in your cars? I'm not gonna shit my car
I just cleaned this car spent three hours the other day cleaning and detailing my fucking good
I'm glad that factor because if you hadn't cleaned your car, it would have been an option
Not an option. I haven't cleaned my car in months. I might shit in my car. I don't know. I don't know I
Don't know because here's what happened. We got home. I
Was in dire straits. I got out of the car. I came around the car
Into the house as I'm coming around the side of the car and says are you okay? Are you shitting yourself? And I go
Oh, no
As soon as she said it
Is she did
Me and I said, oh no
She is happening. It's happening. She dream boarded it. She straight up. This is an impression of me
She's doing impressions of me all day. She goes it's happening. Oh, no. Oh, no, and I go running up the stairs
At least started making shit filling my pants. I'm throwing my jacket away
Ripping my belt off trying to save my wallet and keys. I can feel it ripping out through my underwear
Into my jeans. I'm like this is going to drip on my stairs if I don't get upstairs
Run up the stairs run up the stairs
I'm not doing that to my downstairs bathroom. I
Get upstairs I
Get up this moment. I am going to the closest bathroom. I get upstairs. I throw my
Hands off. I throw everything over to the side. I
Completely have ruined my pants my jeans my underwear my socks
everything I
Sit on the commode and the commode is just the sides are now just
Terrible terrible soft serve of death
And it's just like the stench I'm like, I know I'm sorry I can't control
Matt Matt checked out Matt has left the zoom
And is laughing and of course at the same time saying I'm sorry
I know I know I shouldn't be laughing but you're too funny when you're doing this stuff. You're making me laugh. You're killing me smalls
And I did I made her laugh through the whole thing even though
Most women would just leave that's what I tell her straight up
I'm like, this is not the first nor the last time I've shit my pants. You haven't just left me. So it's fine
So yeah, the guy do all that laughter it's just it's just gonna be stuff going to a suitcase. Yeah, that's the trouble
Yeah, that's gonna be the bad time, but it was fine
It took me about an hour to get everything
So real quick Leon Kasab in the chat just got back in. Hey guys, I just came back
Should I recommend this episode for an obelisk?
Sure
It sums us up it appeals to a certain demographic I
Guess I mean, I'm just I'm just being honest. I'm just being honest
It was a rough night anyway
but
Finally got everything settled down and then yesterday. I cleaned the bathroom top to bottom
So, you know, I did my part to fix everything. I cleaned the bathroom that day and then I cleaned it again yesterday
So yes, I did need the muffler. I did not have my muffler muffler would have saved
But what a muffler have even would have but a muffler have slowed this down. Yes, this sounds like too much for a muffler
This was pretty intense. I have to say
Bourbon barrel like every really just
What are we doing? Yeah. Yeah, I don't know but
it was just crazy how she was like she seriously was like
Are you shitting yourself? And then sure enough I was like, oh god, I am
Wasn't before I wasn't before and now I am and I didn't make it and it was just hell on earth
Hell on the car is fine
Cars fine. I was clear from the car
Everything's fine
Everything's fine now
Well, no, no some underwear got thrown away. Yeah. Yeah. All right and some socks and
Well, no, I didn't get to my socks but
Socks is an unrelated side effect and some carpeting. No the socks. Here's the sock story
So I have socks we're on I have socks that I've probably been wearing for like ten years some of them and now they're getting
real rippy. Holy and so I
Wait rippy. Holy, I bought a bunch of new socks
And so I was like well as I go through and I find my rippy
Holy socks, I'll just start throwing them away because I've got a bunch of new socks and
Just so happens this coincided with me wearing some rippy. Holies for their last time and then and it was so bad
Taking off everything is such a rush that the top ring of the sock stayed on my foot like a
Rippy holies because I was trying to get out of my poop filled clothes
You have tear away socks
So then I use those socks to start the cleaning process somewhat and threw them away. Oh my god
Yeah, okay. It was intense. It was an intense afternoon
It was a heavy heavy
It was a lot. So wait, wait
So then was the this cheesecake Sunday in transit with you while this was happening? Yes
Yes, I said it on the roof of the car and just left it ran
Didn't even get my hot hot cocos till like an hour later. They were not hot by that time. They were delicious
So yeah
yeah, and and got the sundae and put it in a bowl and put it in the freezer for me and then the hot cocos just
Sat in my car till I was able to come back downstairs and get my hot cocos out of the car
It was a you know, well for the love of God needs some roughage and that is the following sponsor
Today's show that madly ice cream social is brought to you by the soluble fiber provided by
Slobby knobby the official glory hole of pod therapy can be located in the hobby lobby. It's lobby
Frozen Cusser in 2023
Hey everybody
I'm vice president JD Vance and if you're like me you love to go to the slobby knobby inside the hobby lobby
Yes, and waiting for me there is a surprise guest. Who knows who it'll be male female
I can't tell all I know is there's an of an old-fashioned country store looking letter R
That has a nodule in the R hole and I put my dick in the R hole and sure enough
I get my slobby knobby and I do too. It's me seventies wrestler. Rippy. Holy
Holy, yeah, that's right. Holy. Did you slobby my knobby? I did I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's me
I need work. Oh here I am
Just do doing my my closing move as you as it were
Yeah, there's no coming back from the slobby knobby
That is a finisher and a half when I heard you were guys. My name is Stephen
I'm the I'm the manager in this hobby lobby. Yeah, and I I am I don't want you guys doing this
Someone needs to be clothesline
Rippy holy just fucked you up and now you're gonna have
He's gonna give you a finishing move right on your belly. Yeah
JD III heard I heard you were coming today. So when I went to do my job
I stuff cotton in my mouth. I just put a bunch of cotton into my mouth
Furniture it did feel like home. Yeah next time if you could coil a rusty old spring on your tongue
That would just really put it put it over the edge rusty spring my tag-team partner
Rusty spring and Rippy Holy, I mean I always loved you guys cuz you did remind me of the old furniture
I used to have sex with
Don't get me in a goodwill that place would get wrecked
Jacob did you see yes, Springsteen deliver me from nowhere. I
Attempted to oh and then found out that it wasn't streaming anywhere. It's only in theaters. Oh
Yeah, you thought you're gonna watch it at home. I sat down last night to watch it and went to pull it up
It was like oh, it's not streaming here. Oh, it must be on a different service
I thought I was gonna have to pay for it. I thought it was I thought it was new
Yeah, but no, that's why I have not seen it that puppy meets theaters my friend
but I see that that thing needs to blossom slowly in the
Seeds of the tens of 12s of people that are going into theater after theater to see it sit a magic
I did watch an extended trailer of it last night and I and I listened to
Nebraska and the count Basie theater. I'll tell you that that the
The extended trailer is probably as good as the movie
Did genuinely make me want to watch the movie. So I think you might be right. Yeah
When we saw the movie Paul was a Paul was respectful
We got in the car and he's like are we waiting to get on air to talk about this and I said
No, we can talk about the car. We just rehashed it on. Yeah. Yeah
And he goes wait, you're the springsteen fan. So I'll let you talk first
You should start Paul said and with this conversation I defer I defer. Yes. I yield the floor
To the gentleman from New Jersey. So first of all to have this conversation
I'm gonna need you to set the tone first of all spoilers
Let's just yes set that out here now spoilers for deliver me from nowhere
Which I can't believe that fucking subtitle. It is meaningless
Meaningless
It's a lyric reference, but besides that it is meaningless. Yes
Here's the thing that really sums up this movie for me
I'm watching the film and I'm getting you know as emotionally invested as one can when watching the boss
Deal with the stuff
He's got this long time relationship
multiple-year relationship happening on screen
With this woman and her child and he's very much been become like a father figure to this kid here and there and you know
All this kind of thing and also just might be to say that that actor Odessa
last name is
She's Australian
She kills it. She steals the movie as far as I'm concerned. Yeah, she was great and I was like, okay Matt
So who was this lady? Uh, why didn't they stay together? What what's what's the what's the fallout from that? Oh, that says
She's a composite character of multiple ways
And I'm like fuck this movie forever then yeah
Because he doesn't even come off that nice to a composite of his
Went out of its way to fictionalize Springsteen leading on a woman with a child and ditching her that's
It is the oddest shit the choices they make
Just like if I'm gonna submit my legacy. It's a superstar. I should put out a movie where I'm absolutely
atrocious
Yeah, the most sympathetic people in the world a single mother a single working mother in a diner
Like somebody said somebody in a writing room somewhere said like no
No, we have to we have to do that like he was convinced to keep that bit in the movie. I'm sure
I don't know man. It's so weird movie
Right if you just watch just old-school movie making
Right, right. You are supposed to ride the dip of that and then that person is supposed to evolve and come back to being a better person
and
There are scenes that set it up
Informatically, so where they follow all the rules of film writing right up to that that that cliff
Where the house supposed to turn around and do make the better choice?
It's like nope. Anyways, he went on to go do some concerts. Yeah, it's the craziest thing. He
Mother and child who knows who knows he meets up with her at a diner where she's been working
Has this big heartfelt conversation?
Was she the best he had ever had not even close. She cries and
Says she does a heartfelt speech like just pierces right through all of his bullshit
Like I hope you find what you're looking for and he's gone. That's it
He never even talks to her again the rest of the movie. She never shows up again
He leaves her he leaves her crying next to a dishwashing machine. That's it. It's over. That's the last thing
She's in there's a scene later
Into the movie is that scene like 90 there's like 20 minutes left. Yeah. Yeah. Oh shit. Yeah, it's almost over
It's a build-up to this moment and this moment is where that speech should make him break down and make the right choice
Right and it's that it's like but that's not what happened in real life. So goodbye and then
Sure, let me composited this together even has this epic road trip, which is which is hysterically
Factual and that Springsteen never drove. So someone had a drive to the California
Springsteen and Copperfield are two two huge celebrities who just never really drove and
Like muddling in the diner with his food in the middle of like, you know El Paso or something and he's going like she's right
She's right
As though she had never spoken he doesn't even move on it's he is absolutely just feather on the wind
He does not do anything. He directs little anything in this film
Aside from recording an album in his bedroom
That's the only thing that he really does and then that same that same moment of him being out in this
Road trip the guy after he's seen him get all upset with his food
gets on the horn to the manager and
Comically, it's the spring scene is like five feet away. He's like, I don't know
He's gone off the deep end
It's the dumbest thing you've ever seen
It's like they want to talk about all the the the darkness in his soul, but it never really it's just I mean
They they delve into his childhood abuse
okay, but
it's just it's just
Abuse in a way that is like if we if you and I went to film school and we're like, how do we want to?
Want to show you boost? Let's cut to black and white and do the most like standard bad dad
Scenes you've ever seen in your land the bad dad
His bad dad is a character actor who's been in a lot of stuff and most notably he plays
Italian gangsters and he played Capone in I want to say Boardwalk Empire
Capone and also in adolescence. He's the tough dad in
Adolescents, though is they hit the big hit on Netflix that for okay. So very pigeon-holed like you see him
And you're already like, oh
His father was Al Capone. Okay bad guy bad guy. Yeah, and
Yeah, it's weird. It's weird. He has a breakdown at an amusement park. It's
Like even Graham is that actor's name? Yes, he's great
Steven Graham, he was really good
Look, you know like he put out he put up this big autobiography and there's a big deal
He does one person show on Broadway and where he was more candid than he'd ever been about his childhood
and his you know, he was he is the child of an abusive father and
And you know as a rock star, you know that obviously has a different, you know, weird weird way of sitting with people
but uh, you know, I
Said to Paul I said basically if you took
Like this moment, right?
This is a moment basically like spacing this finally which with the movie's get into but he's passed his lawsuits
He can finally put out music again
He can finally tour again puts up the river the rivers huge and they're begging him to like come back with another killer album
And he instead takes this artistic right turn puts up the Nebraska album and all that stuff is true
It's crazy. And so like that is a weird turn and like and I said to Paul like any time
Springsteen fans talk to non-Springsteen fans and they say he's just a cheesy rocker most the first words out of most Springsteen fans
His mouth is something about Nebraska like that album is this totally different turn
With with beautiful storytelling and songwriting in it that's not pop right and and so
You know to tell that story as a moment of triumph, you know
Artistically is maybe fascinating and kind of like basically then you pit yourself against the record people and the pressures and all the people
Wanted to be super famous that feels like more of like a typical story and then he's battling depression during this time
That feels like that would be like an underlying kind of B story, right? And instead this movie makes the
artistic choice to put up the Nebraska album against all the pressures of fame as this kind of
Dragging B story while we watch this very in depth arc of depression in the Jersey Shore
We're the only solution is to run away and move to California forever and like she and like that's not a movie anybody wants
To see about anyone
Right. Yeah, so that's that's that's my sum up of it. They flipped the a in the B stories in a way that was so strange
It's just it's it's a weird movie. It's not a bad movie
No, but it's not a good movie. No, it's a problem
Another thing we said in the car was was like it's as if like a bunch of actors got together and we're like
I want to make a movie where all of us get scenes where we get to act our faces. Oh man
It is acting happening in those fucking mo. Oh my god. Yeah, there's some people just really acting hard hard acting
No, no feel bad for the you know, the bear Jeremy Allen white or whatever like, you know
You know your your basic book on screenwriting is in the scene a character should feel different
Than it does in the beginning of a scene, right?
So it starts off feeling one way and by the end of the scene it feels another because that's how we're watching
That interaction that's that's we're watching
Situations where people can possibly change right? That's what makes compelling voyeuristic
Scenic acting movie making work and there are so many scenes where
Bruce is the same exact mood at the start of the scene at the end of nothing changes nothing changes in the scene
So nothing affects him
No
But I did just find out that um
Matt did you know that that nebraska and in cold blood were about the same events? Yes
I think I think am I the only one who didn't know that I think that common knowledge as a matter of fact
I believe if you listen back to our halloween episode jacob just the last episode when truman capote stopped by
I did indeed ask him about that. He did
It's the start. It's the starkweather murders. Yeah, it's clearly
It's clear that I wasn't listening at that moment of the last show. Yeah, you're juggling you're juggling characters stopping by the doorbell
I get it. I'm just letting you know that
Karen and georgia evidence. I just found that out this week
I didn't I didn't know that karen and georgia on my favorite murder just recently covered the starkweather shit
It's awful
And oh, yes for a lot, but for a long time it was framed as this sort of bonnie and clyde type situation
Yeah, oh right. Sure more and more we're learning. This was a 13 year old girl who watched her parents murdered in front of her
It's not like she really had a choice but to go with the psychopath
Oh, no, no, it's it's horrible. It's dark. It's dark shit
But but I mean it turns out that story of murder is a bad story. Well, but but
but the fact that we
Lumped a poor little girl in on it
This country's just fucking dumb
Of all the things that make this country down it wasn't
It wasn't the starkville murders the starkweather murders that they didn't just blame him a 13 year old dragged along for some murders
I think we have indeed figured it out
I think we've righted that wrong ball. I think that's maybe maybe I guess I don't know
Paul paul paul. I got you the country is in trouble and those murders were horrible. Yes, those are both true
They might not be related. I don't know
I don't know. I don't know. It feels like in a lot of ways. It feels like it's just misogyny all the way down
That's what it really feels like. No, I went to um, I told you guys a couple of months ago. I went down to
Prim to to look at some of the casinos down there
So we can just kind of walk through some of the casinos down there before they shut down right and one of the casinos down there
Has uh the bonnie and clied car. Yeah, where where they were where they were shot to death
And you know, it's got all the bullet holes and everything and it's a tourist attraction
And I I just stood there and looked at this thing and I was like this
this car
was uh
two people's uh death site
Uh, the evidence of them of them dying is still here
And uh, they they killed people and they robbed people and they hurt people and they did all these things
This is not uh, this is not a nice story
And I and I just kind of stood there being disgusted that this car was on display for people to come over and look at
That's me with the mom museum. People love going to my museum
There's a little like a little little uh, like a mini dock that runs throughout the whole time
And there's one where this mafia guy is is talking about being a consultant on a deniro movie
And they're reenacting the murder and he's describing like how the murder went down and they're like, oh, they're like, oh man
This guy the way he's describing it's like he actually was there and it's like, oh, isn't that awesome? No
Yeah, it's fucking yeah. He was actually there. He was there and he committed fucking brutal murder. I don't know why
That's uh, that's uh, I don't know why that's a taint tickler for you. Oh because matt it's the uh, it's the fedora
If you're wearing a fedora costa nostra
That's right. That's right
Oh, and he's not black. It's those it's those two things put together
Oh, man
Speaking of vegas icons
uh
sarah has to ross was uh filming a music video
And downtown. Yeah. Yeah, and I was asked if I would play
Uh, not elvis. This is key
But uh a fremont street elvis impersonator. That's that's the key there. Oh, yeah, that is yeah
There's a degree in casting there
Um, and if you need an elvis matt donnelly is not your guy if you need somebody on fremont street impersonating elvis matt donnelly
so I uh
my wife
Mistakenly thought I still had this elvis outfit that I used to have
um, but it eventually just
Like weathered away and became you know
Uh, well she wore it out. Honestly if we if we're just telling the truth like she just she just fucked the shit out
Oh, i'm gonna call i'm gonna screen it but um, my friend jeff calls it's nevada day, uh here that's right and um
My friend jeff knows all the words to the nevada day song nevada the nevada anthem
And he calls every single friend who still lives in nevada every nevada day and sings the entire song into their voicemail
Uh, and so I have that that's what's happening right now. It's my favorite thing
One of the more fun things about nevada is that became a state on halloween. Yeah
Um, anyhow, so, uh, so I went down to star costume and and I was like this is actually it's nothing to do with halloween
I need I need an elvis costume
And so I look
and
uh
In in my sizes, they had this really nice red one. It's really nice red one. Okay
Uh, that looked really sharp. It was a little pricey but
I've been asked to dress up like elvis on multiple occasions and I don't know if it will stop
Figured you're going to get another run out of this. Oh, this was a purchase not a not a rental, right?
This is a purchase because also
When I did virgin voyages and hopefully that went well enough that they'll invite me back
They do a thing called scarlet night where everyone dresses in red
And I was like, wait a minute if I go with the red one I can wear this
Yep
On the virgin voyages representing vegas. That'll look good. Yeah. Yeah, um, and so, uh, yeah bought myself a nice elvis outfit
and then uh went down to
Fremont and I was like, hey you guys are just shooting on the street, right?
She's like, yeah, like so there's no like dressing area. She's like, no, it's like so basically I should arrive as elvis
And they're like, yeah, okay
so
Me which coincidentally is the same note that every person who hires matt to do any gig tells it
I knew to ask I knew yeah
It's so common my my my tier my tier of of of acting is so familiar that I know be like no dressing rooms, right?
no makeup
Matt is an aae actor is what they call him. He arrives as elvis
I
Was just walking up and down fremont street dressed at the toe as elvis and did anyone look at you twice?
No people were loving it
People were loving it and so then I did this bit with sarah that when the music video comes out
I think it's gonna look great. So I won't spoil it, but it was super fun
and um
As i'm walking back to my car a guy literally goes like hey
Are you?
Are you like doing stuff here? And I was like, no, no, uh, sorry
I'm just I just actually just got a music video and i'm just walking back to my car
He was oh, okay
Um, can I take a photo of you anyway?
Sure
and he's like
He like gets down like gets a good angle or whatever. Yeah, he's like
Can't sorry. I mean, can I do is like a self a selfie is okay. Is the selfie okay?
And I was like, yeah, let's let's do it man
We took a nice selfie whatever and he was like, I gotta give you some money
And I literally go like no, no, no, no, no, i'm on my way to the car. I can't
This is you you betta say
You've met a wonderful person I was like
Did you take some money? I hope you took some fucking money
This is the thing I I told the story to sarah and she goes how much you make I said I I said no
No, i'm okay. I want to just want to get home to my kids, you know
and uh, uh
Sarah was like you you're a fool. Yeah
And I was like, I know i'm dumb every person I talked to has been like
What was going to give you it? I was like, I don't know. I don't who knows you probably get 100 bucks
I doubt it, but you never know man. People are crazy out there. No jordan campbell says this is how matt started on his only fans
um jordan this did feel uh
It did feel like a moment of like I I often kind of rack my brain if I could like make extra money or whatever
And so the idea of like oh if I could just go down a free street just like that might be
It felt like too easy like that's it was like I literally was like trying to not do it
And then someone stopped and like made sure they offered me money and I was getting a lot of attention
You know, I was walking with purpose to like not get stopped
But I was causing a lot of attention walking up and down
Uh fremont street dressed ahead to tow his elbows. Yeah, so real talk
I think you might be able to make some money doing this especially in like the earlier hours on fremont street
Not like 2 a.m. But like the 10 p.m. Yeah, yeah, no, I'm thinking like 9 or 10
I'm thinking like early early nighttime
And uh, but when the families are still out
Yeah
Because the people the people taking pictures with people on fremont street
If you don't want someone to be naked in your photograph, you're out of luck
Yeah, like you're just you're just out of luck yeah, or if you don't want like palm
Crucifixes palm crucifixes are naked people like your two options crucifixes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So last time I was down there though
I did stop and watch a a street magician
How was it performed for a few minutes? He was really good. He was really good. Well, that's good news
It's after some money in his bucket. He was great. It's hard
Because there's there's music playing at all kinds of volumes the entire time. Sometimes it's super loud. Sometimes it's just loud
This guy was a genius. I thought about that while I was watching him. He did it most of it. He did silently, right?
That's that's what it would take. Yeah
I saw a guy doing that that kind of like uh, they're all silver and money moves them kind of oh, yeah
Yeah with a magic trick kind of attached to that and I was like, yeah, that's what we can do down there. But uh, yeah
Yeah. Yeah
Um, so yeah, I don't know it may or may not be my point. I think you should start doing this
Just even just just a second time just to see what it's like to actually give it a shot
Really? I think I also want you to go down there without getting a a spot reserve for yourself
And I want to see if you get some shit for not having a reserved spot
You probably will if you that's the thing if you do it with the intention of getting paid you won't get paid
It's the people talk about it all the time
Like when when when folks hit the skids and they're out on the street begging for money
like the first day they feel like oh
We're gonna be all right here
And then after that
It's this weird beginner's luck thing and it just gets really really hard fast. Yeah, you're right
Yeah, that is a lot of stories. That is a lot of people's stories. You're right. I think it's all attitude
I think it's all the attitude
I think I think people can I don't even know how to say it because I don't know what it is
But but I I think that people can uh,
sense that
What the one thing as soon as you are be holy energy as soon as you're actually desperate
That's that rippy holy energy
I'll tell you who else has got that rippy holy energy and that's the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by the squirrels guide to breaking into podcasting. That's right. This is from cup of scoop in 2025
That's a squirrels guide to breaking into podcasting
Hey, uh
My name is nutso nutso the nutty squirrel
Yeah, and i'm gonna teach you all about breaking into podcasting
Hey, uh, uh, say there matthew I got a question for you
Uh, yes
Do you enjoy fast food?
I i've been known to indulge from time to time. Yeah, you're like a baconator
Uh, yeah, I used to do some of the baconator just for the side. Oh, so you like windy's nuts in your mouth
You got me good on that one squirrely you got me good
I would normally cut the ad off here, but squirrely actually paid for five minutes. Okay fair enough
Hey, hey, hey jacob. I heard. Oh, yes squirrely. I heard you're a connoisseur of fast food eateries as well
Sure. Yeah
Yeah, you enjoy a vanilla frosty once in a blue moon
I I do yeah. Oh, so you like windy's nuts in your mouth?
Oh say hey, hey, uh, hey matt, yeah
Yeah, I know you like a lot of different fast food restaurants you you go to the golden arches once in a blue moon
Do you oh old mcdonald's? Sure. I don't mind. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so you enjoy big max
Uh, no, you should just get you know, the regular cheeseburger the plain one
oh
Okay, enter hey scoops check
Really stumped him on that last one there paul chamberlain. He just left the room
It was an unintentional wallachian impression. I did. Well, I guess wallachian is just a squirrel
I did sound remarkably like wallachian
I've never seen wallachian and a squirrel in a room together. So I I can't uh, I can't say for sure that he's not a squirrel
There you go. I was trying to surprise you. It did play to my recorder
So jacob has already played to my recorder, but I was playing the home is nevada day theme is if I get them both my mics here
Holy shit
Is
Every word every word you get the idea you get the you get the amazing amazing who's that singing jeff my friend jeff
Well done jeff. Yeah
Got some pipes on him. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Um
I uh, oh
Go ahead jacob
Oh, I was just going to tag on to the end of fremont street. Uh, I did see a uh
While I was down there the other day. I did see a uh a parent who was watching a performance
uh whose child I would guess uh,
Six or seven was just sitting on the on the ground at fremont street
While the parent was watching something kind of over there, you know a couple of feet away
It's the first time i've ever wanted to call cps on anymore. Wait now
Oh the parent was letting your small child just sit on the on the on the street on fremont street
That's that's already disgusting. Yeah, it's pretty gross
Yeah, I was I was not okay. What uh captured their attention so much. Was it one of the giant gorillas?
No, it was just one of the bands. It was just it was just music going
And the band was great. But did you see any of the giant gorillas while you were down there, man?
No, they didn't see any giant gorillas. There really really wasn't actually a lot going on. I know
I haven't been down there in months without seeing at least three or four giant gorillas
I wasn't I was surprised at how little I mean we were there
It was a you know, it was I was there from around uh, like 330 to five
Maybe of like 5 30
um
I was surprised how little was going on. Like I said, there's a lot of uh,
A lot of unhoused people just sitting in the spots that were designated for performers. Uh, just begging and then
Some some some some some crucifixes and then the one guy painted in silver
Doing his bit
Oh, this was also maybe a tuesday
Maybe don't wake up till later
That's probably that's I mean, that's very possibly true. Yeah, also
Uh, I also went to disco the other night
Uh, oh nice and drove down
And not since I moved here in 2008 where I stick those back roads through paradise and coval to get down to the venetian
Uh, boy, uh, no one just absolutely no cars just driving around absolutely nothing
I was like i've never seen the streets so empty. That's nice and then I pulled right into the link and uh,
Got in the very first row of self-parking just a space wide open for me at seven o'clock at night
um
I was like, uh, the rumors are true. Vegas is dead
Or everybody is avoiding matt
No, I don't think that's it
I could not believe how little uh,
There was anyone around in las vegas. That's so like I drive down those streets all the time
And they are packed all the time
Yeah, yeah, I used to have to go down there all the time and it's packed all the time
I had to go down there to get to fucking uh, the flamingo
Which has gotten even harder to get to now, which is crazy
I should note that they did start building the f1 track. So it could just be a lot of people just avoiding
Uh, that's true
Uh, but that that might be it that could be it but also yeah
There was I mean I walked up and down the link. I was very surprised that that just kind of that's kind of crazy, man
Yeah, yeah, that's kind of crazy. It was weird. It's anecdotal, but it's weird. Sure still
Still i'm gonna go see disco tomorrow. I'm looking forward to it. I haven't seen it since uh since the revamp
Oh, I think yes, I think you'll dig it a lot. I'm looking forward to it. I'll tell you though
He recently added
uh, our friends, uh d and uh, uh, uh, uh, uh grace
Created, uh these clown characters, uh to perform around the venues that are around disco not in the venue itself
Um, but two other people were doing their bit
Uh where they're just oh, yeah, two giant disco balls wearing capes and disco mustaches
and
They were killing it. I I didn't know I literally didn't know who these people were which is weird. I'm surprised. Oh good
There's two people that were just being uh that I need to find out who they were
um
But they were being hysterical so people came out of I always get nervous when people create bits like uh, like d and grace did
And then uh kind of hand them off, right?
The handoff always makes me nervous. So i'm glad to hear that it's going really well. Yes
And so uh, they were just doing a thousand bits and that people nice falling over laughing and I was like, this is great
That sounds oh i'm really looking forward to it. This is gonna be great. Yeah, it's a fun show. I really like that show
Um, it's it's so different and uh, but it's really cool now. It's super it's super streamlined
And it just cooks and our friend. Eli is the uh host
um
And uh, he's just so funny. He's just just so funny like a full person
Yeah, well, that's one reason i'm going tomorrow is uh, our another friend of ours nick is in for eli
I've seen nick do it. Nick's great at it. Nick is great at that. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, nick from uh, banana fame at scoop fest. Yes, we'll be in disco tomorrow. I drank his milkshake
You did you drink it up?
I left a little on the floor for for jonas's wheel, but a little surprise for jonas later
Surprise
But the answer is yes, i'll be dressing up like elvis tonight for my trick and treat i'll be elvis in my neighborhood
And yes, I was just about to ask you
How long are you because I know what time your trick and treat is starting today
I saw your wife last night and she said that you guys are starting at 3 pm today
How late are you planning on going?
We usually go to like nine or ten. Usually the streets get pretty empty at nine
Okay
And then I just you just run in a front yard party until until until the streets get rolled up
We have a set time here. It's it's six to eight
Yeah, yeah, that's something the high mark but people come early some people have little kids they go early
While it's still light out and then also just you know teenagers and all those other kids that go late and for me for the trick
And treating I like the teenagers. Yeah
Uh, oh, yeah. Yeah
For for for magic trick purposes not for sure. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it's it's better to deal with I don't know why matt thinks I mean something else
I'm talking about his magic trick. These teenagers love his magic trick. You want an audience and we disappear
You want an audience that has grasped the concept of object permanence? That's right
Before you uh perform magic. That's correct
That's why matt's baby magic didn't go well
Yeah, and my my my uh, my big ringer when should I fix the clown in time for it to be a jump scare?
That'd be great. And then uh, uh, I got a duck
A wooden duck that uh, whoa pecks at cards and and snatches your card out of a deck of cards
Oh, that's pretty good. Whoa
Is it like one of the one of the happy bird things? Yes. Well, no, no, no nice
It's like it's like a wooden it's like an ornate wooden. There's something you'd see it like a kitschy
Like uh, like a cracker barrel lawn decoration, right?
But it has it has a uh, uh
Mechanical neck so you push the duck you push the duck's head down and it just and it just opens its beak and snatches a card
Out of out of a deck of cards. Oh, I wish my wife had that
What it's a what it's an old it's an old it's an old old magic prop. I just bought one. Oh, it is. Okay
Yeah, it's a known thing that the duck. Yeah, the duck card picker dippy duck. I think it's called
Yeah, yeah hippy duck dip dippy duck dippy duck dippy duck. That makes sense
Hippie dippy duck is a whole different thing
But yeah, you guys want to do a little scoop mail, yes, please let's go let's do a little scoop mail
Message for you, sir
From winter scoop. This is something i've been wanting to talk about for a week now
The jewelry heist at the louvre has my brain screaming
The guys use the construction ladder to access a balcony to bypass the front doors
They were work vests and helmets and stole the jewelry after the place opened up
Guests watched them do it and nobody said anything
They just assumed that they were guys there working doing their job the balls on those guys
That's from winter scoop winter scoop. I'm genuinely concerned that the robbers of the louvre are scoops
I have been advocating bring a ladder for years that you can get in anywhere
These people just took that to the nth degree
So I heard also apparently that that kind of apparatus that long ladder
Hooked to a little scooter cart kind of deal
Is a lot more commonplace out in france because the buildings are so old that they don't have proper
Places for you to unload cargo in a lot of these places. Sure. Sure
So it's not like in the states if you saw somebody with a ladder up to a window you go
Wait a minute
maybe
But I can tell you how you i'll tell you i'll tell you you need uh,
One thing to make it where people don't give you that look in the states when you're when you're doing that and that is
An orange road cone next to the ladder. Yeah, you're right
I mean the if you put a single orange road cone next to the ladder you're done
The safety vest thing really does a lot does a lot of work. Yep, and if you got a radio
Like you can just flush this whole thing out
I think this could happen all the time
I'm really surprised this doesn't happen more often
Like you just fit in you just fit in and go do whatever you want
Um, let's see we got one
I I know people that in magician's world who are thinking that uh, it's uh, it's a it's secretly a ploy to advertise
Now you see me the new now you see me movie coming up
Oh, it could be
That's an elaborate uh elaborate setup, but well, uh
Was was gabriella one of the uh, louvre robbers. She might have been she might have jesse isenberg is
Donating a kidney as part of his promotional work, I guess
What?
Yeah, yeah, jesse isenberg is donating kidney to a stranger
And the bit is they stole his kidney no, he's just big into what is it with these magicians and donating blood matt what's going on?
Does playing with cards enough make you just say that oh I've got way too much blood in me
Um, i'm blanking on her name. She made a documentary about this. Uh, basically like how it's been it's difficult
uh, it's
Some very healthy people have two functioning kidneys and if you are of very good health you don't need them both so to speak
right, and there are a lot of people who need kidneys and um
Just did the one on the satanic temple. Um, why am I blanking on her name? Oh, you don't want penny lane penny lane penny lane
Uh did a doc on this, uh, she found it very difficult to try to donate your kidney to a stranger
She I remember her doing this doc. I never got to see it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
She did a doc about about uh, like rant not even uh random donations, but like random anonymous donations of of organs, right?
Yes
So basically like a lot of times you can put out calls if you need a kidney
Then then your friends and neighbors or friends or friends you put on campaigns to do it and that's how most kidney donation works
Uh, but when it comes to just saying like hey, uh, I have an extra kidney find someone who needs it for me
That that operation wasn't streamlined but that has improved over the years
and so now uh people who just kind of are
You know if you're generally, you know
Like I said, you don't drink you don't really do do it in crazy shit and you can just be a healthy person
Um, you can go go without go without one of those kidneys. Yeah. No one has ever asked me for one of my kidneys
I don't know. I don't know why it's never come up. Yeah, one of your marinated kidneys
Oh ten scoop in the chat mentions. Uh, it's even harder to donate if you bring it in a cooler
I've been sitting on this thing for a week. Come on. It's a couple of youtube tutorials and now here's my kidney
You made me fill my bathtub up with ice for nothing
Cost me like 23 to get all that ice
We got one from pigasus. Hey matt paul and jacob. Thank you guys and especially all the safety cones helper scoops and performers
For putting together another incredible scoop fest. It was amazing seeing so many weird and wonderful scoops
There is a great mix of new and old slash older scoops to hang out with and go on adventures with
It's incredible how you cannot see a scoop for 18 months and pick right back up where you left off from the last scoop fest
Podcast trivia battles and variety shows, especially hollywood squares were some of the very best ever
Although i'm going to try to avoid being conned into sitting in the front from now on quick scoop fest
It basically proves that i'm a potato
Sunday night after scoop fest. I was in an elevator at the orleans when two very friendly and drunk women hopped on
They noticed my hot dog necklace right away said how much they liked it and we chatted a bit between floors
They were on vacation and clearly having a great time while I stood there being well me
When I got off the elevator, I overheard one of them say to the other it's okay. I guess he doesn't want to party
It wasn't until much later at mcmullin's that I realized what was actually happening in that elevator
I just thought they were being polite. I'm already looking forward to the next one
It was great meeting so many new scoops and reconnecting with returning scoop
Thanks again for all the hard work you do to make scoop message a unique and fun gathering pigasus will fly again
Fucking you in the face. That's roger aka the nest scream or nest creamer aka pigasus. All right
Thanks rogers sounds like you saved yourself about six to eight hundred bucks, buddy. Good job. That's right
It's really true. It's probably like you almost you probably were almost about to get rolled
You never know in vegas and you know, I think orleans. It was 350. I thought well hell I think I think
I know for myself just come on
You just kind of default to the no way. This is not happening. This is some candy camera bullshit
I have had multiple friends think that they were doing very well with women
Uh than to realize on their own that they were talking to prostitutes
That's happened to multiple friends of mine and they're sad every time it happens
They still pay for the the sex and everything they still do that, but you know, they are
It's a blow to their ego first
First it's a blow to their ego then it's a blow to their you know, you get it. Good deal. Good deal fair
Uh, let's see. Oh, there's another scoop or another uh, uh
What is the thing we do scoop fest now we don't need to do the scoop best email right now from bear scoop
Hey matt paul and jacob in the same vein as the he did what and other tales
I decided to write in with my story of it's actually what?
A time well one of many when my sheer stupidity revealed itself in true glory
For context I live in a somewhat big city not far from vancouver bc
And for years no decades my commute to and from work
I would routinely see a box truck think a u-haul like a three or four ton with words
diamond delivery plastered on the side and back
Which of course, uh with of course a picture of a huge diamond in the middle
Now, I don't know if I was just in the monotony of my commute every time I saw these trucks
But I always assumed that I made up a story that of course these trucks needed to be this big
They were delivering diamonds throughout my one to two million population bustling metropolis
And the safe the safes used to do this probably take up most of the back of these trucks
That was until my early to mid 30s when I saw one of these trucks parked in my townhouse complex outside of another unit
I found this odd as why would a residential customer be having diamonds be shipped to them?
Oh dear god as I see them taking plants furniture and other crap out of the back of the truck
Diamond delivery is a delivery company not a diamond delivery company
So anyway, that's my it's actually what story fucking with the face that's a bear scoop
Thank you bear scoop, yeah, I uh
For a little while when I was a kid, we used to have uh, swans
Did you guys have swans?
meal delivery
Uh, yeah. Yeah, the like the refrigerated trucks and everything. I I thought it was delivering swans
I thought these people are getting are getting geese
Swans delivery service, yeah
Yeah
People used to eat swans, right? That's a thing
I guess you could eat a swan. Why not?
I mean you did anything with the right attitude
We got one from slurping car. Hey motherfucker greetings face fuckers
I'm writing in response to a conversation or a discussion at scoop fest about bits
And how this community attracts people with a fervent love and commitment to silly bits. Yes
It's it's one of the best things about our community
One of my favorite things this year was being privy to scoops sharing their personal bits with each other giggity
So that we could all go home with fresh road tested material that our spouses and loved ones would still not appreciate
This jogged my my memory of a genius bit
My high school friend nicole invented that I think some scoops will find useful in their everyday life
Here is what she would do
In the middle of class nicole would tilt her head up crinkle her nose and say
Did someone just microwave popcorn?
Then seconds later everyone sitting around her would start dry heaving and coughing uncontrollably with laughter
While some managed to choke out a faint fuck you
Let me explain
This is a bit nicole and her older sister perfected in a prank war as kids
When one of them had a rancid silent, but deadly fart and they wanted to trick the other into smelling it
Through many iterations they found the foulest trick was priming each other
For microwave popcorn scent as it lowered the victim's defenses and when one's olfactory is expecting a sweet
Buttery scent of microwave popcorn the juxtaposition of the actual scent of a putrid ass gas kicks in bad
There is also a delay
So the victim will have taken a full-throated drag and had their lungs filled with the flatuous before their senses could
Smell the the rock had actually been cooking
That's not a result that's a prank
this is
It's a war crime. It's a hell of a move. I hate I hate what i'm listening. That's a hell of a move
I don't this is actually this is worse than what the u.s is doing out in the pacific. Oh lord
Bong rip levels of coughing and retching from my classmates nicole gave and still gives
Zero fucks as she did this popcorn bit every goddamn time
She farts and it was truly one of the funniest things to watch once you're in on the gag
However, she did it to me so fucking bad with this the first time she did it
Uh to me what i was 10 years ago that till this day. I went when I walked through an amc movie theater
Feel free to use this bit at your own risk ps. I'm curious
What other bits scoops might have to share uh, and if they could be uh, so good to share them in a fucking scoop mail format
Figgity fucking your olfactory glands. That's slurpy ka-ay motherfucker
That's really funny that that's commitment. I mean that is that is commitment for sure
That is like geneva wants to have words with you
That's that's just cruel. I mean to do that once is genius to really commit and do it all the time. That's crazy
Yeah, it's pretty wild
Uh, how are you guys on fart humor?
Well, i'm very happy with fart humor when it is the uh, the sound of the fart
And and the funny like oh this was this was a fart thing. Yeah. Yeah, this is great
As soon as I smell something just rank
I stopped thinking it's funny so quickly there is there is a my favorite murder animated
A letter that somebody wrote into them
About this guy. He was working at a post office
And he let a fart that was so stank
That the post office had to be shut down
And the fucking bomb squad got called because they thought it was some kind of chemical contaminant coming in through the mail
It is wild
Wild
Yeah, I never was like all that stuff of the farting is it feels like in the in the in the vein of like, uh,
Like bag tagging or like drawing on the face of someone who falls asleep all that all that kind of stuff
Puts me in a weird place. I don't like it. I'm with you jacob
I think the noise is where the funny is the machines that make the sounds and all that are great
But like didn't they just have a teacher get arrested for putting fart gas on his students all the time
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
There's a story about uh
To the internet jacob
When I typed in teacher arrested the autofill was for fart spray. Okay, this was it so share with it
I don't know the exact what what happened, but uh, let's see when it comes to the smell stuff. That's when it starts to get
criminal
A 32 year old assistant teacher in west florence high school in south carolina was arrested for spraying a foul smelling substance
Through the school's ventilation system his actions which occurred nearly over nearly a month long period
Led to six students and over
55,000 and damages to the school's air conditioning system lewis faced the charge of disturbing schools and malicious intent
malicious injury to property
Uh
I question the quality of that ac system if fart spray
If fart spray takes it out
Yeah, that's not hepa approved. That's for sure
This was and then have you seen the the the cruel thing that the people do for the people who are in the inflated costumes?
Yes, because you got a little you got the vent there you fart into the fart at the vent
Or you put some stinky at the vent and they're just stuck inside
Can you imagine just farting on somebody's vent and they're just like
I've seen people take like like fish bait and just throw it up against the fan
My favorite example of that comes from the harlan williams
rocket man movie
Where he does it he he's connected via a tube to another astronaut
He cuts apart and there's this whole back and forth where they're stuck in there with the fart. Oh
Oh, it's funny when it's on tv and it's a sound and you can't smell it
But I think you're right. Jacob when you smell it, it's just
I just don't want to smell shit. Yeah, this is why I don't hang out in paul's bathroom
Yeah
Just don't want it
What were you about to say matt?
I thought I was at a kids halloween parade. Uh yesterday
Where I saw a lot of the idea of seeing these adorable children being uh assaulted with farts is is really it's just not comforting
Because you because you saw a lot of inflatable costumes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So if you yeah, you're going to get them just hit them with a little fart spray right on the
That's it. They're done. Just do it the old-fashioned way and fart on them
Just go in there and fart on them
Let's do a little jock versus nerd
I'm on the hunt for balls
On the hunt for balls
Explosion up the stairs. Oh, no, it's happening
No, it's happening
It's happening
I'm gonna have to throw these socks away
We got an old-school jock versus nerd coming to us today from king scoop king scoop has sent us a
Timeline jock versus nerd. I think he sent us another one of these a long time ago
This one also might be from a long time ago. I didn't see what the date on the email was
Uh, but this is i'm going to give you an event and then i'm going to give you two other events
And then you're going to tell me which of those happened closer to the primary event. Oh, right. Yeah, these are interesting
So the first one and he he made this so I can't see the answers until I highlight them too
So this is great head trippy
Yeah, so the first one the first san diego comic con took place
Comic con took place. So that's the main event. That's the primary event
Is that closer in time to the berlin wall being built or the fall of the berlin wall?
Ooh
Uh paul, you want to go first on this one? You seem like you got a uh, sure
Some got a handle on does anybody know when the berlin wall was built?
Well, it came down in the 80s so before that
I asked when it was built. Yeah, it was built before that
But it's like the 90s or right out it was not built in the 90s
It got built in like
In like the 50s, right
After the war right
Oh boy, uh, it's gonna be close
Close close close, uh, I guess i'm gonna say it's closer to the building of the wall
Do you know when the first comic con was?
78 I think
oh
Well, then I would also say it's closer to the to the building of the wall
Matt what do you think so I have to get which event is closer to the wall or comic con
Yeah, it's comic con is the is the primary event
Is that closer to is it closer in time to the berlin wall being built or the berlin wall being taken down?
I'm gonna say berlin wall taken down
All right. So paul and I both think built matt thinks
taken down
It is the berlin wall being built, okay
Comic con first done in 1970. Oh 70 was built in 61
So off on that one came down in 89
Okay
Uh, let's see. We got uh, the first major league baseball world series took place
Is that closer to joseph stalin coming to power or coca cola is first sold in bottles?
Uh, i'll go first on this one. I think this is going to be closer to uh, the coca cola
What what's the main event again?
Uh major league baseball first world series, okay
World series stalin or coke
Yeah
So i'm going world. I'm going, uh coke cola
there's stories of like, uh
I think it was like shoeless joe jacks in order for being like an early investor in coke
So i'm gonna go with coke as well
Really? Okay. I feel like coke is super old
And so is the world series
I'll just but this is this isn't coke. This is bottles. This is this is bottled coke. I'll go contrary and i'll say stalin
All right. Let's see
It is coca cola, uh world series 1903
Stalin 1924 coke cola first bottled
Oh, wow. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's it. Oh, that's the other bottling. I know. Okay. That's that bottling thing
uh
I think that's the non carbonated
Bottling of coca cola and you had to you had to have the thing to add you had to have a nation into
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, you had to add the seltzer water in maybe okay, um
I think I might be I might be off on those dates. I should know this my my granddad worked for him. Um
The first disco world novel by terry pratchett was published disc world. Is that closer to
That does say disc world, you're right you got disco on the mind
No, it's a uh, well, yes, also I have disco on the mind. Uh, yeah
So anyway, uh disc world novel was published. Is that closer to israel becoming an independent jewish state or donald trump becoming president?
I have
I don't have a guess on this really at all. I know that terry pratchett is a fairly modern
author
So i'll say trump
disc world was
in the 80s
Oh, okay
I believe
Late 70s early 80s
Uh
I'll go with israel. Yeah, of course this is about israel
Matt I think it's also about israel
Let's see
Point for jacob donald trump, uh
Disc world published in 83 right on that paul israel becomes an independent jewish state in 1948
And donald trump becomes president in 2016. Okay, so there you go. Okay
The first time a player wilt chamberlain scored 100 points in a basketball game
Is that closer to orson welles war of the worlds being broadcast or facebook's founding?
Oh
Chamberlain scores 100 points with the still that's the 70s the big dipper. Yep
No three-point line just scored 100 points two points at a time that thing was in the 50s
the world of worlds
Yep
And
Facebook was found in the late 90s. I think facebook was like, yeah
Something like that. Yeah, it had to been like yeah, very late 90s like 98 or something 97
I'm gonna go with facebook. I think the war of the worlds is older than that
I'll go with war of the worlds
Oh
You put me in a predicament
I'll go
I'll go facebook as well
Let's see here
War of the worlds poll gets a point. We go. Yay back on the board
uh
1960 or sorry, uh
War of the worlds is that uh the hundred point score from wilt is in the 60s. It's 62 not in the 70s
We were off on that. I also thought that was in the 70s
Uh war of the worlds is 38 facebook 38 in 2004
So, uh, basically every single date we said about anything in that question was wrong
Yeah, we were just wrong about everything well and that and that tracks that I would get it right for not having the right math
That's how it works the first ever video game tennis for two was created
Is that closer to the ussr launching sputnik or the movie jaws opening in theaters?
Tennis for two is the video game. Is that closer to sputnik or jaws?
Sputnik was 60s jaws was what 78?
Something like that
And what do you think and what's the main thing the no the tet in the game, uh, yeah tennis for two
Tennis for two was like 60
I'll go with the sputnik
Your sputnik matt your jaws, yeah
Tennis for two
That's gotta be early I think sputnik i'll go sputnik. Yeah, it's earlier than you think
Let's see here
Wait, it's hard to read this, uh sputnik. Oh, it is sputnik. Yay tennis for two 1958
Uh, oh sputnik was launched in 57
Okay, and then jaws opened in 75. So sputnik was really close. Yeah
Rocky marciano retired having gone undefeated in 49 boxing matches
Is that closer in time to computer game space invaders being released or the gi bill is signed providing financial aid to veterans?
Rocky marciano closer to uh space invaders or the gi bill
That's gotta be the gi bill i'll go i'll go gi bill i'll go space invaders just because i'm already losing this game
I'll try space invaders, too
Let's see here. No, I think it's the original space invaders paul
Okay, oh you meant space invaders also. Yes
Uh, let's see. It is the
It's the gi bill. Oh
Rocky is uh 1956 the gi bill is 1941 space invaders is 78
Uh, let's see. Let's do one more dungeons and dragons was first published is that closer to the international space station being opened
Or mcdonald's being founded
Oh dnd
Versus international space station or mcdonald's i'll go mcdonald's mickey d's
Okay, i'll go space station then
Let's see
Sorry, this is a like a word document and then I have to
Look back highlight the area. Yeah
it is
Space station dnd 1974 space station opened in 2000 mcdonald's was founded 1940
Jacob you killed us in this game. You you destroyed us did
Oh, did I? Yeah, I think you won most of them
Oh, well good for me in that case. I win
All the fabulous prizes that go along with it are mine
Yeah
Thank you so much. Oh shit. I just closed it out without uh thanking the the person again. Uh
Whoever you were I said your name at the beginning of that
and
shoot
Oh, I feel terrible now. I closed it out too early. Thank you so much for sending that in
Uh, we really appreciate it. I think that is I think that is that scoops second timeline scooper
Yes, our timeline jack versus nerd they sent in. Uh, so thank you so much for that. Hey scoops.com is reading
Go hey scoops.com go over there. You can send us an old school
Jock versus nerd just like that one just uh that you just heard there
You can also send us an email over there send us some scoop mail over there at hey scoops.com
Also, you can make us a scooper. You can make us a pricey sprite jock versus nerd
You can make us an obelisk jock versus nerd. We're running low on all of our jock versus nerd
So head over to hey scoops.com and make us some new ones. It's great. It's a it's a big part of the show
Yeah, we could really use them. Yeah, do it
Um, I want to thank uh, pens up for this podcast. Thanks pen. I want to thank all all the people support us over on our patreon page
It's the beginning of a new month. So we don't have any of our new, uh, thank yous to do just yet
Uh, but we appreciate you, uh supporting us
Uh paul is on a mission to uh add a a newsletter
To our our deal
And yes, we even had an official meeting about today before we got on air paul's on top of it. He's a motivated man
Um, this newsletter is going to be great
And so is we're doing all kinds of cool stuff just to keep it uh fresh over there on our patreon page
Uh, if you aren't supporting us yet, please think about doing so we have all kinds of different tiers
Monthly or yearly levels yearly will save you some money
Um, and if you can fit it into your budget, it would help us out a lot
So head on over to preachingfun.com and check it out right now
Hanging with you
Or if you too are going to get yourself some new socks for reasons that you would rather not talk about head on over to farts
In a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preachingfun.com it does take you over to our patreon for his where for his little
Is three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air. You can do monthly subscriptions
You can do yearly subscriptions. You can also gift subscriptions to other people. We got the holidays coming up fairly soon here
So if you want to gift a subscription to our patreon to someone else
You can do all of those things right over there at preachingfun.com and of course at farts in a bag dot biz
In my mind paul is still wearing his uh sock anklet
As we're recording right now. I just I just want to be clear about that just in your mind
Just in my mind and on your ankle
Oh
All right, don't get too close to that sock. It'll give you a pink eye
Thanks for listening stay safe out there. Happy nevada day and we'll see you soon
We'll see you soon
Happy november
See ya