Oh hello there, I am so happy you're here, because I want to thank the ice cream truck
drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers, it's a new month, I don't have a new list
just yet, but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver before the show, this
month, we'll do it this month, we're gonna get it done, it's all gonna get done people,
nobody panic.
In the meantime, if you want to become an ice cream truck driver, head over to preachingfun.com,
it's where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows, the
life you save may be your own, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh baby this is what I like, hey Johnny,
do you want to go to an ice cream social, yeah I'd love to, great let's go, that song
is not a joke, none of that stuff, none of those old 50 poppy songs, I was just listening
to one this morning, Splish Splash, it's basically you're arrested on a list for life, oh yeah,
yeah.
It's time for Matt Maddly's ice cream social, sitting at the bathtub, that's Paul Maddly,
sitting at a different bathtub, it's Matt Donnelly, and sitting in the shower, it's
me, Jacob the Audio Guy, we're preaching fun.
Yeah.
Splish Splash.
I jump back in the bath, how was, I don't know, there was a party going on, it's so
strange, they didn't have headphones back then, what kind of, what kind of quiet ass
weird party is happening outside your bathroom that you can't hear it, and you come out with
a towel, and he had a towel on, he claims, and then he's like, I mean, I think the answer
to your question, Paul, is Swinger Party, I think a Swinger Party is going on outside
his bathroom door.
Is that what it's about?
There's an orgy.
I'm thinking that right now.
There's an orgy happening, and he's like, oh god.
Yeah, a whole orgy.
A very, very quiet orgy.
'Cause my boner is going crazy.
There are 18 different, no, 19 different people having sex out here very quietly.
There's one odd man getting double digits.
Oh, that guy is a good sport.
Yeah.
Look at him go.
They turned him into a bowling ball.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, that was a spare.
How you doing, Matt?
Where are you?
Good.
I'm still in San Antonio, and we received some feedback that my audio is super weird
and bad.
One, this is addressable, definitely going forward.
I have traveled with a directional microphone before, it's just I traveled with so much
stuff that I was like, oh, if I could just take a room recorder with me, that's easier.
But we're going to go ahead and call that experiment failed.
But we're going to keep the recorder, and I think what we're going to do is do it.
This is just a good, here you go.
We're going to do like a headset mic or something like that into Matt's recorder so that he's
only going to carry, there's going to be a small additional thing to carry when he's
on the road.
Yeah.
This is something that we were going to address anyway, and then some people said something
about it as well.
And so, yeah, here we are.
Would you like like an airplane pilot headset?
Why not get him the cans that have the mic coming off of it?
Would that work, Jacob?
Too soon.
Bring up airlines right now, Paul.
It's just too soon.
Oh, buddy, are you feeling the crunch?
I don't know yet because I don't know if San Antonio's airport qualifies as one of the
top 40 airports in the country.
It's only the top 40?
It's the top 40, but Vegas definitely does, so the airport you're flying into definitely
qualifies.
I know, and here's the top 40 airlines in the US coming in at number 40.
It's STL, St. Louis's own hub of choice.
That's right.
And it's getting fucked raw dog style by our own American president.
If you can fucking call him that, what a ridiculous waste of skin.
All right, let's see how else he can destroy the middle class even further and kill small
business with his fat, stupid thumbs on every goddamn scale in the States.
What a bitch.
Dear Casey, my dad used to buy me that popcorn Oprah like the Chicago's O'Hare airport.
I was wondering if you could play Chicago O'Hare for my dad.
Here we go.
Coming out at number 39 with no kernels, it's popcorn O'Hare.
You guys got sending me these dead dog stories.
I got to read these dead dog stories and then go right into a pop hit.
Casey, Casey, the mic's still on.
The mic's still on, Casey.
Yeah, well, it's going to be on your ass, you fucker.
Fuck you.
Casey Kasem's gone rogue.
Look, I'm Bumblebee.
No, I'm Cliffjumper and Shaggy.
So eat my shit.
So Mike in the chat says, I don't know what the airport thing is.
Because of air traffic controllers being part of the budget for the government, the government
being shut down, the transportation secretary has asked 10% of flights to be canceled and
they're targeting 40 of the top 40 major airports to cancel those flights to decrease air traffic
since so many air traffic controllers are either quitting or working a second job and
not calling out because they're not getting paid.
They're not actively not getting paid.
Gross.
It turns out they have bills.
We have air traffic controllers who listen to the show.
Yes.
I know several.
And my heart goes out to you guys.
Thank you for all the incredible hard work you do.
Also, goddamn, my old hometown stomping grounds, you see that horrific shit that went down
in Louisville?
Sorry.
I can't hear you outside of a Casey Kasem voice now.
I'm now stuck hearing you in Casey Kasem.
Well, friends, it turns out we went back to the bluegrass state and the bluegrass state
is now blue and charred, charred black with the remnants of thousands and thousands of
gallons of gasoline, jet fuel that dispersed all over human and animal alike, killing them
all in one fell swoop.
UPS made one special delivery to hell.
Oh, that that one is what you're talking about.
Yes.
I did see that one, Casey.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's a horrific event.
Casey Kasem is just here to do the horrible news.
Perhaps it's a little too soon now.
I guess that's the way you do it.
Casey Kasem from now on.
All horrible news is covered by Casey Kasem.
No, it's it's really sad.
A terrible.
I know.
It's horrible.
I that that I flew out of that airport to come to Vegas.
I flew out of there to go to go to the air Chicago.
That was my one way trip there to Chicago.
Then to think what there is on the plane, not the airport.
Right.
Yes.
But the airport got fucked and their surrounding areas got full.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It did crash into businesses.
That's terrible.
It's it's horrific.
Yeah.
It's really, really scary.
They basically closed down Louisville for a day because of the noxious fumes and shit.
Is that what they is that what they're calling the area around your house?
The area of obnoxious fumes, the area of noxious fumes.
Yeah.
Especially if I've had microwave hot dogs.
That's right.
Oh, Jesus.
Can we close this down for just just a couple more hours because he is about to shut down
Pittsburgh.
Oh, oh, green cloud trying to kamikaze it just doing doing this service for mankind.
My guy, my guy has not been happy with late.
I will say that.
I will say that we're climbing and there's a cloud of Paul.
Yeah, it's terrible.
So the airline stuff is really awful.
It's really, really bad.
And I'm just great.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's bad.
I reflect on it.
And I think how grateful I am that I'm not flying anytime soon.
But I think there's so many people that are.
And yeah.
And then and we we narrowly missed coming into some shit with Scoop Fest.
And fuck who knows what the next one's going to be like.
Yeah, we're screwed.
I guess we're done.
All right.
OK, see you next year, everybody.
Happier news.
OK.
Tomorrow.
Happier news.
Are you asking for it?
No, I've got it.
Tomorrow.
Mark's 19 years married to Anne McPheeters for a while.
How about that?
Oh, that'll be good.
Yep.
Tomorrow's our anniversary.
And of course, she has to work.
And so so we spent that as we spent together.
What?
That's not how I work my ass.
She works that ass all the time.
So I want you to guess we took we decided today we were going to do our anniversary.
You will never in a million years guess what we did for our first dog in the Chili's parking
lot.
You're not that far off.
Put on put on bee costumes and culled your own honey into jars.
Nope.
OK.
Shit.
That was my next guess.
What is that called?
What are beekeepers called?
Beekeepers?
No.
No, there's a what's the hobby called?
Keeping bees.
Apis.
That's it.
Thanks, Leon.
Apiris.
There's an extra syllable there.
Not rapists.
No.
Nope.
Yeah.
I keep bees.
I'm a rapist.
Apiary.
It's an apiary.
That's right.
A beehive is an apiary.
So apist.
I guess.
I'm the apist here.
It was called that because an ape invented it.
Oh, beehive, says Rich Scoop.
Good one.
Bees.
They're great.
No, we decided earlier this week, really and decided, but I was totally in on the plan
plan.
We decided that for our 19th wedding anniversary, we were going to go join Costco.
Oh man.
I didn't want to cry on today's show, but that's really just...
Too bad.
Too late.
Here comes the Waterworks.
Everybody in the chat is weeping openly.
Yeah.
Oh Costco, how I love thee.
It was...
I love that Paul refuses to talk over his own song.
He's like, I will not use my own song as an underbed of music.
We will just sit and listen to it.
I'm sipping on my Costco Coca-Cola.
I did get a hot Costco hot dog on the way out.
We both did.
We had our dinner.
Did you...
You ate from one side, she ate from the other, yeah?
You guys ate the hot dog until you...
Yeah.
Totally.
In the middle.
Fucking Lady of the Tramp did.
Who was who?
And then you both tried the same with the Costco pizza, but you tapped out halfway through
because of just the amount of dough in your bellies?
We did.
We did a slice and a dog each, and we both tapped out.
We were like, okay, this is too much food, but it was really good.
It took me too...
As someone with children, I've been a Costco member for some time, it took me too long
to realize I should never order two slices of pizza from that place.
Did Matt just freeze?
He did just freeze.
Matt just froze in the...
He's unfrozen now.
We can see him again now, but he froze in the best pose that he could have possibly
frozen in.
It was good pose.
You looked striking.
All right.
Sorry, we lost you there for a second, Matt.
You've been a Costco member for a long time.
The audience heard it.
They heard your recorder, but we didn't hear it.
Oh yeah.
I'll repeat it here.
It took me too long to realize that I shouldn't order two slices of pizza from Costco.
God no.
I'd be in the middle of that second slice, be like, what have I done?
Just like the whole...
Why do I do this?
The whole world becomes slow motion.
It's almost a quarter of a pizza.
Yeah.
It's a ridiculous thing.
What happens at leaving food on your plate at a restaurant or something?
I'm only just now in my life getting to where I'm able to really do it and be comfortable
with it.
Yeah.
I'm getting better at it, but I don't usually do it.
Dick, if you're actually bringing up a big thing for me, to be honest with you.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
As someone who's trying to be a recovery fatty, I'm going to tell you, thin people leave stuff
on their plates all the time.
They do it left and right.
They don't give a shit.
I've never grown up with a clean plate club or whatever.
The amount of people I know where I go out to eat with a skinny person and they just
know they're done and the fork's down and they're still half the way in the plate and
they're casual and confident about it.
They just wait forever and finally the waiter comes over and goes, "Are you done?"
They go, "Yes."
It's been seen the whole time.
They don't finish their fries.
It's an amazing trait of a thin person.
I have simply tried to imitate this to possibly become thinner by being like, "Can I do what
I want to do?"
Meanwhile, I'm secretly sweating because I'm just like, "When is that waiter coming?
Take that fucking plate away from me.
I still won't eat this entire thing."
But I want to be like a thin person and I want to leave it.
There's no like, "Oh my gosh, you're starving children in Africa," and all that stuff.
None of that holds true for a thinny person.
They don't care.
Starving child in Africa is not getting the food on this plate regardless of if I eat
it or not.
Now, my wife is a skinny person who always insists on taking everything home, which all
this does is light a fuse for three days later, "Why is there so much shit in our fucking
fridge?"
It's like, "I think you need to go into the bathroom, look in the mirror, and ask that
question to yourself."
Which is always a safe answer to give when your wife asks a question that she's upset
about.
In the kitchen, I'm like, "I don't know, gosh, goddamn."
What could it be?
Oh man.
I don't know.
They're multiplying.
We got to get to the bottom of this.
I never got to eating all that leftover food I took home.
I never got to do that.
Hold on.
I'll go beat the children.
Yeah.
They must be putting stuff in the fridge again.
That'd be a good habit to develop.
You have house guests, Jacob.
Paul, you don't really get too many guests at the house.
No, very rare.
Jacob, do guests at your place take food home from restaurants and put it in your fridge?
Wait.
Do they bring-
If everybody went out to eat together, and then they're coming to stay at your place.
So you guys all go to a restaurant, and they go, "Oh, I can't finish that.
I'll take a box."
Do they take a box of food and put it in your fridge?
Rarely.
Okay.
It is probably my biggest pet peeve of having a house guest, because you're in Las Vegas.
You're not going to go, "We should eat leftovers at any point during your vacation."
You are never going to be like, "Never mind, let's just bust out the leftovers and have
a leftover festival at the table my last night in Las Vegas."
Now, what I will do, yes, that is all correct.
Also, what I will do is when the guests are in town, if we go out somewhere nice and they
get a nice meal or something like that, and they're like, "Oh, I'm not going to finish
this other piece here," I'll be like, "I'll take a box for that.
I'll take that home, and I will eat your leftovers later on."
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
That's a pro move.
If it's something that I've had my eye on anyway, that steak looks good.
My mother-in-law just ordered a 16-ounce steak.
She's going to eat eight ounces tops.
I'll just reach over and cut that thing in half right at the top of the dinner, and just
slide one half over to her.
The other half's right there if she wants to get to it, but if she doesn't, it's coming
home.
Smart.
That's smart.
Speaking of ordering steak and Las Vegas parking and weather, hit it, Jacob.
Yep.
It's over here somewhere.
All my buttons have moved around.
God damn it.
Oh, my buttons.
My gumdrop buttons.
My buttons.
Oh, I'm on the wrong page.
That's why.
My sweet candy buttons.
Vegas, parking and weather, no one does it better than ICS.
It wasn't my buttons.
It was me.
I was on the wrong page.
To prove that Vegas is always on the innovation space in the world of entertainment, they
figured out a way to close a show without closing a show over at the Bellagio.
What happened?
Oh, the poor Mayfair.
I feel so bad for everybody over there.
The Mayfair Summer Club is staying open at the Bellagio.
They simply fired everyone.
Their whole thing is dinner and a show.
They have singers and dancers and performers.
They have a stage in there, there's lighting and sound and you sit around it and it's a
very nice restaurant on top of it.
It's a Michelin star, I think, restaurant and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah, they have fired the entire entertainment cast.
So now it's dinner and a TBD over at the Mayfair Summer Club.
Apparently someone is coming in to make up some kind of new entertainment and that is
the amount of news that has been released on that.
Oh, no.
It's funny, I got a message from someone saying they're submitting an audition for the Mayfair
Summer Club and they're coming to check them out.
They don't live in Vegas.
They live in another city and I was like in my head, I was like, "Huh, that's weird that
they're auditioning someone, do a whole new thing."
And then I got the news and I was like, "Oh, it all adds up now."
It's a shame because the Mayfair Summer Club hired locally.
That's 30 just Las Vegas residents who had show business jobs that are gone.
That's killer, man.
Yeah, several friends of ours and a lot of them, because they're Las Vegas performers,
a lot of them have multiple gigs, but it just sucks.
You lose that gig.
You might lose a third of your weekly income or so.
Well, I'll tell you another thing that happened while we were at the Costco.
We had to get the membership, right?
And so went and got the membership and the gentleman there, super friendly guy, we got
to talking and we were talking Vegas and then we were talking improv.
Believe it or not, he's an improviser over at the arcade space.
I was like, "Holy shit."
So we exchanged info, I got him a chip, 'cause always.
So good at it.
Got to do it.
Got to be on it.
Okay.
Yeah, so we'll talk, but in my heart, I felt some, I don't know, relief, kinship because
I too am a retail employee who moonlights as an improviser now of just getting back
into the teaching.
By the way, I don't know if I've mentioned this.
My level one class at Skit is going phenomenally well and I love all those students.
They're amazing.
Oh, wonderful.
That's good to hear.
You have not said that.
That's great.
Fan fucking-tastic.
A couple of them are listening to the podcast now and tell me that they know that I shit
my pants and stuff like that, which I'm just over the moon about.
Good.
Which is great because if you ever leave the classroom going, "It's happening," they'll
know why.
If I leave the classroom squealing, "It's happening, oh no, oh no," they'll figure
it out real fucking fast.
Maybe one of your students to kiss your ass will come up with a thermos, a freshly steamy
microwave hot dog.
It's like they'll open up a little plume of steam coming off the top of a thermos and
just a nice dangly wiener for you to chomp down on.
I saw the fuck, somebody sent me the popeal one.
Nice dangly wiener.
Somebody sent me the popeal one.
That's so nasty.
The popeal one, have you seen it, the popeal hot dog thing?
No.
Please stop saying popeal.
It would slice the wiener when you put it in and then you'd lay the bun on top of it
and there was a bun case and you microwave it bun and all and I'm like, "Don't put bread
in a microwave.
That's sacrilege."
My anaconda don't want nothing unless your bun's got a case.
That's right.
You can do side bins or sit ups.
Sit it and forget it.
You know who else wants a thermos of hot dogs delivered directly to them and that is the
following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by The Internet from Danny Alwine in 2021.
Today's show is brought to you by The Internet with a capital I.
Hey, the end of democracy and your sister's fucking a dog.
That's The Internet.
Enter hey scoops at checkout.
Oh yeah, I have a little update on that.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Please.
So my buddy Sammy gets a call and it's another, you know, you've been approved for some loan
or you want to do something in the medical care system or something.
Oh shit.
Right?
Yeah.
Call center with a scam.
And Sammy goes, "Oh yeah, no problem, yeah, sign me up, let's do it."
You know, whatever.
They go, "Your first name?"
He goes, "Ben."
And he goes, "Sorry.
What's your first name?"
And he goes, "Ben."
And he goes, "Oh, yeah.
And I know what your last name is too."
And he hangs up.
I got him.
Oh shit.
Before he can even- Got him.
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
For anybody who didn't hear that episode, my friend always says to a scam caller that
his name is Ben Schott, which translates in Indian to sister fucker.
Right.
And apparently that's the worst thing you could say to someone in that country.
But it's spreading.
That means that that prank is spreading.
Exactly.
It is.
I don't praise or condone.
I simply report what's happening on the front lines.
That's right.
You are Walter Cronkite.
He came up with a current reference.
I'm still shocked that uncle fucker never really caught on as hotly, but I guess it's
because everybody likes uncles and so nobody, it's not really derogatory.
It's like, "Oh, well, yeah, I mean, you fucked your uncle.
Great."
Everybody has a good- He caught on for a slur for Canadians for
a while.
I guess.
After the South Park movie.
I love that.
That's the whole thing.
That song.
God damn it.
I never laughed so hard in the theater.
Still, to this day, that was the funniest moment.
Was that the one that, was uncle fucker the one that Robin Williams sang on the Oscars?
No, he sang Blame Canada.
That's right.
If he sang Uncle Fucker, that would have brought the house down.
Well, because it had all of the terrible things that it-
It still had some-
Remember, everybody was still terrified of what Robin Williams was going to do on the
live broadcast for the Oscars.
Right.
How's that guy doing?
Robin Williams.
Sister fucker.
Oh, shit.
Bossy.
Oh, man.
Yeah, so we're walking through Costco for the first time, Ann and I, as husband and wife.
She carried Paul over the threshold.
We seriously just kept looking at each other in awe and amazement.
We were really taken aback.
We had a membership to Sam's Club back in Vegas for a little while, but nothing like
this.
This was just amazing.
We got-
Nothing compared to you.
We got a bunch of stuff.
We got mostly dog food.
I don't know why.
As someone who's been a lifelong Costco member, I don't know why I really condescendedly look
when people bring up Sam's Club at the same time as Costco, and I was like, "Sure.
Okay."
No, you're right, because it's garbage trash, comparatively.
We didn't know we were missing with the Costco thing.
I'm a Sam's Club guy.
I'm not.
There's just ... There's a closer Sam's to me than there is a Costco.
Leon's asking if I-
The Sam's Club that I go to is great.
I don't know.
If I saw Big Justice and the Costco guys ... Now, Rizler was working the cash register when
I came through, so we got a bunch of cool stuff.
It's fun because we had-
Yeah.
Scan and go at Sam's Club.
Does Costco have the scan and go thing yet?
No.
Holy shit, this guy came up to the ... No, we've got it.
This guy came up to our cart.
Oh, that's where Sam's Club's got it.
This guy came up to our cart and was like, "You want me to scan you guys in?"
We're like, "Yeah."
He pre-scanned everything in the cart, sent it to our account, and then all we had to
do was present our card at the register, and we're done.
Yeah.
That's good.
Sam's Club scan and go with your phone, though-
Oh, right.
... is superior.
That is one big thing that they have.
I would say it probably is superior, but it's also more open to fraudsters, unfortunately.
Or does that matter to me?
Doesn't matter to you.
I'm just saying-
Yeah, there you go.
No, because the one in Vegas now, the one that I go to now, which I think is a really
nice Sam's ... I don't know why I'm defending Sam's Club, by the way, but-
I'm just saying if you put-
The one that I go to for some reason-
Because you love it, Jacob.
Don't be ashamed of your love for Sam's Club.
If you put being able to price items in the hands of the consumer, they will fuck with
it.
That's all I'm saying.
I don't care about that.
I know.
If Walmart loses money because people are gaming their system, that doesn't affect me
at all.
I'm fine with that too.
Okay.
But yeah, the one that we have, they don't even have to check your shit at the door anymore
like they used to with the scan and go stuff.
It's all x-rayed in there.
It's all like, yeah, there's a sensor thing and everything.
It's so easy and it's great now.
I don't think it's for anything like under 700 bucks.
Like if you're spending less than 700.
So when I check out for Scoop Fest, I have to do it the old fashioned way.
We got a bunch of cool stuff, like I said, mostly for the dogs, but then it was really
nice.
We had watched a video or something.
We saw this really nice collection of Jane Austen's books, right?
Okay.
Specially bound in these, it's a very nice thing.
And then we saw-
She's the romance author, right?
She is.
She's got like Fabio on the cover.
Fabio always.
And it was Costco only.
And we were like, oh no, but when we went today, we were really hoping to find those
books and we found them for Ann.
So it was a good day.
She got her special edition Jane Austen collection.
It was really nice.
It was very sweet.
And they're really pretty actually, they're like in a faux leather binding.
They're really nice.
So yeah, she's on the up and up with her little book collection.
Yeah.
Jane Austen wrote a very special edition just for Costco.
We got one of the signed, very limited signed copies from Jane Austen.
She reached up with her dead hand and she turned into the Joker.
Do you know how I wrote these books?
I saw it.
It's all true.
Boss Grissom reached up with his dead hand and he signed it over to me.
Yeah.
Did you make Ann push you out of the giant cart?
I pushed the cart.
Ann pushed it at first, but then I pushed it most of the time because she was like, it's
getting too heavy.
So I pushed it.
It was a bunch of.
I don't push carts like that.
I don't push carts like that full of dog food, but man, the money we saved.
Holy shit.
The money we saved.
The savings.
The savings, dude.
Honestly, we already paid for our membership.
Just getting dog food.
We already paid for our membership.
It's ridiculous.
Right now, any Costco listening, it just was like, got them.
They got them and they, and the thing is they got Ann.
That's all that really matters.
You can get me all day long.
Oh yeah.
Big bad toy store.
Got them.
Lego.
Masters of the universe for, since I was eight, six, since I was six, got them.
But they, you know, but if it's got Ann, Oh, it's a whole nother thing.
They have, they have these sample people out there, buddy.
Oh my gosh.
She did almost ruin my day.
She gave me this fucking falafel ball in this fucking dip.
I was like, I didn't really want it, but she's like, Oh, I'll get them.
And she, and I ate this.
I was like, Oh, it was so gross.
So many vegetables.
It was so gross.
It was in this, isn't this mint and cucumber dip or some shit?
I was like, Oh God, but I ate it.
It was delightful.
Oh, it was awful.
I hate the whole thing.
It was full awful.
Full awful.
Full on full awful.
Uh, yeah.
So that was my free sample.
I was like barf.
It wasn't green.
It was fried up.
It was gross.
Part of it was once green, just a little fried up little ball or something.
We did it.
We did.
We finally did a little judging of our, uh, Patreon.
If you talk about that a little bit, we did the production meeting.
Uh, again, yeah, more production, twice in a row, twice in one episode.
Uh, we, we raised our lowest tier from $2 to $3.
Let's just get that out of the way.
Yep.
Huge money grab on our parts.
Talk about Costco.
Yep.
But if you, uh, you know, if, if you get a Costco membership though, you'll be able
to afford it.
If they can, if Disney plus wants to charge me $38 just to watch sports center now, cause
it's not longer on YouTube TV, uh, I think we can go up to a dollar, uh, of that one.
Yeah.
Uh, that's the only to be raised any price on.
And as always, if you are a $2 member, we do not take that away.
So your grandfathered in, yeah, of course.
Uh, so, so that's still is a listed, I looked, we actually still have like 28 people still
at the dollar a month.
And I was like, all right, look at that.
Hey, look at us go.
We'll take it.
And of that, by the way, if you're still at a dollar a month, a congratulations B feel
free to revisit your Patriot and see.
Thank you.
I know.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
We make, uh, 12 of those, you know, I mean, make about 12 cents off of the dollar a month
club.
We make about $6 off of your $12.
So like, um, so, uh, uh, uh, but we also took away, we're no longer delivering stickers,
uh, and then, uh, we are going to do any kind of like triple threats or any kind of songs
from Paul.
Those would be like off air deliveries, uh, in return we are, Paul has organized a newsletter
and he sent one out already.
Yes.
I'll be organizing a monthly newsletter and basically people seem to really enjoy these,
these hangs on and off air where scoops get to interact with each other.
Just like the strength of scoop vest is that scoops get to see each other and hang out
with each other.
Uh, knowing that we're not really the big headliner sometimes for some people in this
world, uh, that we've created, uh, we're going to do zoom hangs off air, zoom hangs, uh,
for everyone to hang out, uh, once a month as well.
Yeah.
So if you're a patron, uh, subscriber at any level, you will get the invites to the zoom
hangs.
Uh, and then they're artists.
What level is it?
It's over.
Uh, a level.
It's, uh, I think the $10 level.
Yeah.
$10 leveling up.
You get zoom hangs once a month.
This is all information we could have had in front of us.
If only we had known we were going to talk about this, it's the only thing we knew we
were going to talk about.
You guys five minutes notice before the episode.
It's true.
You did.
It's the only thing we knew we were going to talk about.
Well, and we say we're not sending out stickers.
We're not sending out physical stuff.
That's all we've just taken off the graphic stuff.
We're still sending you the digital files or we're now sending you the digital files
so that not only can you make stickers if you want, you can make fucking anything.
If you want, you put that on any kind of product, you know, anywhere you want to put that.
There are so many sites.
Can you upload images into T public and make stuff right in our store?
Oh yeah.
So, you know, you can even go through our store, use our T public store to order custom
stuff using custom art that we've just sent you for that month and double dip us a little
bit.
Oh, oh, they can't do it.
Oh no.
Are you asking?
No, I thought you were asking if I could do it.
I was like, I can do it.
Oh, you could, but yeah.
Okay.
So this question is probably from the chat real quick, the newsletter came through Patreon.
So if you're getting your patron emails, just check your patron emails for the newsletter.
Yes.
Coming in through the newsletters put out through patron added a newsletter feature
to the.
Well, I'm trying to learn the newsletter.
I'm trying to learn the newsletter proper.
It was just a post this time.
Yeah.
Oh, and the, and the zoom hangs are different from the shows.
So we have the, we have the, the, uh, patreons that are with us on this show recording right
now.
Uh, that, that stays for everyone.
Yes.
So everybody on Patreon, every member gets access to our ice cream social recordings.
Yeah.
Uh, the, the zoom hangs are a different thing.
Those are the all fair things.
We did one this last month where we just had everybody on Patreon do it.
We kind of did the beta test for it last month.
Uh, but yeah, that'll normally be at the $10 level at higher Leon.
Thank you for the reminder.
Make sure you do your Patreon through the website, through a browser and not through
the Patreon app, uh, because the, the Apple app takes a big cut.
Yeah.
And then, and for people here live on this broadcast, I believe Meyer just post the link
to the newsletter for anyone who might've missed it.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
The Patreon post.
So this is the Patreon post.
Oh, Leon, if you can't read, uh, that is a different Patreon level.
There is a Patreon level though for you, if you can't read where I will just read the
newsletter to you, uh, don't worry.
We got you Leon.
But I'll still be sending out, uh, my original art piece and then we're going to send out
old school stickers, new stickers, um, you know, we still keep generating tons of artworks
and people will get access to that artwork.
It's just the actual practice of printing and shipping stickers.
And basically people have like built dog houses out of the stickers we've set over a decade.
Yes.
It's just, it's, it's a diminishing returns.
It's a lot.
And also if y'all haven't noticed postal shit's getting weird.
Yeah.
Uh, if you feel like you're still owed stickers from the past, please send an email to jacob@hayscoops@med@hayscoops.com.
Yes.
Yeah.
But, uh, yeah, moving forward, uh, it's going to be digital rewards, but-
Oh man.
Amy just wrote in chat, Matt will read the newsletter as Dom DeLouise.
That was the second time this week I've been compared to Dom DeLouise.
And as someone who's been slowly losing weight and trying to get their shit together, it's
a real fucking kick in the balls to be compared to Dom DeLouise twice in a week.
Not to say I don't get it, not to say I totally don't get it.
I get it.
I love Dom DeLouise so much.
You know who else loves being compared to Dom DeLouise all the time?
And that is the following sponsor.
All right.
Today's show is brought to you by, uh, 1-800-BITKILL.
Are you stuck with someone doing a bit that's gone way too long?
Call 1-800-BITKILL and our agents will come kill that bit.
That's from Dungeon Scoop in 2024.
Do you need a running joke kicked in the dick so hard it'll never recover?
Call 1-800-BITKILL and we'll be there immediately to dick kick any running joke that has been
going on in your household or family for any amount of time.
As long as it's been more than five days.
Any bit under five days still is in the incubation period and may or may not survive to day six.
After day six, a bit is firmly and securely intertwined into the DNA of the host and then
can only then be truly exterminated from said host.
I mean, is that a, is that like a procedure or is that like something you just come out
and do or what?
What is that?
The dick until the bit is removed thoroughly.
What me or the person doing the bit?
Your choice.
Excellent.
We're not that far off from prostitutes.
Are we?
That's right.
None of us are that far off from prostitutes.
Don't ever fucking forget it.
Sex work is work.
We just, we just did a breakdown of our new patron levels.
I agree.
Yeah.
Sex work is work.
Everybody.
We're all of this whores in this economy.
Enter Hayes groups to check out.
Welcome.
Welcome to it.
Yeah.
I just sent you in the chat, a very nice felt picture of Dom Deleuze from 1975.
Everyone knows that's not what they're talking about.
Jacob.
I'm pretty sure that's a young Dom Deleuze and a very vibrant shirt.
They're referring to him, his, uh, slim and trim days.
That's right.
No, one person said early years, uh, an actual pick saying I had to do a double take and
they were wearing a similar flat cap.
He was wearing a similar flat cap to me.
Oh, I, it was it smoky in the bandit too.
Is that where he's wearing?
I think that is where he's wearing that, that, that one.
And I, I had to be like, I want to tell my friend, like, listen, if you ever think you
should send a photo of Dom Deleuze to someone to be like, I had to do a double take, don't,
don't do it up.
You're safe.
Smokey debate at two.
Isn't it?
Yeah.
There's Leon helping you out.
That's the one in the chat.
Help it out.
But he looks so happy.
Look at him.
Yeah.
No, I'm a happy guy.
I'm not saying I don't understand the comparison.
Oh my God.
So yeah, I said this like great night, but one person on YouTube called the Orson Welles.
And I was like, actually, when you look at a picture of Orson Welles next to me, like,
that's actually who I look like the most.
I'm like, I actually have to hand it to you.
I really do look a lot like Orson Welles, late Orson Welles.
Oh, I saw a great video the other day of Orson Welles outtakes from a wine commercial that
he was doing.
That's a that's a class.
Famous.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Right.
It's definitely a later in life when he was where he's just drunk.
Yeah.
He is just like slurring speech drunk.
The last thing he did was the reason that that's true.
Yeah.
The reason you need to go look at this video again, though, if you haven't looked at it
lately or if you've ever seen it before, look up this video Orson Welles outtakes wine commercial.
The two extras that are standing next to him that are just doing take after take with him.
Oh, yeah.
They are heroes.
They are amazing.
They never comment.
They never look at him sideways.
They never do anything but exactly what they are there to do.
Well, even then he was royalty.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, yeah.
Brian Brushman sent me a clip of John Candy playing Orson Welles in a bit like a late
night talk show.
And it's really, really funny that Latter Day Scoop goes with a thin picture of Orson
Welles.
That's not who we're talking about.
Latter Day Scoop.
Young Orson Welles.
That's not who I'm being compared to on YouTube.
I'll tell you that much right now on my screen.
That picture is next to Matt's face right now.
He's talking about that.
I found out something in the Zoom chat before we started today that has changed my world
forever.
Oh, God.
And that is, apparently, if you do a reverse image search of any house that was ever listed
on Zillow, that's enough to do a reverse image search of a house.
What?
And, like, and find out where that house is.
Wait, say that again.
So if you just have a picture of a house, oh, Scoop Jesus, there you are.
Can you unmute and come on?
Scoop Jesus was telling me about this before we started today.
Okay.
I'm actually in the house, but that happened with.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
So a friend, a named friend, posted a picture of their new house on Instagram that didn't
show the address number or anything, and my wife took the image, reverse image search,
and it popped up and showed the Zillow listing and got their address.
And I just drove down here with that address.
So you were able to find a house with just the picture of the house?
Yep.
I'm terrified.
If we're doing that now, what do you think the government's been doing for the last 15
years?
I mean, a lot more and a lot worse.
Yeah.
Just constantly checking the value of my house.
They've been reverse imaging.
They've been reverse image searching my colon for God's sakes.
They know everything.
We got a note from our HOA about our basketball hoop being out, that we have to put our basketball
hoop away because no basketball hoop and their argument was that it could hurt the value
of the homes around us.
And I just want to be like, you go ahead and Google the value of homes in this neighborhood
and you'd tell me where the dip happened the day I put up my fucking basketball.
Right?
Yeah.
No dips anywhere.
There are no dips yet.
Right back to him.
You know what lowers the property value in this goddamn neighborhood?
All these fucking kids running around.
You know what really lower kids and then I won't have a reason to put up a fucking basketball
hoop.
You know what really lowers get to work HOA Vegas.
What really lowers property values in Las Vegas is not being able to fly to fucking
Las Vegas.
That does hurt property value.
Yeah.
It's a real dick in it.
It sure does.
Oh, a bunch of bulls.
So what was your solution?
Have you put up the basketball goal or are you going to fight them in city hall?
I'm going to fight them in city hall.
Well, I'm actually waiting for the second note to come.
Good.
Because I feel like we definitely don't have the only basketball hoop out.
So I figured someone who's much more of a organized rage person than me.
There you go.
I'm probably answering them already.
Yeah.
HOA is the waste.
The waste.
I have a very reasonable HOA.
I'm actually not that upset.
Yeah.
We used to get a note about our leaves.
I know Paul.
You're very well noted.
I'm really, I just really, I hate the whole idea.
It makes me rage, rage, rage.
Paul, I'm around people in Las Vegas who definitely with no HOA would definitely lower the property
value of everyone around them.
Yeah, I get it.
But see, this is me.
I don't care.
I'm like go nuts.
Do your thing.
Unless you're burning the house, unless you're causing like structural damage or you're toxifying
my land.
Go nuts.
Here's the thing.
Like I have neighbors whose houses definitely are currently lowering my property value.
And like if they would spruce their houses up, I'd appreciate it.
But yeah, it's not worth being an HOA for me.
And I'm with you, Matt.
And I had, because I had a reasonable HOA before I lived here and they were fine.
They didn't bother me.
It's a critical, I like having a little bit of a nice like sidewalk neighborhood, a little
gate area.
They can just get out of control so easily.
They really can't.
They can get out of hand.
Yes.
No, without a doubt.
I mean, you know, like all my friends in New York, what they have to go through.
Oh God.
I can only imagine.
It's just like to own their home.
It's like, it's fucking nuts, man.
No, no.
There are, like this HOA is not that crazy, what I'm saying.
We used to get notes.
A friend of mine just this week was talking to me about their HOA and they were like,
"Oh, our fees are so reasonable."
I said, "Oh, that's good.
What's your fees?"
They go, "500."
For a year?
That's what I thought.
Uh-huh.
I genuinely was like, "Oh, 500 bucks a year.
Isn't bad."
They're, "Oh, no, no.
A month."
Oh ho ho.
Oh, that is terrible.
Oh, eat shit.
Eat shit forever.
Oh my God.
That is horrible.
That's no way.
No, we have a pool, we have a gym.
That's cool.
A pool and a gym.
Yeah.
No, son.
But I bet that person also has a membership to a gym outside of their home.
I have a toy collection.
I would think so.
I could not keep my toy collection going with that kind of money going out.
That would end it.
Okay.
You're making a lot of arguments in favor of it now, Paul.
No, no.
Please.
This glorious basement of nerditude has increased the value of this home tenfold.
The moment a prospective buyer walks in, they're like, "Good God.
May I keep the finished basement and all the trimmings?"
And I go, "No, sir.
No, sir, you may not.
That's a lifetime of collecting."
You can't, however, keep that squirrel.
Let me make an offer that you cannot refuse.
I need all of this bullshit.
Says no one ever.
Says me.
Saving me an email.
Thank you, Steven Marson, who just became a year-long member of the Ten Dollars here.
Thank you, Steven.
Oh, nice.
Fuck yeah.
Thank you.
Your thank you note right here, buddy.
Thanks for doing it.
That's incredible.
Much appreciated.
Yeah.
And we've gotten a lot of great support.
As soon as I put up the post on the Patreon, we got some really nice supporting messages.
So thank you all for rolling with us and for moving forward into this new digital age.
But it's going to be cool.
And yeah, I'm going to muddle my way through learning how to put this stuff together and
get the chats going and all these different things.
And we're going to have a lot of fun.
Oh, and to put a period on it, the newsletter is at all levels, right?
Yes.
Everybody on Patreon should be getting a newsletter no matter what level you're at.
So if you are not getting a newsletter, check your Patreon email, check your Patreon, do
all that kind of stuff.
Well, you're saying newsletter.
There's a new newsletter thing.
I haven't figured that out yet.
All I did was put up a post, the post, this first post went to everybody.
So if you're on Patreon at all, you've got that post that just went up.
What are you titling the posts, Paul?
The first one was just Patreon update.
Okay.
So that's probably why a lot of people might not have, because when Patreon puts an update,
they also put Patreon update.
There you go.
See, I didn't know that either.
You should probably change the title of it.
Well, just next time I'll say, I'll say Ice Cream Social Newsletter for Blankety Month.
Yeah.
Well, I think you should put the name of the month.
I like Blankety Month.
Yeah.
I mean, you can figure it out.
You know what, you're reading it.
You know what month it is.
I'm recording it into a Blankety Month.
Ice Cream Social Newsletter for Blankety Month.
Blankety Month on such and such date.
Can I make a suggestion?
That's legally binding, isn't it?
What?
Can you what?
Can I make a suggestion?
You can.
I don't know why that was so baffling to you.
I couldn't hear what you said.
Okay.
Hey, it's Paul.
I think you should write and then that should be the title.
Like, here's the newsletter.
Oh, okay.
Hey, it's Paul.
Great.
Okay.
I'll start it with Hey, it's Paul.
Hey, it's the Blankety Host.
Hey, it's Paul.
It's Blankety Month, everybody.
And it's definitely now called the Blankety Month newsletter.
Yeah.
Paul Mattingly.
Paul Mattingly's Blankety Month newsletter.
Hey, God, it's me, Paul.
Yes.
That'll work.
Because the more you try to make it sound official, the more it just sounds like a Patreon
email, which is what people, I think, delete all the time without reading.
That makes sense.
All right.
And then people will say, Hey, everybody, it's fucking Paul with the Blankety Month
bullshit.
What the hell?
What is this?
Oh, Paul's character allotment was used up in the title again.
Exactly.
Well, that was the other thing too, because we're also putting up candid photos as well
as the other digital images.
And I put up the max images it would let me do.
And then I used the last image space for the header where I put my new artwork up.
And that was everything I could do.
So maybe they let you put more stuff in the newsletter.
I don't know.
We'll see.
I think they do.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I'm still learning the ropes.
Still learning the ropes.
That is actually one of the more fun things, I think, for people who are already on Patreon
that are going to enjoy this new Patreon even more is you're going to have more direct interaction
with Paul via Patreon.
Well, that's for sure.
That I got news for you is going to be fun.
Well, it's going to be a lot of fun.
It's going to be a lot of this, but it's also going to be a lot of fun.
Yeah.
And I'll take, I'll take criticisms and tips all the time.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Like how the Paul wants notes, how the fuck to make this shit work right.
Cause yeah, I got to learn my, I got to learn the ropes.
So I got some off days coming up and I'm going to try and spend some time learning that.
And I will probably fire off a test, a zoom chat again before too long just to figure
that out.
So it might only be 10 minutes, but keep your eyes peeled.
Well, I'll tell you what else Paul needs to learn and that's the answers to jock versus
nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time for jock versus nerd.
Explosion.
We got a scooperty coming to us today from Smitty scoop gentlemen, I apologize.
I have not submitted a scooperty lately, but Jacob's plea on a recent episode motivated
me to prepare a scooperty.
Here are the updated Smitty scooperty statistics.
All time victories.
Matt has 13.
Paul has three.
I have eight all time points.
Matt has 32,000.
I have 12,400.
Paul has negative 27,800.
I've got to keep it up.
Negative 27,800.
Combined accuracy in the last three Smitty scooperties, 75.6% of questions answered correctly.
Good job everybody.
Combined accuracy on all previous Smitty scooperties, 51.4% answered correctly.
So we've improved over the last three so that's good for us.
Average combined score for the last three is 6,800.
Average combined score for all of them, negative 1,267.
So we are trending in the right directions.
Let's see if you can beat your all time high score of 12,800.
Good luck.
This is a Smitty scooperty.
Let's go.
Oh, by the way, two shout outs.
One shout out to DJ Stormageddon in the Twitch chat right now.
Old friend of ours, DJ Stormageddon from back on the scoop cruise days.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Got his fucking honeymoon.
Got Obelisk on his honeymoon.
Obelisk on his honeymoon.
And also happy birthday OG Scoop.
Happy birthday Andy.
Yeah.
Here we go with the scooperty.
The categories are the most, geography, initialism, and multiple choice.
Okay.
Paul, you're up first.
I'll try multiple choice.
For 400.
Which of the following films was not directed by Amy Heckerling?
Clueless, Fast Times at Ridgemont High, Look Who's Talking, or Now and Then.
Fast Times B.
Fast Times is incorrect.
It's Now and Then.
That was directed by Leslie Lincoln Ladder.
Paul keeping up his negative score trend here on Smitty Scooperties.
I've got it.
It's time to prove.
Already.
Matt.
Geography please, 400.
Which state bordering Nevada is the largest in area, Alaska, Arizona, California, or Idaho?
Trying to get me an Alaska bordering Nevada, nice try.
This is where we find out that Alaska somehow borders Nevada technically.
It could possibly.
Who knows?
California, see.
Got to be, right?
Yeah.
California, 163,000 square miles and Arizona and Idaho both have less and Alaska does not
border Nevada.
It's a good call on all of that, Matt.
You got that entire question right, I'll know what the most for 400.
Which of these NFL franchises has won the most Super Bowl titles, Bears, Colts, Seahawks,
or Vikings?
Is this going to bite me where it's like, Oh, they won the NFL championship, but it
wasn't the Super Bowl yet.
I think it's the Bears.
I'll go A, Bears.
The Colts.
Colts two, Bears one, Seahawks one, Vikings nothing.
Wow.
Oh, all right then Paul.
I'll go initialism for 1200 because why not?
Oh shit.
I'll give you 400.
All right.
What is FYITF short for?
Fuck you in the face.
Nice job.
Or were you just talking to me?
No, both.
Were you answering?
Oh, okay.
Both.
Two birds, one stone.
I will take geography 800.
Galica is the name of Northwest, is the name of the Northwest region in what country?
Austria, France, Italy, or Spain?
I'm sure I'm not saying that right.
G-A-L-I-C-I-A.
Galicia.
Galicia?
Okay.
Galicia.
I'm just going off the correction of my around the chat.
Oh, great.
Galicia, Austria.
Galicia, France.
Galicia, Italy.
Galicia, Spain.
Oh, pass.
Oh, no.
They can pass it to me.
Let's see.
I'll do the same thing that Matt was doing.
Galicia, Austria.
Galicia, France.
Galicia, Italy.
Galicia, Spain.
Galicia.
That's right.
It's definitely Italy.
That's what I think.
I think it's Italy too.
Galicia, Austria.
Galicia, France.
Galicia, Italy.
Galicia, Spain.
Galicia.
That's right.
It's definitely Italy.
That's what I think.
I think it's Italy too.
Galicia, Italy.
Shit.
I can guess.
Galicia.
Let's see.
I'll try geography for 1,200.
Why did I go back to geography?
I don't know.
Which U.S. state capitol is located at the highest elevation, Colorado, Idaho, Nevada,
or New Mexico?
Oh, this is probably a trick question.
I'll say Colorado.
No, it's New Mexico.
6,900 feet for New Mexico for Santa Fe, only 5,200 for Denver.
Wow.
There you go.
Who knew?
Paul.
Initialism for 1,200.
What is CPR short for?
Cardiopulmonary resuscitation.
Cardiopulmonary resuscitation is just correct.
Wow.
That's right.
That is just absolutely correct.
Oh, wow.
I was thinking like compression.
Yeah.
No.
Matt, you're up.
I have a, I think I have a CPR card right here.
Yeah.
And you didn't know?
Did you ever ever suck face with Recessa Annie?
Yeah.
She knows how to do it.
She does.
Matt, you're up.
Geography 2,000.
What African country recently became the second least populous country to qualify for the
FIFA World Cup, Cape Verde, Djibouti, Iceland, or Togo?
Go with Djibouti.
I've been watching Djibouti bounce all day.
Yeah.
This is 2000, so I'm going to pass.
That passes to me.
Man, I want to go Djibouti so bad.
Do it.
I want that Djibouti.
I kind of think it's Togo.
Go.
All right.
It's going to be Djibouti, but I'm going Togo.
Okay.
Nope.
It's neither.
Cape Verde.
An island nation west of Senegal near the Canary Islands.
Iceland is the least populous country to qualify for the World Cup.
So there you go.
Okay.
It's me.
Man, I'm terrible right now.
I'm going to do multiple choice for 2000.
Daily Double.
Frequently hidden in nativity scenes in Catalina, children search for-
Catalonia.
Oh, Catalonia.
Children search for El-
Cogener.
Any guesses?
Okay.
Who is generally depicted as a peasant in a Catilian red cap doing what?
Breastfeeding, drinking wine, pooping, or sleeping.
Pooping, Giggles.
I think it is pooping.
Is there just in nativity scenes?
Yes.
Is there just a guy pooping in the background?
There's just a guy in certain places.
It's a traditional thing.
It's like a where's Waldo kind of thing, but it's a pooping guy.
I'll go with you because I don't have any other guess on this.
So I'll say pooping.
It is pooping.
Yeah.
Told you.
Picture Chef Boyardee popping a squat with a conical turd below him.
Yeah.
There you go.
It's the most wonderful time of the year.
Most wonderful turd of the year.
Just goes to show that even people who believe don't really believe.
Paul.
Initialism.
2000.
What is HIV short for?
Ruining the good mood of a podcast.
Am I right?
Oh, I believe it's a human immunovirus.
You going with that?
Yeah.
All right.
I think that's correct.
Yeah.
Human immunodeficiency virus.
I think you're close enough.
I would say so.
Yeah.
Matt.
I will go with the most, for 800, please.
Which of these countries has the most people?
Egypt, Ethiopia, Nigeria, or Tanzania?
Let's see here.
I mean, I know the population of Tanzania.
I just don't know the other three.
Right.
Pass.
OK.
That passes to me.
I'm going to do my math out loud.
Egypt has a lot of people in it.
Ethiopia has a lot of people in it.
And Nigeria, they've got a lot of people there.
And Tanzania, boy, do they have a lot of people.
Egypt, A. It's Nigeria.
213 million, Ethiopia, 120 million, Egypt, 109 million, Tanzania, 64 million.
We're really throwing off the curve today.
I'm losing a lot of money.
Paul's making a lot of money.
Yeah, baby.
Let's see.
The world is upside down.
Yeah.
Oh, I need points back.
I'll do the most for 2000.
Which of these NHL franchises has won the most Stanley Cup titles?
The Bruins, the Maple Leaves, the Penguins, or the Red Wings?
Hmm.
I would like to use my 50/50.
Paul, which two answers are definitely not correct?
I would say Penguin, wait, is the one the most Stanley Cup titles?
Yeah, Penguins are on my short list.
Penguins have like four.
The Leaves, the most.
You think the Leaves have the most?
I think it's either the Leaves or the Wings.
Yeah.
I'll say the Red Wings.
I'll say Detroit.
Nope.
It's the Maple Leaves.
It was the Leaves.
13.
Red Wings are 11.
It was the Maple Leaves.
Jacob continues losing points.
Paul.
I'll go with Initialism.
For 800.
What is IQ short for?
Intelligence Quotient.
Intelligence Quotient is correct.
Paul must have a very high IQ to know that indeed.
Oh yes, clearly very IQ-y.
Matt Donnelly, you got the most or multiple choice.
You have 400 points by the way.
You're well ahead of me.
I have 5200 points in the negative, and Paul has 4,000 points.
So Paul is one order of magnitude ahead of you.
There is one Daily Double left.
Your only hope is that Paul gets it and loses.
Right, a man can hope.
I will do multiple choice 1200 please.
Daily Double!
In the 2024 US presidential election, what is the one state that Donald Trump won that
he previously lost in both the 2016 and 2020 elections?
Arizona, Nevada, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.
Be Nevada, Tom.
My name is Jacob, but it is Nevada.
Nevada, Tom.
And Paul and Brett Mukai have been blamed for this.
They moved out.
For moving out of Nevada.
Two votes.
Slow down.
You don't know who they were voting for.
I'll go with multiple choice for 800.
The San Marzino tomato originated in the small town of San Marzino del Surro, which is located
in which Italian region?
Calabria, Campania, Sardinia, or Sicily.
This I talk about this all the time.
I talk about Italian tomatoes, all types of Italian tomatoes, nobody loves Italian tomatoes
more than I do.
And that is why I will go with A, which is incorrect.
It was B, what is that?
Oh, the province of Salerno in the region of Campania.
Oh, it was the region that threw me off.
That's what got me.
I was in the wrong region.
Paul closing out the category and the game that he's already won the most for 1200.
Which of these Major League Baseball franchises has won the most World Series titles?
The Athletics, the Cardinals, the Phillies, the Pirates.
And I believe the answer was given in the question here.
Ian Smitty typed out this stupidly because below that it says Cardinals 11, Athletics
9, Pirates 5, and Phillies 2.
So Paul, with all of that in mind, which of these MLB franchises has won the most World
Series titles?
Athletics, Cardinals, Phillies, or Pirates.
But I'm going to have to go out on a wing and say Cardinals.
Oh man, I hope that those are just incorrect stats there.
That'd be funny.
They're not.
It's the Cardinals.
Paul gets more points.
That's the game.
Thank you, Smitty Scoop.
Smitty, I won one.
Paul crushed it.
I won one, Smitty.
Paul crushed it with 5,200 points, Matson second with 1,600, Ivan third with negative
6,000.
Jesus fuck.
I'm creeping towards the positive.
Now you know how I feel on most of those.
Look at you go.
If you want to sit as a scooperty just like Smitty did there, head over to Hayscoops.com.
Hayscoops.com.
You can head over there.
Make us a scooperty.
Make us a Price is Skripe jock versus nerd.
Make us an Obelisk jock versus nerd.
Do all those things right over there at Hayscoops.com.
Do it now.
It'd be great.
All right.
I want to thank all the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
We don't have a new list just yet, but it's one of the things we're working on by streamlining
some of the processes here.
We've got our thank yous earlier in the month.
Anyhow, but if you support us over on our Patreon page, we really appreciate it.
If you love our show and you like that it comes out all the time, every time, no matter
what, then support us today by going over to preachingfun.com.
Yeah, you really should.
Come visit preachingfun.com.
It's better than hanging with your mom.
it's better than hanging with your mom.
I want to thank you for being here.