"She's mighty mighty, letting the shit leak out."
"She's a brick shit house, not terribly affected."
This is the part of the show where we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Our lists are fucked this month, I am sorry, we don't have a new list yet.
I don't know why, but it's all fucked up.
Maybe we'll have one by the time this comes out, who can say?
Either way though, we're going to thank all of you before this month is over.
Thank you to all of you Ice Cream Truck Drivers out there.
Thank you to everybody who supports us over there on Patreon.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver.
And who knows, the life you save may be your own.
That's right, Dead Laszlo, professionals.
Bro.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
Uh, right before we got on air, Paul convinced me of the brick shithouse argument, I'm sorry.
The pause to brick and house.
It's a brick shithouse!
That's what it's supposed to be.
It's time for Matt Madinley's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Madinley!
Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly!
Also sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy!
We're PreachingFun!
How y'all doing?
I'm doing delightful.
I just told everybody on stream, I got a boo-boo from mowing my lawn today.
You hurt yourself mowing?
Yeah, I slipped and fell in wet grass, because I was mowing so early to get done by the time the podcast hit.
Which I did, I got it all done, which is great.
We are injured.
What happened?
Oh, Matt also has a boo-boo on his elbow!
It's mostly healed, mine's from the water slide in Mesa, Arizona.
Oh, brothers in arms here!
Is this a Corsican twin kind of thing happening, Matt?
Yes.
Is that what this is?
Yep, we are Corsican twins.
I knew it.
Oh, Country Scoops.
My elbows are fine.
A lot of people got elbow boo-boos.
They're going for like $7 to $80 a pop elbow boo-boos.
I have tried to get, I just want a green one.
You want a green one?
If I get a green one, I'll quit.
There's an economist, which economist?
I don't know, who thinks the la boo-boo craze is a sign that we're about to hit like a really nasty economic thing in our world.
I concur, and I would say also...
An economist theorizes that the la boo-boo craze is foreshadowing a really bad financial time.
Canary in a coal mine.
I know why he said this, but Paul was really quick to chime in that he also knew.
So go ahead, Paul.
Oh, sorry, Paul, why is this happening?
Well, it coincides with the same thing that's going on within the trading card world, for those of you who play Magic or Pokemon, and have ever tried to even buy the shit.
But what it does, it correlates to people feeling frustrated that they have little to no buying power, and they're seeing this.
It's sort of a gambling kind of thing with the la boo-boos.
It's also the possibility of using their money to then resell it and make a little bit more, and that kind of thing.
And also, it's not that crazy expensive.
Buying a pack of Pokemon cards is not that crazy expensive, but it's a way to feel like you have some economic ability within you.
Am I hitting the points there pretty close, Matt?
A little bit.
I mean, what you're saying makes sense.
This person simply pointed to what economists have used in the past, what's called the lipstick index.
Have you heard of this?
So it's little treat time.
That's it.
The little treat thing is exactly it.
So it's a sign that you can't afford big treats.
So usually right before there's an economic downward trend, a nasty one, the prices of higher-end cosmetics go up.
So suddenly people are spending a little bit more to feel better about themselves during the day on lipsticks and other high-end make-ups because they can't afford to get on a plane and go somewhere.
They can't afford to go to some exotic spot.
They can't go to some property.
They can't buy a new fancy car.
This is why I'm glad my wife is in the coffee business.
Fancy coffee is the ultimate little treat.
Man, Starbucks is definitely just trying to create--
That's their bar and trade.
Yeah, that's the whole thing, man.
High-end drinks for women and drive-throughs.
That's all that's happening.
Every drink has a crazy color or crazy object in it now.
But I still like Starbucks.
Starbucks is fascinating.
There's nothing in Starbucks I love.
I don't know if there's any amazing drink there or amazing food there.
Well, and I guess it's from a coffee perspective.
It's a very specific, very-- is bitter the right word?
Super roasted?
They do a lot of high-roasted, super high-roasted blends.
And they're the first ones to really over-roast arapaca beans when we were all used to drinking Colombian coffee when they first came on the market, right?
And so they torched-- because they gave people a really robust flavor and then charged a lot of money for it.
So we associated that taste with money.
Right.
Because they created it.
Yeah.
So that's become their signature thing.
Some people-- yeah, but some people still like particular blends and things like that from them.
So I don't want to besmirch the grudge.
No, not at all.
Famously, I described when I was a barista, every coffee profile is burnt and gotten troubled by my manager who's training me.
It tastes burnt.
You mean when you were doing your sample tasting as you're onboarding kind of thing?
Yeah.
I'm getting notes of charred grill and whopper.
That's exactly what I did, Jacob.
But they told me to stop saying burnt.
I started going campfire-y.
Oh, this one tastes more like a brush fire.
Overcooked bread.
This definitely got a crematorium kind of vibe.
Oh, this reminds me of one of the seasons in California.
Oh, fire seasons.
Yes, that's right.
Fireworks, warehouse disaster, notes of black cat explosion.
Fireworks.
This tastes very July 5th.
July 5th.
I love the smell of napalm in the morning.
That would be an interesting coffee whiskey blend.
Yeah.
A 5th of July.
5th of July is a very funny--
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Make it like a drink.
Embered.
It's a 5th of July.
Right.
Jacob.
Boo sales are down.
You should get on that.
Boo sales are down?
Yes.
Boo sales are down.
I was reading this the other day.
To no one's surprise, Canadians don't feel like drinking American whiskey right now.
Yeah.
Which at least makes me happy.
If they're not going to come see my little American show on the Las Vegas strip, please
don't buy the easier things to buy too.
If you're going to keep your money away from my shit, go ahead and keep it away from the
other shit too.
It really is funny because we probably have some Canadians here up on our chat.
Yeah, because they're not afraid to travel to our chat room.
But basically, when you go like, "Oh, come on Canada," it definitely is like, "Oh."
And then all that comes to mind is like, "We've been giving Canada shit for so long.
All we do is fucking fuck with Canadians."
And finally it's like, "No, really.
This time, I'm leaving."
And you're like, "No, come on, baby."
Come on.
She never left before.
She always just came back.
Where are you going, baby?
Where are you going?
I can change Canada.
You know my heart, Canada.
You know my heart.
Yeah.
I mean, look, man, for all the shitty American boycotting of businesses, Canada was like,
"No, no, no.
Really."
No, we out.
No, no.
We really can flex, guys.
I don't know if we really can.
Yeah.
We got a couple of people living here.
It's not just some little island.
Yeah.
It's pretty crazy.
Pretty crazy.
It's nuts.
I just listened to...
Oh, that's true.
Scooper Nova Girl with the John Candy movie, Canadian Bacon, with the recommend Canadian
Bacon.
A fine film.
Oh, yes.
It is a fine film.
It is.
There's definitely poignant at this point.
My favorite murder take on the heist, the big booze heist that happened out of the Johnny
Walker distillery, did you hear about all that craziness that's happened in the, I guess
it was early '90s?
No.
Did you ever hear this story, Jacob?
I'm surprised.
I don't think so.
Maybe.
I don't know.
This guy...
Refresh my memory.
What's that really famous old granddad?
Not old granddad.
What's the one that's really high end, the bottle that goes for crazy money?
Pappy Van Winkle?
That's it.
Pappy Van Winkle.
Oh, there you go.
So they had Pappy Van Winkle's on display in this guy.
This guy was working for the distillery for years and he worked his way up from distributing
to being like a warehouse manager.
Basically they had no security whatsoever and he started stealing Pappy Van Winkle bottles
and he'd just steal them out of the display cases in the place.
Yeah, he'd just take them from all over the place.
If he saw one not nailed down, he was taking it.
Yeah, and selling them for lots of money and just started off small and by the end of it,
he was just going crazy.
Yeah, there was a Netflix special about him.
Yes, I believe so.
Because it was at the Buffalo Trace distillery.
That's it.
It was the Buffalo Trace distillery.
That's the ones that make that booze.
They make the Van Winkle line.
He was taking them, he was selling to his friends, he was selling to neighbors, he was
selling them all over the place.
It's a wild story.
And of course, he didn't stop at selling them to his next door neighbor for 500 bucks in
cash or whatever.
No.
He had to put stuff online, got too big, and of course he got caught.
Yeah, yeah, and all the records are on his phone.
He didn't use a burner or anything, it's just his phone, all that kind of shit.
It's like grand larceny that easily reached the stage of being a big fucking crime.
Totally.
And there's a similar incident in Canada, but it involves maple syrup.
Oh, I was going to guess hockey sticks.
Your mission, should you choose to accept it?
A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A. It's a Canadian version.
It's a guy walking out, but everything he touches is sticky.
All his papers and stuff just attached to him as he walks out.
I think you might be guilty, pal.
No, no.
I'm just wearing a sponge suit and I dip myself into a vat of maple syrup and then I'm going
to go home and wring myself out.
Gross.
Sell it to a farmer's market.
I'm so sorry to have to ask this, but did you steal that maple syrup?
I'm sorry to ask, but did you steal it?
I don't know.
If something just attaches to your body, is it theft or did it choose to go with you?
Oh, God.
Did he stole it?
That's a fine question.
He dipped in it and then rinsed it off and sold rinse, rinsy maple syrup?
This maple syrup that I buy from the store, I mean, sure, it tastes like maple syrup,
but the maple syrup I buy from Ted down the street, now it's got a little something.
It's got a zing.
He fucking, he fucking baby birded that shit.
He took a giant straw, and then just waved as he walked out like, "Hmm, hmm, hmm."
Oh, gross.
He kept it in his mouth.
Because he was sucking up maple syrup through a giant straw, it's so upsetting.
He siphoned it into his pants?
See you later, everybody.
Oh, gross.
That's so horrible.
Bro, and he just-
I don't know why that bothers me more than anything else on this show ever has.
It's just a mouthful of syrup, like he's only able to fill up one little-
The medicine go down, the medicine go down.
He fills up those little travel bottles every day, he just fills up a travel bottle.
He's only making like $2 a day with it.
He's siphoning maple syrup, sucking it into a hose.
You guys can drink these fireball on the plane, or you can have grade B tasty maple syrup.
Grade B?
Grade B but edible tasty maple syrup.
Scully's like, "Nah, he butt chugged it like a turtle."
Most fun way to get diabetes for $1,000, Alex.
Jason Victor, yeah, the little maple leaf.
Butt chugging like a turtle.
The little maple leaf shaped souvenir bottles, that's exactly what I was picturing.
Exactly.
Oh man.
But I actually know no details about the maple syrup that you're talking about.
Yeah, it was a similar kind of thing, like insiders figuring out where maple syrup was
being transported and hijacking entire busloads of, truckloads of maple syrup.
Hundreds of thousands, if not millions of dollars worth of maple syrup.
Billions?
I don't know about billions.
Galactic president.
If you count the tariffs, it's billions.
Nowadays it could be, nowadays it could be, everything's up.
Galactic president says, "Custom idea, maple syrup leg."
Oh yeah, not a bad idea.
Not a bad idea.
Ooze.
I went and saw two shows recently.
Okay.
Ooh.
I saw Lucy Darling over at the NGM and she was playing, of course, with our good friend
Sarah Hester-Ross.
Awesome.
Amazing.
How was that?
It was incredible.
It was fascinating.
I say that just because, you know, obviously I come to Lucy through the magic world.
Those of you who aren't familiar, you probably have seen Lucy Darling clips on your social
media because she's really blown up.
Right?
Oh yeah.
She's everywhere.
She's still on improperly crowd work and so it's funny because like basically magicians
want to like hate her for being successful, right?
You actually hate everyone who blows up like when Justin Willman first came around, everyone
wanted to hate Justin Willman.
Like it just happens.
But people say like the dumbest shit, right?
So at first they were saying, you know, she's putting up, she's selling out these theaters,
but they're very small theaters.
And I was laughing and I was like, "Yes, please."
Are you selling out a small theater, sir?
Yeah.
Give me that problem tomorrow.
Wait, what are they making?
So they're making fun of her for saying that she is selling out theaters and they're coming
back and just being like, "Yeah, yeah, but they're little."
The base kind of says she's not as big time as you think she is or something like that,
right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Fine.
Right.
Exactly.
And by the way, like she would sell a small theater, but like eight shows in a row.
So it was like, "Okay."
Like basically that just means like she could have played a big theater and went, "Oops,
I booked the wrong theater."
So like, okay, great.
And she's smart.
Like she's figured out something that I am chasing, right?
She's figured out how to put herself online without spoiling all of her magic tricks.
Yes.
That is true.
She just has her interacting with people, getting laughs and it's out, right?
Oh, you know, yeah, that's true.
She's putting like funny moments of her show online, but not really revealing the tricks.
Man, if you had funny moments in your show that you could put online, that'd be so convenient.
The problem is those aren't as easy to buy as magic tricks.
That's true.
So it's like-
Now foiled again.
Now I hate Lucy Darling too.
I put the ads out on Fiverr.
I just can't get the jokes.
So then someone said, well, you know, obviously people were just getting into her because
of her crowd work.
Some people were going to the show not even knowing she's a magician, right?
Oh no.
Right.
They're just being like, that's what's going to like ruin their experience.
Like I came to see-
I came to see it.
I'm a comedian.
She does magic tricks.
I'm fucking out of here.
And now she knows what card I picked.
Fucking out of here.
Disgusting.
Well, I'm here to go ahead and put a bow on that as well.
Because when I went and saw her in the show, I was curious.
I wasn't in agreement with these people, but I was curious about what am I going to go
see?
Of course.
Yeah.
I didn't even know I was going to see Sarah Starrus.
I didn't even know that Sarah Starrus was there.
Nice.
And I know those two have been doing shows downtown at the- what's that spot called?
Where our old improv theater used to be.
The Inspire?
Yeah.
No, no, no.
I know what it used to be called.
Norman Square, where the Onyx was.
Yeah, yeah.
Now there's a venue there.
Anyway.
Oh really?
There's a venue there.
Yeah.
Yes.
Is it that same space?
No.
It's in the middle there.
A newly built space.
Kind of new.
What's his name?
Look at me with all the fucking details.
Left Caesars and started running that space.
And I saw Sarah Starrus there.
I had all the details when I talked about going to see Sarah Starrus's show.
Okay.
Remember I talked about how she packed it on a Monday night.
Anyhow.
Let's see.
The Beverly, the Huntridge, Third Street, Notoriety.
Nope, nope, nope.
I'm just looking at downtown theaters.
I don't know.
We'll figure it out later.
We'll figure it out.
That's cool.
I'll figure it out.
Yeah.
Anyhow.
So they have chemistry.
Like amazing chemistry.
Yes.
Like they really play off each other like very well.
And it's really, really fun.
And Sarah Hester Ross is so much dirtier than Lucy Darling, which is really funny.
And Sarah is filthy.
For people who have only experienced Sarah Hester Ross on this show, you don't understand
how filthy Sarah can be on stage.
And she's the, she's the headliner, so to speak.
She's the second act.
They just share the stage.
She's a piano player.
Oh, awesome.
They just play off each other.
It is awesome.
And Sarah Starrus was a sniper, right?
Like, you know, she's, she's used to running her own show.
She's in like maybe she's like 20% of the show for this show.
And so she just was like stepping up and just killing it every time she needed to.
It was really great to see.
Okay.
But this audience indeed loves Lucy Darling and just wants her to do crowd work.
And that's what she did.
It was a 90 minute show.
The crowd was eating out of her hands the entire time, like roaring and loving everything
she was saying.
They were saying her lines for her, famous lines from her TikToks for her.
And she did all of two magic tricks to two, two and 90 minutes.
I didn't know she was going to do magic tricks.
Well, it's, it's kind of like Brad Sherwood was saying crowd work slash improv.
It's a kind of magic trick.
Just tricks, right?
Sure.
She, she has, she basically just kind of gave like four people roles, two people with big
roles in the show and just kind of dared them to play along with the storytelling stuff
and improv.
And that sounds awesome, man.
Exactly.
Right.
Like I was laughing because like Emily Gillette has always been very kind to all of us and
was super kind to me, especially early on in my Vegas time here producing improv shows
and things like that.
And whenever I talked to her now and I talk about being magician, she always goes like,
like, she's always like, and I'm always laughing like, why, why do you hate that I'm a magician
now?
Right?
And she always goes, I just don't think it's the only thing you're going to do.
I just think you're going to do more.
Okay.
Which is, which is fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's a fine answer.
But I really didn't know what she was talking about.
When I saw Lucy darling show, I was like, oh, this is what Emily Jett would love if
I was doing like, this is actually, I did two little magic tricks in the middle and
did 90 minutes of just me fucking around with my comedy friends and just making the audience
roar with laughter.
She would love it.
Who was that dude?
You're right.
That very, I don't want to use the word pretentious exactly, but it was a very Matt Donnelly.
Precious.
It was a very precious magic show.
It wasn't a lot of magic, but oh, I know who you're talking about.
I have, I have his t-shirt.
It's a classic magician here in Vegas.
He's not around anymore.
Hill Bill.
Oh, yeah.
I thought you were going to say, I thought you were going to say, Hans clock or something.
No.
Steve.
Steve Weirich.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was a Broadway special that this guy, and he had a moment about three years ago, I want
to say where he was the kid.
You're talking about Derek Delgadio.
That's who I'm talking about.
Oh, okay.
What's up with his new, is he doing something else now?
Is he just, what's happening?
He's doing a whole fish noodling thing.
Okay.
He was hanging out with him the other night by accident.
He's fine.
Okay.
He's always fine.
You know, he's, he's very much in demand in corporate and private show settings.
So he's got it.
He's got his niche.
Yeah.
That's great.
We don't need to set up like a Kickstarter for him.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Is he still doing a version of that show anywhere or is that kind of retired?
He's just, uh, I believe that's retired.
Right.
Yeah.
So they had partnered with this guy Helger, I think was his name, Spanish guy.
And they did a two person show with like all card tricks that Neil Patrick Harris fell
in love with and produced.
And it had like a crazy run at the Geffen theater, like a, or unheard of like six month
run in Los Angeles.
So he's had a couple of real feathers in the cap already.
So okay, cool.
Yeah.
He's like a real, uh, kind of like highly esteemed magician in the ranks or whatever.
He also, uh, famously tried to get brushwood kicked out of the castle for dress code violations,
um, uh, for performing out of dress code.
So, uh, in fairness, anytime I go to the magic castle, I try to get Brian brushwood.
Why are magicians such catty bitches?
What the fuck?
I mean, this is all old news, but it was just funny because three tricks for them all to
share Paul, because I only ended up hanging out with them happen in the happenstance way.
And so I literally was like, Oh, and that's funny.
It's like, and basically my brain is going like, do not bring up Brian, do not bring
up Brian.
Do not.
That's all I was going in my areas because the answer could have been like, Oh my God,
that's so embarrassing.
I was so into it back then and I was trying to be a castle boy and blah, blah, blah.
Or it could be like, I still think the castles got too much and it was like, no, it could
definitely be like, fuck that guy still.
And I was like brushwood even told me the story so long ago.
I was like, I don't even, like, I, like, I was like, I don't even know if he might not
even remember it.
He, he might've been like, you did not.
If I said, if I brought it up, he'd be like, please tell me you did not bring up that.
So I kept my mouth shut.
So you brought it up?
No, I, this is it.
I'm laughing because 10 years ago, I absolutely would have just been like, you know, I had
to ask cause I got your back, man.
You know, I've learned because of Penn and Teller, I used to carry other people's water
for so many conflicts and they'd be like, oh no, we buried that.
And I'd be like, what?
Oh shit.
I've been furious at that guy for eight years.
That's really fucking funny.
Even with, I mean, maybe I shouldn't say this, but even like at one point, Tapeface and Piff
had beef.
Oh yeah.
And Piff totally forgot to tell me that they absolutely buried it.
That they absolutely, like, that they absolutely like made amends and get along and whatever.
And I was like, what?
I was carrying around hatred in my heart.
I was, I was awkward with him at red carpets.
Cause they weren't even like big beef.
They were just like, it was like misunderstanding beef.
And they both knew it was misunderstanding beef before they squashed it.
I think.
Yes.
They were, they were basically both.
They were both okay even before they squashed it.
They ended up being accidentally played against one another via casino people and about like
trying to find homes and casinos and stuff.
It was just, you know, business stuff that actually is pretty boring when you break down
the nuts and bolts of it.
Yeah.
It sounds exciting on the surface, but it's nothing.
I'll tell you who else has beef with Piff the magic dragon and with Tapeface.
I mean, the three of these people are going to fight Piff Tapeface and this following
sponsor are definitely going to have a physical altercation.
Today's show is brought to you by, where is it?
God damn it.
Here it is.
I think I just put it in the more prominent place on my cell phone.
Not, not in the middle of row two on screen four of my apps, but a cat scratch fever salve
cat scratch fever salve is our sponsor and it's from semi pro dad in 2022.
That's cat scratch fever salve.
Hey, what's going on everybody?
It's me, Paul Stanley.
Yeah.
I'm here to help out my good friend who can't be here today.
The YY man himself, the cat scratch fever boss, you know him, you love him.
He dates children.
I can't remember his stupid name, but anyway, that's not important because he's not here.
I am.
I want to tell you about some really good stuff that he's selling that I'm pimping.
It's called crat scratch fever salve.
You ever get a scratch from a kitty kitty, you ever get a little bruise, little scratch
on your arm.
Do you want that to get infected?
No.
Here's the best thing to do.
Go ahead.
Oh, I remember his dumb name is Ted Nugent.
Anyway, so what you want to do is go ahead and get you some of Ted Nugent's Paul Stanley
cat scratch fever salve.
Ted Nugent's Paul Stanley cat scratch fever salve is guaranteed to end inflammation and
stop irritation and prevent infection.
Yeah.
Some of you might have been using wipes.
Some of you might have been using disinfectant alcohol.
I'm here to tell you what's better is Paul Stanley's Ted Nugent's cat scratch fever
salve.
It's medicated, it's vibrated and it is perforated for your enjoyment.
That's right.
Take it from me.
Perforated?
The star child.
I wouldn't lie to you.
Buy it.
Enter Hayscoops at checkout.
Buy.
Saying "buy" is hysterical.
I said "buy" but I should have just said "buy".
Oh, I thought you were saying like I'm done making this commercial now.
Goodbye.
It's over.
I'm through.
I'm through that idea.
Buy it.
There it is.
Cat scratch fever balm.
It's real.
How about, how about old Gene getting into the Kennedy Center?
Gene and Paul both?
You're at the Kennedy Center.
Stop it.
Paul agreed to go?
Well, I mean, they are, like Paul and Gene are kiss.
No, I think it's just, I think it's just Gene.
Paul's been pretty adamantly anti.
I don't know that they're going to go together.
I'll be very surprised and disappointed.
I mean, somewhat surprised.
And talking about the Kennedy Center honorees this year?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
By the way, I don't have any beef with anybody going in, like the honorees, I'm fine with
all the honorees.
Does anybody care about the honoree, like, are people saying these people shouldn't be
going into the Kennedy Center?
Sharing is exactly what we're talking about here.
It reminds me of when Barry Bonds was breaking the home run record.
Yeah.
A little bit, yeah.
And everyone was like, they want to do all this stuff like launch the ball in outer space,
you know, all this other stuff.
And Brandon Asterix on to it.
What someone said is like, all that's going to happen is we're going to stop caring about
the home run record.
And that's exactly what we did.
Yeah.
We just stopped caring about it.
Yeah, that's it.
And then someone does a trick with baseball cards, I can tell you, the ramifications of
the steroid era are real, because when I ask people who likes baseball, and it's mostly
young people in the audience, no one says yes.
And sometimes, audibly, people go like, not me.
Yeah, not me.
And I don't really go like, oh, no, and I'll even come with them with a bucket of baseball
cards.
And they literally look at me like, no, I hate baseball.
I'm like, it's the first and the last thing.
I hate baseball.
Can you chill out?
They hate baseball so much they're like allergic to baseball cards.
They literally recoil.
Holy shit.
I mean, I'm coming at them with an evasive extending pole and bucket.
Sure.
That it might not be.
No, I understand the recoiling.
Might not be.
Might not be just the subject of baseball.
I'm a little off putting myself.
But it's amazing, the negative impact of baseball.
And even now, even in my baseball card collection that I use, I have a lot of old players in
there.
And I thought about replacing them with new ones and it's basically.
Nobody cares.
Nobody knows.
I can maybe put Otani in.
Yeah.
I can maybe put Judge.
A-Rod.
A-Rod's the latest, right?
I think you put Otani.
I think you put.
Yeah, A-Rod's in there.
That's why A-Rod features in my thing is I think it's the only one.
I think it's the most.
And that's just because he was married to that dancer lady for a minute.
J-Lo.
Jennifer Lopez?
You could maybe do Mike Trout.
Was that her?
Yeah.
That dancer lady.
A very famous celebrity.
She was a fly girl.
Yeah.
Yes.
Everything Paul is saying is true.
Dancer lady, fly girl.
Please don't write us saying that Paul was right.
We know he's right.
I mean, if you look up her IMDB, it starts off with famous dancer lady, Jennifer Lopez.
If you look up her IMDB, which no one has done.
We also have owner of the Minnesota Timberwolves as well as a result of multiple lawsuits, A-Rod
is the owner of the Timberwolves.
Oh, I thought you about to say J-Lo owns the Timberwolves.
No, no, no.
That was going to be surprising to me.
Yeah.
But I mean, like that's it.
Like A-Rod is featured in the tricks simply because that's the one I believe that most
people would know.
Right.
Even if you don't like sports.
Yeah.
And that's an old joke, right?
Like I made that decision eight years ago, right?
And so right.
That's crazy that that's that it's that old and it still seems like that's it.
Like what else?
Like you're right.
Like Otani is the only other name I even know.
I've been a couple of Pirates games.
I couldn't tell you any of those players.
No, I actually I haven't done that a lot, but I should.
I really want to ask my kids like name a baseball player, name a professional baseball player.
Like a current one.
Is there a, is there any way for you to get Savannah banana cards in there?
Because you could put like still no one still knows individual Savannah bananas.
People know what the Savannah people know still in those individual play.
They will not still.
I don't know stilts.
He comes.
He plays.
I understand what you're saying.
How do people not know stilts?
I believe that if I were watching a baseball game and there were a player on the field
wearing stilts and I heard people referring to a player called stilts, I would know which
player to pick him out of a lineup that night, but after that I'd be able to using the context
clues.
I'd be able to figure out who you meant.
If I were to say scooped up by Roberto Clemente and thrown over to stilts, I don't think the
audience would be like, yes, you're right.
This is Savannah bananas.
I don't think he just made a Savannah bananas reference.
What about characters from the sandlot?
There we go.
You're right in that I'm trying to consider doing a whole different deal altogether rather
than I don't want to go back to cards, but I'm trying to think of something just entirely
different.
There are Marvel trading cards.
Everybody knows Marvel characters.
Somebody did say earlier, Marcelo in the chat said earlier that you could get rid of the
baseball cards and just put in Pokemon cards.
Pokemon would be really funny too.
I think Marvel is a stronger move than, we've turned this into a brainstorming session,
but I think-
It just has a stronger grip on the zeitgeist.
Everybody knows Marvel.
Not everybody knows.
For Matt Show!
Except it's my production.
It's the My Newly Magic production meeting.
Production meeting for Matt Show.
No, Marvel characters are smart and it's actually smart too because I really want to get a Disney
cruise ship.
Oh yeah.
There you go.
That's the way to go, man.
Go with Marvel art cards.
Oh, well they've got to be just Disney trading cards.
No.
There's Lor-Kana.
That's got to exist too.
You don't want to do Lor-Kana.
Jacob.
Mine are fake anyway.
Yeah.
No, but there are Marvel art cards from back in the day.
What?
Oh shit.
This is what happens when people pretend to steal.
Like I have like Mickey Mantle and stuff and they pretend to steal it in their pocket.
In fact, someone has stolen a card from my-
Oh no.
I thought it was a valuable baseball card.
Someone stole a Cal Ripken.
They think it was a valuable baseball card and so when they do it, I go like, "And if
you think you're taking an actual baseball card from a working magician, you go ahead
and keep that in your pocket and you tell all your friends."
If you think this working magician has a Cal Ripken rookie card that he's passing around
to you.
No, the answer is fucking Marvel Super Heroes.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
It's easy.
That's just the answer.
Anyhow, that's not what I was trying to talk about.
Do they have to play baseball though for the trick to work?
Yes.
They have to play baseball.
That's going to be a little-
It's Iron Man playing baseball.
People will know that this is a secret softball game that takes place every year between DC
and Marvel.
Let's go Marvel.
Fuck DC.
No.
I am just going to go Marvel because Disney owns Marvel and doesn't own DC.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm just going to just go Marvel and then, no, I can narrate an event, Paul, instead of
narrating a baseball game.
Fantastic.
I can still narrate an event.
That would be cool, man.
Yeah.
That would be very cool.
Because even my intro of it is like, the intro of it is when I was a kid I liked the movie
Field of Dreams.
That's getting diminishing applause.
Sure.
Eight years later.
Yeah.
It was nice when Kevin Costner was hitting again with Yellowstone, but that's gone now
too.
That's gone.
Well, I think Puddles has stolen all the Costner fire.
That's just-
That's true.
There's nothing left.
In fact, when I was doing it, Heidi Klum came in off the street and said, "Stop stealing
everything from Puddles," and then went back out on the street.
Just wanted to make sure she hated him.
I think Puddles did that after you started talking about it.
Well, our attorneys will figure that out.
Sure.
I'm referencing, by the way, when I failed on America's Got Talent, and while they were
judging me, I pulled out an apple and I sliced the apple with the knife I used for my card
stab and started eating the apple, and Heidi Klum yelled, "You can't steal everything
from Piff," at me with a hatred that was trying to stop a protest or something.
It was with a family passion that she yelled at me.
Yeah.
It was really startling.
We're talking about our blood oath loyalties.
In the chat, we're getting some really good people talking about the times they were convinced
to take a blood oath.
Let's see here.
Too many people have chatted.
I've lost track.
But someone in the chat was like, "An Olive Garden fired their cousin, and so the whole
family protested all of Olive Gardens."
The long-term grudges?
Oh, I see.
I see.
The blood vendettas, not the blood oaths.
Right.
Jason Victor.
Jason, are you unmuted?
Yeah.
What happened?
You were fired?
No.
Who got fired?
My cousin.
Actually, it was kind of messed up.
My cousin was a waiter at Olive Garden, but he was really theatrical, and he would sing
at tables and do all this.
He was a tremendous performer and everything.
He was in all these plays and shows.
He would use tongs and pretend to be a crab and scuttle across the floor.
Everybody loved him.
A week before he was set to retire, they fired him without a cause.
My grandmother was like, "No.
We will never go to Olive Garden."
A week before he was set to retire, did he get knocked out of benefits and things because
of that?
Yeah.
Whoa.
It was messed up.
Also, I'm finding out right now that Olive Garden has retirement programs.
Now, this is third-hand storytelling.
That's what we're built on.
We're built on hearsay and conjecture.
That's fine.
That's what makes this work.
We don't have the authority to be a primary source podcast.
No.
That's not where we're at financially.
Also, we don't have an ombudsman.
It doesn't matter.
We do not.
Nobody's checking.
Who knows?
It was one side of the story, times three times people I've heard it from, so I don't
mean to create a beef for the whole podcast here.
Oh, jeez.
We're getting a phone call right now.
It's the following sponsor, but the following sponsor is Olive Garden calling in to rebut
this story.
Here we are with Olive Garden and their rebuttal, Take It Away Olive Garden.
Hey, it's a me, Mario Olive, and that's my brother, Luigi Garden, and today we are
going to tell you that we don't fire people because we don't want to pay for their retirement.
We fire them because we hate the singing.
We hate singing so much.
We hate theater, and we often will not deliver food to any Broadway show.
We will not offer endless breadsticks to anyone who knows how to play piano.
We do not, we have a very firm, we've been against music from the inception of the founding
of our company.
How are you going to come to Olive Garden and sing one endless breadstick in the cover
of your face?
How are you going to sing an endless breadstick and a bottomless bowl of soup?
Do you ever hear the phrase, "You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel"?
That's the truth.
You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel.
So don't do it.
It sounds a little different in Italian, it's more poetic, but keep going.
In Italian it sounds like, "You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel."
But translated that means, "You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel."
Yeah, yeah.
That's much better.
I'm sorry if I lost anybody there.
The English version sounds ridiculous.
In my old country talk, boy I feel like I'm back at home.
I feel like I'm back at home like a big old macaroni in my mouth.
Oh.
Enter the scoops at checkout.
We should get a little occasion at the end.
Oh, I like me some macaroni.
Oh boy, what a guarantee.
Go ahead and give me one.
Yeah, I'm going to roll this game.
I'm going to roll this LP role all the way over now.
I'm going to give me some macaroni.
I want you to go ahead and give me some of that.
Go ahead and make my bolognese really spicy.
I'm looking for some of that delicious lasagna.
One last question for Jason.
Did the protests hold?
Have you never gone to an Olive Garden, and do you know that none of your family's ever
gone to an Olive Garden?
I think most of us have kept away from it for the most part, but if anyone did go, they
would definitely.
Wow.
I think it's a real awkward Thanksgiving, I think, because you'd be like, "Really?
Still?
None of us?
Not one Olive Garden?"
It's so affordable.
It's right near the movie theater where I take my kids, you sure?
It's not great, but it's pretty good.
You know, this is a blood feud that actually benefits your blood from a salt perspective,
so that's kind of good.
Yeah, and this is like decades ago too, at this point.
This is a really old ... This happened a while ago, but I still remember, she's like, "No,
we can't go."
She called up everybody.
She's like, "We can't go to an Olive Garden."
Was there a lawsuit after all that?
I don't think so.
I got to actually ... I got to call them and see what they're doing.
Is he okay?
We got to get it.
Yeah, you get us an update on your cousin.
We're so busy hating Olive Garden because of the foiled retirement.
We never forgot the check.
Oh shit, my cousin died in 2020.
This was before GoFundMe's could help people like him.
Turns out he died right before COVID hit.
That's terrible.
My father won a defense case on this.
Everyone presented all of these evidence of threats and all this other crazy stuff and
phone records and all this stuff, and my father on cross-examination was like, "Anyone check
on him?
Anyone see if he was doing okay?
Like anyone ever talk to him about the threat?"
The answer was no.
No one actually went to see if the person actually had anything threatening happening
to him, and he got him off.
Logic wins the day.
I never get tired of hearing stories about Dave Donnelly getting guys off.
I know he's happily retired now just so everyone's not worried about Gary, but he's okay.
Does he still sing at the table?
I saw him recently, and I think he's still performing at the community theater down in
Florida.
Every Christmas, he's like, "When they fired me from Olive Garden."
Oh, it's the story.
Oh, Gary's doing his song again.
Gary's doing his story song again.
We've heard this song.
Why is it every Christmas?
I was only a week away from retirement.
They cut me loose.
Shut the fuck up, Matt.
I love this song.
All right.
With no excuse.
Oh, this is your first Christmas with our family.
I forgot to tell you.
My uncle sings about the time he got fired from Olive Garden.
When you sing at the table, the devil dances on your navel.
Everyone knows that expression.
We all know that expression.
Have you guys never heard that?
No, I've never heard.
I've heard it in the original Italian, obviously, but never the translated version.
How was the Italian again?
When you sing at the table, and the devil, he'd dance on your navel.
That's it.
That's what I remember.
Bossy understood that, but nobody else got it.
Sure.
Very clearly.
Thank you, Jason.
Oh, my heavens.
I hope his cousin is okay.
I mean, he's alive.
I think he's fine.
I'm sure.
I went into a bathroom the other day, a public bathroom.
Stop it.
Gross.
I was going to use the said bathroom.
They had recently, it seemed, maybe painted the floor in the bathroom.
The paint they had chosen to use was that black paint that always looks wet, depending
on how you look at it, like from what angle you look at it.
So I'm in the bathroom, and I was like, "Is the whole ... " I thought the whole floor was
just wet, and I was trying to move her.
Oh, no.
I was so confused.
You know, when you walk into a public bathroom and you just see like a little, like, some
wet on the floor there, you just walk around it, you know, whatever.
This was, like, it was everywhere, and I had a moment of just sheer panic and didn't know
what to do before I realized it was just a terrible choice in paint by someone.
We had this happen when I was a kid.
Back in the day, we used to go to Kings Island as a family, back before I was working there.
And way back in the late '70s, which is when we went as a family, they used to have these
caves, these man-made ... They were basically, what do you call those, like ...
Holes.
Drainage tubes, big enough that you could walk through, you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
But they build it like a half-tunnel, right?
So they made these tunnels, and they were these themed tunnels on ... One of them was
like a Tom Sawyer, so you'd walk through and you'd see Injun Joe and Becky Thatcher.
It was little static scenes of statues and things, but kind of retelling moments in the
stories.
Well, we go walking into one of these tunnels, and it had been raining that day.
And there was a pool of water in the tunnel, and the light was hitting it just right.
It looked like a pit.
It looked like a deadly pit that you couldn't go any further.
You would walk on it and you'd fall to your death.
But what it turned out was it was a reflection of the ceiling from that water puddle.
Gotcha.
Yeah, yeah.
It was an optical illusion that it made it look like you were going to fall and die,
but there was nothing.
But I take your point on the freakiness of walking around on a floor.
I was like, "Why would you paint this floor with this paint?"
Because then when it is done ... Dead Lazlo's been boycotting Boston markets since 1998
because they wouldn't let them get two of the same sides out of order.
Stop it.
Fair.
That is a reasonable reason to boycott Boston markets.
Why would you not be able to do that?
For 30 years.
And also that your boycott might work is really funny.
You indeed might have put them out of business.
You didn't help.
Boston market had a smell, didn't it?
It did.
It had a very particular chicken seasoning.
It was real strong, real pungent, almost like not as offensive to me as a Subway, but same
kind of vibe.
That's Subway smell.
In Portugal, there was a Subway in Lisbon, a Subway sandwich shop in Lisbon, and I went
and stuck my head in just to see if they had the same smell.
Really?
Yeah.
This is a true story.
And they did.
They did.
Okay.
Same smell.
Overseas Subway shop.
Didn't matter.
I think it's just when you handle meat, it gives off a certain odor.
I think it's a meat-handling odor.
I think you're right, Paul.
If you suck it on maple syrup, it gives a different flavor palette.
Yeah.
Ugh.
Especially with my syrup, it was baby-birded to me by someone who worked at a Canadian maple
plant.
God damn it.
That's why he got fired from the Olive Garden, because he was spitting the linguine onto
the tables.
It was baby-birded.
How many times do I have to tell you not to baby-bird the linguine to our customers?
I'm here with some cheese.
You fired my uncle for his singing.
No, we fired your uncle for spitting food into other people's mouths.
I've got some grated Parmesan, say when.
When?
I didn't want you to say when.
Okay.
An hour ago when.
An hour ago.
Okay.
I'll be back if you need anything.
I'm sorry, do you have any fresh black pepper?
Hold on, I've got some between cheek and gum on the other side.
Oh no, God damn it, why did I ask?
Oh, I regret this.
I keep several different kinds of cheese and spice in my mouth while I'm serving.
So that I can dispense it at any time.
It does sound like Cher.
I'm sorry.
Okay, if you want to know how to impress Cher, all you got to do is imagine you've got a
mouthful of paprika.
Paprika.
We should say, we've addressed some housekeeping, reading a little stuff on the internet and
some confusion in the chat.
So I accidentally, when I uploaded our last episode, uploaded it with today's episode
number and so it came out as 1236 to the 1235 and then people thought a crazy trend was
happening because they said also we can't find another episode on there and I won't
even name the number.
And so the answer is one was my error and so you're not missing two episodes.
You are missing one.
Yeah.
And that's temporary?
Yes.
But a listener, just like Jason came on here and shared a lovely story there, if all of
a sudden his uncle was like what the hell and also he started ganging up on his uncle
on the internet then we would maybe try to like not be the cause of someone's
Mitigate that.
Yeah.
So yeah, it turned out someone was getting picked on by jerks on the internet and so
we took down the episode to stop being a source of woe to one of our listeners.
And I'm going to edit that episode out.
I've got all the little spots to edit out.
I just haven't been able to do that yet.
I'm hopefully going to
By the time this episode comes out, I'm hoping that that episode will be back up as well.
It will be back in the meantime, please help yourself to one of our 1,230 other episodes.
Which I am proud to say
Feel free to look around at all.
I am proud to say we have stuck to it.
Our base episodes have been up and free and unpaywalled from the jump.
Yes.
I am really proud of that.
That's right.
Except for this one.
This one is behind the paywall.
It's not behind the paywall.
It's not.
Oh, you can pay me and I'll send it to you.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
There's ransomware here.
It's also not even the
@AudioguyJacob, pay me.
I'll just send it right to you.
It's not even the first time we did this.
We did pull down temporarily the one where I wasn't going to get sued by the people
who made Marilyn.
Yeah.
Let me put that back up.
Right.
Yeah.
That's fine.
These things happen.
Yeah.
We've got the finger on the pulse, people.
This is what you get.
We caught up in the mix.
Sorry for misnumbering to the point of the fact that we did take down an episode.
So, yeah.
Right now, you're missing an episode.
I'll be back soon.
Two different things happened.
Yeah.
But the one we're listening to right now is
Quantity over quality.
OG.
OG with the zinger.
I know.
OG coming in hot.
You're not wrong, Andy.
We're not arguing with you.
We're just laughing at the fact that you said it.
But there's also a reason why Subway was successful.
The smell and the quality.
Yeah.
They said, "We'd like to make this restaurant smell like the tunnel of the New York City
subway system."
Yeah.
And much like a Subway sandwich, we were also worth hitting an ICE officer in the face with.
Oh.
Hey.
You know, I had a good one on that one.
A friend of mine sent me one of those Gaston flag parodies with that and the sandwich was
being thrown at his face, you know.
And it's like  it said like, "Don't  " what is it?
I got to  it was like, "Don't sub  "
All I know is I'd rather have a dildo thrown at me while I'm playing basketball.
Oh my God.
That's outrageous how much that's happening.
And have a Subway sandwich thrown at me at any other time.
But it was like, "Don't sandwich on me," or something like that, you know what I mean?
And my quip was, "That guy should be referred to as Hoagy's heroes."
That's pretty good.
Glad we looped around to pick that one up.
I know nothing.
That's great.
I laugh at the  you know, we all get spammed every day with people trying to scare us with
different bullshit things.
I never changed my New Jersey area code on my phone.
Right.
Why should you?
The spams are like, "This is New Jersey DMV," or like, "This is New Jersey Power
Authority."
I have a Louisiana number and it's the same thing.
I've got the 702, which tips me off every time these motherfuckers come call.
I'm like, "Well, you  I don't even live  I don't even  I don't even
know her.
I don't even know her.
That's my purse."
Lucy Darling and Sarah Soros play each other tremendously well.
Sarah Soros is a sniper.
70 minutes is the crowd was just loving and roaring with her.
Merch line out the door.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
It was one of like a dozen shows where they were all sold out at the MGM in Brad Garrett's
old space.
Brad Garrett Comedy Club moved.
Yeah.
That's how out of touch I am.
And it's Tapeface's theater.
The new space is good, too.
Tapeface, who I have no problem with whatsoever.
Love me some Tapeface.
Yeah.
That's how I like Tapeface.
In his theater.
And it was once I was like, "Oh, she's famous.
She's hit.
I'm waiting an hour for her to say hello to all of her fans and then I can hang out."
And when I looked at her, I was like, "Hey, I don't know what this show is."
And she was laughing.
I was like, "It's not  I mean, you're not doing traditional stand-up.
You did two magic tricks.
It's not a magic show."
I was like, "You're really like keeping a bit in the air?"
Yeah.
You keep like five bits in the air and the audience loves it and then you bounce back
and forth between these bits and the audience just loves you for it and it's crazy.
But people loved it.
I mean, people were just clapping for her, cheering for her, laughing for her.
I was laughing hysterically for the whole show.
I just realized right now that I might have sounded like I was qualifying myself outside
of the laughter.
But I was not.
I was part of it.
Also went and saw Atomic Saloon, so I want to see our friend Tyler before he departed.
Nice.
Where's he going?
He's going off on a Broadway tour.
Water for Elephants.
They went ahead and made a musical of Water for Elephants, which is an amazing book that
people love.
And then in it, there's actually a little person in it who's a real three-dimensional
character, not some magical elf, actually plays a dramatically awesome role in the show.
And then Tyler's getting to play that amazing role as the first Broadway tour, and I guess
that's worth doing.
Man, we got to get him back on again after this run.
We got to get him back on to talk to tour.
That'll be fantastic.
No, I'm so excited for him.
I ran into him happenstance at a bar the other night, and so we got to chat for about half
an hour, 45 minutes or so.
And I didn't realize he's never done a Broadway tour before.
He's never done anything like this before.
So this is just all new experiences for him as well.
I'm like, I'm excited for the show.
I'm excited for him.
Yeah, it's going to be great.
Oh, he has to do it.
And I was saying, obviously they didn't want him to go.
He's great in the show at Atomic Silver.
He really, really makes that role so special, and he's so good at it, and he's so funny.
He's so personable.
He really connects with an audience.
He really just is a natural born entertainer.
And it's really special to watch him work.
My family and I saw him do a random panto show in New York, because it was only after
I saw him in Mavericks that we were like, oh, we're in New York.
He's doing a show.
Let's go see it.
We kind of knew him.
We weren't as friends with him like we are now.
We just had to see him.
So we love Tyler.
And so it was really great to see him in the show.
And the last few times I've seen it, it's still great.
It's the best it's been.
Atomic Saloon is in the best shape it's been.
I think it's an awesome show to go see.
I'm so glad to hear that, because I really enjoyed the fuck out of that show.
I saw it twice while I was still out there, and it's great.
Yeah, the host now and the bits are just so much more present and right with the audience,
and then the kick-ass acts that are in it are well.
Our friend Christian is back in with his little dog.
He does the acrobatic act with the dog.
So good.
It's such a fun show.
I got hit with a bunch of bread rolls.
Oh, good, good.
I was the kind of tap percussion duo that's been there from the fucking beginning.
I was looking at those like, Jesus, wow, because they were back in from Vegas Nocturne.
That's right.
Yeah, Suzanne and Peter.
Suzanne and Peter just been in this town, entertaining like that's nuts.
And they do a bit where they do this percussion, but they're like the whatever the hillbilly
twins or whatever.
And he has a bunch of bread rolls in his pocket and you don't see it.
He snipes people.
He just dances around.
All of a sudden, boom, a bread roll just comes flying across.
It's great.
And right before the show, I was in like the back of the main little orchestra section.
And they're like, do you want to move up?
And in my head, I was like, how much do I want to get hit by bread rolls?
But I was like, yeah, let's let's go for it.
Let's go.
Let's get moved up.
And I got clunked, right?
Bread rolls.
Yeah.
Last time I saw it, your wife was in it and our friend, Matt Morgan, they were the duo
in it the last time.
Yes.
And so they got me up on stage.
Matt is also a very funny preacher and can't resist that, but he's basically the director
now.
Yeah.
But I saw Heidi host because I my wife was I haven't seen Heidi do it.
She's very funny.
It is different.
It is definitely different than Sarah's and everyone else's.
And it's really good.
We're talking about Heidi, Brooker Morgan, who we've had on the show with Matt Morgan
before.
And yeah, they are just a powerhouse in everything that they do.
Yeah.
But Sarah was not performing with Tyler before Tyler left.
So I went and saw Heidi do it.
Nice.
Yeah.
Kick ass.
That's good.
You've seen Sarah plenty.
Yeah.
And over over the Venetian giant Wizard of Oz display over there.
I have my tickets.
Now the sphere and Venetian are two totally different entities, right?
They are.
But I believe they have kind of a partnership.
Yeah, because basically just became like haphazard, like the only place to park to go to the spheres,
the Venetian.
Right.
And so the Venetian started charging like event pricing during sphere events.
Which is great for me because it has taken out the question.
So now I just pay the ridiculous amount of money to park at the sphere because it's close
and it's convenient because Venetian is now charging like ten dollars less.
Yes.
Well, that's that is worth that ten dollars to me to not walk across the city and get
to this event.
So I guess I'll just pay the extra ten bucks and not have to worry about it.
Thanks Venetian for being assholes and charging too much for parking.
Yeah.
I mean, it is mentioning that there's a place called Lambert's in Alabama, famous for throwing
bread rolls across the dining room.
Do you know, Matt, was that taken from that place or not?
Maybe I know that it was not.
OK.
Oh, yeah, because I know Lambert's and they have they have a couple of places.
They have one outside of St. Louis as well that I've been to where and they do they just
chuck like if you need a roll, you just like throw up your hand and like roll like roll
and they just chuck it across the room baseball style.
We saw some videos of that, Anne and I and we.
Oh, but I asked about that when that when the Atomic Saloon started and nobody it became
it became a running joke for Anne and I.
She ended up buying us big Lambert's mugs with the guy throwing the bread roll on it.
Home of the Throed Rolls.
That's right.
Throed being the Throed Rolls the way they say it there.
Yeah.
So are you going to this Wizard of Oz show, Matt, or you just went to the display?
I have yet to see any show at the Sphere.
I don't know if the Wizard of Oz is even open yet.
It is not.
I have tickets to go see it though in September.
I think I have I think I have tickets to go see it before Scoopfest.
Yes.
I know it is opening soon and our friends flying out to come see it.
This is going to be a gigantic hit.
I think so, too.
I was just talking about this on another show the other day that this actually on on what's
the sorry Brian and Justin I just forgot Great Nights Patreon only section that they do.
Their bonus episode that they do.
The Bones.
Thank you.
So I was on the Bones with them and we were talking about that and that's what I was saying.
I was like this is they tried the nature video.
They tried all that stuff.
The thing to make money when they don't have the giant concert going in the Sphere and
I think Wizard of Oz is going to do very well in that regard.
And they're hiring live entertainers to be a part of it.
Yes.
And so some of our friends are getting really good gigs out of this as well.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's great.
And so it makes it makes me more hopeful about it.
Oh, and scuba nova girl is in the chat saying that that she saw the morning video on CBS
and it didn't look good.
I believe that because nothing is other than I think the movie itself.
I don't think anything else is done.
I think they're still creating everything.
So I believe that the advertising for it at this point would look but I think also it
is unfortunate that I think they are incorporating some AI gobbledygook into the side effects
around the giant screen kind of thing.
So I've seen some clips that because like there's you know, they're doing part of fucking
everything.
But yeah.
Yeah.
I was just going to be in there.
Yeah, I hear that that's not going to be the film in its entirety.
It's a lot.
I'm going into it with a I'm going into it with a positive outlook on it and I'm hoping
that it's going to be great.
Right.
Yeah.
And I'm not if it's not I'll let you know, I'm let you know, like, look, I'm not a big
Backstreet Boys person and I can't speak to whether that's a good good thing.
It's a hit.
I can speak to the fact that the Backstreet Boys are punching up like that was a way over
achieving experience.
I want to go see their show at the Sphere.
Yeah.
So I'm saying it's going to be a gigantic hit.
I don't know if it's going to be like my cup of tea.
I'm just saying it's going to be good.
I'm looking forward to it.
I mean, Wizard of Oz.
And I say that as as the Sphere exists as a black hole that is slowly sucking and destroying
every other piece of entertainment in this town, I can I can speak objectively to all
of those things that that giant snow globe is going to cause a lot of my friends their
jobs, so I'm only happy to at least creating a couple on the way out.
There's at least that because we've become a the town with the basic spheres becoming
slowly becoming Disneyland or Disney World.
Now, Metallica is the next one that's rumored, but more than rumored, I think.
I think they're they're they're aiming.
I think they are pretty strong, pretty strong.
Yeah.
There are so many more steps to saying yes to playing the Sphere, which is why you'll
hear so many more rumors along the way, and it's because it takes millions of dollars
on any artists back and our front end on the artist end, whether they take it from the
back or front.
Don't you worry about which end I'm on.
You have to invest millions and millions of dollars into the graphics that fit on the
on the sphere.
Right.
It takes a long time to get to your concert, so it takes a long time.
Yeah.
Guar show at the sphere would be in fucking saying, hey, did you see that they just created
I want to do a dinner show before all the concerts where they have bread rolls come
from thousands of feet away, every which way, just launching them to the fucking billion
dollar Lambert's dinner theater before any production of the Sphere every night with
Guar.
Yeah.
Guar is the band that would sing at the table while the devil dances on your navel.
They would be able to shoot fucking blood soup at you while you eat it.
Be amazing.
Instead of instead of blood.
Hear me out.
Drawn butter.
Right.
You had me at drawn by just millions of gallons of ghee fired right at you.
Daft Punk.
That I can't believe that you just said millions of gallons of ghee fired at your face because
that is the prize today for the winner of Jack versus millions of gallons of millions
of gallons of.
The hunt for balls so much.
We got an obelisk of it as today from Winters scoop.
This is the one where we have questions ranging from $200 all the way up to $5,000.
And of course the winner will be covered in the first question is $200.
It's coming to me first and it's true or false stars.
Nobody wants to steal this early so let's see what the question is.
Warning, difficulty steps up fast.
Okay.
Clint Eastwood has a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
A, true.
B, false.
C, blank.
D, blank.
Okay.
Just to tell you how the game works, I have a 50/50 lifeline that I'm not going to use
right now.
Right.
I'm going to go ahead and just say true, A, true.
Oh, B, false.
Clint Eastwood does not have a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
Does that mean that it never happened or that because those go in rotation?
No, no, no.
No, they don't go in rotation.
What?
Once you have a star, you have a star.
No.
Yeah.
You're kidding me.
Yes.
It's there forever?
Yeah.
The fuck out of here?
Ask Fatty Arbuckle.
It's still there?
Fatty.
Fatty, it's Jacob.
Hey.
It's Jacob.
It's been a minute.
How's your star on the Walk of Fame doing?
I'm okay.
What seems to be going on?
I was in the middle of eating a lot of food as I want to do.
Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry, Fatty.
I think I called the wrong Fatty.
I'm dipping all of my food in ghee.
Oh, never mind.
I called the right Fatty.
Yeah.
This is a PB in ghee.
Peanut butter and ghee.
PB in ghee.
Oh no.
Oh, I'm so upset.
Oh, Paul.
I'm choking on my PB in ghee.
I'm just going to reveal this true/false weather question and hope to move on.
Tornadoes have appeared in every state of America.
True or false, Paul?
Oh, man.
I'm sorry.
Are we boring you?
No.
I'm just trying to think.
You've got to define a tornado, sort of, but I don't know.
Let's hear you define a tornado.
I'll go false.
Let's try it.
That's true.
Ah, shit in my ass.
Boy, two questions that were 50/50.
We've not done well on them.
I don't hear a lot about Alaskan tornadoes or Hawaiian tornadoes.
Yeah, but I don't hear much about much.
Aside from Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, am I right?
Alright, let's go for it.
Give me the question.
Let's see here.
How many movies have been produced in the Harry Potter universe?
Eight, nine, ten, or eleven?
Eight.
No.
What?
That's my answer.
I'll go.
Okay.
It's D, eleven.
I was answering for speed, not for accuracy.
Alright.
Five hundred dollar question.
We've all missed a question so far.
Eight hundred dollar question.
We suck.
Corporate history.
Oh, the Harry Potter universe has those newer movies too, right?
Yeah, the Johnny Depp ones that were big failures, the mythical beasts and how to find them up
your asshole.
Yeah.
Johnny Depp was in those?
Look up your butt to see a mythical critter.
Huh.
Yeah.
Harry assholes.
I mean, I did that.
The butthole you're finding.
Yeah.
Yep.
Let's see.
It's me.
Corporate history.
Anybody want to steal anything?
We're getting into some stealing territory now.
What is it called?
Corporate history?
Corporate history.
Nah.
No, not that one, Jacob.
No one wants to steal corporate history.
Come on.
What year did Wal-Mart start?
1968, 1969, 1970 or 1971.
At least the options are nice and spread out.
So if I know like a rough time that Wal-Mart started, I might be able to guess them.
My question is when will it end?
Am I right?
Talking to you, Boston Market.
I smell partnership.
I have no idea.
Boston Wal-Mart.
Oh, I can't pass.
I'm not going to use my 50/50 on this.
Come on, Wal-Mart.
I guess, you know what?
1969.
Nice.
Yeah.
Come on, Wal-Mart.
Sexiest year ever.
Fuck yeah!
It was.
It's so filthy.
I love it.
Filthy Wal-Mart.
Oh, now I'm holding onto control.
Actor origins for 1,000.
Actor origins?
Anybody stealing?
I'm super stealing.
I want all of your 800 points.
Whoa, shoot.
Matt is living on the edge.
You're hot with the super steal.
What country does Cate Blanchett come from?
Australia, the UK, Canada or America?
Australia, A. Australia is correct.
Wow.
And I don't have any points again.
It's just like the old times.
Oh, boy.
Arkansas represent.
$1,200 questions.
Drinks.
Oh, I want nothing to do with it because I know nothing of drink.
Let's see.
Which country consumes the most tea per capita?
The UK, America, Turkey or India?
Well, this is where it gets tricky here, right?
Per capita.
That's that magic word right there.
Yeah.
Per capita.
Who's got the more capitals?
Right.
So India is too populated.
It's just no matter what the tea is, it won't add up.
You are spilling some tea on that.
Sometimes I bet drink way more tea than UK as a whole, but I don't think I don't I don't
think per capita, right, because then we're I think everybody in the UK drinks tea.
A lot of people in the States drink tea, but maybe not everybody.
Actually, I'm going to say Turkey gets no respect.
I'm going with Turkey.
Yes.
Gobble gobble.
It was Turkey.
It's Turkey.
Look at you.
It's fire Thanksgiving every day with this motherfucker.
Can't stop won't stop.
Let's see 90s music.
And you want to steal my amazing amount of points.
I'm going to double down.
Paul.
But do I?
Yeah, I just did regular steel.
What is the most successful one hit wonders from the 1990s was the most successful one
hit wonder wonder maybe from the 1990s, baby got back ice ice.
Baby Macarena or Mambo number five, which is so strange because Mambo number one through
four is pretty amazing.
But no respect, no respect.
This is all of these.
I'm going to I'm going to go with baby got back.
It's my gut boom boom boom boom boom boom boom Macarena Macarena.
Your guts filled with regurgitated linguine mouth garden.
Paul got that wrong and it's back to 16 hundred dollar question.
American history.
Fuck it.
I'll steal.
What are you going to double down that?
How far are we?
Oh no, we're not close enough.
Go.
All right.
Which state was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?
Arkansas, Georgia, Louisiana, Oklahoma.
You know what?
Arkansas is a little slow.
I'm going to say Arkansas.
Hey, it's Oklahoma, Oklahoma, where Christmas we don't give a shit about it.
That's two attempted seals to try to wrest control away from Matt Donnelly.
That's right.
They've both been unsuccessful.
It's still Matt Donnelly's board to two hundred dollar question.
Body science.
You guys can super steel me on body science.
Up to you.
Body science.
Oh, oh, I can super steel body science.
Thanks, Matt.
I'll do it.
What the fuck?
All right.
What is the name of the process by which DNA is copied to produce an RNA molecule translation,
replication, transcription or mutation?
I'm a go with transportation.
Transcription C is correct.
Oh, shit.
Who's got that?
And with that, you just transcribed my points to yours.
That's right.
Yeah, you did.
You can call me CRISPR because I'm modifying your fucking score.
Boom.
There's three questions left.
Paul is now in the lead with fifty five hundred points.
Matt and I are tied at zero.
I'll steal.
Oh, no.
Oh, but you can't super steel me.
Three thousand dollar question, philosophy Matt is stealing.
I can't super steel.
Which of these ancient philosophers is credited for the allegory of the cave, Aristotle, Plato,
Socrates or Homer?
E, your mom.
Oh, that's right.
She is a cave allegory.
Sit down, mom's cave.
Do you call the come in there stalagmites or stalactites?
That's right.
I stalagmite.
You might get pregnant.
I'm going to fifty fifty at Jacob.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
That got rid of Aristotle and Homer.
Now your options are Plato and Socrates.
Allegory of the cave.
Yes.
Socrates is Plato's prodigy, right?
I think it's the other way around.
Oh, Plato came second.
I think Plato was after Socrates.
Which had the barbershop playset?
That's Plato.
OK.
That's the one I'm familiar with.
The wacky hairstylist.
Yeah.
Right.
All right.
I'll go Socrates.
Socrates is incorrect.
It was Plato.
Socrates nuts.
Just like that.
Let's see Eurasian history for 4,000.
I am going to Supersteel.
Oh, no.
My money.
Eurasian history.
My specialty.
I'm always talking about Eurasian history, you know that.
I mean, every other night you're going to P.F. Chang's.
Yeah, exactly.
The Congress of Berlin in 1878 aimed to resolve which conflict?
The Russo-Turkish War, the Crimean War, the Franco-Prussian War, the Austro-Prussian War.
Well, shit.
I seem to have stepped in it.
I guess I'll use my 50/50.
You got this.
Oh, well, you got a 50/50.
That's pretty good.
All right.
That got rid of the Crimean War, which is what I was aiming for.
That's good that you got rid of it.
Look at that.
So you saved yourself.
And the Franco-Prussian War.
That's out.
So it's either the Russo-Turkish War or the Austro-Prussian War.
War huh.
Good God, y'all.
What is it good for?
Absolutely nothing.
Say it again.
Let's see.
I'll say, you know what?
Those Prussians, they were a feisty people.
So I'm going to say the Austro-Prussian War.
Here we go.
Final answer.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it was the other one.
Russo-Turkish War.
It was the other one.
And Paul closing out the game.
Paul, you could double down.
If I double down, I lose everything though, right?
Paul's doubling down.
No, I'm not doubling down.
Which law of thermodynamics states that in a closed system, entropy increases over time?
First law, second law, third law, or fourth law?
I like that you just have to know the laws of thermodynamics to get the answer to this
question right.
First law of thermodynamics.
Shoot, this guy used to sing it to me in Olive Garden.
Now I forget it.
Yeah, that was everybody's favorite.
Well, they fired him.
The first law of thermodynamics song.
Could you bring us a basket of garlic bread and sing the thermodynamics song?
You got it.
You fucking got it.
The first law of thermodynamics states that entropy increases over time, but only in closed
system.
I've got a 50/50, so I'm going to use it.
I'll use my 50/50.
That got rid of first law and fourth law, so it's either the second or third law, Paul.
It feels like third to me.
Oh, does it?
Okay.
Let's see.
That's what I'm guessing, see.
Fuck my dick.
It's me.
Shit my butt.
Second law.
Ah, poop my ass.
I think that means that we all missed the question that we used our 50/50 life line on.
But I didn't lose anything.
That is the game Paul wins, but only with 500 points.
Ah, balls.
Oh, you lost 5,000 points.
How did I lose anything?
In a game that goes-
Did you lose 5,000 points?
Bullshit.
In a game that goes from 200 to 5,000, the score is 500 to 0 to 0.
This is, that's why-
And that's from the winter scoop.
Obelisk is a great game.
This is why it could actually work on TV, probably.
Yeah.
People only give away 500 bucks.
Obelisk is our best, that's our best on-screen game for sure.
They're making a ton of TV right now, so it shouldn't be a problem to pitch this.
They'll play.
Yeah.
TV sucks anyway.
No issues there.
Fuck TV.
Yeah.
They're making a ton of TV right now, so it shouldn't be a problem to pitch this.
I don't know if you subscribe to the apps, but a ton of new shows are coming out left
and right.
Thank you for running that Obelisk.
That was a great Obelisk.
Yes.
That was Winter Scoop.
Thank you so much Winter Scoop.
If you want to send us an Obelisk or a Jock vs. Nerd of any kind, head over to HeyScoops.com
right there on the homepage, HeyScoops.com.
Make us an Obelisk.
Make us a Price is Scryte Jock vs. Nerd.
Make us a Scooperty Jock vs. Nerd.
Do all of those things right over there at HeyScoops.com where you can also-
So, while you're there, purchase your tickets to Scoop Fest.
Yes.
That's right.
It is coming up here at the end of September in beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada.
It's going to be fantastic.
It's going to be at the Orleans Hotel and Casino.
Get your rooms there.
Stay there.
You can just walk right down to the convention space.
Walk back up to your room when you need something.
It's really convenient.
It's really nice.
And the Orleans is going to give you a really nice room discount offer if you just tell them
that you're staying there for Scoop Fest.
Or you can use the code, Paul.
What's the code?
S-C-F-I-25...
C?
Yep.
C.
K?
No, no, no, C. Yeah.
That's right.
S-C-F-I-25-C. Head over there.
Get yourself a cheap room at the Orleans.
It will be fantastic.
And if you don't have anybody to come with, it's great coming by yourself.
That's right.
If you're looking and you want to, go to seeyouatthecone.com and purchase your tickets to Scoop Fest today.
Is that true?
Yep.
That's what I just found out.
Click in the chat there.
See you at the cone.com.
Yep.
There it is.
See you at the cone.com.
Which is awesome.
You guys are fast.
All the people that joined us in the chat, if you want to join us in the chat, you need
the link.
If you want the link, you got to go to our Patreon page and support us at any tier you
feel like supporting us at, either yearly or monthly.
Yearly will save you some jingle.
And getting on there will save you some jingle.
If you want to go to Scoop Fest, you'll get a discount code that will save you a good
amount of money.
That's true.
On your Scoop Fest ticket.
That can be done at preachingfun.com.
Or if you got fired for singing at an Olive Garden, even though you didn't work at an
Olive Garden, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with preachingfun.com, it's extra to our Patreon page, where for
as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Thank you so much.
We love all of our listeners and supporters out there.
Yes, we do.
At least one of and maybe two of our listeners are getting married.
We had some physical Scoop mail that came in today, and part of the physical Scoop mail
was a wedding invitation that we got for Macy and Danny.
So congrats to Macy and Danny out there.
When's their wedding?
Their wedding is September.
Oh, it is September the 27th, 2025.
We are busy then.
I think we're busy, and it seems like they might not make it to Scoop Fest as well.
Well, you know, ship's in the night.
Unless they're getting married in Vegas.
That's true.
Boy, what a honeymoon.
If you're getting married in Vegas, come right on over to Scoop Fest right after the wedding.
Let's see the details.
They're going to have an open bar.
They're going to have a cigar bar.
They're going to wear formal attire, and it's going to be an unplugged ceremony.
That sounds really nice.
I will be there.
Wow.
Jacob, okay.
What a commitment.
I'm going to skip Scoop Fest, and I'm going to go to this wedding.
Brock, we've never needed you more, buddy.
I hope you're listening.
All right.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the concert.
Thanks for joining us in the chat, everyone.
If you have a public restroom that you are in charge of, don't paint the floor so that
it looks wet.
That is off-putting inside of a public restroom.
It's gross.
It's really gross.
See ya!