Oh hello there I am so glad you are here this is the part of the show where we
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers we are having issues getting our list this month but we will thank each
and every ice cream truck driver at this part of the episode before this month is
over even if I have to go in and learn I don't know different languages and get
the lists myself through translation I'll do it to thank each and every ice
cream truck driver who are the ice cream truck drivers what these are the fucking
assholes that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
if you want to be an ice cream truck driver and I hope you do head over to
preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is where you go to be an ice cream truck
driver and who knows the life you save may be your own here's a program hey
Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
Matt the more I thought about your friend who gave your son cologne
yeah or I'm convinced that that person hates a teenager and just give it a
teenager thing to spell yeah it's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social city in
Las Vegas it's Matt Mattingly sitting in Pittsburgh at Paul Mattingly city in Las
Vegas it's me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun yeah like he's gonna be a
teenager and teenagers don't have but they pour too much stuff on everything
that's right like he's he's just gonna smell like stinky teenager dunked in
cologne are you worried that he's just gonna develop like a new expensive habit
is that what your problem is with it you think he's gonna do I hadn't even
thought about that oh yeah now he's gonna become a real scent connoisseur I
think he's just gonna be stinky well I mean it's crazy you go shopping for some
of those those perfumes they're big money some of them I bet they are I bet
how much is a like like a standard bottle of cologne now how much about a
standard bottle of cologne 20 bucks well I spent I spent almost nine for my
generic I'm ahead of you on this one what we have done is we have ordered
ambergris in bulk and we're gonna do a DIY cologne kit in our backyard because
it's cheaper to just order the whole whale eat the meat and get the ambergris
out then to just buy the ambergris separately and plus that gives you oil
for your your whale oil right if you like the home if you like the meat you
might as well just buy the whole whale that's it why fuck the ambergris when I
can fuck the whale for free wait is that how how does it go that's not an
expression anywhere but yeah no I'm making in my new expression why smell
the ambergris when I can fuck the whale for free there you go there you go yeah
we're gonna put a bunch of vats in the backyard but like you know bourbon in
one and then like you know some kind of weird floral arrangement and another
we'll just see how it goes yeah this is this is smart this is this is that Matt
Donnelly smarts that I tell people about oh again disruptor of the space disruptor
of the perfume space we're going to we're going to in styles 16 best
smelling colognes for men according to the real sniff tests top picks Giorgio
Armani Acqua de Gio what what said did did you get for your kid or did I put a
Gio did no I don't know I don't know no I don't know I don't remember I don't
know best yeah best long-lasting as far as I can tell they all they all smell
like anyway Creed Aventus on Amazon best spicy cologne for men Eve Saint Laurent
la nuit de homme at Sephora you mispronounce Tabasco best code under 50
bucks cremo spice and black vanilla at Amazon best vanilla Cone cologne for men
Tom Ford tobacco vanilla I was looking at first I really expensive I told the step
it up I told him to step it up and I haven't just put muscle cream on that hot
cream just to make you smell more mature yeah smell like he just worked out I
figured that's the way to get the ladies is like he would be wearing muscle cream
unless he did work it out right he's a real what's that Charles Atlas kind of
guy yeah okay okay here's where here's where the rubber meets the fucking road
okay there is a limited edition special deluxe Dior okay and this Dior fragrance
comes in a a special trunk okay okay all right now it's a little case yeah and
that trunk goes inside a collectible canoe and then you put the canoe into the
ocean you say how do I how do I steer it and you say use Dior this is this is
actually just a trunk it doesn't nothing from Manningley nothing from Manningley
on the or oh I'm you're too excited to read facts off your phone I got confused
because I thought it was the expensive clone it's just a box for your cologne
Oh the cologne box is expensive guess how much that fucking box cost that
Kristen Dior limited edition cologne box and you got all these I don't think you
can kick this one in the dick nope higher $1,200 hundred no hundred dollars
no twelve thousand dollars six thousand dollars to just hold my cologne just your
cologne box how does that so for that purpose I'm supposed to walk into like
work or wherever or a party am I supposed to walk into a party with my
cologne bar a this is where you put your briefcase I just want you call it what
you call it before your your fragrance wardrobe this is where you store your
your scent wardrobe I don't understand spending that much on something like look
you spend a lot of money on a watch people see the watch yeah I don't I don't
I don't think you bring your cologne with you to other places right I mean if
you're traveling all the time you want something nice to keep your smells in
Matt you're traveling all the time I didn't realize that client he's got fish
to keep his smells in you are the target demographic if you if you see me three
weeks on a cruise ship holding up that box with the title I work for free
you'll know why you'll know why there's that Jean-Paul Gaultier the mail that
one that looks like a dude's torso that's 320 bucks so yeah some of these
things are fucking oh my god Creed Royal English leather Jesus Christ from the
band yeah I just heard I just from the band I just smelled as much as we can do
this the whole pod but I think you can continually find things that are too
expensive in the perfume world if you keep searching the internet I didn't
search very hard and it already gave me a lot just that was the very first spray
with arms wide open those are the instructions good one that's a good I'm
so alone I sprayed too much cologne and now I'm all alone hey off-air we came up
with the best solution for yesterday's or sorry last episodes rather excuse me
last episode scoop mailer saying what do you tell people when they ask about your
son's circumcision right and off-air I said oh you should check out this podcast
I listen to called some other kids dick Chronicles I already know you love other
kids dicks love this ML Kennedy is batting a thousand here the Creed cologne
smells like a worse version of pearl jams use my atomizer Scott step let it
spritz you clean and clear step spray me with that spritz use the atomizer off-air
we're gonna do it yesterday which was I've had I've had a couple of clips go
maybe viral is too strong of a word but my most popular clips clips have taken
off I get stats right and so yeah these these one a couple of clips do well a
couple comes do well and also I get stats that say you know 75% of people
watching and commenting are not your followers right that's like a sign that's
what you want right right external engagement and it's one where I'm
handling a dickhead it's just two videos part one and part two I'm handling some
dickhead at one of my shows this is the state of the world man all people want
his crowd work and I and it's funny because when things go popular means I'm
gonna get criticized right so there's a lot of like you're thin-skinned you're a
terrible person that guys making reasonable requests to a show that I
went to a show and then during the show opened his mouth and just had a
conversation with the person on stage about what he wasn't doing these are the
people who are on their phones the entire time that a movie is happening in
this so we'll do some backstory I'm at Mystique dining and Folsom when with
that clip right and they just have like a security camera and if you know
basically for like liability purposes like is a magician loses it which I
came close to so that's not my camera that's just the the don't get sued
camera at Mystique dining so a couple things he's he's one in the first clip
he's lecturing me about how he saw some other magician and he went to bed that
night he figured out the card trick and he won't let me move on my show unless
he tells me the story and Mystique dining is a parlor environment right so
it's me at a table surrounded by 24 people in a room right and I perform at
a stage where the front row is 30 feet away so when you when you tuber me the
story yeah there was more to the story than I went to bed and figured it out in
my sleep there is more to the story and that like okay so what happens is I
start going I said the first joke is like and no one cares right and it gets
this it gets this big laugh from the audience and the reason why it's cuz the
way Mystique dining works is you you go there and you have this opulent
beautiful meal with everybody in the room before the magician comes out the
magician is the last 45 minutes of the of the of the experience right so this
gentleman had been the mayor of dinner yes so when he told me that story it was
probably the fourth time the audience was hearing that oh my god and I'm
hanging out right I'm back I'm on the backstage area waiting for the things
so I know this I've already been told this guy keeps telling the story about
how he figured out a magic trick and he won't stop telling people told he told
the one waiter told the other waiter he told Steve the the emcee and Booker Steve
Branham who runs the room told him and then interrupted my show while I was
trying to start a card trick to do it and so it just been blitzing people the
story the whole time so when I start laying in them I it's getting these
huge laughs because they freakin heard it they're done with it yeah they're done
with it now it's weird to have this clip take off for me personally like I I mean
he's an old guy right it's like I am picking on an old guy right like I do
feel bad like he's not he's not being an egregious drunk heckler you know
he's just make himself mayor of the room yeah right and then the second clip is
when I start to get into my card trick he starts busting my balls for not
having a sealed deck to start off the thing with okay and some other magicians
have chimed in going like it's a reasonable request
magician bullshit magician to magician abuse and you don't have to take it man
man there's oh I feel you brother I feel you that is that is a nonsensical that
is awful this business too long bullshit magician responses I've been performing
for other magicians too long and also is the only people that that would be
reasonable from is another magician at like a magic conference or something
like that or in a fool us type setup where they're doing any of that bullshit
because what you're doing isn't doing you're not teaching people how to do
fucking card tricks you're doing a show but not even that it's one of those
things that speaks to ignorance because any magician worth their salt knows that
sealed or not it doesn't really matter yes you can gimmick a deck to be sealed
yes sealed it's an ignorant comment it comes from a place of ignorance and
trying to be ignorant it's trying to wind up it's trying to one at one up no
I don't even mad at some I dealt with some similar shit at the guy who
disrupted the show I'm really angrier at the magicians who are defending I don't
see so much in a in a in an improv way recently and it got me it sent me to 11
immediately I'm just like shut your teaching no no no no no discussing
discussing intros of all things oh I was just like shut the fuck up you are you
are just talking shit to talk shit now yes yeah it's just like the like devils
advocating on the fly to make it seem like you're being smart apps of fucking
yeah giving giving an example oh my god my dogs are going crazy yeah no I was
just I was talking about it too they're angry no no I want to I want to hear
your opinion on this Matt so I was just talking about introing and one of these
simplify an intro because we had previously done an interview and the
interview got really dark and so at the end I grabbed your line which the this
is all intended to be comedic in nature yeah yeah to get us out of that death
spiral yeah and we and we were fine but I said hey in light of the fact that I
don't think anyone has any fun stories to tell right now about their day to day
yeah why don't we just go with song titles or rather song lyrics for a get
right yeah and and I was describing the thing and this is the way I put it I was
like so we'll get a song you know we'll get a lyric and I want you guys to just
think about a lyric that you're gonna call out don't you know really ponders
think about something that actually means something to you don't just shout
out who let the dogs out just give me a lyric and you know what as a matter of
fact give me a couple give me like two or three and I'll pick my favorite one
let's see what we do and I got oh you don't want to be fishing yeah wait yeah
thank you is accusing you of trying to cherry-pick the most in that the
description of how we could do how we could do it not in doing it just in the
description of saying hey no you give me three I'll pick my favorite and was
saying oh we don't want to be fishing I'm like you are so wrong on this you
couldn't be more wrong oh and so I kind of laughed because I was mad to the point
of explosion and I was like well you know there's burning kind of - we're
burning the who let the dogs out yeah thing and that kind of thing and and you
know I did I couldn't in the moment get my head back around but like like even
Liz the great Liz Allen has articulated to me you can do that you can pick you
know it's not like you're not I'm not you know first of all look most of the
time the audience shouts out a bunch of different suggestions at the same time
anyway usually exactly you've heard anyway so you end up you end up
assessing the situation anyway the idea no but the idea is that you were you
were disparaged that's what happened and it took precisely and it made you so
angry in the moment you couldn't get your words back around on you and I get
that completely yeah but the idea that someone would use you of like you're
literally trying to like you he literally just like made you into some
kind of cheap artists some sort of hack yeah yeah meanwhile you're actually like
trying to spread a wide net yeah that would drive me crazy yeah I needed some
validation it's also not a quiz it's not it's not a test it's not like let's see
who the best Improver is by seeing who can take suggestions the fact is it not
do this is a goddamn show no shit dude well that's that the ultimate the
entertaining the that's the ultimate thing is like okay let's go around all
this loop-de-loop and then the end of the day you're gonna you're gonna show
me something on stage worth a fucking right reminds me of the time the
emphasis brigade was on Conan O'Brien early days right so so they were on the
core for including Amy or Amy Poehler were on the stage and they go like Conan
Bronson cuz he you know we really love improv and I got hooked into this I was
like oh they're gonna let them do improv on Conan like this is awesome and they
go like oh can we just have like you know a setting or whatever they're like
all the Swiss mountains they're like oh and then can we have like a character
from fix you know history like Buddha and like oh and then we have like you
know whatever something you might count as like it's like cakes or whatever and
like okay we take you to a mountain where Buddha is having a birthday cake
and they make like noise in the curtain raises up they have a perfect set of the
perfect set just made exactly for that right exactly so the idea like so that's
yeah is that you're like you're like oh wait let me see if I can get it close to
my my right yeah yeah yeah I'm really hanging on to ain't no holla back girl
soon as I get no holla back girl then I can strike because I've got a great I've
got a great Gwen Stefani in the pocket like what the fuck I came here to do a
Gwen Stefani impression and I'm not leaving until I do it it just made no
fucking sense to me I'm just like you want to see what you're fishing what
environment was this where were you I've already said okay okay okay it's a weird
that's a weird one yeah so I should just say like more more on the the clip
because I told everybody in the zoom there was more to it the clip goes on I
do get it I do get a sealed back so like right part of part of the things that
I'm like grappling with as I take on the dumb internet comments is I think I'm
being funny the whole time I know I'm I know that I'm being upset but I think
I'm being upset in an amusing way if I thought I was being upset in a way that
wasn't amusing I would have I would stop and that's the hardest thing to convey
right like like if you look at the who that goat episode that we did with the
with the guys right if you go back and listen to that episode on our feed I am
the butt of that episode and I tee myself up for it numerous times you you
open that door over and over again yeah but it's what the show needed right so
I'm all purpose and you served it yeah I do it right so a couple people came up
to me and they're like hey man that was really tough up there I go what no that
was exactly everything went exactly the way we wanted you know I remember Justin
Robert young shooting people like no you don't know what's going to go away stop
talking to him it's like no I did what was supposed to be done in the show
right I'm very happy and so it's very hard to convey that like I am taking the
piss out of the guy I think he knows it a little bit I know it and the audience
is going with it and so I thought the odds would go with it on the internet as
well and for the most part they have right I'm pointing out the the few dicks
but I will say what my social media team edited out what's me finally opening up
a sealed deck which probably took forever because that's another thing
about the that's the other joke about like why are you using a sealed deck the
primary reason is that it is a pain the ass open a fucking back of cards and I
used to open sealed decks for my tricks and it would sometimes take forever and
it's got to deal with the cellophane yeah you got to deal with cracking the
box yeah then you got to dispose how many just that cellophane the two tops
and the two bottoms here the two jokers on the bottom and the two cards on the
top instruction cards yeah and then you got a shuffle them and else other stuff
right and so I do I do I do oftentimes skip a go here's here's the deck I've
been using from last night look they're all shuffled and I have the person look
at them and I give them a quick shuffle or they can give him a quick shuffle and
it's just for time it's just for time yeah it's just but also if you look and
you see that it's a real deck and if you're handing it to other people that's
it's 99% of the time that's gonna be just a deck you're not gonna hand a
gimmick deck to a person right there are tricks I do where I don't have the deck
sealed but if they if they're looking at the deck and they're able to shuffle
that deck and hand it back to you that is better than a freshly unsealed deck
yeah that is as much as clusterfucky as you can get mathematically right so it's
so it's edited out as I finally get all the cards out and do whatever and I put
the cellophane and the advertising cards and the stuff right in front of his face
okay and I go here I'm gonna shuffle while you inspect this garbage is that's
not in the clip that's great that's things like I I actually thought it was
fun for the audience to actually be annoyed but then follow through on all
of his demands right so like I did I did I actually did yes and him and do my
card trick under test conditions but that's not good social media right so
so that's the hard part is so I'm getting accused of like not playing fair
with the guy and you're like no I actually if you saw the whole thing you
did another guy goes I don't get it every every clip I see you and you're
just some thin-skinned guy losing it and I was like that means you just saw two
clips yes because my other clubs don't show that my other club don't have it at
all so I was like alright this good Jesus it's called a brand so yeah I got
it like I have a tick-tock page I don't even look at that my social media runs
entirely goes that clip killed on tick-tock and I was like oh man this is
not it's always the stuff you don't expect though right I know no I mean I
put that up there thinking it was gonna be something I when I said the cuz like
I said it's a security camp footage so I said right I said this is this is bad
this bad quality but I think this will play and so I was actually right in that
well good instincts yeah I'll tell you else only wants to see seal dicks and
that's the following sponsor today's show Matt manly's ice cream social is
brought to you by night as in nights of the roundtable nightmare the nightmare
dedicated to wordplay that is hopefully still funny when I'm sober that's from
goofs scoop in 2023 over it up that is nightmare the nightmare that's the
product hello tis I nightmare the night mayor yes I'm the mayor of the night how
about that I'm a man drunk and this is the funniest thing I've ever heard in my
life I'm a mayor I'm also a mayor and a night and a mayor of the night and a
nightmare this is the mayor of the night
the mayor of the night do we have any old business the council will adjourn
after we dedicate a tree oh tree oh yeah the mayor of the night yeah better
haze groups check out I'd like to apologize to all of our listeners there
the mayor of the night was really cherry-picking what business he wanted
to attend I'm sorry it was in fact it was offended by it was in fact a
cherry tree I was planting a cherry tree so that I could cherry pick the whole
thing yeah yeah yeah so there's someone reporting their tin scoop part two of
me with the sealed deck it's got 217,000 views tick-tock tick good and that'll be
great as soon as tick-tock starts to monetize I would tell you also the
weird thing about it is because I've had some of those clips do well but they've
not gained me followers this one's gaining me a bunch of followers which is
a weird which is a weird moment as well and I can't chase this right you can't
go like after oh I should start really busting everyone's balls then you will
just be a thin-skinned magician like we're gonna experiment with this company
with our podcast right we're gonna give them a month run and see what they do it
and they asked me they're like is your brand on ice cream social like like
similar to your brand as a magician like do they compliment each other and I said
oh not at all no I'm a relatively clean magician and I am absolutely filthy on
this show so no it does not not exactly brand synergy no I started off as a
magician I was filthy when I started there so originally it did it did
compliment each other right right but I don't I was remembering that I used to
ask for a borrowed iPhone by asking for a hand jobs machine right yes for the
hands jobs machine I asked for the hand jobs machine I still haven't donated my
Halloween candy I gotta look for a place to do that still I got 20 pounds of
candy download just send it with a Sarah to work she'll bring it to work it'll be
gone in 20 minutes European acrobats we'll eat the shit out of that candy we
already got we already got snow up here oh no yeah yeah yeah we already got snow
and it actually stuck to the ground so I'm very concerned about what's coming
this winter yeah yeah yeah but I'm also pleased to say that my Christmas
decorations went up at a very timely time because half the neighborhood is up
and cooking now a week after I put my stuff up so it's it's all good you're a
trendsetter buddy I was I was speaking of our regional news Jacob are you
excited that the shuck era has begun down in New Orleans what's happening so
is this a is this a ballplayer of some kind yes let me say some my kids are
suddenly into football enough that they're curious about watching it when I
watch it okay but part of it was we were sitting around two quarterbacks came up
one was Michael Pennex from Atlanta my kids literally were like does that say
Penix and they were hysterical that someone else playing football has a
robot penis called called the Penix and we just made robot penis jokes if the
Atlanta Falcons were smarter they would follow your lead oh yeah and then then
it was the beginning of the Tyler shuck era in New Orleans and which my kids are
really loving being part of the shuck era they don't give a shuck they're part
of the mother shuckers they're ready to rock is it his name pronounced show is
that true I don't think it I don't think you say the C at all in his name oh I
have only listened to anyone pronounce it shuck is it pronounced is it
mispronounced I I thought it was Tyler show I don't know okay I could just as
easily be the person wrong here is it Patrick wah is that right yeah the old
hockey player there's some new ones too there's a new Roz out there are there
more was there are there's one who plays for Vegas now yeah but yeah no that's
that's great and to answer the question you're really asking I can't get behind
the New Orleans Saints this year at all they're just so bad I get I mean we're
on we're on our own text message shades and everything so Matt sees that I get
genuinely aggravated when New Orleans wins the game we want the draft pick
stop it yeah what are your guys sincere feelings now that the FBI has come out
and said that all of all of organized sports is a Psyop is there I guess you
haven't really lost interest it hasn't changed my view on it in any way okay
because there's not a single part of what they're saying that I'm surprised
about right I don't know what you're talking about Paul oh that's a just you
know the corruption of betting throughout all the coincides with the
fact that like games are fixed and rigged and yeah fixed by the Mafia
leaning in on on individual players so it's scarier than it being rigged like
ha ha ha they wrote a book of football or something like oh it's scarier yeah
but it's yeah but it's funny so what's crazy to me is specifically the
pitchers indicted for throwing a first pitch ball on purpose right because
that I know it sounds strange but the competitive balance of that is really
funny to me because everyone's happy right so if you're betting the first
pitch is gonna be a strike that's a really hard task for the pitcher right
but the batter also wants the first pitch to be a ball right and and the
other team wants the first pitch to be a ball so the idea that like I'm gonna
throw a ball first the catcher is to just go like oh let me just stick my
glove over here no problem like it's like the ease of everyone making money
off of a first pitch ball is hysterical to me because it's like everyone's like
great that's just easy and fun and for basketball and for basketball it's
hysterical where people are betting unders mean that like I'm gonna go in
and not rebound I'm not gonna grab a ball I'm like that to me is like
hysterical and as you uncover the stories like these are people who are
making a lot of money suddenly making money on like dumb bets that don't pay
in the in the arena of the money that they're making right and so like one of
the players it turns out like he just had never paid his taxes on his crazy
NBA salary and had just a crazy ass tax lien that he was trying to get out of
and so that's why he got into it people being roped into illegal poker games
the poker game thing with like Chauncey Billups and all those yes that's that's
bizarre and what this one Paul no so it's literally like sports celebrities
luring just other motherfuckers into playing poker games with them and then
not playing an honest poker game yeah so so illegal poker yes I did hear about
that illegal poker rooms and states that don't have legalized gambling of the
ice poker running illegal poker game so they're running these crazy rooms using
celebrities basketball players to lure in people with money yeah and then using
literally like microchipped cards and like I saw I saw technology I saw like
right they had these glasses on and you could see every card like every card was
clearly visible from the back like I knew what everybody had the whole time
yeah it's wild and I was laughing at someone who's one of those sports
podcast listeners a big card collector and stuff as he goes to card collecting
conventions and he goes I mean I don't want to say nothing but I was wondering
why Chauncey Billups was at every one of these events why is this active NBA
coach and Hall of Fame basketball player finding time to go to every card event
there is he's getting paid like 50 G's each time because coaches make the
fucking doughnuts coaches make millions right so like the idea is no way these
card things are paying and like that's actually worth the time but yes they are
in a way they are in a way yeah right yeah it's just free money that's crazy
what's crazier is the argument so like what happens is this is this is a thing
where both sides think they're totally correct right we should stop all this
legalized gaming gambling on sports it's gonna mess with people's lives right and
then the fucking degenerates that are like no no no by having the best out
there and we and we're catching these these spikes of weird bets we're
exposing what could be happening behind the scenes or off off books and smaller
books other places like you want to keep it out and play in sight you want to
get some I feel like that's a really good point I think it's a good point
with all of them except for first pitch ball that's the only one that I'm like
you just can't everyone's favor to do it like it's just everyone will take it
it's the worst thing what do you think about the always go into game seven
thing or often going to game seven thing oh I don't we've tried to rig that I
don't I don't think those stuffs can be that on that level I don't think things
can be rigged on that level I just don't think that's tough I mean especially
with this World Series which was crazy great the amount of ones I went to
extra innings I mean you can't say let's have one game go to 18 innings when they
have to play the next day at 5 o'clock like yeah no one's writing that right
like no one's Reagan that but the fact that three of the games that went went
to extra innings I think in the World Series including including one literally
literally a bonus game they literally did 18 innings they accidentally played
yeah they don't they played eight games so I think it's just I think it's it's
just a testament to the competitiveness of you know these athletes are still
athletes are they're still psychotic to be professional athlete you have to be a
psycho like we have to remember right so I don't I think you'd only rig it so
much football being the hardest one right like that's the one where like you
you can't oh football is is just impossible to rig the full game without
like truly cooperation well that yeah conspiracy theory level cooperation if
you like leave these real dumb plays where you're like oh that was an
intentional fuck up but the thing is the thing is it's so precious right so like
if you drop a pass on purpose yeah to underperform to pay a bet you you might
get yanked out of a game for good like like like you're right it's so the
marketing that ego for those guys too yeah like the a team maybe scores four
or five times you know an entire game you know they basically get like eight
to ten chances at driving it's just not there's just not enough leeway for
someone to purposefully underperform and then not suffer dramatic professional
consequences for it yeah it's just not it's just not the this is the I mean I
could be proven wrong I would be some of the stuff that's come out it's been
baffling I reserved the right to be corrected but so far I mean look look at
look at me like the Giants are trying the hardest and for three quarters
they'll do well and then for the fourth quarter I guess you could probably
that's your best argument it's that the Giants are paid by the mafia to stop
trying in the fourth quarter there's really not a lot of evidence to support
against that you take that's pride fucking with you that just seems like
it might be true yeah I again I have made good on my promise not to watch any
NFL this season and I haven't but I do see the memes keep coming up in my feed
because I am in the Pittsburgh area and you can't avoid it and it's just every
week I see them I see Steelers shame themselves like stuff like that like
Steelers embarrassed and in primetime and I'm like of course you hired a
schlocky freak to be your new QB they are a confusing team they're confusing
team you ain't kidding why I'm glad I'm not watching this year because it's just
dumb every time they're like these guys are dirt they come out and they score
like a thousand points and they look like a juggernaut and then right you go
like oh I guess they're good and then they're like oh we can't score at all
no no no no ten scoop says the Giants are great it's the damn game that's too
long yeah you're right we've got that fourth quarter out yeah three period
game why don't we just if they just copied hockey to be undefeated three
quarters in my in my family in my family in my family text read my oldest
brother said it he doesn't trust anyone who dies their beard anyway and I said I
feel attacked and then the goes right though and the coach got fired and I
this week and I just thought up it's bad week for the beard die boys bad bad one
my brothers and beard die beard die that that that that adds up quick man that
ain't cheap yeah no it's not like cologne you know I actually you should
see that I just bought a $7,000 case for my beard tie for my just for men right
in yeah yeah yeah yes different beard dies for different events well some days
you're going all gray some days you're going and instead of having like a one
through ten for the for the for the for the case lock it's just different jewels
right it's just diamond real jewels yeah yeah it's all hold your eight dollar
just for men okay that's right that shit is such a mess to do too I've only done
it like twice yeah I was in 50 shades I was using the brush and stuff and that
was easier so III do I do both yeah now we're getting into yeah now we're
getting into it I the the brush in one can feel like a little a little cakey on
the yes it definitely does and so I find it like makeup yeah I find it hard to go
to bed right like oh yeah you got to watch that shit off your face right but
then you're trying to scrub it and when you do comb in beard die when is it
washed like when is it done I don't like I don't have a base of all white you
know what I mean so like right I just simply go from yeah it'd be easy for me
there's there's my all white beard then I go to bed with like a big scratchy face
but it looks so much better the the the comb and beard I look so much better
than the just for men died it does look sharp right yeah someone pointing out
just for men not the most woke name and the modern selling points right yeah
just for men I mean that's just uh that's just on them they're just they're
just losing money by still having it called just for men right yeah that's
the whole that's the whole men problem thing that it's all just you heard that
whole crazy thing with the the the art gallery and the ladies her art project
was a women's only club and yes yeah it was that was fast no wait let me it's
something to do with a bathroom yes yes yes I think about think about it let's
do a let's do a sponsor and then we'll and then we'll do this when we get back
it's someone yeah so someone someone in the chat chief you can dig it up there's
a woman got in trouble for putting a women's only art gallery together but
she did in response to a bathroom controversy someone could find that and
post a link idiot basically proved her point over and over again yes yeah yeah
it's a good story and I want to get the details right so yes if someone wanted
to post a link to that I'm going to go to our following sponsor today's show
introducing the forest gump vibrator get get off from coast to coast with one of
two settings the intermittent stutter vibe or the more regular never-ending
strip menus setting ping-pong paddle shaped to focus on that special spot
thwap that twat new random setting lasts your session wait let's your session be
a box of chocolates leg braces sold separately warning knock recommended for
use on a park bench this person did the whole ad they didn't Paul you don't
think anything right they wrote the whole thing I got it yeah it's a super
trooper scoop in 2024 mom always said life is like a box of dildos you never
know what you're going to get this here one is called the forest plump it's all
about girth you can inflate it to three times its normal size once inserted use
it at your discretion lieutenant Dan has one that he puts in his
butt lieutenant Dan boy lieutenant Dan is fun at parties he's easy to get at
because he ain't got no legs enter hey scoops to check out I put a vibrator up
his butt a museum in Australia oh I didn't I did a bad job of 46 ish great a
museum in Australia is being forced to allow men into art into an art exhibit
originally conceived for women only after a tribunal ruled discriminatory following
a complaint by a disgruntled man who was designed a denied entry right let's see
so Tasmania's Museum of old and new art Mona has been ordered to stop refusing
entry to persons who do not identify as ladies to its ladies lounge exhibit
within 28 days after ruling was made blah blah blah does it say why she did
it yeah it's hard you have to find out why she did it yeah experimental artwork
by artist and museum curator Kershah K A E C H E L E is billed by the museum as a
tremendously lavish space where women can indulge in decadent nibbles fancy
tibbles and other ladylike pleasures hosted and entertained by the fabulous
Butler some fella from New South Wales had paid the $35 Australian entry fee
it's about $23 US and was barred from entering the exhibit on April 1st last
year so was barred on April Fool's Day according to the documents he said that
made an equal rights argument yeah there you go there's basically there's a
priceless like Picasso was it like in the women's restroom was the her first
argument for putting it as women's only okay but I thought it was done in
response to something but I might be I might be just trying to find it here
yeah Nick Newman you're in the chat unmute yourself if you can are you
walking around where are you I'm here fellas what can I do for you I was
realizing the other night why we came up with the turn barn and you can tell me
if I'm wrong on this all right I'm learning this as you are yeah yeah
because if you said horse house it gets really confusing I'm only gonna call it
the horse house from now on please bring all that hay to the horse house please
built the horse house oh we should call it something else people think sex
workers in my backyard speaking that I just got my tickets to a great show for
January 23rd jokers of magic oh awesome you're coming out oh this is
Lexington you come you'll be back in town I'm back in town and that's my
birthday oh wow we got to go out to your birthday yes do that yeah because you
are now you're at your other horse job right now right you're at the West Coast
where it doesn't rain it does not rain what's what's what's what's the horse
news out there what's what's going on out there on the West Coast you know it is a
whole different ballgame out here this ain't Kentucky kids now Kentucky I
think Kentucky is like very like lavish horse farms a lot of like crazy money
going into these like perfect conditions for horses and that kind of stuff it's
right out there if you're on the West Coast and you have that kind of money
you will buy a two-bedroom house right or groceries different different level
of investment I want to grab like cuz here in Solana Beach it's a it's an
upscale place mm-hmm and I want to grab people by the shoulders and go you know
that very small house you live in you can buy an entire horse farm in Kentucky
that's exactly what happened to Las Vegas post-pandemic before the pandemic
is to say it all the time I was like wait till people from California realize
they can sell one of their houses and buy two out here and then just commute as
needed as soon as the work from home thing took off that's exactly what
happened out here is we can't even get one house in Vegas but we could get one
in Pennsylvania right yeah well it's close to Pennsylvania that West
Virginia is one of the few states that have a uptick in in population because
the one thing people left those these terrifying hell scapes and went to West
Virginia and bought all the land you could have right now the big the big
race out there's the Breeders Cup the Breeders Cup just wrapped up so that it
just the first week in November it wrapped up so that's the world was what
was the big news what was the big scuttlebutt from the Breeders Cup last
minute scratches horses got all the way to the gate and they they were not
allowed to participate because of due restrictions because we have federally
oversight it now we have federal oversight gate it got all the way to the
gate and they were like no not you there's like leading horses off the
track yes and it's like oh okay and then like owners just embarrassing it's
really embarrassing when your horse has to be led off the track by the pony
without a saddle on the reasons the differing reasons but but veterinarians
seeing signs of soreness or or not okay unsound horses but the track that they
run it at the particular track had a problem for a couple of seasons of an
unusual amount of horse deaths not that particular track the okay the track
you're thinking of is Santa Anita which is in Los Angeles oh yes you're right
the track here I have to say has one of the highest safety ratings in the world
it's it's it's San Diego got it okay okay I'm mixing it I'm mixing my West
Coast tracks this track was built how dare you this and I'm Paul if you want
to warm up this track was built on in 1939 on a loan taking against taken
against the life insurance policy of Bing Crosby that's true so somebody just
bet against being living and won 100% they shorted being Crosby's life
insurance to build this track how does that even work it was a friend his name
Pat O'Brien so I'm fucking friend yeah very buddy boy I gotta let you know this
cough isn't getting any better go ahead and take a shot
hey that sounds well all right nobody I've said it for years nobody does a
better Pat O'Brien impression the Nicholas that's it oh I like it let's
have some more horses coming up and they're wearing makeup like a beat-up
person just like just don't mind me I'd sure like to race today I just fell
down the stairs fell in the paddock you know what I I should have cooked the
dinner right I should have cooked the oats right oh you you don't know Bob
Baffert like I do he can change I can change them everyone the other claim to
fame of this of this track is that this is the place where Chris Jenner and
Robert Kardashian first met oh so everybody brings it up like that's this
boy is that what's going on I didn't hear you go ahead is is it an old cursed
Indian burial ground as well is that what's going on with that fucking place
kind of might as well be it was fucking Shawnee ghost popping up in the middle
race during World War two this track was used as a as a plane wing assembly
factory where was the where was the fancy wing assembly factory that is a
really interesting Beverly Hills here in Del Mar that's a really interesting
tidbit I wonder what they use Santa Anita for and then everybody immediately
was like don't ask so then I looked it up and it's like oh what was it it was an
internment camp yeah and I was like well that's not that's good not gonna be on
the tour that they at least get to race the horses so what were the big horses
that won and should we keep keep an eye on them for upcoming not for long
episodes and then also what was the attendance like oh absolutely so the
attendance was was was like a thousand down from land from last year okay a
thousand fewer guests which is hardly noticeable in a place like that you're
talking about sixty three thousand people over two days okay okay okay okay
and then the so your current world champions are the Japanese are the
current world champions of horse racing oh they the the current world champion is
a horse named forever young from from Japan okay did Japanese horses usually
do well in these races so I last year they sent 19 horses to this event and
and they won none of the 14 races no that's a tough that's and I said they
could have sent 19 hermit crabs and got the same result so this year guess who
called Newman's bluff and sent 19 hermit crabs literally they can't they sent nine
horses this year and just absolutely crushed oh wow okay all right well then
that's exciting we'll have to look out for so they're figuring it out and then
I I got to briefly talk to micropoly listen to not for long micropoly is a
real character a real treasure so Mike on Twitter has named himself the
commissioner of horse racing yes good good categorize himself as a real
disruptor of the space as he walked by me we made knowing eye contact and I
said hey good luck commish three paths on the back and a smile so that's there
you go he got so Frankie to Tory had himself a nice weekend Frankie to Tory
this is the best thing if you again not for long podcast that the shirt tries
to make it crazy that Frankie's still racing at his age and then we find out
that it's very common for racers to race at his age they say down those lock and
he's just trying to clutch at any opportunity he gets and he ends up
working with Bob Baffert one of the world's famous trainers and they give
them a horse in the Breeders Cup so it's like really that's the it's the last the
last that's that hard Scrabble Road we're following with him he's just
falling on hard times but possibly due to his suspension and we will just say
for legal purposes made up the fact that we also think he's a coke head and so we
often make jokes about that as well total fabrication we're just a comedy
show we're just a comedy show we're just wacky we're wacky guys we made Robin
Lee to cut the maniac we just do these things and so we can't be held
responsible for things that we make up Frankie to Tory's bread surrogate so
Frankie he would never eat bread that guy get real that man hasn't seen a carb in
30 years so Frank he did not he was not riding the Japanese horse I imagine he
was not all right. Well, I'm still looking out for that tough luck kid. I
feel like he's still going to find a place to shine. He's going to land on
his feet somewhere all four of them.
Well, thank you. Thank you Newman for I want. I wanted my Breeders Cup update. Oh
wait. Also, how's the how's the horse you and my dad bought claims in as that
horse still training well looking for that first start should be fine at that
point your dad's gonna have a lot of fun with that it should be fun. What's the
site you guys went to? Yeah my racehorse.com. My racehorse.com you can buy really small
shares micro shares of racehorses so my dad owns like a hundred twenty dollars a
hundred twenty dollars share of like a five hundred thousand dollar horse. Is your
father the world's oldest brony at this point? My dad? Yeah. World's oldest like
that's the world's oldest brony. He's basically a My Little Pony fanboy. Yes.
He's basically living out of My Little Pony fantasy. This is amazing. Yes. Yeah.
Does he have does he have a small statuette replica of the horse? That's
how I should get him for Christmas. Actually get him a custom pony. Get him a
little get him a My Little Pony with whatever share it is like one you know
three thousand. Do they do some horse hair in an envelope? My Little Ponies
like they do custom the the if only there was a way that you could figure
that out. Oh my god. What's Briarfest? Okay so Briar horses are the the
collectible horse action figures. What? They're made by the Briar company and
they're not getting into that. I dodge that fucking bullet. I bet. And they have a
full-blown like week-long festival for these plastic horses here in Lexington
every year. Oh my gosh. And they are fanatical. To the point where we think
about closing to tours during that time. Oh there's so many people come out for
the for the for the horses for the toy horses. They will they'll buy two hotel
rooms at the Clarion and they will get permission to remove the furniture from
one of them and set up. And they just turn it into a store. A store for people who will do your your
plastic horse's hair for you like a salon. Yes dude. On their website they've got like
pictures of these of these this horse that they are I guess introducing the
2026 Briarfest celebration horse Corgi Hill Flinka. And it's a real horse. Yeah yeah
it's just a picture of a real horse and then right below it they've got like the
plastic things that they've made of that horse. And they and the kids I give to
their credit they did a good job. The adults will fist fight over that horse.
Right. I can't picture someone getting their horse's doll's hair done to
present it to another person like huh. Oh you can't. They have they have a
legitimate show. Let me bring you into my world. Wait but do you show off the grooming of the hair of your
figures? It's all about customization. Yep. So you get your base you get your base
bucks yo like this is your standard buck and then it's all about people who can
trick these things out. There's a guy I follow on YouTube. His channel is Mr.
Home Arcade. This cat has got money and he gets four of everything basically. Yeah.
And he also pays all these other awesome creators to send him customs. So the
stuff that he has is one-offs, totally unique, but really cool, really well done.
But a lot of it is you take the base figure and then just build on it from that.
Yeah yeah yeah. So it's all about that base. True or false Newman? One of the
biggest Briar collectibles is just a Catherine the Great with her legs wide
open. Catherine the Great playset would sell like hotcakes. Talking about fist fights. That is the longest, saddest fist fight.
There's gonna be two punches. Me hitting you and you hitting the band. Me hitting you and me hitting your surface.
And yes Scoop Jesus with legs wide open. But they do like custom saddle readers. A person making tiny little
saddles out of real leather. See that's where that's when it gets really yeah
yeah yeah yeah. See with with the Masters of the Universe especially, that's my forte, it gets to
like characters and people that were featured in the cartoons that have never
been made into figures. Which that's getting that list is getting smaller and
smaller and smaller. Of course. But there are still some and these
people want these one-off figures. It's been their dream like oh I really want
this figure from this episode and if it's never been made people will make it.
But then the interesting thing is the fandom will respond and if it's a nice
enough custom and enough people go oh well I really wish I had that figure too.
Mattel follows those boards and they build out figures based on fan demand
and that's how we get a lot of these really rare weird one appearance. I'm
telling you right now the person making custom leather saddles for those Briar
outfits doesn't know that there's a whole battle cat saddle universe out
there. Oh yeah I don't know I thought they might be they might know they might
know. Looking at some of those Mondos but but that's it that's the fact too is I
would not be surprised if some of those what do you call that Newman the whole
ensemble. I guess it's a lot of livery right? The tack. The livery the tack is
that what it's called? It can be livery yeah. So that would encompass the what
the Jockey rides, what the Jockey wears, the colors. Oh that's livery for sure yes. And then the
saddling and all that kind of stuff would be tack. So I mean I'm gonna go out
on a limb and say there's probably been an occasion where a model tack maker has
inspired a real-life replicae. Oh sure oh yeah I'm sure I was worried we were
gonna look at this like as a strictly parasitic relationship but no no no it's
copacetic. What are you talking about? I agree symbiotic. Symbiotic yeah not copacetic. Yeah yeah yeah no these guys these guys
absolutely inspire you know the the big boys to make the big toys. That's how it
goes. Alright does have three battle cat saddles already you're right Rich Scoob. I
have more than three. So past Breeders Cup how long is your season out there
Newman? I'm getting right ahead home just for it to be cold in
Kentucky. And then what's the next big race on the radar for possible
Triple Crown people because the Breeders Cup starts at all right? The Breeders Cup
starts at all the Breeders Cup Juvenile starts at all and then the next in March
there there are some there are lots of there's the the Arkansas Derby there's
the Rebel Stakes there's a Florida Derby but what everybody's really got their eye
on because of the international horses that are making a bigger impact is that
the Dubai World Cup the the United Arab Emirates Derby is probably gonna be the
next. Oh that's that's early early March. Okay flying horses makes me scared. Mayor
Force One. So cuz dude do Americans set up their best horses to Dubai or is it
all cautious thing? Oh always. You said a horse flight's the most boring flight
in the world right? I hate it so much. Well it's not that boring it's like a
it's like fucking Russian roulette the way you described it. Yeah standing on
there with with a knee with a put down and a dope up in both hands. It's almost always a very
boring flight. It's the ride of your life. That that reminds me of how I used to
describe being a fireman. Oh yeah. It was just long periods of just complete
boredom and then every once in a while it goes freestyle crazy. So that's about
what it is. Okay back to chili. I forgot about the
put down juice Paul. How could you? You can murder a horse at 30,000 feet that's
amazing. Numerous times someone has spent tens of thousands of dollars to ship a
horse to somewhere and have it arrive dead. That's what has happened.
The numbers not zero. And you know what else that makes me sad about that is just like my
recent experience with the injected dye. I'll wager that if you put death juice
in a horse you can't really go glue or meet with that bad boy either. That's
pretty best. You're pretty much just throwing him on a fire pit or great
question Paul. Nick how edible is a horse after you kill it? So it's okay. Yeah all
right. The half life's pretty low. Well it's kind of like how much rat feces
they'll let into a McDonald's hamburger. How much phenylbarbatol they'll
allow into an average mix of puppy chow. I don't know what's going on. Skippy's
just kind of logy today. He got his breakfast. I don't know. Ate a lot of horse meat. He had his
purina. He had his kennel ration. I don't know. Thank you Newman. Thank you Newman. We're going to do a little Jack vs. Nerd.
Buddy thank you guys. Go get them. Purino failure. Here we go.
Jack vs. Nerd. Explosion. Of irradiated horses. Oh they didn't make it. Oh that's too bad. Man I paid a lot of money for this
flight. Do I get any of that money back or anything? Oh no no no no. Oh I guess
you did transport the horse. That is that is all I paid you to do.
That seems only fair. By the way the ladies lounge is the name of the
Tasmanian Museum Mona. It's the name of the art installation in Mona. It was
ruled illegal by the the first judges who dealt with it. It has gone through to
the Tasmanian Supreme Court who did uphold the legality of the exhibition's
women-only policy. There are now ways that men can see it. There are a couple
different ways that they've made it so that male visitors can go in and
see the display. It features what you were saying Matt. It features
expensive jewelry and art including Picasso canvases as a comment on sexism
and historical exclusion. Though some pieces were later revealed to be fakes
or replicas. I guess you're making the point. Yeah that was it. He
inadvertently made the point of you know how dare you exclude me. Oh yeah. Meanwhile
women have been excluded from male spaces forever and there are still so
many of those things still on the books today. Yeah so it's almost like that guy
didn't didn't get it. He didn't. He really didn't. We got a scooper coming to us today from
Canadian Scoop Crystal. Canadian Scoop Crystal sent a whole email along with
this. We will get to that email at a different show. I've got it set up in the
queue. This is a scooperty all about Canada. It's provinces, Canadian singers,
Canadian actors/rests. Actresses. Oh that makes sense and animals. Oh it's me first.
I'll try animals for 200. What animal is found on our nickel and started the fur
trade? I mean your mom. Oh it's your mom and it's her beaver because it's also a
beaver. It's her mom's beaver. It's the beaver. Matt you're up. I will take actors. For 200. What
actor is known for humor superhero movies and was the world's second highest
paid actor in 2020? I was the second highest paid actor during COVID. Ryan
Reynolds? That's probably my guess. Oh it is Ryan Reynolds. Good job. Paul. I'll go
singers. For 200. What Canadian band wrote the theme for the song, the theme
song for the Big Bang Theory? That would be Bare Naked Ladies. The Bare Naked
Ladies. Look at us, three for three on Canada. We're so much better on Canada than
we were on the other country the other day. It's almost like it's closer to us.
Let's see I'll try provinces 200. What province has a significant cultural
heritage shaped by its long history of fishing, whaling, shipbuilding, and funny
accents? Oh wait is this the is this the Newfies? Is this the Newfoundland?
Newfoundland yes. The Newfies. Matt. All right we've cleared out the 200s guys.
It's anyone's game. Yep. I will do actors for 400. Who started out as a model on
home improvement and is now acting on Broadway? Broadway? Broadway. Shoot there
are so many there was three three different models but is Pam Anderson on
Broadway right now? I think so. Is Pam Anderson on Broadway? Yeah Pam Anderson.
Pam Anderson is correct. I don't know what she's doing on Broadway but I didn't
know she was on home improvement. Yeah. Was the whole thing with her and Liam
Neeson was that completely staged or was that partially real or does anybody know
did it ever come out? As far as I know it's real. Are they still together? Oh see
as far as I know it was staged. Well I we actually I thought about trying to even
have him come on but I know one of the writers of the movie. Okay. I know who
wrote Airplane and he says it's legit. Oh well there you go. But it's also in his
interest to say it's legit. Sure. That's fair. Paul you're up. I'll go with
Canadian singers again. For 400. This singer started her career at 16 and has
won 10 Junos, a Canadian Music Award and nominated for eight Grammys. Now Canadian
Scoop Crystal I recognized you felt like you had to tell us what a Juno was. You
had to tell us that it was a Canadian Music Award and you were correct. You did need to tell us that.
100%. Alanis Morissette. Alanis Morissette is incorrect. It's Avril Lavigne. Avril Lavigne. The other one.
The other one. There's a bunch. I'll try Animals for 400. What urban animal plagues
most cities especially here in Canada that we created a sidewalk memorial to
one? Most cities especially here in Canada. Okay is this gonna be like a rat
or is it gonna be like a moose? I think because it's Canada. I think it's a
raccoon. Oh or a raccoon yeah. Raccoons are big in Canada. They had a cartoon called
the Raccoons. It was mostly it was made by a Canadian animation house. All right
well I'll pass cuz I have no idea. Okay. Matt. Matt passes to you. I don't know. I
mean I want to guess pigeon but. Oh that's a good guess too. Oh yeah yeah. The
chat wants me to say raccoon. I'll pass. Paul. I will go with raccoon. Raccoon is correct.
Matt you're up. Provinces for 400. What province is home to the to the large
nickel a wonder of the world and is surrounded by most of the world's fresh
water? Pass. Passes to Paul.
Nova Scotia. I'll pass. That passes to me. I is it Ontario? That was gonna be my guess.
Ontario right? Yeah. I should have guessed it. I should have guessed it. I should have. I'm an
idiot. I'm a weak weak person. Well we both passed on Raccoon. I wasn't passing
on Ontario. There you go. That's true. Paul. I'll go Canadian actor. For 600. Daily double. Oh here it is. Now the real money.
Redemption tour. What actor is Canadian and known for being optimistic despite
his diagnosis that he has a foundation for in finding a cure? That'd be Mr.
Michael J. Fox. Michael J. Fox is correct. Yeah. I always forget that he's
Canadian. Yeah he seems too aggressive. Agreed. Agreed. I'll try I don't know.
Animal. 600. Other daily double. Whoa man now the scales are flipping. What
Canadian animal was adopted by a vet and ended up in a zoo in London, England to
inspire a writer to create a beloved character?
What Canadian animal was adopted by a vet and ended up in a zoo in London,
England to inspire a writer to create a beloved character? Okay this is a real
this is a real long way to get Canadians credit for this famous English character.
It's Bullwinkle. A moose. It's just a moose. The moose and squirrel. Let's see
there's Bullwinkle. There is whether like beloved animals could come out
of their London. Is this a bear? Is this a bear? Is this a bear? I don't think it's
Oh it could be Paddington. Paddington bear is mine. I'll say a bear. I'll say it's a
bear. It's Paddington bear. Oh Winnie the Pooh. Winnie the Pooh. You should just stay with bear buddy.
I should have just said bear. Why didn't I just say bear? I should have just answered the fucking question. Matt you're up. If I just answered the question I would have got the right. I don't
know Winnie the Pooh is British. Christopher Robin that very American
name. Yeah yeah apple pie Christopher Robin. Okay I think I'm gonna go with
singers. For 600. What country artist once worked at McDonald's starting
writing songs at age 10 and was forced to take a hiatus from music due to vocal
issues caused by Lyme disease. We all know this famous Lyme disease McDonald's
worker. You worked at McDonald's at age 10? No he started writing at age 10. I'm trying
to remember. I don't know pass. This country artist was forced to take a
hiatus from music at age 10 due to Lyme disease. Paul? She was a Christian singer
and then not I think. Okay. That's who I'm thinking of. Amy fuck. Amy fuck. No. Show me
Amy fuck ah it's not what is her name Amy fuck fuck fuck fuck Amy fuck fuck fuck fuck Amy fuck fuck fuck fuck the chat is trying to help you again Paul if you want to look at the chat and cheat it's right there I'll pass well I mean yeah but I'm gonna I'm not gonna cheat oh that passes to me I have no idea and I can't see the chat so I pass oh that was wrong that was the other one I was thinking of the Amy fuck of country music
well she thought Amy fuck wouldn't sell records as you change her name she was wrong imagine my career that Shania Twain could have had as Amy fuck my favorite joke one of my favorite jokes is you know Shania Twain's not a real
name it's shenaniel Clemens that's such a good joke that's a really good one shenaniel Clemens oh fuck me that's not a real name at all shenaniel Clemens I will close out Canadian singers Paul you closed out Canadian singers what band is a
Canadian indie band known for neighborhood rebellion and black mirror fuck I don't know pass oh shit it passes to me oh I think I do know well what is it my only guess would be Our Lady Peace but I can't answer it in good
conscience because I don't like them but I don't think they're indie they're pretty big I don't know I don't even know what makes an indie band indie anymore it seems like half the indie bands are
signed to record labels and I don't understand how that works I'm passing to Matt this is obviously Brian Adams guys oh no no pass pass oh it's Arcade Fire oh they're an indie band they're indie and a Canadian I didn't know they were
indie I'm Canadian for that matter it's all crazy to me it's me I'll try animals for 800 what animal medium sized wild cat character's eyes a character character's eyes by long dense fur triangular ears with black tufts at the tips and
broad snowshoe like paws is that a Lynx that sounds good to me I'll go Lynx oh my goodness Jacob Tari's failed system let's do a score check Jacob score check Paul and I are tied in the lead with 800 a piece but Matt is right on our heels with 600 there aren't anymore
daily doubles left but there are three questions left provinces for six and eight hundred and Canadian actors and actresses for 800 it's gonna be tough you're up hmm do I want to leave the two province questions for you two or not let me just remind you that I got Ontario I'll take
Canadian actors please for 800 who had a career spanning 60 years he appeared in more than 100 films and 150 television programs portraying more than 220 actors and our characters and died in 2010 I have to remember a Canadian actor who died in 2010 that's that is precisely what the question is asking you to do yes I'm just okay where was I in
2010 and let me try to picture when I was grieving that loss of Canadian actors let's see I had been really upset about 9/11 for nine years at this point I can't I pass I can't I can't Paul John Candy died before that right yeah yeah I think so
yeah who else is kind of like John Candy lemurs screamer creamer says or name one of the 220 care oh man it's red green no I have to pass I don't know it passes to me I definitely know this but I'm passing anyway out of sportsmanship Leslie Nielsen
oh that was who I was thinking of who hilarious but I was like no you just have airplane on the brain because the earlier questions oh it is Leslie Leslie Nielsen okay yeah that was thinking of that's so funny Wow there you go could have one to cost me the game guys cost me the game well Paul and I could both miss our questions Paul you're up gamesmanship I have to go for 800 800 going for the win what is the most recently added territory to Canada it was added in 1999
oh my goodness it's just it's just I gotta go Edmonton Alberta it's just some town in Vermont that everyone's really nice it's Detroit you're going Edmonton Alberta yes I just said Paul all right none of it none of it none of it none of it damn it and Jacob closing out the category and the game provinces for 600 will Jacob win this game
who knows what provinces home to the world's largest hockey stick it was
originally created for the expo 1986 huh Oh pass it Jacob is Montreal a city or a province mmm great question I think Montreal is wait is Quebec a province shit in Montreal part of Quebec
isn't that the province I think it is I'll say Quebec British Columbia well played I really have to say this might be one of my least impressive wins
and I owe it to just the fact that Jacob could just just passed fun to guess it is it is game but my my passivity is never you know weaseled me out more than this is this game scooper to eat such a weasel yeah I had two right answers in my head and didn't even guess them
Uh-huh. So I know that was the right strategy. Ah, you got it though. That's from Canadian
Scoop Crystal. Thank you Canadian Scoop Crystal. I'm going to get your email later. Your email
is in my queue here. If you want to send us a price of Skrite Jock vs. Nerd, an Obelisk
Jock vs. Nerd, or a Scoopity Jock vs. Nerd, just like the one you just heard, head over
to HayScoops.com. HayScoops.com, right there on the homepage. You can also send us an email
to be read as part of Scoop Mail. But yeah, do all those things over there at HayScoops.com.
We need some more games to play, so head over there, make us some Jock vs. Nerd games and
send them on in. We'd love to hear from you. Yeah. I want to thank all the people who support
us on Patreon. We'll be getting our lists together soon, I hope. Me too. Me too. But
yeah, it's normal to read the thank yous for everyone who supports us, and we really appreciate
it so much. And we've got a lot of new signups, so we have a lot of new people to thank, which
is also awesome. Yes. Welcome all of our new patients as well. We're very excited about
that. But you can join the ranks of our supporters by going over to PreachingFun.com.
Or if you, like me, found out today that Bing Crosby is entirely responsible for the Kardashians,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz. That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com. It takes
you over to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this
show on the air. The reason we were able to do this show is because of our Patreon supporters.
So if you would like to join their ranks, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those
are the places you can go if you think this show is worth more than $0. If you can't go
over to those places and do any monies, just tell people about us. Be part of our Obelisk
scheme. Tell one person, one person only, if you tell more than one person, it's a pyramid
scheme. That is unethical. We don't do that. We do an Obelisk scheme. You tell one person,
one person only, they tell one person only. Find that person that you think is going to
really dig on this weird thing that we've got going on over here. Let them know and
help us out. And always subscribe and review. Leave us those five-star reviews. They really
help us.
Mike Lush, thank you for becoming an Ice Cream Truck Driver.
Thank you, Mike.
Yeah. Just that email in the hopper. All right. Thanks for listening, everybody. Stay safe
out there. We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
[Music]