(upbeat music)
Oh, hello there.
I am so glad you are here
because I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Well, those are the folks to deliver that fucking ice cream
straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now, I'd like to thank
Darth Scooper,
David Walker,
Ted Laszlo,
Dirty Old Scoop,
Dr. Scoop Little,
and Elton Magic Scoop.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver,
just like these fine folks,
head over to preachingfun.com
that's where you can go to sign up
to be an ice cream truck driver
and who knows,
the life you save.
Ah, the fade out button didn't work.
It was the--
(laughing)
- That was the stop button?
- To be fair, to be fair,
I suppose the fade out button might work.
I haven't tested it,
but the stop button works effectively.
- Okay, good.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- The stop button works just fine.
- I literally was like, wait, do you have to start over?
Like, what's happening?
- No, no, no.
I'm covering it with all of this.
See, nobody even noticed it
because I covered the lack of a music fade
with this clever banter.
(laughing)
- Hey, Johnny,
do you want to go to an ice cream social?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Great, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- Oh, I'm so excited, guys.
We're broadcasting from Core Sensors
in Morristown, New Jersey.
(laughing)
I'm in a conference room.
- Yo, very nice cabin.
- Yeah.
- Nice cabin in the cabin.
(upbeat music)
- It's time for Matt Godley's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Jersey, it's Matt Godley.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Vegas, it's me,
taking the audio guide.
We're preaching fun.
- Oh, that's where you're wrong.
I don't know if I can break a computer with that.
- I couldn't see, what's in there?
- Pressure sensors and pressure transducers.
- That's what's on display.
- That's what's made and sold here.
- Do you have an in with the pressure sensor
and transducer mafia?
- I do.
- What's going on?
- Who's your hookup?
- I've been connected to the pressure transducer industry
for quite some time.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
- Who's your pressure transducer pimp?
- Who's your pressure transducer guy, Matt?
- One of my original roommates
in my party house of Fort La Forge, my buddy Sam.
- So the ones that are on display in that cabin.
- Where was this one last week
when I was like, I need new pressure transducers.
Where were you then?
- I don't want you to take it up my supply.
- Come on.
- The ones that I'm seeing in that cabinet,
are those on display as check out the hotness
or are they our vaunted history?
What is this?
What am I seeing?
- I don't even know.
I wasn't given a clue.
- Or are they free samples?
- I was, 'cause here's the thing.
So my buddy Sammy, it's his company.
I'm staying at his house.
His office is closer to my magic show
that I have to literally, as soon as we wrap,
I'm leaving and going to do two magic shows.
- Oh, okay.
- And he said, "And the internet's stronger here."
So he said, "Let's just sit you up in my conference room."
- What a nice guy.
- Yes, he's a very nice guy.
And so, yeah, I did not get the two penny tour though.
So I'm very curious myself as to what is on display
on these shelves as well.
- And I assume when you leave,
you will be given several pressure transducers.
- Oh yeah, I gotta bring the kids home.
There's something.
- Does he end every sales call?
Does he end every sales call with, "No pressure."
(laughing)
- No, no, no, no.
- Good, 'cause that would be the end of his business.
- He did tell me something.
So he gets, you know, he's a business owner.
He gets cold called all the time and spam called.
- Sure.
- Ah.
- He found out if I should betray this or not.
- Oh shit, here we go.
Getting the fucking pressure sensor tea, y'all.
- There it is.
♪ Do, do, do, do, do, do, do ♪
♪ Pressure ♪
♪ Pressure sensor, talk ♪
♪ Talk and pressure, sensor, sensor, pressure ♪
♪ Pressure sensor ♪
- So--
- It's our new segment on the show.
- If you're spam called by someone in India.
- Uh-huh.
- There's a term, you can use an insult in India
that basically makes people break script
and either curse you out or hang up on the spot.
- Wow.
- No.
- Yes.
- There's a magic super curse
that we could be using this whole time?
- Yes.
And it basically translates to basically sister fucker.
Like you're--
- Okay.
- You fuck your sister.
- It's a good one.
- So we're implying that they have more fun
than they're comfortable having, is what you're saying.
- It's pronounced, you know, Ben shot.
That's how you pronounce, that's the term.
So right now we just got--
- What did you say to me?
- Exactly, we just got flagged.
- We apologize to our Indian listeners right now
who are zooming into their phones.
- We just got, and he indeed proved it to me.
He took a spam call while we were having breakfast.
- Huh?
- There was someone trying to buy his home.
- Uh-huh.
- And they said how much?
And he goes, "About 140, 150 Ben shots."
And the person hung up the phone immediately.
- Hilarious.
(laughing)
150 Ben shots.
This is one of those terrible things
because on one hand I feel it's a little punching down
because the person running the phone
isn't the asshole who's doing all of the shitty things,
but they are the one actively doing it.
So it's, yeah, I don't know.
I do like it though.
I like having a magic word just in these phones.
- It's a good solution, nobody gets hurt.
- I've been getting a lot of phone calls lately
from numbers that I don't have saved,
so I've been answering unknown numbers
when they're popping up.
And yeah, so I've been getting hit
with a couple of good spams lately.
And I'm glad to have a code.
- I really couldn't believe it.
- Yeah.
- When I saw it in action, I was like, "Oh my gosh."
- Yeah, I'm seeing in the chat with a T,
it's with a D, shah-duh.
- Oh, shah-duh.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Which part of it is, is it a direct translation?
Does shah-duh mean like fucker?
- I mean, I think like it's like a, to a degree,
like the ultimate degree, right?
- Okay.
- Like I know like in Italian you can say like Blanco
or like, you know, whatever that means white.
But if you say like Blanchesumo,
it means like the most whitest white.
I said that to somebody.
- How do you know that, Matt?
- I was joking with an Italian where I was talking
about whether I was good at basketball like my brother.
And I said, I was not only Blanco, but Blanchesumo.
I was the most white and it made him laugh really hard.
- It's weird that basketball is the place
where we get to talk about race
with the least amount of concern.
- Right.
- No, yeah, yeah. - It's in life.
It's really kind of nice.
- I was, you know, hanging out on the ship.
I just got off yesterday.
And one of the artists was, he was from Israel.
He lives in, you know, the United States currently,
but it was from Israel.
And we were out with a black comedian.
This great comedian named Orlando Baxter.
- Okay.
- And I already had some like weird conversations
with my Israeli friend as he would drift
into certain politics from time to time.
- Oh, he had interesting views
that you didn't necessarily find incredibly comfortable
to talk about?
- Yes.
- Oh, okay, okay, interesting.
- And somehow the topic came over to the Cosby show.
(laughing)
And then the fact that Malcolm Jamal Warner
had died recently.
- Oh, that's right, yeah.
- He had died drowning in--
- Yeah, swimming, yeah, it was terrible.
- Costa Rica.
- Trying to save his daughter.
Did his daughter live?
- I don't know.
- I believe so.
- Okay.
- I'll find out.
- And this person then made a joke
about black people in swimming and I excused myself
from the table and went to the bathroom.
- Oh dear, oh my.
(laughing)
- Because you were laughing so hard
you were gonna push yourself.
(laughing)
- Jesus Christ.
Oh, God damn it, God damn it.
What the fuck is wrong with people?
- No.
(laughing)
And then he brings up that, Orlando brings up
that his wife is indeed a chemist from Harvard
and then my mentalist friend then brought up
that Harvard was supporting genocide in Sudan
and that he should be mad at Harvard.
(laughing)
- And then Matt had to excuse himself again
because he was laughing hysterically again.
- Why, why, who taught you that this is the way
to have conversation?
(laughing)
- All right, this was so similar.
My mom used to teach, when my mom was a college professor
she would teach all of these international students
and it was not uncommon around the holidays
for an international student or eight
to show up at the house for the big holiday meal
because she would invite them over
because they didn't have family or whatever in the area
to go spend the holidays with.
And there was this cat one time,
never saw him again, never met him before
but he was just an Israeli student of my mom's
and I remember his, because he was Israeli,
he had been in the Israeli military
before coming over to the US to go to college
and his job in the Israeli military had been peel potatoes.
He had worked as a cook and so he was like,
I peel thousands of potatoes a day,
let me peel the potatoes for dinner,
I can peel them instantly and he could.
We gave him a potato peeler at first
and he was like, I don't know how to use a potato peeler,
I just need a knife.
And so I got him like a little paring knife
and he peeled enough potatoes for like,
there were probably 20 of us at the house that day,
he peeled enough potatoes for everyone
in like a minute and a half, it was incredible to watch.
- That's awesome.
- But I was over there, I was probably in junior high,
maybe young high school or something like that
and I was over there and he was telling me about
like Israeli military and telling me jokes
about Israeli military or jokes
that they would tell each other in the Israeli military.
And yeah, as a young teenager, I was like,
I need to not be in this conversation,
this guy is saying things that I am not.
This is his thing, I'm gonna go piss myself in the bathroom.
- He has forgotten the first rule, the potatoes have eyes.
- That's right.
- You can't just go around behaving however you want
around the spuds, yes.
- Malcolm Jamal's, Warner's daughter was saved,
she was saved by a surfer, so yeah, she was okay.
- Cowabunga, dude, what happened to Theo?
No way, gnarly.
- Matt, were there any jokes you wanted to repeat
about Theo Huxtable drowning?
- No, no, no.
- Oh, interesting, okay.
- No, I didn't think of any in the bathroom
when I walked away.
I didn't think of any.
- Oh God.
- I just saw a preview for something last night
with Malcolm Jamal Warner in it,
and I was like, oh shit.
- Oh no, yeah, yeah.
- Was it the ocean?
- I know, that was what it was, it was Davy Jones locker.
- Yeah, no, no, that wasn't even
the only awkward conversation.
- Oh, I'll bet, I'll bet, I'll bet.
- It wasn't even the most awkward conversation.
- You know, if I gave a damn enough to wanna talk to people,
I'm sure I'd have a lot of fuckin' awkward conversation.
- Right, right.
- I don't push myself, you're a bold man.
Also, you're stuck on a boat, it happens on boats.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can't, you know,
we all have to like, what am I gonna do,
like, you know, get irate and then spend the last three days
giving someone the silent treatment
for not walking around the ship?
- Yeah, and you're gonna see 'em every five minutes.
- Yeah, exactly.
- You're playing pinball with people on the ships.
- Yeah, yeah.
- No, no.
Oh, speaking of awkward conversations,
I forgot to talk about this one.
I went out with Rondell Sheridan when we went out.
- Oh, yes.
- We went out, and so we went to a little bar
after the comedy club at the bar.
All the staff wanna take pictures with Rondell.
We get back out on the street,
and the four of us are waiting for an Uber,
and there's a gentleman, like, 10 feet off
of our conversation who just sees us jokin' around.
- Ah, good.
- Decides to insert himself.
- And he was into his cups.
- Oh, yes!
- Oh, dear.
- He was like--
- You met the mayor.
- He was, I met the mayor.
He literally, and he literally just stumbled towards us.
(laughing)
He had this big maroon UMass sweatshirt on over shorts.
- Fuck yeah.
- And he had a perfect newly for my first mustache,
like, 22 years old.
My first bushy mustache-like mustache.
That looked like it was put on by a costume person
and didn't belong on him.
And he literally, while wobbling,
smiles ear to ear and goes, "Can I get in on this?"
(laughing)
- Damn it!
- And that person is a hero.
- Damn it, damn it.
Can I get in on, what the hell?
Can I get in on this?
- Y'all having a good time?
Let me get in on this good time.
- Oh my God.
- You look like a bunch of good time fellas.
Let me get in on this.
- Good Lord, can I get in on this?
- And then like, we just like, I hear that,
but my two friends are still talking,
like, just keep talking, you know?
- Yeah.
- And he's like, and he's just like leaning in
and going, "Uh, yeah."
(laughing)
- Seamless transition.
- Just like, like as if he's like,
camouflaging into a party or something.
But like, it's just the four of us.
- This is great!
- Can I get in on this?
- And the other three are like, just like,
including Ronella, just like, not, like looking at me,
like, I am not engaging this man, right?
But he like, is not gonna get in here.
- Oh, because they don't wanna live.
- And he is staying like, two-dimensionally confident.
Like, he is just still doing like, listening,
like, eyebrows and listening ears and like,
he literally puts like, an arm up like a teapot,
like a teapot arm.
(laughing)
- I am in this conversation.
- Like, uh-huh, uh-huh.
- This is a conversation that I'm gonna be a part of.
- Finally, just go like, all right,
I'm gonna jump on this grenade, I'll isolate.
And I just, I just square to him and I go like,
you doing all right, pal?
You having a good night?
And he's like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah."
You guys seem like a lot of fun.
You guys, you guys like comedy?
I like comedy.
You like comedy?
And I was like, I can't tell whether he is
or isn't making out Rondelle Sheridan or not.
Do you know?
Like, why is this happening?
- As much as I have involved my life with the comedic arts.
- Yeah.
- I have never, ever initiated a conversation
or even said the words, "I am into comedy."
- No. - I don't think.
You know what I mean?
Like, I've never, I've never said that, I don't think.
(laughing)
I mean, I'm into comedy.
You know what I mean?
No, no.
- It's in the same, it's in the same category
as people who criticize jokes right after saying
that they really like to laugh.
You know, I love to laugh, but you know,
this joke just really pushed me in the wrong direction.
- Right, right, right.
- You know, it's that same family.
- Oh.
- My buddy.
- I'm really into comedy.
- My buddy, Tom, noting that I stepped in it,
decides to just push me further in,
and he goes, "Oh, if you like comedy podcasts,
"he knows a bunch of people who do comedy podcasts."
(laughing)
- Oh, hero.
- I mean, this is a guy to chip.
If there was ever a guy to chip, this is a guy.
(laughing)
Get him listening.
- And then I did probably one of the most obnoxious things
I've ever done.
(laughing)
He keeps bringing up famous people that he likes
that are funny from the improv comedy world.
- Good.
- Oh boy.
- Do you remember any of his examples?
- I'm not gonna say examples, I'm gonna tell you what I did.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- I got out my phone and showed that that person
was someone I could call, and then said,
"But we're not gonna call him."
And I would close my contacts,
and he brought up someone else, I go, "Oh, sure.
"Yep, we can call that person too, but we're not gonna,
"you and I are not gonna call that person right now."
(laughing)
- That's a good asshole move.
- That's a hell of a move.
- I just kept showing him all these people I knew
from the UCB theater from back in the day,
'cause that's what we liked from the comedy "Bang Bang"
and other kind of podcast space.
And he literally was like, "Whoa, whoa, whoa!"
- I can't believe it.
- He was like flipping out.
- There's no way this could be faked.
- Exactly, exactly, right?
- There's no way somebody could have these names
stored in their phone without the correct numbers.
(laughing)
- Good point, good point.
I could have just been like, "Sure, Alec Baldwin, here."
You know, whatever, just made a contact.
- Look, it says Alec Baldwin.
- Got it.
- Isn't that the NoteZap?
- Isn't this amazing, though, Matt?
- It's not the NoteZap.
- I'm just thinking this is-
- Matt's NoteZap says, "Alec Baldwin, wow!"
- We're here now, we're here now for phone.
We are fully here now for phone, right?
If I'd done this 30 years ago,
people would have thought I was insane.
- Yeah, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
- This means phone.
- Yeah, oh, you're talking about the gesture
that I'm holding a brick?
- My creepy claw hand means phone.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Matt's just holding up his hand to the camera
like he's holding a phone.
- Yeah, we don't do a hang loose-
- No, we don't do that anymore.
We don't even do hold like a thing, like a receiver type.
We do claw hand.
- But we still do the crank thing for a car window.
- We do somewhat, we do somewhat.
Well, I will say that-
- And of course, we still have the picture
of the floppy disk to save things.
- The car that I have right now-
- Nobody knows what that is anymore.
- The car that I have right now,
which is just about to turn six years old,
or rather 10 years old,
is the first car I've ever had with power windows.
- Uh-huh.
- So, it was only a decade ago.
- Just so you know, if you ever get a text from me
with a celebrity's name on it,
it means you're about to get a phone call
and you're supposed to be that celebrity
when you answer the phone.
- I, oh.
- I would do that in a heartbeat.
I would do that in a heartbeat.
- Deal, deal.
- That's a really good idea.
- That is, yeah, yeah.
- That'd be really fun, actually.
- The three of us need to remember that.
- Yes, yeah.
- We should, we should remember that.
That could be really good.
I did a bit for Teller. - Daniel Craig.
- I did a bit for Teller a couple years ago.
- Oh, this is Daniel Craig, isn't it?
- He had a friend that wanted his kid to talk to Batman.
So I did Batman for the kid.
- That's pretty great.
- He ain't doing it on Batman.
- On a phone call?
Yeah, I did.
- Ask me, Batman, what do you want?
- It was very bail.
It was very bail.
I was like, I understand you can help me find the Joker.
- Oh, nice.
- And I was like, the kid was looking for the Joker
for like a week.
(laughing)
I was like, yeah, totally.
Keep an eye out.
When you're in a parking lot, just scan.
Make sure you look everywhere.
(laughing)
The kid started haunting the Joker.
So yeah, I think that's a good bit, Matt.
- That kid grew up to be an ICE agent.
- Let's start.
(laughing)
- You sent him down the wrong track, man.
- No, I don't know.
I don't think they can find the Joker.
- We have this guy that's gonna change his wife's name
to Bob De Niro on his phone.
That's great.
(laughing)
- Oh, it's me, Bob De Niro, isn't it?
Now they're gonna--
(laughing)
- Gonna get me some bangers and mash 'em, Bob De Niro, I am.
- You guys are just getting better and better
at your PIF impression.
- Yeah, we were just doing PIF the whole time.
- It's true, it's true.
By the way, anybody who goes to see Matt
at any of the magic shows,
if you come see Matt at a Scoop event,
feel free to name celebrities
and see if Matt has the name as well.
(laughing)
- It was obnoxious.
I just, I didn't know how to, like,
he wasn't gonna go away, so I just,
I literally was like, it literally was like shiny keys.
Like, how do I bounce shiny keys in front of his face
to keep him from, I basically was like,
I have to keep him from either recognizing
or festering Rondell Sheridan, is what I was thinking.
- It was probably, also, it was probably
the nicest thing you could do, really.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 'Cause you probably made his day, like, oh!
I'm two degrees from that guy!
- Lemur Screamer Creamer wants Clooney Batman, Paul.
Let's hear on Clooney Batman now.
- I don't know what your game is, Freeze.
(laughing)
- Perfect.
- I don't know what your game is, Robin.
(laughing)
I don't know what you think your game is.
- Batman didn't know a lot of game.
- I don't know what you think your game is, Poison Ivy.
- Jesus, and Myra wants post-cancer Kilmer Batman.
- Jesus.
(laughing)
- It's a lot quieter.
- I don't know what your name is, Robin.
I don't know what your game is, Batman.
Wait, I'm Batman.
(laughing)
I don't know what your game is, Poison Ivy.
- Wait, no, two vays was the one in mind.
Also, the--
- I'll tell you who else definitely did not feel
uncomfortable by that impression,
and that is the following sponsor.
- Today's show is brought to you by Dicks Out for Democracy,
Crouchless Shorts for your next anti-Trump rally.
(laughing)
- Hello, I am Jerry "Daisy" Duke Farlaflon.
And I've started a company--
- Of the Montana Farlaflons?
- The same.
Out here in God's country, we all like to free ball,
but we also don't care for the rubbing of a denim.
So what we've done is we have eliminated the middle man,
literally.
We've cut out the spot where your wiener's at
in all of our jeans.
And I don't sell just jeans.
I sell Daisy Dukes, cut high and tight
to where you can't tell if it's ass or what it is,
because it's so high.
(laughing)
- Ass or other options?
- Right, ass or who can say?
(laughing)
And now we've confused the issue even further
by eliminating more of the material on the jean
to let your dick and balls fly loose.
- That's right.
Go to FreeAsYourOwnBalls.org
and sign up today to get on the mailing list.
We're just pre-ordering them right now.
- There is nothing more democratic
than crotchless Daisy Dukes
and the question of what is that?
Ass or what have you?
- There's a time people debated whether the snake
or the turkey or the eagle was the greatest symbol
of us in our rights when our own free swinging scrotum
was hanging right there the whole time.
- Seriously, it incorporates both snake and eagle.
(laughing)
Because you have the serpent-like phallus
and the comfortable bald nest of the majestic eagle bird.
- America, oh America. - There's nothing more American
than a coiled wiener sitting atop
a pile of fuzzy balls.
- Enter Hay Scoops at checkout, patriots.
- I also would like to endorse this product for the grave.
- Thank you, Val.
- Oh, Val Kilmer, Batman.
- Yes, I wore very tight pants.
I wish I'd had a hole for my ween ween
'cause, boy, I had to hold my pee in a lot.
On most days, many days I couldn't pee.
What's your game, Killer Croc?
- There've been some good drug ads lately.
An acne medication that I saw the other day,
it had a warning that it would just cause eye problems.
Instinct eye problems.
That's all it said was eye problems.
- What is this? - And I thought that was--
- Did I take this medicine?
- It was probably a pall medicine.
It caused eye problems.
And I thought that was gonna be the worst one I saw.
I saw one last night.
I paused it and had to rewind to it.
It caused an increased risk of lower limb loss.
(laughing)
- Lower limb loss.
- But it doesn't say legs.
It just says lower limb.
- And it doesn't say what the loss might be.
'Cause the way it's phrased,
it definitely looks like it's just gonna fall off.
- Wow, and what does the drug help?
- This was a cholesterol medication.
- All right, lucky you.
- Well, I mean, I guess I want that low LDL enough.
I'll give up a foot.
I guess, this seems,
if we're gonna advertise drugs in this country,
the warnings at least have to make sense.
- No, there's no, no, they don't.
- And I know our European listeners are just confused
about drug companies being able to advertise on TV.
We are too.
- It's insane times, man.
It's insane.
I was just seeing somebody talking
about the whole Tylenol debacle, right?
- What do you mean, debacle?
We figured out what causes autism, that's Tylenol.
- Well, this is a cause for celebration.
- The thing that they mentioned,
and I don't know, it seemed to make some sense to me
that they were like,
why wouldn't Tylenol have started a lawsuit by now
if their sales had been impacted in any way?
Apparently, nobody's listening to this bullshit.
Everybody's just still piloting fucking Tylenol.
Right, I mean, we're in the land of commerce here.
That's all that matters is bottom line.
So apparently it's not hitting them
in the pocketbook enough to make them,
'cause there is no more litigious society
than the United States.
- Right.
- So I, you know, I can only, you know.
- Not only has Tylenol stock not dropped,
it is trading near its 52 week high.
- There you go.
So there it is.
Okay. - Yeah.
- It was a brief significant drop in September.
But apparently it bounced right back like the next day.
- Okay.
Interesting. - There you go.
- That is fascinating.
That actually makes me feel good
that it was that dumb that people were like, okay.
- And it also kind of makes me feel good
that they aren't suing.
Like they're like, oh, we can't demonstrate damages.
So I guess we'll just leave this one alone.
- Yeah, that's so strange.
- Oh, I never, Bassey, Bassey in the chat,
just the thing that was created in the '50s
is responsible for something that was discovered in 1911.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
- I need to think about that aspect of it.
That's a fine way to think about that.
- There's not a whole lot of medical research
going on here at all.
- Well, I didn't believe it until now.
I mean, it's not like Bassey's statement
just caused me to shift my opinion on Tylenol.
- Excuse me, excuse me, Jacob.
You're talking, you're talking out of your neck.
I gotta tell you, I'm pretty sure just looking at you,
'cause I could just look at people and diagnose them.
I'm pretty sure that you were circumcised way too early.
That's what I think now.
- Damn it.
- Val Kilmer?
- It's me, Val Kilmer, back from the dead.
(Val laughing)
- Quado from "Total Recall"?
- Watch your game, Freeze.
- He'd be an amazing, he is an amazing villain.
What the fuck am I saying?
He is a fucking Batman villain.
- He is a Batman villain.
- Jesus Christ, we're surrounded by Batman villains.
- And not in the good way.
- No, not, there's nothing fun about it.
- None of them look like Uma Thurman dressed in plants.
- Oh, Uma Thurman.
- No, Uma Thurman.
- Uma Thurman.
- Sorry, everybody, I just got Paul started on jacking it.
He just set him off, everybody, I'm sorry, that's my fault.
I said Uma Thurman.
- Come on.
- I'll be back in five and just a nap on camera.
- So we're getting the house repainted.
It's been crazy out here.
We're trying to juggle, making sure we get home in time
to help them get the stuff they need or whatever,
and, you know, but we're staying out of their way
as best we can, but we gotta put the dogs outside sometimes,
but then the dogs, the stuff's getting painted.
So stuff got painted last night,
right where the dogs were outside,
so we had to lay down some cardboard,
and then the dogs wouldn't go on the cardboard,
so we had to carry the dogs all around.
It was a sight, and had to go get some special new clothes,
'cause she had a special interview come up last minute,
last night, yesterday.
So we were out--
- I thought you meant the dogs were such a mess,
she had to go get new clothes.
Did you do like an '80s movie montage
where you wait outside the dressing room,
and she just kept coming on outfit after outfit,
and you were like, "Yes, no, maybe."
- That's how we do it.
- That's the one.
- Every time we go to Cole's, and I go first into Cole's,
I have her wait in the car, and I go into Cole's first
and grab a couple of scarves and sunglasses,
and I basically transform into the character of Hollywood
from "Mannequin" and "Mannequin 2."
And so I take on this new persona,
and when she comes through the door, I just say,
"Oh my, let's find something for you that will just work."
And then she starts trying things on,
and then as she comes out as Hollywood,
I will then comment and say,
"Well, I guess the 1950s called back."
Something to that effect.
And then she'll come out again and be,
"Oh, goodness, no one told me Ms. Greta Garbo
was going to be in the building."
Huzzah, things like that, things of this nature.
- Huzzah.
- Things of this nature.
- I wonder what percentage of our audience was not alive
when the movie "Mannequin" was released.
(all laughing)
- That makes me scared to think about.
- 'Cause it's not zero, it's not zero percent.
- Yeah, you're right, it's not zero.
- That movie's older than a seat of medicine.
- Someone in the chat says,
"The seat of medicine was actually used back in 1893."
I don't, I mean.
- Whatever.
- I think we can fact-check everything,
including the link between Tylenol and autism.
Is that fair?
- Yeah, missing link.
- Fair.
- The missing link.
- Yeah.
- Nobody thinks that we know what we're talking about.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
I admit it.
- Of course, apparently nobody thinks that RFK
knows what he's talking about either,
since that doesn't affect Tylenol's stock price.
- That's for sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm constantly doing this noise
while I'm going down on Cheryl Hyde's, so she's just.
(laughing)
Her pussy is just full of this voice.
It's hard enough, most men, to find the clitoris.
Her clitoris runs away from my voice.
(laughing)
- All right, Andy Cheek points out
that we have done more research than the government
on the link between Tylenol and autism just here.
I believe that's true.
I believe that is true.
- Agreed to disagree.
(laughing)
- Oh no, he got us.
- What's your game, calendar man?
- Drove through Taco Bell the other night after work,
and the guy on the speaker goes,
yeah, it's like 1 a.m. or so,
and the guy on the speaker goes, hey, how's your night going?
Yeah, it's doing all right, how you doing?
Shitty, man.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
- Thanks for asking.
- So I put my order in, I pulled up to the window,
and this dude just leans out of the window.
He goes, man, I've been having a night.
(laughing)
He proceeds to tell me, just all the jerks
that have pulled up to the Taco Bell drive
through that night.
And he just needed to vent.
- That's amazing that you were there for him.
- I was like, what you got, buddy?
I'm here for you, man.
- I was just talking--
- We just sat and chatted in the drive through
for about five minutes, too.
We had a nice little chat.
He's a good guy.
- We were just talking Taco Bell at work the other day,
and some of my younger coworkers,
I was like, guys, I don't know if you know,
but back in the day, if you spent $20 at the Taco Bell,
you had ordered the entire menu.
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- But now--
- But you can get the big case of tacos.
- Yeah, you can get a box for like $3.
- For like 15 bucks, yeah.
15 bucks for like 16 tacos.
It was crazy.
Yeah, and now it's just, it's a hard time.
♪ Get ready for some Middle East ♪
♪ What I got on ♪
- Things used to be cheaper.
- Brought to you by Taladol.
- Yeah, yeah, we're raising the prices of tacos.
Don't say taco around the Mr. President.
He doesn't like that.
- Paul Brogan in the chat already mentioned
that they were not alive when "Mannequin" came out.
- Well--
- So there's one already.
- Brogan, I hope you have at least seen "Mannequin"
and "Mannequin 2."
- No, Brogan is shaking their head in the chat.
- Well, Brogan, you've got homework.
'Cause Hollywood is I fucking conic.
Yes.
- Brogan, you don't have any homework.
You don't have to watch "Mannequin."
Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social
does not want to encourage people
to watch the film "Mannequin."
- I mean-- - Oh, I do.
- Peak Andrew McCarthy, you know?
- Peak Andrew McCarthy.
- That is true.
Peak Andrew McCarthy for sure.
- It's, what's her name?
It's, oh my God.
- Kim Cattrall.
- Kim Cattrall at the height of her powers.
My God.
She's unstoppable.
I mean, if you wanted a little peek
into what formed old Paul,
baby Paul's idea of--
- 'Cause it was so mysterious up until this point.
(laughing)
- Who would have thought that Paul's ideal woman
would be a beautiful Kim Cattrall
that could then turn into a life-size action figure?
(laughing)
Who would have ever imagined?
- I'll tell you who else wanted to fuck a mannequin
when they were a kid, and still kind of do,
and that's the following sponsor.
- That's the whole thing about "Mannequin."
He sets up these beautiful, elaborate sets in the windows
and becomes famous for his beautiful sets.
I just wanted to see one where the mannequin is dripping goo.
(laughing)
- Did they use this mannequin and shoot a "Ghostbusters?"
It's covered in slime.
(laughing)
Following sponsor.
- Why does this Macy's display say,
"Mine if I use your shower?"
(laughing)
- Today's show is brought to you by--
- It has an eyewash station.
(laughing)
- Please do not touch the mannequin goo.
- Seriously, no wash? - It's in the open stores.
- Seriously, no washcloths?
Today's show is brought to you by
Feral Child's wedding video voiceover service.
That's right, if you need a wedding video voiceover,
you can get it done by Feral Child.
That's from Nola Scoop in 2021.
- What was like when proposed to stay together for life?
Well, now can remember with Feral Child's voice.
Remember, mom and dad walk down aisle?
Remember dog carry ring?
Oh, remember little boy pee on altar?
Accidents happen?
Remember bridesmaid get caught on fire
from standing next to candelabra?
Remember bridesmaid require eight years plastic surgery
to regain facial recognition?
Remember bridesmaids still not right in head
about terrible burning?
- Oh, I gotta fast forward through this part.
- Bridesmaid.
(laughing)
- I'm gonna fast forward.
- All right, let's see what this is.
- And bridesmaids say vengeance will be hers.
- Oh man, we got a lot of bridesmaids.
I'm gonna fast forward a little more.
- Hotel rooms from state to state.
(mumbling)
- Okay, here we go.
- She's still alive.
Most of head look hamburger, but she not gone.
- Enter eight scoops and check out.
- Short surgery, not successful.
(laughing)
- That bridesmaid ruined my wedding video.
- I mean, it's an event to remember.
- It is.
- You'll never forget that time the bridesmaid caught on fire.
- No, you won't.
You won't.
- Oh man.
I watched hacks, season four of hacks on the plane.
- Okay.
- On the plane here.
- I fell off of hacks.
I liked the first two seasons a lot.
And then I fell off somewhere at season three.
And then I picked up a season four,
obviously missing some of the information
from the end of season three.
I feel like I gathered all that information pretty quickly.
(laughing)
And then I just watched three episodes
of them being horrible to each other
and them being horrible people.
And I was like, where are the jokes?
What am I supposed to be watching?
- Because the first two seasons of it were like,
they were too close to home for us.
- Oh, sure.
- It was too much Las Vegas showbiz.
It was too accurate.
- Yes.
- And yeah, now it's, oh, well, this is just,
okay, I get it now.
All right.
- Yeah.
- Broken people being mean.
- And they changed what the show is.
They changed it from, she's like the older person
who's trying to revitalize her career
and now she's just rich and powerful.
- Yeah.
- And I was like, who am I supposed to be rooting for
and where and why?
What am I supposed to, who do I want to do things?
- Right.
- And I just was like, oh man,
it put me in such a bad mood.
I was really in like a sour mood getting off my plane.
And I literally was like, why am I in a bad mood?
I was like, today's nothing.
I'm just traveling.
All I'm doing is traveling
and get to get to get to my friend's house
to go grab dinner and watch football.
Why, how am I in a bad mood?
And I was like, I think hacks put me in a bad mood.
(laughing)
- Thanks a lot, Elizabeth Smart.
- Well, there's your hacks hacks.
Don't watch it.
- And I know people who write on it.
I know people who film it and stuff,
and I pulled their names out on my phone
and showed them to my friend.
(laughing)
- Gene Smart, thank you.
- Who was it designing women with me, Shaq Taylor,
who played Hollywood, iconic mannequin character.
(laughing)
Seven degrees to Hollywood.
- You know it all goes back to mannequin.
You know it.
- It all goes back to mannequin.
- Paul, Paul, Elizabeth Taylor.
- Okay, Elizabeth Taylor, married briefly to Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson, married briefly to Priscilla Presley.
Priscilla Presley, married briefly to a mannequin
named Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson was a mannequin.
Hollywood.
- I say only four degrees.
- Four degrees. - Only four degrees.
- Four degrees.
- Elizabeth Smart was a girl who was kidnapped, right?
- Elizabeth Smart is the poor one that got kidnapped.
- I would rather watch that
than the rest of the hack season.
(laughing)
- You'd rather watch Elizabeth Smart be kidnapped.
- I'd rather just watch it.
- Apologies to Elizabeth Smart.
- Oh yes, and Andy Cheek is pointing out I got it wrong.
It wasn't Priscilla Presley.
It was Lisa Marie that he married.
- I mean, I don't know that he didn't marry Priscilla.
I'm not a Michael Jackson historian.
- Exactly.
She went from one King of Pop to the next.
- I am watching "Task."
- You're still doing it.
- Okay, yes.
It's so depressing.
- You're putting Matt in a bad mood.
- But I'm just in.
It does make me so sad.
But I'm at least prepared.
I know, but I'm going to bed then.
- You're ready though.
You're ready for that.
- I'm gonna go to bed sad.
- I did that for my whole childhood.
- No, so.
But the thing about it, this is so Mark Ruffalo,
he grows his hair out, you know,
he's got like kind of like bushy hair.
And then he gets like a head injury at one point,
and he also gets beat up.
So his back is all jacked up.
So at one point he walks in, it's like a dead serious scene.
It's like a pivotal scene in the series.
And he is walking and talking like Columbo.
Like he is just being Columbo.
- It's full on now at this point.
- It just looks like Columbo.
And he's literally doing the like, yeah, just one more thing.
And like, he's bringing up things that he knows
that he figured out.
And he's trying to make a guy basically cave.
- He is Peter Falk in it.
- And I'm so distracted.
Cause I'm like, this is like four o'clock in the morning
on my cruise ship.
And I'm like, this is just Columbo.
I'm just watching this thing from Columbo.
(laughing)
- This guy could have found Elizabeth Smart.
- Six episode windup of watching the most depressed hunk
of like American life.
And I am just totally distracted
by this Columbo impersonation.
I'm watching that happen on this thing.
It looked right out of Columbo.
- Wow.
(laughing)
- Mark Ruffa Columbo.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, my other excitement and all the fracas
that went on last night
and getting everything squared away
and getting the dogs where they need to be
and cause we're wrestling around.
I'm wearing my, this new hoodie that Mizzoula got for me
which I love.
It's this really cool Star Wars hoodie that he got for me.
And I put some doggy treats in the pocket to
cause I was, you know, wrangling dogs.
I'm doing laundry today and I put it in my second load
and I go to clear out my second load
and I had left the doggy treats in the pocket.
(laughing)
And I'm like, fuck me.
- Cleanest doggy treats in Pittsburgh.
- I'm so mad.
And it's just, luckily it was the gunk of it.
The treats were all just in the pocket and the sweater.
- It didn't break out.
- Oh, that's good.
- No, you didn't get the rest of the laundry exactly.
But I had to clean, clean, clean the sweater out
and it's still not coming clean exactly.
It's in the dryer now.
But I took the rest of that load that looked fairly okay.
You know, didn't have like stuff in it,
but it had been washed.
- I've always said that about your loads.
Your loads usually look fairly okay.
- They look fairly okay, but well,
they look best when dripping out of mannequins.
- Sure, sure.
(laughing)
- But I--
- Use the eye wash station.
- Please, save yourselves.
But I threw everything in the dryer
and then I go to take the stuff out of the dryer
and I'm taking it out and I, you know,
'cause I use the like the little, the scent booster stuff,
the, anyway, the downy scent, whatever it is.
- Yeah.
- Anyway, I give a little sniff
and it's got just this sort of very faint,
but they're sort of beefiness to it.
And it was like, fuck,
I have to wash all these clothes again.
(laughing)
Why did you have to wash?
But they already had the scent of beef.
Why did you wash them again, Paul?
- I'm trying to rid myself of the scent of beef.
I'm trying, I'm trying to un-beef my laundry.
- You have beef experience.
- I do, brother, do I?
So this is--
- I'm looking for that right now.
- This is my afternoon is--
- I know what beef is.
I have had beef experience.
I know beef.
- It's true.
And brother?
- Hoo, know it, I wear it.
(laughing)
- Exactly.
So, yeah, that's my excitement for the day,
is cleaning my new favorite shirt
and finding I sabotaged my new favorite shirt
with a bunch of fucking dog treats.
- With beef scent.
So hopefully--
- Some say sabotage, some say improve.
- Hopefully it's fixed.
We'll see.
It dried finally.
We'll see what's going on.
Good Lord, I don't know.
- I want all of Paul's wardrobe to just smell like beef.
- Well, give it a couple days, it might.
We'll see.
I need to put some more perfume on it, maybe.
- Yeah, that's probably what it's missing.
You wanna do a little Scoop Mail?
- Let's do Scoop Scoop Scoop.
- I ache for it.
- Message for you, sir.
- We got one here from Poutine Scoops.
Hello fuckers.
Here's an Italian air show story from my childhood.
Back in 1995, there was a referendum in Quebec
to separate from Canada.
As dumb as 13-year-old me and my friend thought,
we're gonna need our own money as a country.
We proceeded to heat up a Canadian penny with a lighter
to engrave it with a fleur de lis or something.
The lighter didn't soften the penny enough,
so we went outside and grabbed the red gas can
for the lawnmower.
Oh, gas can, gotta be gas.
Grabbed the red gas can for the lawnmower
and tried to soften the penny some more.
Spoiler, you can't melt a penny with gas as a 13-year-old.
- What?
- Jet fuel doesn't melt steel pennies.
- No, I guess not.
We put too much gas on, and at some point,
my genius self tries to put the fire out by stomping it down
with the first thing I got on my hand,
which was the red gas can.
What?
So you had a fire that you were trying to melt a penny
in the fire, pouring gasoline on it,
and then you had the gas can in your hand,
and so you tried to use the gas can
to then tamp out the fire?
- To tamp out the flame, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yeah.
- We now have a significant red gas can fire on our hands.
My friend runs to grab the water hose,
but the full red gas can on fire won't stop burning
because it's a gas can.
- Quick, get more gas.
We gotta put up this gas fire.
- Throw some rice on that.
- Oh, that would have fixed it.
Now, do you guys remember the red gas cans
exploding in '80s movies?
Because I did, it's gonna explode and destroy the house.
I'd better kick it further away from the house.
- Oh, no.
- So the bottom of the red gas can
had already melted on the grass,
so only the top of the can got kicked away
and the not yet burned gas went everywhere.
So as a 13-year-old on fire guy, I proceeded to...
I don't know what that's supposed to say.
This is an oddly written letter.
I think this person might still be on fire
when they wrote this letter.
- This is a traumatic event, clearly, for this individual.
- Yeah.
- I am watching it burn right now.
I type as I...
- I'm doing Voice the Text!
- Scope is reliving this, yeah.
- Went all the way around the house to the back
to get my water hose friend who then extinguished my legs.
- Oh, my God.
- Your legs caught fire?
- Yeah.
This reminds me of a wedding video I just saw.
- Of the girl with the flame...
The girl with the flame on the chain
and she tosses it all over the place?
- Oh, I haven't seen that.
- Oh, okay.
- Did it really happen?
She burned up people?
- Yeah, yeah, she like tossed up basically a flame ball
into the crowd of people at a wedding.
- Did they all freak out when it happened?
- Yes, yeah, yeah.
- Did anybody die?
- Three months in the hospital, skin grafts,
all the things. - Oh, shit!
- My legs still look weird,
but they work great.
- Dear God.
- Worst thing about it is my scars won't sweat
and it's a good part of my legs,
so the end of the scars sweat like crazy
because it's all going out wherever it can.
- Oh!
- It gets a little itchy, but no big deal.
- What a strange set of facts. - I'm so sorry, Poutine Scoop.
Oh, that's so awful.
- Oh, the referendum went 50.2 to 49.8,
so no, I'm still Canadian
and we still don't have our own pennies.
That's Poutine Scoop.
- You know, I don't think Canada even has pennies now.
- So it's all for naught.
- Well, I don't think they even have pennies now,
just like us.
I think they also got rid of their pennies.
I see Crystal Twist is saying I'm right.
They don't have pennies anymore.
- Oh!
- So not only was it for naught,
but it wouldn't have even worked before.
- Huh.
Well, technically, the US has never had pennies.
We have one cent pieces.
The English and the Canadians have pennies.
There's no US-- - Poutine Scoop.
That is such a heartbreaker.
As a former young adolescent boy who played with fire,
I can only say that I, there but for the grace of fate,
do I not join you in insanity.
I remember one day we were at a friend's house
and he put gasoline in one of those little
plastic dinosaurs that are about six inches tall, right?
Do you remember those old hard plastic dinosaurs?
- Yeah, yeah.
And they were hollow in the middle.
- Exactly.
So he filled it up with gasoline
and he set the mouth on fire
thinking it was gonna look like breathing fire.
- I'm with this kid.
This is a smart kid.
- It didn't really do much.
It just started melting the face.
But then he went and tipped the tail
and the gasoline barfed out of the thing
and it filled this basement with fire.
And lucky there was nothing on the floor.
- You were inside doing this.
- Yeah, it was inside a basement.
It's a concrete floor.
And luckily nobody got hurt and it got out.
But it was scary.
- It didn't burn the house down.
- It was scary for a minute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's actually pretty scary here
at the core sensors building.
Zach broke the light.
So there's a light broken.
Zach broke the light and now
we'll never find our way out of here.
I live here now.
- Well, at least you've got some sensors and gauges.
- That's right.
- I'm wondering how much pressure
I'm under to finish this episode.
I can actually figure out that number right now.
- But I appreciate Poutine sharing that trauma with us
for our entertainment.
- We definitely went through like a fire period
when we were kids.
- Yeah, every little boy does.
- Everything we would hear about.
Yeah, but like everything.
There was this period of time in the '80s and '90s
where you'd hear about these things
and people would tell them as cautionary tales.
Like make sure you don't mix, what was it?
Ivory soap and gasoline on an electric stove top
because that's how you can make napalm.
- Yes.
- And would be told that, it would be like,
well, clearly that's what we're gonna do now.
- I'd say it's time to make some napalm.
- Yeah, and we would do that.
We had like a hot plate out somewhere.
Like somebody had gotten a hot plate
and I remember we were in a culvert one time
in some neighborhood.
- A hot plate in a culvert?
- Yeah, it was crazy shit.
We read one time that if you cut off
a whole bunch of Strike Anywhere match heads
and shoved them into a tennis ball
that it would act like a hand grenade.
- Right.
- Which it shockingly almost worked exactly like that.
It was, you talk about like pouring gas
on the floor of the basement.
The hand grenade tennis ball was my pouring gas
- Where'd you throw it?
- We were outside and I don't think I threw it.
I think one of the other guys threw it
and just up against a brick wall.
- Oh shit.
- And like it just went.
It exploded and little nubs of fire,
just thousands of little nubs of fire
just went in every direction.
- Wow shit.
- And it definitely started a couple of fires.
It was terrifying.
- Oh God.
- Yeah.
- We used to ride our bikes up to the recycling center,
steal newspaper out of the recycling center newspaper
and then we took matches from a bucket of matches at 7-Eleven
and then we would go light newspaper on fire.
- It's its own fault for being so flammable.
- That'll teach it.
That'll learn it.
- We got one here from Anonymous Scoop X.
This recently happened and understandably
I can't possibly tell anyone in my life,
but this is where you three boys
and your confession booth of frozen dairy delights comes in.
- Yay.
- Here we are.
Now we're actually serving our purpose.
- This gentleman falls within the first blow job topic.
- Oh.
- Been a minute.
- Falls in?
Sounds like there's some qualifiers here.
- It sounds like there might be.
I've been dating my almost 40 year old partner
as a 34 year old woman.
I can't bring myself to say boyfriend
for the last few years.
We were flirtatious friends for many years,
which escalated to friends with benefits
and finally to long distance partners.
We'd meet up every month or so in person,
go on dates, play games, and perhaps most crucially,
fuck for hours.
It's been a journey of exploration for both of us.
We both have what is probably an unreasonably high sex drive
and we both enjoyed exploring new kinks and experiences.
I take particular pride in bringing any dream
or fantasy to life for the chap.
As a former cosplayer, I've also had a lot of fun
sewing costumes, making outfits,
and embroidering and embodying new characters.
- Amazing.
- As much as I've wanted to play out some of these things,
it's the first time I've met someone
who was as adventurous as I was,
who I was comfortable with.
- Jacob, this is clearly AI
or some weird old penthouse forum thing
where someone's just pretending to be awesome.
- I never thought it would happen to me.
This is not, this can't be true.
This can't be true.
- This is real life, David.
- Matt, Matt, all of those penthouse forum letters
had to come from real people.
So I mean, clearly those things really happened.
- All right.
- Oh, this is important context for what came next.
It was always a running joke in our friendship group
that my fellow was two scoops of plain old vanilla.
As an alternative lass covered in tattoos
and arresting bitch face to rival the best in the business,
we managed to go completely under the radar
for a long time, but behind closed doors,
he was very different.
We dabbled in toys, different positions, role plays.
We would laugh about how if they knew, they'd be shocked.
Cut to a few weeks ago, years down the line,
two days in a row, I'd woken the chap up
with a good morning blow job.
He recovers quickly, so both mornings,
he'd managed to come twice in a row before work.
- Holy smoke. - What can I say?
I'm dedicated to the craft.
- That's an incredible refractory period.
- That is.
- Anyway, after day two-- - This man should be
studied by R.F.K. Jr.
- I don't know how you do that.
- Anyway, after day two, we were talking away
and it got into the topic of porn.
He let me in on the fact that he watches role play porn.
The boy watches it for the plot.
I was in absolute hysterics.
I couldn't believe it.
I didn't know these people still existed.
He's really rooting for that pizza delivery boy.
He asked what porn I watched and I had to explain
that I didn't think he would know
what all the letters stood for in my search term.
I'd simply said, if there are less than four people
in the room, I'm probably not interested.
He was also surprised when I said
that I can't stand the introduction,
so I just passed forward to the good bits.
- So L-E-M-O-N, those are the types of things
that you put in there?
- That's right, that's right.
- Lemon party. - P-A-R-T-Y.
Because I like it.
That's when the situation escalated
and it hit me like a bus to the face.
Well, I'm quite vanilla.
You know that, or I was before we met.
Before you, I'd only had one blowjob,
he mumbled, somewhat embarrassed.
Then in an even quieter voice,
he said, well, sort of half of one.
He explained, one girlfriend once had tried it
and decided it wasn't really for her.
(laughing)
Had been married since,
and she was absolutely not forgiving it a go.
Boys, I'm ashamed to say I laughed my fucking ass off
for a long time.
Throughout the day, periodically,
I laughed repeatedly, and not a chuckle.
I laughed at the volume of a demented, drug-addled clown.
I couldn't believe that he was telling me
this many years down the line
what must be literally hundreds of blowjobs later.
He'd had four blowjobs in the space of 24 hours
compared to the half a job he'd had
in the previous 38 years of life.
It's important to say I wasn't laughing at him.
I was just laughing at the ridiculousness of the situation.
Although apparently clarifying that
did not make up for how hard I was laughing at the time.
So that's my story of how my partner's dreams came true
when he realized he'd met a human vacuum cleaner
who'd happily putter around in a homemade poison ivy outfit.
Ooh, poison ivy outfit, full circle.
If it meant he'd be happy,
although not quite a first blowjob story,
you'd have to have a very specific category
for the first blowjob story for that one.
Thanks for giving me an outlet for this tale.
The podcast brings me absolute joy.
That's Anonymous Scoop X.
Thank you, Anonymous Scoop.
And like most people that like our podcast,
Anonymous Scoop insists on remaining anonymous.
(laughing)
People don't want to like our podcast openly.
I get it, I get it.
Hey, the fade button works.
- Nice.
- That's a nice change.
It's time for "Jock vs. Nerd".
(howling)
- It's on.
- You wanna do a little "Jock vs. Nerd" action?
- Oh, am I?
- Fuck yeah.
- I'm on the hunt for balls.
(upbeat music)
- No!
We got a scooper today from Swedish Scoop.
The categories are San and Santa,
Shakin' My Spear,
Ol' MCD, Deformed Farm.
- Do you think that girl went on to blow someone else?
Like, do you feel like she's also had to retell that story
to a partner and be like, you know?
- The one who didn't, who wasn't for me.
- Yeah, yeah.
Like, do you think like later she was like, you know,
got used to it?
- Tried another?
I doubt it.
- Hello, I didn't used to like this nearly as much
as I do now.
(laughing)
But these days, I don't even talk without a cock in my dick.
That's right.
- Ol' McDonald's Deformed Farm.
- Oh, that's what that Ol' McDonald's Deformed Farm
and songs I weep for.
- Okay.
- Paul, you're up.
- Well, I gotta try Ol' McDonald's Deformed Farm.
- For 400, this animal had an ab-ab here
and an ab-ab there, here an ab, there an ab,
everywhere an ab-ab.
That's A-A-B is how ab is spelled.
- Oh, geez.
- I mean, like a deformed sheep, I guess.
- I guess.
Oh, a dyslexic sheep.
- Oh, they all have a condition.
Okay.
- All right, we get it now.
- All right.
- Matt, you're up.
- Songs I Weep For.
- Eponine, I never remember how to say her name.
- Eponine sings this song of unrequited love and loneliness
in Les Miserables.
- What's it called?
♪ I love him that every day I'm learning ♪
- Master of the House, that's it.
- Master of the House.
- I can't remember, Pass.
- Passes to me, shit.
All I can think of is, oh wait, is it Castle on a Cloud?
- That's the little girl song.
- Yeah, I don't remember who is who.
I don't remember what French name belongs
with what character in Les Mis.
- ScooperNovaGirl typed it into the chat
if you just want to read it and get it right.
- Oh, okay.
Why, I can't see the chat.
You guys can see the chat during the--
- Oh, I didn't realize we had this advantage on you, Jacob.
- Oh yeah, no, I can't see the chat during the Scooperties
'cause I'm sharing my screen so you guys
could see the Scoopertie.
- Pretty great.
- Oh, is it, on my own, on my own.
Wait, you can't see the chat?
- Hey, you grabbed.
- No.
- That's so funny.
- He grabbed it.
- All right.
- I mean, I know the show.
- You knew the song, yeah.
- Yeah, I just had to find it in my head.
Me, it's, I don't know what San and Santa is,
so let's try that, 400.
Jesus' mom in Espanol.
So, how do you say fictional in Spanish?
How do you say historical fiction?
What, so it's just Mary in Spanish?
- I think it's different than that.
- Okay, I pass then, Paul.
- I think it's Magdalena.
- Oh, I see.
Santa Maria.
- Well, shit on me.
- Shit on my penis.
- Mary Magdalena.
- Paul.
- Fucking shit my dick.
I'll do songs I weep for for 2000,
'cause I gotta get on the board.
- Fire Maple Song is a single off the first album
by this '90s rock band,
better known for Wonderful and Santa Monica.
- Oh, that's Everclear.
- Everclear is correct.
- I saw them at concert.
- Paul on the board. - They were terrible.
- No.
- Yeah, they were awful.
- Matt, you're up.
- I left before they were done.
- I'll do Shakin' My Spear for 400.
- I've never gone out of my way to see Everclear.
This tragedy focuses on a pair of star-crossed lovers
from Fair Verona.
Did you know the girl was only 13?
- Yoinks.
- It's about Jerry Lee Lewis.
- This is Romeo and Juliet.
- Romeo and Juliet.
Is that the whole answer?
I don't know, I forgot what the category is.
- I believe that's the answer.
- Oh yeah, Romeo and Juliet.
I didn't know if it was gonna be like a Romeo and Juliet,
get fucked or something like that.
(laughing)
Let's see, I'll try, I don't know,
Shakin' My Spear for 800.
Daily double!
Tomorrow and tomorrow and tomorrow is a famous soliloquy
from this Scottish play.
That would be the Scottish play, Macbeth.
- MacGregor the Bridge Builder, no.
(laughing)
- Macbeth is correct.
Paul.
- I'll try Old MacDonald for 2,000.
Wow, this animal had a crack, crack here
and a crack, crack there, here a crack,
there a crack, everywhere a crack, crack.
- Oh my gosh, it's probably an arthritic duck,
but I don't wanna guess for 2,000 points.
I'll pass.
- Matt.
- Pass.
- Or what's that condition that Mr. Glass had?
- A drug dealing duck.
- Oh, drug dealing duck, good lord.
See, there's a lot of ways I could've gone,
crack, crack here and a crack, crack there.
- Yeah, I would've gone like a plumber duck or something.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Matt, you're up. - Yeah, I could've been
a plumber.
- Shake Me My Spear, 1,200.
- This title Prince of Denmark asks,
am I a coward in Shakespeare's longest play?
- Hamlet?
- Indeed.
- Hamlet is correct.
Where's the thing, there it is.
Me, I'll try, I'll close out Shake Me My Spear,
I actually know these.
Shakespeare's wife shares a name
with this modern actress of The Dark Knight Rises,
Selena Kyle and Le Miserable, Fantine Fane.
- It's your girl, Matt.
- Oh yeah.
- Catwoman.
- Batgirl or Catwoman, I don't remember,
but it's one of them.
- It was actually Catwoman, but she went Batgirl.
Who was Batgirl in that movie?
- I can't think of her name.
- Princess Diaries. - I got to pass Paul.
- Now you got me on it.
- I can't really remember her name either.
I don't like her at all.
- Pass, baby, pass.
- Matt's just sitting there just slowly jacking it.
He's just keeping it in half staff, he's ready to go.
- I can't remember her name.
- All right, half staff, Donnelly, what you got?
- And hath a way about her.
- Oh, yes, there it is.
- Don't know what it is. - And hath a way.
Where there is a will and hath a way.
- Yeah, she does.
I'll try songs that weep four for two, 1200.
- It's not time to make a change.
Just relax, take it easy.
Sings Cat Stephen, Yusef Islam in this tearjerker.
- Oh.
- Oh, this is a good one.
- This one got me, this one got me for real, in real life.
'Cause I listened to that, I went to the Cat Stevens binge
when I moved to the Virgin Islands,
and I was like living off of my own.
And then I listened to it after I had a child,
and I indeed felt both sides of the song,
and it fucking destroyed me.
Yeah.
- I have to pass 'cause I can't remember the title of the song.
- It goes to Matt, what is it?
- Father and Son.
- Father and Son, that got you?
- Believe it or not, yeah, yeah.
- Huh, huh, interesting.
- I hope you don't ever have kids, it'll really get you.
- Yeah.
- It's really, you know, the lyrics respond back and forth
between father and the son, and it's super, super deep.
- No, I think it's a really good song.
- That they sued, who is that psychedelic band?
Ended up just absolutely just copying the song by accident
and had to pay up in the lawsuit.
- Oh, I don't know.
- I'll look it up in a sec.
'Cause I'm gonna check and look it up.
- Was it in the '60s they did it?
- No, it was in the late '90s or the 2000s.
There's Flaming Lips, that's who it was.
- Flaming Lips, yeah.
- Oh, Flaming Lips basically ripped one off.
- It was too similar to Father and Son.
- Yeah.
- In the settlement, the bands agreed to a royalty split
with Stevens receiving 75% of the publishing royalties
for a fight test.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Man, Cat Stevens had some good lawyers on that lawsuit.
- He sure did, he sure did.
- Holy shit.
Let's see, what is it?
Matt, your turn.
- I will do...
- Score check, by the way,
Matt is crushing both Paul and I.
He has 4,800, Paul and I both have 1,200 each.
- I can step into it with Daily Doubles here.
I'll do songs at week four for 800.
- Daily Doubles! - There it comes.
- Oh no. - You got this.
- From your mouth to my ears.
This legendary Academy Award winning song asks,
"If happy little bluebirds fly, why, oh why can't I?"
It also ranked number one on AFI's 100 years,
100 song list.
- That's Baby Got Back.
Somewhere Over the Rainbow.
- Somewhere Over the Rainbow. - Somewhere Over the Rainbow.
- Oh, I just brought back a flashback of Judy Garland
singing that 100 feet high in the sphere.
- Was it crazy? - I'll try.
Yeah, it was, it was really crazy.
Santa and Santa for 800.
This is what you get when you eat breakfast
on the beach in California.
High property taxes, am I right?
(laughing)
- I don't know.
- What's the thing, salmon sand?
- I have no idea, I'll pass, Paul.
- A breakfast sandwich?
- Oh.
San Diego.
- Oh, San Diego.
- Yeah, I get it now, Paul.
Old Deform McDonald for 1200.
- This animal had a rubbit, rubbit here,
and a rubbit, rubbit there.
Here a rubbit, there a rubbit, everywhere a rubbit, rubbit.
- It's gotta be a habitual masturbating frog.
- Habitually masturbating frog?
Close enough, perverted frog, yes.
(laughing)
- Man. - A horny toad.
- I'll do San Santa. - Oh, horny toad.
- 1200. - Great horny toads.
- Musicals adore this New Mexico city
with characters in both Newsies and Rent,
dreaming of running away to there.
- Santa Fe?
- But how do the songs go, Matt?
Come on.
- I don't know the Newsies Santa Fe song.
♪ Santa Fe ♪
- But I'll do the whole score of Rent for you right now.
- The Newsies are trying to get to Santa Fe?
- The one, Christian Bale's character,
he sings the whole song about Santa Fe.
- What?
- It's like, it's the big torch song.
It's like Santa Fe, I'll be there.
I don't remember anymore.
- I mean, I've been to the city, it's fine.
- It's a perfectly plausible song.
- How can that compare to New York?
I don't get it.
- Well, that's why there's only two songs about it,
not the dozens about New York.
- I suppose you're right.
- Let's see, it's me, I have 1200, Paul has 1600,
Matt has 10,800.
There are two questions left and no more deadly doubles.
- Anybody's game.
- I'll try Santa and Santa for 2000.
This character threatened Chris the octopus
in a heartwarming children's tale.
It isn't Chris's fault, he lost his hat.
- Yeah.
- So that's the homeless guy, the bum.
- No, no, no, he didn't threaten him.
- Okay.
- What's the category, Jacob?
- Oh, I don't remember.
- Santa and Santa.
- Oh, he's the bum dressed as Santa?
Is that what it means?
- It's just Santa Claus.
Santa Claus is the villain in "Christmapus".
- Right, yeah.
- Santa Claus is basically the bad guy in "Christmapus".
- Isn't Santa Claus the bum though, too?
- No, he is the surrogate for Rudolph.
- Oh, I haven't read "Christmapus" recently enough.
- I get that, it's all right.
Well, we're working on the sequel.
- It'll be a big thing.
- Yeah, I'll bone up on the original
so I'm not confused by any of the plot lines in the sequel.
- We're gonna do some reprints, yeah, it'll be awesome.
It's gonna happen.
- Paul, close it out, the category and the game.
Old Macdeform, Old Macdeform Farm, yeah, you know what it is.
- Yes, Old Macdeform Farm.
- This animal had a hith hith here and a hith hith there.
Here a hith, there a hith, everywhere a hith hith.
He also starred in Disney's "Robin Hood",
the animated "Robin Hood". - Mike Tyson's a snake.
If Mike Tyson was a snake, this is what I would sound like.
It's a, it's a, it's a lispy snake.
- A lispy Mike Tyson snake?
Nailed it.
And that is the game.
Matt Donnelly ekes out the win with 10,800 points.
I'm in second with 3200, Matt said,
or Paul's in third with 2,400, that's from Swedish Scoop.
Thank you, Swedish Scoop.
If you wanna send us a scooper to your price,
a scrype jock versus nerd, or an obelisk jock versus nerd,
or just send us some email, head over to HayScoops.com.
You know what else you can do at HayScoops.com?
You can buy Scoop Fest merch, that's right.
There is 2025 Scoop Fest merch there.
You got Fezzes, you got a hat, not hats,
the Fezzes are the hats.
You got Fezzes, you got robes,
and a pair of T-shirts that you can choose between.
They're all really cool, do the thing.
Oh, and if you buy a T-shirt, a robe, and a Fez all together,
there's a discount that kicks in at checkout.
Ooh. - There you go.
There you go.
- Yeah, yeah, so if you buy the whole package,
there's a discount that kicks in later on.
- Get the package, Scoops.
- Yeah!
- Yeah, and post those pics and tag HayScoops.
We wanna see you in your robes and Fezzes.
- Yeah, we do.
- Also, yeah, this Thursday,
what time are you hearing this?
But people on Zoom, but this Thursday,
you can see Paul and I at Tierney's Tavern.
Just come out to Tierney's Tavern, it's 20 bucks.
- So soon!
- We're gonna do some improv,
we'll do some stand-ups, some magic, you know.
It's gonna be a casual fun day.
- It's gonna be super, super fun.
Super, super fun.
We've already got a bunch of Scoops going.
It's gonna feel like a homecoming for Matt.
It's gonna feel like a mini Scoop churn out for us.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be great.
- It's gonna be very fun.
Can't wait to do it, so come check it out.
You can go to HayScoops.com/ComedyNight
and grab your tickets there.
- Yes, you guys, yeah, you continue to make us look
like rock stars when we have these events
and lots of you show up.
It's pretty awesome.
- Can I confirm or deny Chris Christie's attendance?
Cannot confirm or deny.
- Keep it hush hush.
- As long as he doesn't have to get on a bridge.
(laughing)
- Can he fit in Tierney's?
- I wanna thank the following people
who support us on our page.
All of these people played both Batgirl and Catwoman
in my musical version of Batman.
- Fucking range.
- Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess, Scoopy Bartfast,
Scoopy Ramone, Scoopy Dooby Doo,
Scoopy and the Beast, Scoop Trek the Experience,
Scoop So Hazzard, Scoop-O-Metrics,
Scoop Nick, Scoop Neon Black, Scoop La Qeesa,
Scoop Knack Patty Whack, Scoop Kata,
Scoop JD, Scoopiter Ascending,
Scoopia Lauren, Scooper Nova Girl,
Scooper Metroid, and Scoopa Luga.
By the way, quick shout out.
I watched the movie Ballerina on another flight.
- How was it?
(laughing)
- Plot not dissimilar to Gymkhada.
Plot not dissimilar to Gymkhada.
- Really, okay.
- Yeah, very similar plot.
- She has the, her dance moves
are her special weapon kind of thing?
- Like, no, it's just goes to,
like in Gymkhada, it just goes to a village
and just people just wanna kill 'em
and that's the plot.
Is that a bunch of people--
- Oh, yeah.
- Send 'em out of where they go in the village
and just--
- And the village happens to have a pommel horse
in the center of it.
- Yes.
- Right, right.
'Cause if it's not for that pommel horse, he's dead.
- Yes.
(laughing)
Ballerina I found to be very similar to that movie.
- Okay, all right.
- There's a ballet bar in the middle of a village.
If it weren't for that ballet bar, it should be dead.
- One of the whole walls of the village
is a mirrored wall with a ballet bar.
- Yeah, yeah, they have a ballet bar
and a mirrored wall.
- It goes for like eight miles.
(laughing)
Good lord.
- Paul.
- Oh, the following people.
I had one.
- What was it?
(laughing)
- I had thought of a joke.
I forgot it.
- I did.
I had thought of a joke.
- Do you want someone else to go?
Jacob, go.
- Oh, shit.
No, I don't have a joke.
What do you think I have a joke ready for?
- Yeah, don't--
- I don't have a joke already.
- I'll finish up then.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll come up with something.
The following people.
- I gotta go.
- Looking for love in all the wrong places.
Scoop de Jure.
Scoop a real good.
Scoop Emily.
Scoop Dave Ville.
Scoop Chang the Beijing Mugles.
Scoop Bucky.
Scoop Brady, Scabby the Rat Scoop, Sext Guy Jimmy D Scoop,
Sarah Boyle, Sandra Petrovic, Sam Reed, Salt Lake Scoop,
Second Mingle, Ryar Appledorn, Ryan Hayward, Rose,
Rod Heck, Roger Edge, and Rodimus Scoop.
- The following people all approve and disapproved
of Annie's different outfit choices
in a montage in an '80s movie.
Scooped Mids.
Scoop Paul's Drag Race.
Scoopa Troopa.
Scoopaholic.
Scoop T.
Scoop Skywalker.
Scoop of Saltwater.
Scoop Nurse.
Scoop Mepha.
Scoop Lord Tristan.
Scoop Lindsay.
And Scoop Jesus.
- The following people are interns cleaning mannequins.
Robots Ahoy.
Robert Paulson.
Richard Hill.
Richard Graffiti.
Richard Fastnot.
Richard Dunn.
Richard Dunn again.
Reverend Nick Dingman
of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster.
Remember the Alamode.
Refrigerator Perry Scoop.
And Randy Glenn.
- And the following scoops all wrote in
and specifically asked me to say their names
very slowly this month.
This is Randy.
This is Ralph Barrett.
This is Raggedy Girl.
Radioactive Scoop.
Matt, just get comfy.
Quiet, Quiet Scoop.
Priro, Proto Scoop.
Proper Scoop.
Pick it up, pick it up, pick it up.
- He's out, he's out.
- Matt's out.
Philip Guyton.
Phil Tomlinson.
Phil Renly.
Petty Officer Scoop.
Peter Sansone.
Peter McDougall.
Peter Hines.
Peter Burford.
Peter Bougie.
Peter Romano.
Pebex Scoop.
P.E. Scoop.
Polygon.
Paul's Brother.
Paul Hosier Scoop.
Luxton.
One Fel Scoop.
Okie Scoop.
Nicky Benoit.
Nicole Levin.
Nicole Busenbach.
And Nicholas Petty.
Thank you all so much.
- Thank you all so much.
If you want to be thanked on air
or get discounts to our events
or get ad free episodes of our show,
there's all kinds of different rewards and tears for you
over at Patreon.com/HeyScoops.
Oh, so confusing.
- Oh no.
- Type in preachingfun.com.
(upbeat music)
♪ Come visit preachingfun.com ♪
♪ It's better than hanging with your bar to keep it ♪
- Or if you've had a rough day
and need to explain it to somebody
in a Taco Bell drive-thru,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
♪ Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts ♪
♪ Fartsinabag.biz ♪
- That's fartsinabag.biz,
along with Preaching Fun,
that will take you to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
That's right, this show's got bills.
Hopefully you think it's worth more than $0.
And hopefully you'd like to go over to preachingfun.com,
fartsinabag.biz.
Sign up today to be a Patreon.
Hey, that Patreon, the whole goddamn thing
is about to get turned upside down on its head,
not Patreon in general, just ours.
We're gonna change it all up.
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
So, keep your eyes out.
- We're changing like a few things.
- Hey, huge changes.
Huge changes. - Dogs and cats
laying together. - Mass hysteria.
- Very casual pruning of our Patreon happening.
- No, no, it's huge changes.
- I like that technical support
looks like he's giving technical support
in his window there.
- Yeah. - Oh, good.
- It's legit, the name's legit.
- Nominative determinism.
(laughing)
- Oh, he's got the company shirt on and everything.
All right, I wanna thank Core Systems
for giving me a home here for the day.
(laughing)
- Pocket some of those pressure sensors.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I want to thank Pendula for creating this podcast.
And I want you all to stay safe out there
and know that we love you.
And we hope to see you soon.
- See you soon.
♪ See you at the Cone ♪
♪ See you at the Cone, see you at the Cone ♪
♪ See you at the Cone, straight at the Cone ♪
- I got a fucking fly in my face.
I let all these spiders live down here.
They're not doing their fucking job.
(upbeat music)
Maybe the squirrel ate the spiders.
- But why would he eat the spider to swallow the fly?
- I don't know why.
- Okay.
- Maybe he'll fucking die.
(laughing)
- Perhaps.
- See ya!