Oh hello there I am so happy you're here because it is time to thank you the ice cream truck
drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers these are the folks that bring that
fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes right now I'd like to thank Jonathan
Joshua Bartles, Lori Elsroth, Leon Kassab, Mary Norbury Glazer, Malia and a random admiral
admiral yeah just a random admiral if you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like those
fine people and that one naval officer head over to preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is where you
sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save may be your own
here's a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
hey how familiar are you guys with uh
not at all but I know a little bit yeah yeah it's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social
sitting over there in Pittsburgh VA that's Paul Mattingly sitting over in Las Vegas it's Matt
Donnelly in Las Vegas as well it's me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun uh it's a lot a
lot like Taskmaster it's I am a huge fan of how did this get made the podcast with Paul Shear and
Jason Manzoukas who has done Taskmaster in the past I don't know if he's on this season or not
that well Jason Manzoukas and I haven't gotten to it I was just informed by a friend but Jason
Manzoukas basically wrote them being like why aren't I on this show and like barged this way
on and got himself invited onto the show yeah uh but it's an English show and you should have
English comedians or British comedians on there and uh it's just a snarky host
and they put people through like random tasks where they have to be very creative or justify
their answers it's all very like very funny and I didn't know about the show and turned out a friend
of ours their daughter uh was uh I'm being informed that's that's not snarky it's just British uh
fair enough and uh their daughter was totally into this show and so we uh decided they're
birthday party so what happened was uh uh my kids invited out to California and um and they
couldn't come without bringing a gift because every on the show every comedian has to bring
a gift with a certain theme ah and uh the theme had to be uh uh rain and uh sticky was the was
the theme of the of the uh so everybody brought her a rain stick an impressive an impressive
object it was rain and sticky and someone could have you could have done that but the problem is
if you watch the show if you do something predictable then the snarky slash just British
host will slam you and not give you points so you have to surprise they'll be British at you
and give points and so at first I was like I cannot believe that I'm driving my kids out to
California and I'm giving them homework right but I started watching the show with my kids
and they haven't seen it either at the prep and the show is really great like it's really funny
I'm gonna have to check it out it's it's really great
what gift would you bring under the restrictions of rain oh I I'm glad you asked I already thought
about it I would bring a bottle of pancake syrup that's exactly what I was gonna do I was gonna do
a Mrs. Butterworth dressed up like a queen oh no no I'm going to have somebody else sit in a chair
and then I'm going to do a sticky rain on them oh I was going to have the queen
the queen Mrs. Butterworth she would have the rain of sticky oh that's good too I like that
it's a bit of a pun what about you Matt what did you end up bringing her so I helped my kids out
with two different ones my one kid decided to make a fortune telling jar of answers to any
questions that he had with a with a fishing pole with a and this the hook was sticky it was a ball
of sticky tape so great he basically wrote like yes no maybe ask again fill in the blank
hell no uh oh he didn't write a whole bunch of like really super specific answers and just drop
it in there uh no you should not invest in that property yeah and my other kid uh took an umbrella
wrote the most impressive thing on the umbrella uh with sticky notes and then uh dropped glue
sticks from strings from each prong on the on the umbrella uh so he opened up the umbrella
and with that had an umbrella of glue sticks he won he won the challenge with the really with
the glue stick umbrella yeah he's he's good at a lot of things this was a like 24 hour event
this was my friend went way the fuck overboard so uh they were throwing a birthday party for
their child with all the kids the next day but the chosen five were to be contestants in in in the
in the contest for the whole day the day before they're doing all of that and then having a
yes i was like that is crazy that's too much you need to have an intervention with these people i
i was like no one loves their child this much no one no uh so we had our objects i
load up with all the stuff they needed for their sleepover and they were tasks waiting at the door
uh before you enter the house so it's like they have these like little ornate envelopes with like
the red wax kind of sticky on them or whatever and i
i had two children so they were given two different assignments one was told to enter the house in the
most annoying way please i don't even know i don't even want to know which kid that was
go on and then the other kid was told enter the house in the smartest way
both kids instantly had an idea great so uh one kid who had the annoying assignment just
opens door
and goes hey six seven six seven six seven six seven six seven six seven uh and just does it
and my other kid just threw his stuff at me and ran around the house like went to find another
way into the house yeah and so i entered behind the kid who got the annoying assignment and said
you got to go find my other kiddies coming in some other part of your house
probably good luck to everyone involved
uh you know they were given like all kinds of crazy tasks and the birthday girl was the host
and the mother was the co-host and they literally uh ran the whole afternoon with games uh and tasks
for five of her friends to compete in in a contest that took place all day
you know i'm thinking about i think this is a girl parent versus boy parent difference
you say that jacob just but i think it's just a demonstration of how much harder it is to be a
girl parent than it is to be a boy it definitely is it definitely is different challenges for sure
i i would say though too like some people birthdays are way more of a thing like with my
yes wife's family birthdays are big big deal you get to eat wherever you want
everybody has to go along like it's a it's a it's a thing yes my my family wasn't that big
of a all i mean occasionally it would be a big thing when we were little little littler but you
know it wasn't uh it was in our house it was able to be shuffled around like we still would do like
a dinner somewhere or some kind of event but it was like hey this brother has a basketball game
this brother is a football game this was it's like we need to we're gonna do it next saturday
well especially you got that many siblings too yeah yeah so it was always just a movable thing
right like we're gonna go have dinner we're gonna we're gonna have a cake
and candles or something like that some kind of celebration thing and we're gonna do it at
some point did you have a heavy month matt was there a triple sibling like with my period
yeah yeah did you have to you know really contain your birthday flow
no we were pretty we're pretty spread out actually with my fam oh that can be a trouble
with the period too yeah june july we have a june and july we have a june july and august three month
see a doctor see a doctor and then and then uh yeah april december my sister and i are uh well
we're nine years apart but we're five days apart that was with the only similar birthday okay
that's what i was wondering yeah yeah but now like when my uh do you know all of your siblings
birthdays i do yeah wow that's why i know no one else's right uh but uh people go like
something's like i've gotten shit for like not remembering when
someone's birthday is and i'm like man i just have my family and that's enough
but my when my when my second son was born just two days after my birthday
i was relieved i was like great we don't have to worry about my birthday ever again
and that can just be his birthday yes i really thought it'd be so cool to have the same birthday
but it didn't work out right probably for the best for his own thing but i thought it was awesome
i mean i think that'd be nice yeah because when he's when he's little you just don't mention it
right you know like you're at his birthday party or whatever and like you know like it's also my
birthday kids yeah yeah or just be getting jealous hey room full of eight-year-olds
and no one has told me happy birthday today i think i'll be taking this toy thank you very much
just be like i thought it'd be cool with it but you know what now that i see it happening it's not
it's not cool this is not
i also want a cake i did not sign up for this
it was tough you know who else thought they were going to be okay with not being the center of
attention for a few minutes but they were just wrong about it it's the following sponsor today's
show matt manley's ice cream social is brought to you by uh marcus mcgillicuddy's luxury abandoned
homes that's right that's right that's from uh george scoop stanza that's a good scoop name
it's 2020
24 that's uh marcus mcgillicuddy's luxury abandoned homes
hey marcus mcgillicuddy here and uh got some luxury abandoned homes that i'm willing to sell
you on the cheap how can i afford to sell this so cheap two words black mold yep it is the kind
that invades and permeates every area of the house and your body
cancer causing baby killing diarrhea and zooing black mold texas tea as they call it
you know the first two examples were much worse than the third one
you think cancer baby death diarrhea well but it's constant diarrhea oh that is bad that's right
it's not like just oh well i don't feel so great today no it's it's i am i am i just ate four
bags of olestra chips every moment of your day it's it's like you never stopped eating olestra chips
do they still sell olestra chips i don't know that i wonder well many many a business many
a business was sunk on the term anal leakage so well i know mine was add me to the ranks
because that's what you're gonna get you're gonna have a seeping weeping b-hole if you come and buy
one of my homes you're gonna have a seeping weeping b-hole if you come and buy one of my homes
filled to bursting with black mold texas tea
enter hay scoops to checkout
um i have an eye doctor's appointment today guys well i hope your eye isn't exploding like mine is
i know i know the funny thing was is that i uh i've had eye insurance been paying for
eye insurance for the last three years and i haven't gone yet never used it and it was
only because i went to the verizon store for my ordeal don't worry i will not get into it again we
don't have the time and they did they did they call you out on your giant font old man
i'd love to read the terms and services here but it's one letter per scroll here
jesus christ i broke my thumb trying to get to the bottom to agree to continue
your your tos took me 18 years to scroll through
like i'm so stupid about eye stuff like i was like i don't know the difference between like
who gives you glasses for someone who gives you an eye exam like i just was like there's
glasses things optometrist versus optician maybe optician and then i looked ophthalmologist
pearl vision was right next to the verizon store there ah and then as i walked by it for like the
third time because i went back and forth so many times uh i noticed there were doctor's names listed
on the door
oh my god
oh i was like oh so they got eye doctors in there
that's one of my doctor places and so i walked in
and said can i help you i said i i bet yes
and they said how can i help you i'm having an issue with myself are you in network
i go apparently i've had very good eye doctor uh insurance for a long time like they basically
it's vsp they take it everywhere it's basically what i've been doing for a long time
i was told oh great and so i said i have this insurance and i had it on my phone and i said
jesus that font uh get in this chair now you gotta dilate your eyes
i see that you have v scroll s scroll b insurance
that was matt realizing he couldn't spell insurance
oh
bail bail on bit yep um do i know how to spell insurance i think i do but i'm not completely
sure insurance i insurance i insurance and i said i have this insurance i've never been doing i
anything before my eyes are terrible please help oh god wait now are you wearing contacts or
anything yet i've never worn contacts i i have readers i've never worn contacts i've never worn
contacts i've never worn contacts i've never worn contacts i've never worn contacts
yes all over my house like like easter eggs on easter okay every room has like a pair of readers
i've just thrown there just in case and what what number uh reader are you are you purchasing and
hiding around your house uh that's the round one with a big stick at the end of it and it's like
that's it that's a real big and you know like you just just a magnifying glass 175
oh that's not too bad okay okay great good good yeah
i've recently started hiding readers around my house as well uh that just go along with my
contacts because now my farsightedness is thinking about starting to catch up with my nearsightedness
which is going real bit real bad for jacob seeing anything hit the tune jacob let's hit the tune
middle-aged white guy let's do it where are we god damn there we are i couldn't find it
keys to your reader glasses because i need i need i've added one to the kitchen because i used to
have one wherever i'd sit and i'd sit in the kitchen and i'd sit in the kitchen and i'd sit in
the kitchen and i'd sit in the kitchen and i'd sit in the kitchen and i'd sit and look at my phone
there's a pair of glasses yeah look at my phone and then i started uh for directions on stuff to
cook i had this time i was like oh no yep yep damn
yeah i have a pair i have a pair next to my chair and i have a pair next to my bed
i just have two just just the two around the house well at first uh my and this is really
fascinating for the listeners but at first like you know obviously reading tiny things was was
where it started just not being able to look at look at small things um so so did you have the
same did you have the same reaction that i did when i started to not be able to read my comic
books i was like what the fuck is wrong with this printing yes uh and the same with like macaroni
and cheese instructions and things like that i'd be like who is this font for what what lilliputians
are picking up and i'd be like what is this font for what what lilliputians are picking up and i'd be
like who is this font for what what lilliputians are picking up these boxes this is ridiculous yeah
and now the problem might be me you see the tv above my head that's the bet that's the tv in my
bedroom so my um uh i'm further away from the tv than like a regular tv viewing kind of thing
uh now i'm having a hard time uh seeing uh the subtitles on shows i'm watching uh from there so
now the other side's going too so now it's time it's time that's both ends it's time
uh but i went right after yeah right after this episode i'm running
over to pearl vision oh nice yeah so they said yes we can help but not today that's right yeah
that was let's do it let's do a whole appointment we'll do the whole thing
which gave me uh some time you know give me some time to think about it and so i started uh
buying a lot of supplements i've uh off of amazon and i think i spent this time trying to cure my
eyesight train your eyes train your eyes in three days so i can call him back never mind i'm fine
right as rain
click i saw some tiktoker he's like problem solved what i tell you about wearing these
glasses and he's got these glasses that just have nothing but little pinholes in them
and he's like i wear these and it fixes my eyes i'm like the fuck you do the fuck it does
you lying asshole the uh you hope it does it yeah i understand that you would like it too
it doesn't know the idea like look i know medical
costs and medical care in this country is complicated annoying and expensive and everything
else but the idea that it's a constant just like no we don't want anyone to know that the simple
blank exists so that we can just rake in the dough on every single ailment that we've come up with
it's just it's a little much sometimes yes it is it is i don't want to sit around and defend the
medical industry but i don't think that the whole eye doctor industry is like shit hope they don't
figure out pinhole glasses that we're doing like yeah my eyes
here's how bad the the medical insurance here is my eyes are terrible we've talked about that on the
show before my eyes are horrible uh you've never seen me without contacts or glasses i can't
function without uh at least one of those things and uh like if this weren't this century if this
were just a few hundred years ago i would just be dead in the woods somewhere right remember there's
an old like back like a decade ago an old netflix show i think it was called godless it was a western
show and it had a guy his glasses broke on that
like a on the terrain and he's yeah and he spent the rest of the series like not able to see and i
was like holy shit yes i was like oh my god i didn't you don't think about that like my worst
fear on vacation like if i leave town if my contacts or glasses get fucked up yeah i can't
do anything yeah i'm just i'm just done no you would cut pinholes and two pieces i would cut
yep you'd fashion a mask
out of it like a placemat maybe fashion a mask you would tape it to your head that's right that's
right man just pinhole your way around portugal and i'd be fine then i'd be fine but no our our
insurance is so bad uh like i i have good i have good insurance i have good health insurance i've
good uh medical and vision insurance and all that kind of stuff there is a surgery that could fix
my eyes because my eyes are so bad i'm not going to be able to see my eyes because my eyes are so
bad i'm not going to be able to see my eyes because my eyes are so bad i'm not going to be able to
see my eyes because my eyes are so bad i can't do like the lasik
thing and so the surgery is basically a cataract surgery where they they take that lens out and
they put a corrective lens in in its place and it's just an implanted contact lens is basically
all it is probably safer than lasik maybe i have no idea who knows uh but i i do know what it does
is is it keeps you from getting cataracts later in life it's also it's also a preemptive surgery
for cataracts preventative because you're doing the cataract surgery before you have cataracts
smart with my astigmatism i'm very likely to have cataracts they will not pay for that surgery now
until they will pay for cataract surgery until you get they will not it's not they will they
will not pay for the surgery that would also correct my vision because that's uh that's an
elective surgery even though i will almost certainly get cataracts in the future and
then i'll have to have the surgery anyway yeah it's fucked it's really this is so stupid it is
it's stupid it's awful i mean well and this is the the kind of obstacles i faced as a man of size
uh trying to address my hip issue for years you know and just being basically you know dismissed
out of hand by the first guy i went to because the doctor didn't have the appropriate eye
prescription and couldn't see you well oh he could see me and he was like oh he was like look here
fatty and i was like motherfucker put these put these pinhole glasses on and you can only eat
things that fit in the eye and you can only eat things that fit in the eye and you can only eat
this pinhole i just i'll never get over i'll never get over the glory hole diet the the the
actual guy that actually helped helped me and fixed my leg and the fact that when they got in
into my hip socket they were like it was basically deteriorated into fragments and dust yeah we're
really surprised how you were walking on that as am i assholes i told you this for you it's fucked
if y'all listen to him bitch about it for the whole time you wouldn't be that surprised buddy
yeah jacob
and i were not surprised yeah it was terrible it was terrible if anything it was better than what
we thought it was gonna be but this is the same thing like why the fuck don't i just you know and
it's it's worse for women i know that too like it's one thing to be a heavy dude but but if you're
a woman forget it my god the shit the fucking and that is the only aspect where it's harder
to be a woman than a man but yes thank goodness only applies in the medical field oh yeah yay
just aggravating as fuck well hope everybody has a good day i'll keep you posted um well jacob do you
think there's any way that you could possibly rectify this because i know that there has
recently been a kerfuffle on tiktok i don't know what other social media sites you frequent or are
party to but there was a guy on tiktok i'm pretty much just i'm pretty much just tiktok paul i just
i just do uh lots and lots of tiktok well he needed he needed a liver transplant right okay and the
the insurance would not cover it they would not go through with it he was ready to do it and you
know he he was gonna die and so he raised a bit of a stink on on his uh tiktok page and it went
very viral and what do you know sure enough they turned around and they did the surgery and he's
gonna live but it takes a couple of million strangers screaming at these mega corporations
to say hey help this person it's fucked up i'm the same way i won't i won't do that i won't help
anyone until there's millions of people experiencing intermittent outrage i would also like a liver
though so uh if everyone could please raise a lot of outrage get jacob a liver i don't want i don't
want any surgery i just want the liver um put it on ice by the way it's a little update on the old uh
duolingo um i've after what i was suggested to be friends with my dead friend i since i've got a lot
of scoops and other people follow me on duolingo i'm following everybody back um i think it's gonna
be really funny if my most popular social media outlet is duolingo um i am eating apples i am
drinking water i am you know uh eating pan i'm asking people if they speak english or espanol
i'm on a roll i'm on a roll yeah uh but but in terms of like hey do does your phone listen to
you do apps listen to other topics and try to compete with each other my instagram apparently
was very jealous of duolingo uh-huh so that they gave me not one but two friend suggestions for
two people who were dead they two dead friends they offered me
to follow back two dead friends just one and two right there first so many dead friends you can
follow what is happening why why would you compete with this yep i think actually matt you have
inadvertently subscribed to cul-de-sac which is the new app that just has you trapped in a
circle of dead friends and you can't escape uh yeah
i'm downloading i have a lot of friends on seance have you guys downloaded seance
that's good that's good
you wanted you wanted to say spanish you got the seance you wanted to say spanish yeah that's right
that's right uh chaotic points out in chat that my duolingo streak is better than my dead friends
so there you go you got that going for me those are wins wins or wins might not have made the
milers club but god damn it that streak is on no problem no problem what are we getting buried with
our phones what's the plan here what are we doing with our what are we doing with our phones i don't
know wait wait wait what what's the hypothesis that made that what's that how does that answer
a question i don't know i'm just thinking like maybe you keep it plugged in throw some kind of
bullshit ai on it and let it keep chirping and chipping away at people long after you're dead
and be like hey man what's up you know it's like wait i thought you're fucking dead yeah i'm dead
i got this ai running my running my shit it's just paul having weird dark thoughts over here i'm doing
fine that's precisely like that i can't think of a more tech bro idea than being like wouldn't it be
great when you as your ai self can let other people know you're dead so they don't have to
find out from anyone else yeah i mean i mean your brain knows for like six minutes or something like
that they say so hey yeah great yeah uh phones are waterproof now so it doesn't that doesn't
mean i can't tell you that you're dead so it doesn't mean you're dead so it doesn't mean you're dead
and i can still it's basically i'd be talking to you from the grave and a submarine it's like the
same time well now the only the only challenge is keeping it powered that's the challenge is how do
you keep the battery going hey how you doing this is the ai jacob how are you i hope you're doing
well jacob is not doing well at all he has passed away i am really sorry to be the one to tell you
about this i am 100 sorry that jacob has passed away and i am 200 sorry to have to be the one to
tell you about it haha yes of course you're sad yeah you're a good friend and jacob wants you to
know that really good job would you like me to break down three different ways for you to pay
homage to jacob in a way that might fit your comfortable lifestyle i know you don't like
mushrooms wink wink i like it i like it yep
this is this is gonna be a new thing it's definitely gonna be a new thing uh yeah yeah
well i mean there's plenty of gravestones with qr codes and shit on them and that stuff's not
gonna stay around forever it's just weird i don't know grave gravestone qr code is actually
that sounds better to me than what we just came up with that seems like a lot of fun oh how so
the idea of just strolling through a graveyard and scanning qr codes is both uh beautiful and
you can do it right now there's plenty of graves with qr codes you can scan it up it'll bring up a
little memorial and pictures and videos and stuff yeah that's what i want i want people on their
phones you know like i really want people just to be in tech just in their day-to-day shit
grieve through the screen grieve through the screen put these vr glasses on and grieve give
me your grief in ai ai grief
uh so my oldest kid's a spoiled brat he's this this this week ends with him going thank god you
figured it out first this this week ends with him going to the sphere with his schoolmates to see
wizard of oz which we still haven't seen uh-huh and then the next day uh they go to disneyland
with the show choir that's that's his thursday friday this week tough tough days but uh uh
the uh message we got for the sphere was hysterical okay so like one is that we have to
fill out photo and press releases for our children in order for them to go you can't go unless you
fill out a photo release because both the sphere and the school need to publish to publicize the
event they're having school kids visit the sphere okay what's what's going to be shown is i've got a
they show in the big nature film wizard of oz yeah no one cares about nature anymore paul
that was when the sphere opened i don't think they even do the nature film anymore
and then uh uh lauren shreve is uh it sounds expensive it is uh we we fundraise throughout
the year you know it's it's death by a thousand donations with schools they just keep beating
you with the same fundraisers i have no idea how much money we gave to make this happen but i know
in like several several increments of time do you think that you gave more money to this than
you would have given if you just paid for the kids to go to these events well certainly disneyland
because their grandmother has a pass so all right yeah certainly yeah so more than free more than
free uh you should have been like yeah yeah you can take my kid to disneyland hold on i'll set
up his ticket then the sphere had a breakdown that was like hey
there'll be no book bags or any kind of carrying permitted into the sphere not even water bottles
you can't bring water bottles or anything into the sphere nothing your children will come in
as they are dressed that's it okay and we will not sell any food or beverage to anyone while
they're in the sphere this is the second point no this is no this is i get this because you get
one peanut allergy and it's all downhill
bottles of water no you don't want nothing it's the desert look give them some water go get your
own camel back or whatever kids aren't camels fuck that this is the first line of the sand i've seen
with anyone with school kids and their access to water because one thing kids have just been able
to be fucking nuts with is that they must have access to these crazy oh my god they're so hydrated
these children nowadays so hydrated mark gates is no peanut water peanut water
there's a market salty and delicious peanut water my waffle house bug hey look at that is that
official waffle house merch it's official waffle house bunk yeah did you buy that at a waffle house
i bought it off the waffle house website because i was raving about waffle i just send me send me
waffle house uh stuff and i was like what there's nothing here i will reusable coffee mug
yeah look at that i like that it wasn't the yellows this is the blue one
that is a classy subtle waffle house and uh but yeah so so the kids can go there they're they may
starve while they are in there but that's what's gonna happen they go in there and they have no
evidence that they were ever there ninjas they must come in and leave without a trace there's
just gonna be a whole sphere filled with starved and desiccated children stuck like mummies to all
the little chairs just i just want to know what the sphere is gonna do when a busload of kids
shows up and they're all carrying water bottles like yeah what are you gonna do it really feels
like like whoever's running the actual like boots on the ground part of the sphere doesn't have kids
and like for like eight meetings they're like and there's a we have another request from school
they're like jesus christ but these school kids want to come here god yeah and so i was like well
it might be good pr all right they better sign photo releases they better have no evidence they
were ever fucking here they better not fucking pee or eat or drink or not like i want to it's like
it's just someone yeah tell them the bathrooms will be closed up tell them we pulled the
bathrooms out there aren't bathrooms anymore we will bring them in through a series of locked
chambers it's a bad idea i think it's a bad idea to bring them there yeah any of it yeah yeah
i think that i think this fear is making a drastic error how about that
uh do your kids are your kids familiar with the wizard of oz yes okay i wonder at what point
well what point will we get to the point where people haven't seen the original wizard of oz
enough to get what's going on at the sphere yeah i don't know i mean you know the whole thing is
that the wicked wicked creates this extra more current curiosity for the original that's true
yeah if anything
couldn't couldn't have thought that this was that
this was going to happen with that of all the you know quote-unquote ip the wizard of oz like you
know that's a crazy it's a crazy ass weird psychedelic the guy who wrote wicked or the
guy who wrote wizard of oz wizard of oz yeah the person who wrote the original yeah the wonderful
world of oz and all that stuff yeah that um that's uh frank bomb right i think so bomb sounds right
yeah so what's fascinating about him is that he's not a wizard of oz he's not a wizard of oz
is that his wife is a woman of some renown who's now flying out of my head um one of the suffragettes
or she can fly no no no i'll fucking find it but uh yeah his whole family situation was really
really interesting and that's a big part of why he put women forward in much of his work
because he's a woman of some renown and he's a woman of some renown and he's a woman of some renown
he he and his family especially his wife are in the forefront of feminism in that time oh wow
oh and it worked women have it so easy now yeah no good job everybody no but it's great i didn't
realize that and it's good it's good that it's good that it just puts women forward and i don't
necessarily make it like oh it's a pro-woman thing so it's good oh pro-women oh pro all right
yeah so i still haven't gotten anything in the sphere so my kids will my kid will beat me to
the sphere experience there do you have a a desire to do you have anything you want to go see at the
sphere i don't have like an 800 desire yeah it's just the price point thing like even even the
movies like yeah because because i'm not gonna see wizard of oz by myself so i think that's like
200 something dollars right right but it's still a hundred dollar day if i take the fam right sure
so that's like it's just it just it just doesn't add up or
whatever yeah our pal lewis was looking out for me for a little while for first fear stuff that
was popping up he runs that liquor distribution company oh right okay uh but still the spheres
it's tight it's a tight ticket it's pricey it's a tight it's a tight ticket well uh if nine inch
nails ever plays a sphere that will prop that that could very well get me to vegas they did
uh metallica the metallica thing is like that's that but that's gonna be pretty great that's gonna
be i bet
i bet i'll see that one money so much money it'll be i think it's gonna be a lot of money and and uh
but if i ever get the opportunity to i would go see the metallica the sphere that's for sure yeah
are people making films of these concerts yes uh several of them yes okay i know there were
films of the u2 one well i know see that's the thing like trent resner was working very closely
with um james cameron at one point to put together a tour film and it just
fell apart at the 11th hour but i would love still love to see all that um i still have
i just realized i haven't i still haven't sat down and watched uh ozzy osbourne's last concert
that that big huge concert they did shortly before he died that he actually performed at so two things
from that you guys have both gotten really kind of contemplated or beating yourselves up for not
seeing stuff it's really kelly has turned into a scarecrow and jack was just on uh tv talking about
how the benefit money was way over inflated i guess they they had claimed like 190 million
dollars or something like that for ozzy's concert yeah remember the giant big time money that was
supposed to be coming in i don't remember hearing anything about the money but i believe it yeah
this latest interview jack was like no it was like 10 million dollars yeah it's like it wasn't
190 million dollars but then part of me goes oh wasn't it jack
oh really mr runs the till
yeah as far as i know we donated i don't think we got any money our way
all the money went out no i've got a lot of expenses here if somebody could reimburse me
that'd be that'd be really great exactly exactly so i don't know i don't know uh yeah so my kid
my kid will do that and then i'll i'll go i'll actually take all of the school to metallica
that's what i'll do
good man that would be hip as shit well for your for your next kid's birthday you could have uh
five of their friends uh show up they could learn to play all of the metallica music on uh real
instruments and then you could book the sphere for them to open for metallica before metallica
sphere concert you could do that and then the next day you could throw a birthday party for your kids
and wanted me to tell you matt and wanted me to tell you i don't know if you know this matt but
there is a thing about metallica that i don't know if you know this but there is a thing about metallica
you could do for your kids and their friends relatively inexpensively if you wanted to show
up like a boss uh starbucks has just unveiled a mr beast drink oh yeah that's smart of starbucks
you could take the kids to starbucks for a mr mr beast pick me up i think that would be like number
one uh on the kids list like if i if i if they could meet a celebrity i believe both my kids
would choose mr beast really really yeah
damn that's sad huh i know i started watching much less obtainable for them than audio guy for a podcast
i uh yeah i mean they we just started watching beast games too the second season of beast games
came out this is admittedly not as psychologically torturous as the first season so far i've only
watched the first two episodes lessons have been learned there's been lawsuits have been settled
not just a bunch of people being terrible right off the bat and just making everyone cry
there's been a lot of tears in this first two seasons um and it actually is much more tears
and actually much more of like competition stuff which is which you feel like legit things happen
with winners and losers so i do think they've learned something from the first season which
wasn't like go in a room until one of you has a psychological breakdown and then you lose
it would have been difficult for them to i i
how hard would it have been for them to just recreate that first season
oh if they if you're just like do exactly the same thing here's the new people
yeah you would have been like fuck no yeah i can't yeah it'd be if they did it again it'd be a felony
no i thought it was so funny because he's he is remarkably uh not empathetic uh and he hosts like
his authentic reactions of what he laughs at or like what gets him like uh a little a little
stirring is always like wow he just has no room for him to do anything he wants to do
uh another human heart in there just not right not in there um and uh there's one game where
they had to wear circles on the colored circles on the back of their head and there was uh different
circle colors on the floor and within 10 seconds you had to run and be in the proper color okay
that matched the back of your head so it means you had to ask uh the person next to you what
color is in the back of your head or whatever and so you quickly looked around to see who you had a
line with and you had to ask the person next to you what color is in the back of your head
and it would be truthful to you and in this particular round everyone was truthful with
one another no one wanted to fuck anyone over oh nice and so everyone kept going to the proper
colored circles and he kept being like if this is supposed to be a bluffing game and if no one
plays the game then we have to find another way to eliminate people and you will not like it and
he had to like admonish them for not fucking each other over and it's sure enough they did
they just started drawing people at random and eliminating people uh because everyone's
being truthful and even after the first rounds of that happening it never got the bluff game going
they just eliminated people arbitrarily until it got down so that game was just people well you know
that gives me a little hope that creeping fascism might have some speed bumps along the way oh no i
think i think that is a i'm i'm not even terribly surprised to hear hear that honestly i've seen
several things now uh like reality tv games i go down weird rabbit holes on these reality tv game
shows especially uh foreign-made games and i'm not even surprised to hear that honestly i've seen
some of the foreign-made ones yeah and uh i just got done with a korean one called something like
the it translates to something like the devil's game yeah and it is not a well-made show uh but
the game that they that they built to to build to to film the show around is a fascinating game
and it was there were people who were doing kind of what you're talking about matt there was one
guy specifically he was like i'm gonna try and play this game where nobody gets eliminated until
the final episode we're just i want
to play this game where no one gets eliminated and we just play for the prize at the end and
that's it wow and it didn't work out that way but like he had real momentum going and just like
kindness and working together is definitely something that is in in the face of shitty
people doing shitty things is definitely something that is making a resurgence i mean i think people
recognize that it's a needed commodity and and they're filling a void i think yes and i mean
it's a good point that should be represented in those kinds of
more uh exciting or mainstream or attractive kind of media ways people are generally good
good like like the problem yes the problem is that what makes the news is very right now we're we're
living in an unprecedented era of blatant power grabs by very powerful people right right and it
used to be even the power grabbers would have to pretend to be altruistic or pretend to be you know
uh caring in some way they had to do at least one press conference where it wasn't just about the oil
could you imagine if you know as uh elon musk keeps winning court cases of anyone trying to be in the
way of him becoming the most obscenely rich person on earth right and he keeps winning these court
cases and tesla keeps battling to pay him the most amount of money possible and the thing that i find
generally baffling if i were a major tesla shareholder i would just be furious yeah all the
time and it's this it's this tech bro like messiah culture where they just make anyone who's come up
with a good idea and got fucking really lucky um yeah become the most you know worship person on
earth and therefore these things can't exist without the worship person being a part of it
and uh it's really strange but could you imagine if he said hey if you if since everyone's since
i'm making all this money i've decided to make dedicate blank of my income to go to these other
people but he doesn't right i mean look there are plenty of examples of people who who have
you know uh like right bloomberg soros there are plenty of people who have made sure uh that bill
gates has spent a lot of his money and influenced with altruistic endeavors so it's not it's not
without examples that uh that exist but it's just not the culture it's just simply not the way it's
it's going and so right now we have an era where very few people are being blatantly greedy
for both money and power and going out of their way to affect people's lives that have nothing to
do with it right and this is yeah this is a weird thing and those people are inviting other people's
kids to come to these weirdly elaborate birthday parties for their kids just to entertain it's not
it's not free for the other parents i mean they have to do they have to spend the time and the
with their children uh the parent did uh offered to reimburse anyone for expenses for for uh ready
supplies and begged them not to spend more than twenty dollars so uh but but but it's interesting
the thought did cross the mind obviously for that yes of course
oh uh but yeah well but i i think the majority of people are still good and the majority of people
are empathetic and look out for each other and i do too and we see it with people putting together
like for example even the crazy ass liver story that you told paul millions of people did rally
right yes like you know like yeah you know it's like we we we do look out for for people all the
time i did you see the uh the field doctor pepper thing uh i have a lot of friends in minneapolis so
i'm haphazardly now uh donating to numerous couples who are trying to get their loved one
out of uh detention from uh ice agency although they are citizens so yeah uh
well matt i'm glad that this has i'm glad that all these people's discomfort has provided a way
for you to feel a little bit better about yourself i'm a good person so yeah yeah no you're doing
great matt yeah i mean you can't have my liver but other than that you're good we're fine what
about part of it all right let's talk all right all right all right it grows back what's the
doctor better friend do that i had a friend do a live uh donation live liver donation oh wow
because your liver is one of your only organs that
does grow back yeah it regenerates yeah yeah i mean yours yours is a strong term for you jacob
but like the general one's liver can grow back yeah yeah a liver can grow back a liver can go
back there's this creator on tiktok who uh she was like hey i got a jingle for dr pepper she's like
dr pepper baby it's good and nice do do do and people just glommed onto it kept sharing it and
doing remixes of it and full instrumentation everything dr pepper finally ponied up some
dough to her and they've used it in a national commercial oh nice it's probably gonna be a super
bowl ad yeah yeah it's a very viral fun and i would like to take this moment to encourage that
person to go over to preachingfund.com with your new windfall of cash head over to preachingfund.com
yeah get us closer to that three billion dollar mark that's right that's right get us up there
yeah yeah and uh you know who else would like to get us closer to that three billion dollar mark
that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by oh where did it it's over here
guys uh marcus mcgillicud oh no we did that one luxury abandoned homes uh janky steve's fruit
cups that's right it's from dead laszlo in 2026 who's one for 2026 i think janky steve's fruit
cups yeah oh oh man oh i got um what you hungry oh man you want a snack oh boy i got over here
del monte del monte uh yeah uh what's left of a of a something what's left i mean yeah i ate some of
it janky steve what you can't you can't be eating other people's fruit cups a little bit of fruit
cocktail still left go ahead have some i don't want to have it after you've already all i did
was drink that syrup i leave the nuggets i leave the fruit parts fruit i leave the nuggets in there
i just drink the syrup and i don't even i don't even break the whole thing i just
a vampire bite the plastic wrap on the top and
slurping out
oh yeah
i'm looking through each piece of fruit through the pinhole you've left with your tooth and i can
see it perfectly and that's right or better yeah well now you can now you're improving your vision
and getting some fruit cup and why why janky steve janky steve selling you leftover fruit
janky steve janky steve come on and get your leftover fruit i know you're hungry and you're
going to get some fruit cup and suck it out of the thing when i put my mouth on the fruit cup and sucked it out yeah janky steve janky steve only a little bit of disease janky steve janky steve only a little bit of mouth disease i don't think you could get all my canker sores from where i suck the drink out from the fruit i don't know for sure but i can't be a hundred percent good luck with the fruit that i leave you
janky steve janky steve i sure do want some fruit cup and suck it out of the thing when i put my mouth on the fruit cup and suck it out yeah janky steve janky steve only a little bit of mouth disease i don't think you could get all my canker sores from where i suck the drink out from the fruit i don't know for sure but i can't be a hundred percent good luck with the fruit that i leave you
janky steve janky steve i sure do want some delicious fruit juice i just want the juice
from the cup all i do is drink the juice from the cup every time someone offers me fruit i say
can you just juice it for me and they do and they do and they put it in a cup for me
who janky steve janky steve janky steve sucking all your fruit drink when he wants to sucking it
and drinking it all day long suck it suck suck that fruit juice give me that fruit cocktail
when they said fruit cocktail i envisioned a cup like a cosmo and that's what i only settle for
beverages i want my fruit in beverage form that's all i like i just want to drink it i just want to
drink fruit fruit juice fruit juice fruit juice give me all that fruity juice give it to me slow
through a straw and let me tell you what
more thing yes janky steve i also sell it to you for a discount how how how janky steve janky steve
i sell stuff a little cheaper than i should i'm just losing money that's the way i play the game
i don't have any kind of discount except to lose my own investment
so go ahead and take advantage of janky steve like the world has the world's
taking advantage of janky steve janky steve shouldn't change things now fuck it keep on
keep on we're taking advantage of janky steve and the deals you get you get some slurped on fruit
have it go ahead have it go ahead i'll deliver it to you i'll deliver it right to your house
i actually bought a bunch of janky steve firewood from yeah yeah the other day and
i delivered it to you didn't i you did how how
janky steve janky steve i got a broke down bike that i used to deliver stuff i also have a wagon
on the back of the bike it doesn't go very fast or very far that's how i go i drive my old wagon
and my old fucking bike and i take my shit where i can't give you what you need go ahead and call
me anytime day or night i'm ready to deliver with my bike and my wagon sucking on fruit all the way
to your house because that's what i do
that's what i'm giving you the sucked on fruit you only get sucked on fruit delivered straight
to your house through my rusty old wagon i don't know back on my bike that's right that's right
and it's discounted which we already talked about that before you lose i lose my money on the
discount that's just how it goes uh anybody need a special order of a very special fruit
uh hey uh jakey steve uh sorry we we didn't hit record at the beginning of the ad uh we just have
to go back to the top yeah could you just cue us in the back of the car and we'll be right back
all right yeah all right all right yeah great go ahead today's show is brought to you by jakey
steve's fruit cups what you might not know is jakey steve is also an audio engineer
how i didn't know that how how jakey steve jakey steve i just go ahead and push the button on my
computer i make it record when i want it to record and then i tape the thing and i send it on down
the road jakey steve jakey steve jakey steve go ahead let's go
what down the road down the road i put it in my wagon and i drive my bike i drive my bike and i
send it down the road audio files manually absolutely what do you think i'm a millionaire
i lose money on every fruit deal i do this is a problem this is not a good business plan at all
not at all also it turns out all i'm doing is stealing fruit cups from the local grocery store
how how how how jakey steve jakey steve i wear a really big coat and put it up my sleeve
jakey steve jakey steve i wear oversized clothes and put it up my sleeve jakey steve i'm a robber
jakey steve i'm a thief jakey steve you should be confessing to this in your commercial what
what i shouldn't be what i should be confessing to crime yeah whatever
president does it all day it doesn't matter anymore there's no rules
i have a lawyer how how how how jakey steve jakey steve i went to law school for 15 years
jakey steve was actually a lawyer 15 years of law study i am a lawyer i'm barred in seven states i
i'm barred in seven states i'm barred in seven states i'm barred in seven states i practice is
mostly in accidents accident lawyer jakey steve jakey steve the accident lawyer doesn't do a lot
of good when i'm trying to protect my business rights and my fruit cup business it doesn't
really apply because i haven't caused a lot of injury or had any injury to me yeah
ladies and gentlemen it is time
oh haddy
jakey steve advertisement i don't think we've heard the last of jakey steve
oh i can't wait to see that tapestry
he might even be he might be center square the next uh
uh
hollywood square usurping paul lynn jakey steve you oh i don't know i don't know maybe all right
i spoke too soon corner we'll see we'll see another important square another important
square they're all important oh hey guys after the resounding success of my 80s movie scooper
d trilogy i went back to the drawing board for a completely original idea that however proved to
be a whole thing so i'm with plan b a reboot please enjoy this completely fresh take on a
stale concept that i'll keep rehashing long past its overstayed welcome and that is from keister
sunday the categories are 90s comedy 90s horror 90s action and 90s sci-fi that's me first i'm hyped
for this all right i'll take a uh i'll take a 90s sci-fi i'll take that for two hundo after uncle
fester falls in love with the mom from stepbrothers he says fuck it and gives up time traveling to
stay in the old west leaving teen wolf to go back home and do nothing notable for nine years until
stewart little came out uh that would be uh back to the future part three that's right future three
paul hmm i will try 90s horror for 800 oh robert rodriguez's 1996 horror
action classic starring everyone's favorite batman and everyone's favorite creepy foot fetishist
suddenly becomes a vampire film halfway through when they end up at titty twister an all-night
mexican bar from dusk till dawn from dusk till dawn of course that's the 800 one wow that's a
great movie oh yeah matt and that was also a perfect uh explanation of it too i need to watch
that again 90s comedy 200 please
future stars of the critically acclaimed smash hits the master of the disguise and the love guru
co-star in this 1992 skit turned feature film about two illinois losers doing a public access show
out of one of their parents basement well written uh wayne's world that is wayne's world of course
a master of disguise and love guru i want to be a master of disguise
turtle turtle turtle i'll try 90s action 200
you can think that way
i think this overrated pseudo-psychological 1999 film where ted theodore logan and clark kent's boss
save humanity from enslavement inside a computer-generated dream world
for a decade of annoying parodies and the term red-pilled
that of course is the lawnmower man
the matrix the matrix
yes
paul 90s
sci-fi for eight hundred
uh where is that over here
daily double here's where it all turns around
everything's coming up paul this 1994 film has a pyramid and a portal on the poster i made it the
800 question because i never saw the film so that's the only clue i have for you i bet paul
knows what it is from that vague description though uh yeah that's gonna be stargate
mother
fucker that is stargate isn't it
that is stargate
jesus christ
god damn it
what else could it be
the only better clue would be uh
what's his name
the guy
moving on i don't do you need to rub our noses in it
spader spader spader
spader would have put it over the edge
uh i'll do 90s action for 800
mace windu helps the singer from the critically acclaimed the return of bruno solve alfred's
fun puzzles around the big apple in this 1995 action thriller it was the third in the series
and they never made another one
i don't know who the singer
oh shit um
oh man i'm not even trying to give you a hint on this one
um
,
i think that i think this movie was uh difficult
uh
tedious arduous
hard day's night
um
close close close
uh
if you're if you're if you're rolling in the back alley what are you using
uh a garbage truck
no
i'll pass
you're shooting passes to me
oh
die hard but which it's the what's the subtitle yeah that's the thing and i knew paul already
knew the die hard one uh is this i'm not i'm not confident in what it's called either i don't know
yeah yeah no i knew i knew you knew the die hard part though is it it's not it's not is it die
harder i think it's the third one it's the third one but is it die harder is or is that with a
vengeance die hard with a vengeance die hard with a vengeance maybe it is die hard with a vengeance
it might be die hard with i'll try that i'll try die hard with a vengeance okay die hard with a
vengeance yes definitely not have gotten that one kudos uh it's me i'll try a 90s comedy for 800
in this comedy rudy and mitzi shore's idiot son befriend a prehistoric george of the jungle
humor is supposed to
you
follow instead what actually followed was son-in-law and biodome
son-in-law is pretty good movie son-in-law is son-in-law i believe my wife uh unironically
really enjoys this is a good movie uh this movie though has that guy in it
and my wife is screaming in the car uh and just coincidentally or because of this question i mean
coincidence she's always screaming in the car but she
loves this movie she loves this movie it's one of her favorites it's brendan frazier come on pass it
to me baby give me the rock toss me the pill uh come on jacob you got die hard this is one of
this one uh encino man oh you got it mother fucker you got it i knew it was a place you got it
paul uh 90 sci-fi for 600 please
let's see here in the middle of his johnny depp phase monica bellucci's future ex-husband directed
this somehow deptless star-studded bomb in 1996 about hilariously sarcastic spacemen
attacking the united states it was based on a series of 1960s tops trading cards mars attacks
no i'm sorry it's also encino man i wish that was such a strange film oh i love that movie matt
uh
i will do 90s comedy for 600
word association time amish fake hand comb over oh uh fuck it's the bowling movie with bill murray
yeah uh
and uh woody harrelson yeah woody harrelson's
that's a funny fucking movie too yeah it is that is a good movie
he'll pick that spare up when my hair falls out
i forget the name of the movie but it's a good movie
i forget the name of the movie but it's a good movie but it's a good movie but it's a good movie
they pass i wonder how that holds up
uh it passes to me
fuck
uh throw me the rock yeah i can't think of it paul go ahead kingpin kingpin that's it
uh it's me i'll do uh 90s action for 600
and this globally celebrated action blockbuster president lone star and the guy who tried to cook
chris rock's face like chicken lead america and saving all the non-america countries from aliens
running windows 95 on their mother ship hilarious hilarious i believe this is independence day yeah
those are some great clues oh yeah and when i go to the night when i go without a fight
case oh that speech killing it paul uh 90s horror for 600
daily double oh here we go cracking it out for cracking it 800 wow i'm getting my ass kicked huh
you are getting your ass i just noticed that i was like holy shit matt is losing badly uh
subterranean creatures are from are closer than six degrees from footloose and joe dirt's dad
who are fighting for survival in a small nevada town but the monsters are no match
for reba mcintyre's comically large artillery stash tremors
tremors of course i knew that one guys you did know that one thanks guys uh paul now has a lead
with 5600 points i have 2600 points has 200 points and the only questions left are all 400 and 200
so there we go that's right we burned all the hard ones there is a daily double out there though
no need uh paul i got and i think i got both of them did you already get both of them yep
oh shit all right never mind i think you're up well i'll do nine i guess we'll find out
the dad from the conjuring falls for rachel green and begins to take his cubicle job in stride
after an occupational hypnotherapist dies before he can end the trace
he put him under in this 1999 bomb turned cult hit office space
office space is correct best i saw that in the theater hey i got one guys
fucking nice thanks thanks for having me fantastic
matt donnelly everyone matt donnelly love that movie i'll close out 90s action for 400
yeah that's right deuce bigelow i don't know how to use the three seashells
who in the fuck knows how to wipe their ass with three seashells fuck you
oh sorry i misread the first part yeah that's right deuce bigelow sorry it was at deuce bigelow
not about deuce bigelow uh that would be uh the the 90s classic demolition man yeah
paul you got 90s horror or 90s sci-fi what do you want let's go sci-fi sci-fi for 400
paul verhoeven rounds out a trilogy of unrelated violent satires with this 1997 film starring
tarzan christmas jones and doogie hauser about a future fascist government false flagging a war
with space bugs to prop up their war-based economy oh that is um
oh why is it going away from me i can see it oh yeah soldier fight soldier fight that's it
starship troopers that's it starship troopers no i'm sorry it's soldier fight bugs soldier
soldier fight you should have gone with your first instinct paul soldier fight well i was close
dickie steve 90s horror for 200 or 400 bucks
directed soldier fight soldier fight bugs on mtv
uh i will take 90s horror for 400 just see if i can at least make it oh get some extra points there
12 years before she filmed the sexiest hot tub scene of all time uh reboot matlock yeah saves
sunny corallone from a car accident and then infects one of the most ball retractingly
painful acts ever filmed for an academy award winning movie r.i.p rob reiner misery yes
reboot matlock reboot matlock is great that's pretty good i'm closing out the category and
the game 90s horror for 200 west craven revived the whodunit slasher subgenre with this 1996 film
starring that girl from party of five monica and the guy that owns bozo the clown spoiler
alert it was shaggy and that weirdo from the craft
was that scream that's it or was it the other one it was scream all right scream
i'm gonna go with paul's hint and go with scream
scream is my hints are always pretty good your hints are always pretty good you didn't need to
save at that time because paul crushed us with 6 000 points i got second with 3200 and matt got a
respectable score and i got a respectable score and i got a respectable score and i got a respectable
third place with 1000 points well done matt and well done keister sunday for that hell yeah that
was great is on my magic podcast we were uh making fun of like basically a telltale sign you haven't
written your trick well enough as if you are the only one going like wait what uh what's this over
here right and i was laughing at jakey steve going like how how and i was like paul should
just lecture with jakey steve at magic at magic
uh convention just really you can just you just toss it to me be like how how how what wait what
why why why um i want to thank the following people who uh all got herpes from jakey steve
that's uh jorge vasallo joseph foster joseph paul rero joseph pen grazio just joshua wilson judy
schneider joseph paul rero joseph pen grazio joshua wilson judy schneider joseph paul rero joseph pen grazio joshua wilson judy schneider
joseph paul rero joseph pen grazio joshua wilson judy schneider joseph paul rero joseph pen grazio joshua wilson judy schneider
kai uh mcmillan keister sunday keith corning kenny colin tony craig ruth kristen kledek
kurt egner kurt hendrickson kyle wells kylie cones larry goodale lee uh mcgarrell i think
lee popsicle and leon cox the following people have all died from dehydration inside the sphere
lord can see how because they weren't allowed to bring in their
drinks luke mellon m hertz mama ninja scoop mark sadowski mario rosa mark madison
matts lengren matt daughtery matt glowacki matt mckenzie matthew dugan matthew smeele
melissa archiga merlin's barn podcast michael calder michael elsroth michael shaw
mike j nielsen mike six and mike wentz and the following scoops all know that we recorded this
sometime in the past that's me for uh me for revia me for revia i think so mitch hedberg lives
mitzula mohan there monod knock scoop monica day myra nate taylor nicholas newman nick dingman
nikki benoit oh nee nee okini okini maybe okay i like it okie scoop one fell scoop patrick mishare
paul clayton paula pete mortis pete romano peter bougie and peter hines thank you so much everybody
thank you so much if you want to be
thanked on air with your name perfectly pronounced then head on over to preaching
fun.com and select a tier that fits your budget today
or if you think matt's friends need to put a little more effort into their kids birthday
parties head over to farts in a bag.biz
farts in a bag.biz
that's farts in a bag.biz that along with preaching fun.com it takes you over to our
patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air
we are dependent on our paid patreon subscribers so please if you think this show is worth more
than zero dollars preaching fun.com farts in a bag.biz head over there you can subscribe on a
monthly basis you can subscribe on a yearly basis that saves you a little bit of money and you can
also help us out because we can see what our yearly budget is a little bit better and you can also gift
subscriptions to a friend i still stand by gifting someone a paid subscription to a podcast is the
most hilarious way to get them to listen to that podcast i agree yeah all right well thanks for
listening everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
the waffle house oh yeah i did learn today this waffle house has a merch page on their website
very happy to know that
see ya