It's that time, it's my favorite part of the show.
This is the part of the show where we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
I want to thank Scoop Brady, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Cata, Slippery Caye Motherfucker, The
Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, and Travis Jaguari.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks, deliver that fucking
ice cream straight to people's fucking ear holes.
Head over to PreachingFun.com, PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
And now, a program.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
I confirmed that my wife's band that we talked about on the last episode is in fact not a
secret.
So I am not in trouble.
Okay, great.
That's good.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Socials sitting in Pittsburgh.
That's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt Donnelly, and in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio
Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
Yeah, my wife's band, next year, 2026, is the 250th anniversary of the United States
of America.
Are you sure we're going to make it to that?
No I'm not.
We're prepping just in case.
But yeah, next year is the 250th anniversary of the United States of America, which also
means a bunch of cities and towns across the country are also turning 250 years old.
So this coming summer, there's just going to be an assload of town festivals and city
festivals and fairs and all of this stuff.
And so SJ and one of her agents had this idea, like, let's put together just an American
rock band.
And I just kind of do, yeah, so that's the style.
My favorite band name that I've come up with so far is Imminent Domain.
It's not quite right, but we do really like that name.
That's beautiful American stuff, though.
That's it right there.
Yeah, it is.
It really ties in.
So with us in studio, we have Dr. Mike is here.
Dr. Mike.
Dr. Mike!
Thank you, guys.
In studio, I mean, we're on Zoom and you're in Australia.
Right, yes, as close as I could get.
In a room, it's Dr. Mike.
Now how old is your country?
What birthday are you guys celebrating?
Depends on who you ask.
If you ask the indigenous population who have been there for sixty five thousand years, I
would say that the country is many, many, many thousands of years old.
But if we're talking about colonial, seventeen eighty eight.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
So what does that make it?
Not that old.
Not as old as the US.
Just a little behind us.
Not far.
Yeah.
We're seventeen seventy six.
Oh, there you go.
Is that number is that is that year a number that Australians just know?
Like I think I think most citizens of the US know the know the name or they don't know
the date.
Seventeen seventy six.
Is that is that something?
You know what?
The reason why I know it is because there is a part of Australia called seventeen eighty
eight, which is where they landed.
And that's the only way that I remember it.
Despite your way of history, you guys don't agree on what your oldest bar is on your three
bars that argue that's their oldest bar.
That's the oldest bar.
There's one down the road for me, which is supposed to be the oldest in Australia.
Yeah.
And then you go for a drive down the road again and there's another one.
I like this.
But you wrote a book.
I did.
Yes.
The Body A to Z.
You've sent me a blurb to to preview it and I read none of it.
I read not not a single part of it.
And I appreciate it.
I think it's I think I think it's it's fine.
I only sent you the blurb with twenty four hours ago.
Yeah.
That's not your fault.
And I was like, I said, now the procrastinating is on my end.
But I know you've been working on this book for a while.
So tell us what went into the book is you always know the title.
What motivated it?
The book's called The Body A to Z.
I'm a professor of medicine in Australia.
I've got a YouTube channel where I teach people how the human body works.
I've got a podcast where we do the same thing.
And I'm on social media talking about, you know, this and that in regards to people's
anatomy and physiology.
And in all honesty, the only medium I hadn't touched yet was book form.
And Matt, who I do all my YouTube and podcast stuff with, likes to likes to joke that the
people who watch my tick tocks, probably the Venn diagram of those that watch my tick tocks
and read, it doesn't overlap significantly.
So that's right.
Two distinct circles.
Right.
Yeah.
Two very distinct circles with a big gap in between.
I've got bad news for you if you think you're finding readers on our show.
Hey, hold on.
So yeah.
And the book came out a couple of weeks ago.
It's an alphabetized.
It's not a textbook, obviously.
It's an alphabetized journey through some of the lesser known structures and functions
of the body.
It's for anyone from 12 to 112.
We go through topics like the external anal sphincter.
We talk about why, for example, we that is important for 12 year olds to talk about that.
I'm glad I'm glad you said the age thing before talking about that.
Yes.
There's there's there's a lot of there's a lot of interesting topics.
I think the the Scrotox topic, have you guys heard of Scrotox?
I have.
Sadly, I know what it is.
So I believe I know exactly what it is.
I can't wait to hear you describe it, Matt.
If you are worried that your ball sack looks older than it should, all you got to do is
pull a little Botox in that bad boy to de wrinkle it, smooth it right out.
Yeah, man.
Who is that?
Smooth it out.
A baby's ball sack.
I met a guy who actually had Scrotox and I was like, run away.
I mean, it's true that one third of the ICS hosts have had it done.
Dr. Mike, regarding Scrotox, is that something you would advise or recommend?
No, I wouldn't.
For a couple of I mean, one, I'm not sure.
I mean, the aesthetics, I don't know who is staring, who is staring at that part of the
body.
I don't know.
And if you've got a common misperception, it's a common misperception that people do
it for vanity.
It's for aerodynamics.
Well, OK, if it is aerodynamics, I'll give you if it's for aerodynamics, because then
that means you're already shaving.
Right.
But if you do that without the intent of shaving every day, you're just wasting your time because
you can't see the non-wrinkle with the hair in the way.
That's why I started putting Botox in my chin.
Frozen Cusser is right, though.
It helps with some people who have excessive sweating of their balls.
They will do that as well, because Botox paralyzes the muscles in that area.
So one, the aesthetics, two, the sweating.
But the ass sweatings.
Exactly.
Three, the aerodynamics.
So you have a very informative YouTube videos, you have over a million subscribers.
You must get some strange questions to answer as a doctor from YouTube.
What are some of the strangest questions you've been asked?
I would say the strangest questions, I did call back radio for three years on our ABC
radio station and the people that would call and the questions that were asked.
I mean, there was one guy that that said he could smell snakes so he could walk into a
shed.
Yes.
You heard me.
He said he could walk into a shed and know where a snake was in the shed by his nose.
And he wanted me to explain how he could do it.
He doesn't know why.
He just said, I knew where it was.
And I said, what did it smell like?
He said, I had a musky, musky smell and I could pinpoint exactly where in the shed this
snake was.
Did you just tell him he's clearly house-slytherin?
There was another guy, he wasted a genie's wish.
Like what would you do for the other two?
It was the oddest super power I've ever heard.
Really?
I'm getting a thing.
I'll be back.
Paul has announced that he was getting a thing and left.
Hope he's okay.
Paul's scrotal botox person has arrived to the house.
He's got to let them in.
They have a lot of set up.
Paul's going to his garage, maybe he'll smell a snake while he's in there.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Maybe he can locate one for us.
In Australia though, isn't it, I mean, isn't that kind of a bullshit trick to be able to
be like, this shed has a snake in it?
That's just a safe bet, right?
Like, yeah, yeah, there's a snake in that shed.
Point in a corner and there's a snake.
It's not even 50/50.
It's just, it's likely there's a snake.
No, I got a lot of strange calls.
One guy that was trying to argue with me about, for some reason, sunglasses don't protect
your eyes in any way.
I didn't understand his point.
And he kept referring to his Turkish friend as evidence and saying that I've got a Turkish
friend who's never worn sunglasses and his eyes are okay.
So explain that, which I found difficult.
I cannot, I can't explain that.
So he had a one person case study.
Yeah, he just called up, he called up and he goes, I've got one for you.
I've got a Turkish mate, never worn sunglasses and his eyes are totally fine.
Explain that.
Did he believe it was tied to his friend being Turkish?
Was that part of the deal?
Did the Turkish have heartier eyeballs?
He did refer to him as a Turk at least a dozen times in the question.
I don't know why I was so focused on this friend is a quote unquote Turk.
How long have you been working on the book?
So the book took us about 12 months to write.
God, I have to say writing a book is not an enjoyable process.
Many people refer to it as like, like, like, like in like surgical ways, like it was like
losing a limb or like, like they basically just all talk.
Most authors talk about writing a book as if it's torture.
Yeah.
I would say it was, I would say it was like losing every limb and then getting pushed down
a hill and trying to keep your, keep your balance.
It was, it was just trying to find the time to write a book and then, you know, you've
got to, you need a lot of intense time.
You can't write 30 minutes of a book.
You've got to sit down and get into it and, and figure out how you're going to present
it.
And Matt and I aren't writers.
So we have to learn how to write during this process.
We're academics.
We know how to write academic papers, but to write something that is fun and enjoyable
for everybody to read was not easy.
Now Paul helped you a little bit with, with, with jokes, is that right?
Yeah, so we're writing a second book at the moment and Paul, which is going to be A to
Z of diseases and Paul is helping us punch it up.
So we're throwing him some of our draft chapters and he's sending back some of his, so, you
know, he's got some very good, very funny quips, but he's also got his typical obscure,
you know, metal lyrics from a band that nobody's ever heard of.
We might not necessarily keep that particular reference.
That's your mistake.
That's good.
I actually wanted you to talk to you about Paul when he wasn't on air and then you did.
So it's good.
This is, this is what now he's coming back.
No, no, he's been, Paul has been fantastic.
Which is definitely all that was said.
Dr. Mike said that you've, you're, you're, you're, uh, you're doing some additional writing
for A to Z diseases.
I am working on some, uh, punch up, uh, editing for, uh, the chapters.
Yeah.
It's been a lot.
How do you think that's going?
I think it's going great.
Um, I mean, I can only say they've been very kind, uh, in their responses to my, uh, silly
stuff.
You've been fantastic.
So all has been silly.
Yeah.
Absolutely fantastic.
It's been great.
It's been wonderful.
Uh, I can, what, what's fun for me is having this, this, uh, opportunity with Dr. Mike
allows me to now proudly say I am juggling basically four jobs at once, which is awesome.
Uh, welcome to America 2025.
Well, you've been, it's, it's been super helpful for us.
Um, you know, Matt and I, we think we're funny.
We're by no means funny and when we get into that mindset of writing something about the
body, we tend to lose, I'm worried that we lose humor because we're trying to get facts
and you're pulling us back in with the humor, which is brilliant.
Uh, it's been, it's been really fascinating for me.
I'm learning a ton of stuff.
This latest chapter that you just sent me, can I speak on that at all?
Yeah, absolutely.
So it's all about the dancing sickness, which I am actually familiar with.
So what I'll do is Michael send me the stuff and I'll, I'll read it and then I'll just
let it go for a day or two and let it percolate and then come back to it.
Um, but yeah, the, the dancing sickness, I don't know if you guys are familiar with this,
but it was a, uh, mold in the bread.
You remember this Jacob?
Well, it's shaking like you got the St. Vitus dance.
That was it.
It's the same thing.
That's exactly the town that it happened in.
And so, yeah, people, uh, people got affected by this and they've just danced themselves
to death.
Uh, many people did because it gave them these weird, uh, brain conditions from ingesting
this bad mold that came from, what kind of grain was it?
Mike?
Oh, that's a good question.
I can't remember.
I think it was oat grain.
I'm actually wrong.
Someone should write a book about this.
Oh yeah.
I think it, I think it was oat grain.
But anyway, it was moldy and that's what it was.
And it caused people to get sick.
Nobody knew what it was.
You know, of course everybody thought it was possession or some kind of, or something wrong
with the water, a million different theories came up, but then it spread to a bunch of
different places.
It's crazy, but they finally figured it out.
Thank God.
Our FDA is rolling back protections on shit so we can get this dancing going again.
That's right.
You that, that is a bit frightening.
A bit point because I mean, well, we said, we said Paul, a chapter on lead poisoning
and the potential link between lead poisoning and mass murders, you know, the way things
can become contaminated quite easily.
And without oversight, that can lead to a huge amount of issues.
I think one of my favorite chapters with the new book that Paul's helping us with at the
moment, um, is, uh, a disease called Monday disease in which, so, uh, Alfred Nobel, I've
got a case of the Monday, not you think, but this is awful.
Yeah, it's a, so Alfred Nobel, he basically created nitroglycerin, the explosive and felt
bad for the amount of lives he potentially has lost because of that.
So he decided to put money into, you know, the Nobel peace prize and so forth.
And that's where that's gone from there, but, uh, nitroglycerin and, and, uh, nitro or
nitrous oxide, it, nitrous oxide is a vasodilator tells you blood vessels to relax, but very
chemically similar to the explosive and the people that were working in the factories
making the explosives were exposed to this chemical and it would dilate or relax their
blood vessels.
Very easily absorbed through the skin.
Exactly.
And the, when you get a headache or a migraine, that's because your blood vessels are suddenly
relaxing too quickly.
And so they'll get headaches coming back to work on Monday, but because it relaxed their
blood vessels, those who had heart disease got relief while they're at work because their
blood vessels were relaxed.
And then they'll finish work on a Friday, go home for the weekend, start to get chest
pain over the weekend again, potentially suffer angina or even heart attacks and then come
back to work on the Monday and then get the headaches all over again.
And that was the Monday disease, but the Monday disease was a temporary relief for people
with a heart condition.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
And that was through that.
They discovered how that could be utilized for the alleviation of vein type problems in
the body.
That happened to me when I had that scary incident before I was put on blood pressure
medication where I came in to get it.
Oh, really?
I came in to just get it.
What happened?
I came in, I talked about this a long time ago on the show, this was, I went in to get
a sign-off because I was going to get sinus surgery to remove polyps from my nose, which
I still never had.
And my book-
You never had the polyps or you never had the surgery?
I never had the surgery.
Okay.
No, I was convinced by a stage hypnotistic that I had nose polyps and he never snapped
his fingers.
That's horrible.
Anthony Cools played a terrible prank on Matt Nottole.
Anthony Cools, what a bastard.
Anthony Cools.
Come on, man.
Give me back my sinus is Cools, uncool Cools.
My blood pressure was through the roof and they literally were like, I was like, so I
can't get surgery tomorrow?
You can't leave this office.
And I was like, oh, and they took a big nitroglycerin, I don't know, they took a big clear gel and
just put it right on my all across my chest.
And it was awesome.
And I was like, I, cause I take pills now to keep it regulated, but that gel thing was
so cool.
I was like, I would like to do the gel, but apparently it's like, it's like, you can't
control it or whatever.
Yes.
It's only done.
It's hard to get dosage right when you're smothering someone in a gel.
Say it again, but slower, Dr. Mike.
But that's exactly what happened with the, with the stuff they've, you know, they found
all these different uses for this, for this heart condition medicine and they had a controlled
test, a controlled experiment with these miners who were coming in and they kept giving all
these miners these blood pressure, no, they were actually in the hole digging miners,
still not children.
Cause that's coming back into America as well.
We're letting 12 and 14 year olds dig holes.
No, they're smaller.
You don't have to dig as big a hole.
You're right.
And Hey, they haven't lived a life.
They don't care.
Exactly.
Yeah.
They don't count.
So, but all these miners come in and finally, after months of these tests, one guy goes,
Hey, uh, I don't know if this is anything, but I had a raging boner at night.
And the other guy was like, Oh, well yeah, me too.
Yeah.
I did also.
We all had raging boners all the time.
And so finally they go, Oh, fuck.
Now we can make some money.
That's how they discovered.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
I have a boner for over four hours last night, but they're so embarrassed to even talk about
it.
They almost missed it.
God damn it.
We need sex ed everywhere.
No way.
I looked up, uh, Dr. Mike, I looked up the St. Vitus dance and this one's talking about
being a, a neurological disorder, not that was, that was thought to be caused by mold
and it's something else.
Is that something different?
Yeah, there's, there's another condition, which is St. Vitus disease, um, which is a
neurological and it affects the way that the body moves.
So the person moves rhythmically because of the way that the motor system is being affected.
So that's a different condition.
Oh, but that's not, that's not like a life threatening disease.
Yeah.
Richard in the chat was mentioning it was ergot.
That was the specific mold that caused the problem.
Oh, gotcha.
Yeah.
Oh, neat.
Ergot the rhythm, ergot the music, ergot my brain exploding on the floor.
Yeah.
Uh, I'll tell you what else ergot and that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by, of course, Dr. Mike and Dr. Matt's book, the body A
to Z, which you can get somewhere.
Yep.
And it's correct.
You can't get it somewhere.
It's your local Walden books.
Is it available in America yet or no?
Well, I, I don't know if you guys know this, but there's these things called tariffs that
are happening in the U S but is it affecting the economy at all?
Um, well, I don't know again, Matt, you might not be aware, but, um, yes, significantly.
Um, and it's affecting my book sales in the U S because shock it costs if somebody in
the U S, uh, well, if my publisher wanted to make the book and sell it in the U S people
would have to pay about 60 U S dollars for the book.
And my book's not worth 60.
What is your MSRP on that bad boy?
What is it normally going for?
Uh, well in Australia, I think what Paul's trying to ask is how much for raw book.
Right.
I'll ask you for raw book.
I'll rule book you Paul.
Okay.
Don't worry about that.
I appreciate it.
You can get it in Australia for $37, uh, which is Australia, which is a little more three,
three U S dollars probably.
No, but yeah, but, but you can order it, uh, and they can ship it to the U S through readings.
It's, it's, it's a publisher, a distributor called readings and they will ship it to you
or you can get it as a Kindle through the, uh, U S Amazon.
Yeah.
Okay.
So you can get it through readings.
All right.
Yeah.
The body, A to Z, uh, Dr. Matt and Dr. Mike, uh, they are the authors on there and yeah,
it's on Amazon, uh, for a Kindle and get the physical one in all those ways.
Also $37 Australia is about $24 U S there you go.
And now I've answered all the questions that today's show is also brought to you by the
hemorrhoid razor, a razor to cut your hemorrhoids.
That's from NOLA in 2021.
I'm glad there's a doctor present tells us about how well this works, the hemorrhoid
razor.
Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm the hemorrhoid razor cutter.
That's right.
Looks like you've got a polyp on your bottom bud.
Time for the hemorrhoid razor.
This sharp one's going to slice you clean.
Come on over, spread those cheeky weakies and let me get a slice in.
I've cut you to the quick, I have slippery slice.
No preparation needed for this H E double hockey sticks.
That's right.
I'm taking you to hell ass first with my hemorrhoid razor.
It's a simple slice right around your colon, but just before it, your GI will never be
the same.
Look here, when you clench that sphincter, I'm going to make it pinkter when I slice
with my hemorrhoid razor, a slicey slice.
Your little chocolate starfish better make its last wish as I come in with my hemorrhoid
razor.
Your eye of Sauron is going to be a power on blood when I get my hemorrhoid razor, slicey
slice.
Please do not shit for four to six weeks after the use of the hemorrhoid razor.
Smart.
Enter hate scoops at checkout.
So Dr. Mike, let's talk hemorrhoids for a second.
There are several different causes, right?
What's the ultimate?
Let's describe.
What is the hemorrhoid?
So there are veins that sit around the anus and they can basically enlarge.
Because they're lazy and don't want to get a job?
My hemorrhoids sit around the anus all day.
They sit around the anus all day.
And when they get larger, they can be facial.
So it's an enlarge.
And why should we razor blade them?
You know what, I've been a listener for 10 years and I had to be part of the episode
where it was like Gio said, it's the worst, most disturbing ad I've heard so far.
Putting a razor blade to a hemorrhoid makes me feel sick.
That would do a lot of damage.
That would really not help, right?
That would exacerbate the problem.
I mean, if you think about how much blood can come from a hemorrhoid just from excretion.
And I do.
Right.
And I do often.
Yeah.
And Jacob often does.
Putting a razor blade to it wouldn't be good.
I mean, some of the ways they get rid of it, banded surgery.
So they banded up to get rid of a sheep's tail.
Oh my God.
That's got to be a big hemorrhoid.
Yeah.
Well, we'll have challenge accepted, Paul external.
Okay.
All right.
Ben, have you ever met anyone with a prehensile hemorrhoid?
Use it to climb a tree.
When I'm scared, I could hang from a branch by my hemorrhoid.
Oh my God.
Um, there's, there's a new way that they're doing it, which is they sonicate it.
They actually use sound and what the sound does is I actually don't know what the mechanism
is.
I don't know if many of the, um, it's a guided by voices album.
Look man.
Is that just a blast speaker?
Not a lot of hemorrhoids here.
So thank you.
That's right.
Now we have a very specific, uh, follow up coming from a listener here, Jacob.
Can you also highlight, uh, Jessica Jane Peterson, please?
Uh, Jessica Jane is in chat there.
Oh, that's a, where is J, where is J. J. Oh, there she is.
Hey, JJ's here.
Hey.
I was trying to get JJ to join us in our first episode, but she's here for the second episode
and she just texted me with a question that has to go directly to Dr. Mike.
Do you want to ask her?
Ah, good.
You know, I feel like, okay, I should say I escaped from a straight jacket eight times
a week, hanging upside down on 35 feet in the air.
But if you know about straight jackets, which I'm sure you do, you know, it has that special
crop strap.
Can that strap cause these hemorrhoids?
So how is this strap wrapped around?
Very tightly around the back.
But then I'm hanging upside down.
I was like, it hasn't happened yet, but I'm wondering if like there's preventative acts
to prevent the hemorrhoids that could be caused by this straight jacket.
Do you think you need to do like a water tank?
Is it like a G-string bungee?
Okay.
It is.
It is like a G-string bungee made of canvas through Spanx with fishnet.
I think your hemorrhoids are safe.
You think the Spanx and the fishnets probably do enough cushioning to prevent the...
There's no preventative measures that I need to take because I just, this sounds terrifying.
I did not know they fled.
I didn't know any of these things.
I texted Matt.
I'm like, I am learning so much about hemorrhoids.
My Lord.
So the fact that you're upside down means that the pressure is probably reduced in that
area and it's all going to your brain, or at least going to your head.
Sorry.
Whereas my tightwired act where I just taint myself across, where I just keep shaking my
legs until I inch myself across, that's, that's maybe a bad idea.
Keep going, Matt.
Keep doing it.
Matt's raking his asshole across a tightrope.
Look, man, it's the only way Popov will let me into his pet circus.
So I have to do that act.
Damn you, Anthony Cools.
So when, when can we expect eighth, eighth, the diseases A through Z, do you expect it
to sell more or less than the body A through Z?
Oh, I, I think the diseases A to Z is going to be really fun because Paul's helping us
punch this up.
I think it's also going to be very funny.
It's coming out same time as this book.
So this time next year, a Christmas book, I just got to get it done by, we've got to
get it done.
Paul by June.
Oh, easy peasy.
Yeah.
Cool.
I'm stepping it up.
Paul will not be done by June.
No, I'm going to tell you that right now.
He's killing it.
We send it to him.
He's, he's, he's back in a couple of days.
He's killing it.
I'm trying to get faster on it now.
Yeah.
But I have a much more, a much more full schedule.
So that allows me more funny.
I allocate time better now.
So it's good.
Well, thanks.
And where do you want to send people, Dr. Mike to check out where your stuff is?
If you, I think go to our YouTube page, Dr. Matt and Dr. Mike, have a look, there's videos
there for everybody or our podcast.
And yeah, if you want to have considered buying the book, go for it.
Otherwise hit us a subscribe and a, and a like, and I'll be happy.
All right.
Well, thanks for coming.
Bye.
Thanks for waking up early.
You woke up at like four o'clock in the morning to be on the show at your time.
So thank you.
Appreciate it.
I did, but it's all good.
All good.
Thank you guys.
It's like I said, I've been a listener for a decade now and I continue to be a listener.
Please, please clear up any of anything we misquote medically.
Please always, always fact check us.
I'll be too busy if I did that.
And I can tell you, honestly, the new book that we're working on is fascinating.
And I'm sure eight is ed with the body is just as fascinating.
You're going to learn a ton.
So check it out, give it a read.
I've already learned a ton of stuff just in my editing of this new book.
So I can't wait to pick up the other one, Paul.
Bad news is that now you have to become a doctor by June as well.
You have to also be good news, good news, Matt.
Those kinds of degrees in the States are now not professional any longer.
So I'm technically a doctor already.
I'm technically a doctor.
Come at me, bro.
I've only seen the reactions to this.
I don't know the core event that happened that has caused us to talk about medicine
not being professional.
I can tell you what's going on.
You want me to break it down for you?
The way they're doing this bullshit, because it's always some bullshit loophole.
What they're doing is they're using this formula wherein if a degree's income, if when you
graduate college, the money you make from your income is not significantly greater than
what a high school graduate would make, then it is rendered as though it is null and void
beyond a high school diploma.
By who?
Right.
Who?
What are you saying?
Who renders it null and void?
What's left of the goddamn Department of Education that's being systematically dismantled.
Okay.
So what they're saying is that degrees that do not provide a significant monetary payout
that can be compared to the money that a high school graduate makes in its first year.
Now that does not take into account that as you go through the ranks of these things,
you make more money.
And of course, especially with nurses and internships and that kind of thing, it is
a gradual progression, especially with education.
A lot of that early education is being pulled out from this stuff too because it takes a
little while to get your feet under you and make actual money and tenuring and all that
kind of thing.
So that's the loophole that they're using to undermine many of these degrees as being
anything more than what would essentially be a high school diploma equivalence.
And so they're labeling them as unprofessional or nonprofessional through that loophole.
And what does that mean?
Does that mean the government doesn't have to fund things?
Does that mean the government doesn't have to do things?
It means that you don't get recognized as professional.
The biggest thing about it, and shock of all, this giant pedophile ring is deciding that
these specific careers that also happen to be mandatory reporting careers, which means
that if they are informed of any kind of sexual abuse from a minor, they have to report it
to the authorities.
These are also being undercut as nonprofessionals anymore.
So that's going away too.
What do you know?
Shock and surprise.
So that's what's really at the heart of it is making it so it's harder for crimes against
children to be systematically reported and cataloged.
And guess what is not being systematically eradicated through this? Degrees such as fucking
religious studies, which are not having to be reporting because that's where it's happening.
I'll tell you what else they're not paying attention to, the body A to Z. You should
be paying attention to it.
You should be paying attention to that.
Dr. Wright, can we move to Australia, please?
I know, right?
Do you have room?
Come to Australia. I've been trying to get the boys to Australia for a long time and
they refuse.
No, we want to go.
We want to go.
At this point, I think all of our visas would be flagged, but what are you going to do?
Who the fuck knows?
Arms wide open.
Well, thank you, Dr. Mike.
Thank you, Dr. Mike.
Thanks for your time, Dr. Mike.
Appreciate it, man.
Thank you all.
Have a great day.
You too, buddy.
Hey, you too, buddy.
You rock, dude.
I'll tell you who else is punching up Dr. Mike's next book, and that's the following
sponsor.
Today is brought to you by 19th Deck Handjobs from Captain Scooper in 2025.
That's 19th Deck Handjobs because sometimes I'm tired of just walking up there.
Well, I was born one day shuffling spades, I finally decided to change up trades.
I went ahead and I jacked off 18 dudes, and the next one showed up, he was already nudes.
You got 19 decks.
What do you get?
A whole bunch of slop and stuff on your neck.
You can't escape all the jizz that comes and goes.
I owe my soul to these jacked off hoes.
Well after 19, I thought, where do I go?
I went back out and found another hoe.
Number 20 came and number 20 went, but number 21 was already spent.
You jacked 19 decks, what do you get?
Your face covered in jizz and soaking wet, St. Peter, don't you call me unless you are.
The actual St. Peter who has Peters by far, yeah, give me those St. Peters.
And her hate scoops checked out.
There you go.
Oh, you know what that horn means, Matt Dolly is heading up to old 19.
I can only listen to books on tape for so long.
I'm about to head out to the-
Just get forward.
Yeah, right after Thanksgiving, I head back out to the old Sun Princess, miss the old
gal.
How long are you going to be out?
Just a week, which is good.
Jessica Jane, are you at sea?
Yeah, I think so.
I joined the Disney Destiny in, oh God, in three days and I still have to write two more
routines.
Crap.
They work you hard on that ship.
But then I go to Star Princess.
So wait, when are you on Sun?
I'm on the Sun in December and then I don't go to the Star until March and then I'm on
the Star in May and June.
Okay.
Well, you don't know whether you're booked then there or are you already booked out?
Disney's got stuff till like 20 to 27 because they don't want me to have a life.
So they own me.
I am owned by the mouse.
I'm even on the Star in August, I'm on the Star a ton but I won't run into you, you won't
get booked.
Because Jessica Jane gets booked as a stage magician, I get booked in Little Magic Castle
Experience so I could be on this ship.
And then we can do a show together in the Pavilion thing.
Yeah.
No, I do have two Star Princess dates in March.
So we'll see.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yay.
I miss you guys though.
Hi, JJ.
You were supposed to come to ScoopFest and you bailed on it because we were working on
a project together.
I was going to say, yeah.
Yeah.
We need you to block out some dates on the next ScoopFest.
So yeah.
Yes.
Yes, we can, JJ.
We can definitely talk about whose fault that was.
Vinnie Grasso.
Can we talk about Vinnie Grasso?
Fuckin' Vinnie Grasso.
Yup.
Because who got sent to the Virgin Cruise thing because Matt wasn't available and Mike
had what?
His daughter's dance recital or something and Vinnie's like, "I don't want to do it,
so send JJ."
That's right.
But we missed you.
You recently-
Vinnie came by though.
Vinnie came by ScoopFest.
He was there for all of it.
He came by and really hung out.
Yeah.
He came by and hung out for a lot of ScoopFest.
Are you frickin' kidding me?
Vinnie went to ScoopFest?
You're frickin' kidding me.
Matt Foster.
I knew that'd make her mad.
I believe Jacob is kidding you.
I believe he's kidding you.
Vinnie was not kidding.
Oh, he is kidding.
I was so mad.
Vinnie was in Italy.
That's why you had to go on.
Oh, okay.
It was almost not available.
I can't accept that.
Yeah.
You weren't at ScoopFest because I was supposed to be on the ship during ScoopFest and I said
no because of ScoopFest, so you were there.
JJ, Vinnie-
But I was there in spirit, just a lot taller.
You talking about Michael Ellsroth dressing up like you for the ScoopFest?
Can we please, for the next ScoopFest, Mike, can we wear the exact same outfit and walk
around together arm in arm?
It would make me so happy.
You do not need to ask Ellsroth twice to do an elaborate bit.
I'll tell you that much later.
No, he will very quickly commit to that.
He'll run with it.
Yeah.
We'll do it immediately.
So we were-
We should both be mermaids.
Oh my God.
Wait a minute.
He was there.
Oh my God.
I'll misremember.
That bastard.
I'm texting him.
You were at ScoopFest?
You told me that you were in Italy.
I just saw a picture of you at ScoopFest.
I was supposed to go to the ship.
To do the Virgin gig, so let's talk about that, Vitti Grasso.
I love it.
Drama.
I'm just there to ruin JJ and Vitti's relationship.
I believe in truth.
I believe he came by for about five minutes one day.
I think he came through on his way to the airport.
He was there just in time to grab a Fez and run.
Yeah.
Okay.
We got to get you a Fez, JJ.
Oh, I would love a Fez.
Yeah, yeah.
That would be awesome.
JJ is now our neighbor, Jacob.
I knew you were in town.
Where are you?
I'm on Bracken.
So I'm really close to the downtown arts district area.
Oh, wow.
I think I'm a 10 minute walk from the Haunted Museum.
Oh, how nice.
Have you been yet?
No, I have not.
That was one of my gigs.
I worked at the Haunted Museum.
Really?
Yes.
Before they opened and during the opening months.
I was there for just about three months.
Yeah, Vitti Grasso got Paul the job there.
Vitti got everybody who he really liked jobs at the Haunted Museum.
Motherfucker.
He did not.
I got that job myself.
No, but I worked with Zach.
I helped write a lot of the pattern that the guides use throughout the entire museum and
I worked there for several months.
I was there for, we had to postpone our opening because October 1 happened.
So the next Monday we were going to open and we had to postpone it till Tuesday because
it was too crazy.
We had to just chill.
Mass shooting in Las Vegas.
That's what October 1 is.
So then I was there for Friday the 13th and for Halloween.
And it was in fucking Sane.
Yeah, Halloween was nuts.
We had some crazy shit go down during Halloween.
Yeah, I never had anything too crazy happen to myself, but it's an interesting place at
the least to check out.
There's a lot of really cool stuff to see.
So yeah.
Did you ever have any moments though where you got freaked out?
Well, I had to actually, I actually had to go turn off lights at the end of the night
because I was like a mid-level manager type.
So I did always say hi and bye to Peggy, Peggy the doll.
So I didn't even, I didn't even fuck with that.
The only weird thing, there was a couple of weird things.
There was a latch on this gate that opens and closes for the basement.
And I would constantly have to relatch that basement gate.
It was all, that latch was always coming loose.
And then upstairs in the room that held the Dibbock box, which was right next to Peggy's
room.
- That's the golf thing, right?
- Yeah.
- Dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip,
dip it box, dip it, dip it, dip it, dip it, dip it box.
- Which is basically based around the conjuring stuff.
The dipping box room, I had to go in there
to turn on lights one morning, and I went to try
the door knob, and you know, did you ever grow up
with siblings of any kind?
- Yeah.
- You remember how if your brother or sister
was on the other side of a door holding that door closed,
and you could kind of twist the knob,
and you couldn't really, and you couldn't really,
I felt that feeling.
And I couldn't get the door to open,
and I tried it again, and it was the same kind of thing,
and I just had to let it go, and I just,
I was like, okay, I'm going on.
- It turns out Paul's brother was on the other side
of that door holding it.
- You never know.
Those were the only really weird things that happened to me,
but plenty of other stuff happened to people
that were around, but a lot of it is
because he doesn't let people have drinks in the place,
and they all get dehydrated and pass out.
That's really a lot of it, yeah.
A lot of it is just people suffering from Vegas,
and just passing out because it's a lot to take in.
- You pass out saltines and espresso on your way in,
and then you can't drink water.
- Honestly, yeah.
- That's a sprainy little salt.
- Well, there's a lot of fog machines and stuff in there too,
so that can affect people too, so yeah.
- Can we have a scoop group visit to the museum?
- An excursion to the museum would be really, really fun.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That would be really fun.
I know somebody had contacted me from over there
about some of my Houdini stuff,
'cause I was like, well, I live close by,
and it'd be safe there, but--
- You should chat him up, drop my name.
I mean, he'll remember me.
And I left on good terms.
They said, come back anytime, so it's all good, yeah.
Bacon was his right-hand man while I was there.
He might still be his right-hand man, I don't know.
- Nah, I think Vinnie Grasso's just running the place now.
- Could be.
- Vinnie Grasso just texted back.
He goes, I stopped by on the way to the airport
to give Matt a magspied for Oscar.
Nothing to discuss, Ms. Peterson.
- Oh, boy.
(laughing)
Giving you the business.
- Ms. Peterson.
- Did you owe me a cell?
- He was only there for two and a half days.
- Yeah.
But seriously, JJ, your routines would be a huge hit there.
He is a mega circus fanatic.
He has an entire area dedicated
to classic circus memorabilia,
and he has a giant circus diorama built out
with little tiny pieces that move
and little elephants that jump through hoops
and stuff like that.
- So he's a sideshow fan and stuff, too?
- Big time. - 'Cause this shit
I haven't-- - Big time into that.
- Oh my God.
- So if you're right next door,
you should absolutely stop by sometime,
say, "Hey, if you got special events happening anytime,
"I'd love to come by as a performer,"
because he's always looking for that kind of stuff,
and just a little more money in your pocket.
- Some of the stuff I have here is hardcore,
'cause I lived in Gibsonton, Florida,
when we would winter with a sideshow.
So I lived in the trailer outside Ward Hall,
the king of the sideshow's house.
- Holy shit.
- And he had all the stuff from the early 1900s.
I have jars of things where I don't even know what they are.
- You got pickled punks and shit back there.
- Oh, yeah, and I know where all the pickled punks
are buried in Gibsonton, Florida.
- Get the fuck out.
- Because basically, yeah, they made it illegal to--
- To have 'em.
- To put actual dead bodies on display,
and it used to be the flow off of the sideshow.
So you go through the sideshow, and at the end,
you pay an extra dollar to see what's behind the curtain,
and then they open it, and there's these babies in jars
that were real, and they would talk about,
you know, this is why you don't do drugs,
people, ha-cha-cha-cha, and then you leave them,
and apparently, when it was made illegal,
they were worth too much money.
So all the people that live in Gibsonton live by,
it's a law that you can have anything on your property
as long as it has to do with circus.
Government can't do anything about it.
- Okay.
- Like, there's frickin' half-set-up rides,
and like a tiger over here, it's insane.
But there's a field where all the pickled punks
are buried, like, hundreds of them.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Wow, now see, and that's the kind of stuff he would--
- This is why you don't let circus people make the rules.
- No, but that's the kind of stuff he would buy.
Like, he went out and bought David Koresh's Hot Rod
a couple years ago, and stuff like that.
Like, he's always--
- Yeah, I don't think Zach should be in charge, either.
- He's always looking for that kind of stuff.
You guys would hit it off.
You should definitely look him up.
- I feel like we'd be friends.
- And--
- You would, you would.
You guys would be.
You would be, you know.
- You can vouch Zach pays really well, right, Paul?
- Here's the thing. - Zach pays great.
- I was just about to say,
whatever you're thinking of charging,
just charge double, and you'll be good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Okay, okay.
He's classic sideshow in every way.
Classic sideshow is GTFM, get the fucking money.
- That is, he is, he loves Barnum.
He loves P.T. Barnum.
That's his whole, that's his ideological guru.
And that's why he's got all that--
- Oh, I've got a Barnum letter in the back room
that's written by Barnum.
I've got like crazy--
- Hey, you looking to make some quick cash?
Honestly, that's the kind of shit he will buy
in a fucking heartbeat for his museum.
- Well, you've got me wondering.
Yeah, I've got, there was a murder in Gibsonton, Florida.
There was this guy called The Lobster Man.
And The Lobster Man abused his family,
so they hired a hit on him.
His name was Grady Stiles.
And I have an impression of his hand,
like in, like the actual impression of his hand.
He was the one that was murdered.
And there was this crazy story around it.
- You've got Circus Freak and Murder Mystery Story
and Murder Mobilia all connected.
He will pay you crazy money for this shit.
This is exactly the kind of stuff
he loves to have in his place.
Wow.
Yeah, you guys will hit it off.
- Yeah, if you guys don't know that story,
look up Grady Stiles, The Lobster Boy.
- It's been a long time since I've heard that.
But he had hands kind of like the penguin
in the Batman Returns.
Yeah, yeah, the pincers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, oh fucking shit.
You guys absolutely have to chat at some point.
We gotta figure that out.
Yeah.
- A Pickled Graveyard.
Yes, Andi, it's a Pickled Graveyard.
- All right.
Shout out to Richard Bruins for doubling his Patreon
while we were on air.
I'll keep doing this if people keep doing it.
So I'll just keep doing it.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Thank you, Richard. - This is great.
Yeah, we love you guys so much.
Thank you so much for sending us--
- Coach Rat Bastard just became
an ice cream truck driver, everybody.
- Fuck yeah, Coach Rat Bastard.
Yeah, baby.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Welcome to the feed.
(imitates truck engine)
- Is Mike technically an ice cream truck driver all the time
since he's actually driving his truck?
- I mean-- - Hi, Mike.
- Kind of, yeah.
- Oh, yes. - Yeah.
And he was kind enough to say that he's gonna up his Patreon
as soon as stuff gets squared away from the holidays.
So thanks. - Right, so.
- People who are doing it can fit it with their budget.
Obviously, we do not want people to take any financial risks
to up their Patreon. - No, no, no.
- whatsoever. - No, no, no.
But we desperately appreciate everything
that everybody does for us, so yeah.
- Well, there is still the experiment
that we're gonna run after we get $3 billion.
- That's right.
- We're gonna give each of us a billion dollars
and see how we spend it.
- We're gonna see if we can be better people
than the billionaires that we have today.
So we'll see how that goes. - I know I could.
- My guess is no. - I could.
- Well, once JJ sells all of her memorabilia to Zach,
she'll be a billionaire as well.
- I'm telling you, you got some money to make.
- Help fund us.
- Well, at the very least,
yeah, you guys would actually hit it off.
- Yeah.
- That's, well, first of all,
JJ hits it off with every single person on the planet.
- I know, I know, I know.
I'm not like breaking news here.
JJ gets along with someone.
- Yeah, but we've got sawdust in our blood.
- Yes, yes.
No, I think you guys, because of the circus thing.
Yep, mm-hmm.
- For the Zach Baggins turn,
I was trying to get to the lead of why we had you on here
is you just did a concert with Alice Cooper in Arizona.
- Hey. - Oh, you did that one!
- Yeah, that was interesting, that was very interesting.
- What happened?
- Well, here's the thing, I'll just tell you what I saw.
I saw that you were, at one point, you were eating fire,
and at one point, there's a picture of you eating fire,
and normally when you eat fire, your head is back,
your neck is up.
There's a picture of you eating fire,
and your face is forward,
and you're just shoving a ball of fire into your face.
- I hurt my neck, I couldn't put my head back.
(laughing)
And then I just did it, and I had no eyelashes afterwards,
but it was worth it, they said I looked like a fat ass.
- There's no doubt, no doubt.
So, sorry, tell us all about the gig.
- So, David Minkin was the one that got it,
'cause he's been friends with Alice and his wife for years,
and they are the nicest human beings in the world.
And the gig was for this thing they do
called Alice Cooper Solid Rock, basically in Arizona.
Any kid that wants to learn an instrument,
learn an art, anything, they can stay after school
until 10 p.m. at their facilities.
They get their instrument for free,
they get training for free.
- Oh, wow, oh, that's awesome.
- It's insanely cool, and so they had the winners
of their annual School of Rock type thing in this concert.
And then it was me, David, and Chris Mitchell,
Collective Soul, Don Felder,
his guitarist that was insane.
I forget what her name was, Nina, I think something.
And then Alice Cooper performed with the original band.
- Whoa. - Oh, cool.
- Bad ass. - Yeah, yes.
But so I got there, and obviously I'm like,
we're the magicians, we're not gonna get
a dressing room or anything, which I was right.
So we go downstairs, I'm trying to find a place.
I was like, I gotta curl my hair.
I just got off a cruise ship on a plane,
and I said, is there any place with a plug?
And they pulled me down the hallway,
and they said, oh, in here's fine.
I was like, oh, this is nice.
There's nobody in it right now.
So I curled my hair for like 20 minutes.
And you guys know, I shed like a Siberian husky in summer.
Like there's red hair everywhere, all over the floor.
And so I'm trying to collect some,
like I could make another JJ out of it.
Actually, Mike, I should just give you my hair for a year.
That's what I should do for your next album.
- Elsroth, for Elsroth to have JJ's hair.
- Yeah, well, I got, so I finished,
and I just had a feeling like I need to get out of here.
I leave, I leave the dressing room,
and my shoulder brushes somebody going into it.
They had put me in Alice Cooper's dressing room
thinking he wouldn't be there yet.
And I literally just made a mess of his dressing room
with my hair.
It was so embarrassing.
And I saw David Meakin and Chris Mitchell
on the other side of the room going.
And then my other fail moment.
Have you guys ever misquoted lyrics
to a person who wrote them?
- Oh no.
Something I'm very capable of.
- Yes, yes I have.
- So Jacob, what was your misheard lyric
that you quoted to that person?
- It was an Ozzy Osbourne lyric.
Not too Ozzy, but to the person that had written this song.
I don't remember what the lyric was,
but I was definitely just like singing part of it with,
like through with this guy.
And he was like, that is not the lyric at all.
It was embarrassing.
- Oh shit.
- Dude, so Collective Soul, I love Collective Soul
and Ed Rowland, like the lead singer for it.
And you know that song, the, whoa.
I thought it was, never let your light shine doll.
- Oh my God.
- And I didn't know what the real lyrics were
until yesterday when I told the friend this story
and they're like, they didn't correct you.
And I went, no.
And then the other one, Ed Rowland filmed on his phone
to send his family 'cause he loved it.
You know that song that that dadada dadada dadada.
I thought it was turn your head now, baby.
Just say meow.
- Turn your hair.
Now, baby, just say meow.
Oh, turn your head.
- Just say meow.
And he laughed so hard during the show
when he sang whatever the real lyric is.
(laughing)
I was like, oh, it was bad.
But no one corrected me.
I still didn't know what the real lyrics
were when I clapped. - My wife thought
the collective soul was, oh, physical attraction
is what she thought it was at high school.
- What?
What are you guys, what is wrong?
Everybody just got hearing problems?
What's happening?
- Baby, just say meow. - Physical attraction.
- No, Jacob, not everyone has hearing problems.
(laughing)
- I told him, I used to think the boots are made for walking.
I thought it was one of these days
these boots are gonna walk on over to you.
(laughing)
- No, it's- - Like, magically?
- Wow.
- It's much hotter than that, JJ.
It's much hotter than that.
- They're gonna walk on over to you.
- Oh, God.
As a kid, I thought "Jump and Drive" was "Drink and Drive."
(laughing)
Spin the wheel, you gotta drink and drive.
- A beautiful- - Spin the wheel, you gotta-
- A beautiful anthem to drunk driving,
like this wonderful party song.
- And my mom let me sing it.
Drink and drive, then you bail, you gotta
Oh no, I'm dead!
- My favorite Ska song is "Man Slaughter III."
(laughing)
Oh man.
- Yeah, my parents weren't good parents.
- You genuinely believed that the lyric
was now, "Baby, just say meow."
- Yeah, I didn't, you know when you hear something
and you just sing it that way
and you never even think about what you're actually singing.
- It never occurred to you to even think about it.
- Well, no, I- - And these are all like,
these songs all came out when we were younger
and this is before the Shazam and iPhones and stuff.
You couldn't look up-
- This was dentist jargon though.
It's dentist jargon.
- What's dentist jargon?
- Turn your head and spit me out.
(laughing)
That's what it is.
- That's what it is.
- Turn your head and now baby just spit me out, yeah.
But it's talking like a dentist.
- But like, who's giving head in a dentist's office?
- I mean- - I mean, you gotta go
to the right place.
- I guess. - Yeah.
(laughing)
- I can tell you right now it took me forever
to find one that was covered by insurance.
- Yeah.
- But turn your head and spit is a dentist thing.
- It's a PPO.
(laughing)
- But if you break that down,
turn your head and baby just spit me out.
- I hear it now that you're saying it, JJ.
I get it.
Turn your head and now baby just say meow.
Yeah, but he sings with a very affected way.
I'm gonna beat, I don't like Collective Soul,
but I know a ton of Collective Soul songs
because when I was coming up as a young man,
that was on the radio 24 fucking seven.
Their stuff was huge.
You couldn't escape their songs.
- Yeah, that's why it was everywhere.
- I think it's funny that you think it was
turn your head and now baby just say meow.
- I want an all JJ cover band
that just sings her lyrics for every song.
- The wrong lyrics?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Jacob, the wrong lyrics, that's a band name.
- The wrong lyrics is a good band name.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Speaking of all these bands, I saw Bowling for Soup.
They had a free concert on Fremont Street the other night.
- They are great live.
- Oh, they're so good live.
They're so good.
A friend of ours was opening for them.
So we went down and saw our friend open
and then we hung out and watched Bowling for Soup a little bit.
They were so good live.
They were so funny.
They talk, they do the songs and everything.
Scooper Nova girl in the chat saying 1985.
So that's one of their big songs.
It was so goddamn funny.
They're up there, they're playing.
We're kind of on the side of the stage.
And we see them.
We see all the signs and people are holding up signs.
This is 1985.
Between every song that they do,
people are yelling for 1985.
They want to play it.
And finally the front man chefs fucking kiss to this guy.
He goes, hey, hey, how many hits do you think we have?
We've been doing this a long time.
We're gonna play our big hit last.
Quit asking us to play 1985 now.
We're gonna play it.
It's gonna be last.
- When I saw them, they were playing the small room.
It was still the hard rock instead of Virgin.
It was still the hard rock.
And they were playing the smaller room.
And they were playing vinyl.
And they go like, we're gonna play.
This is a song we wrote for Katy Perry.
And they played you're hot, then you're cold.
You're yes, then you're no.
And they played it awesome.
They played it fast as hell.
They just rocked it out.
And then when they finished, they go,
we didn't write that for Katy Perry.
Do you think we'd be playing this room
if we wrote that song for Katy Perry?
We'd just be at home swimming in our money.
We wouldn't be here.
(laughing)
- That's freakin' great.
- I laughed so hard. - That's freakin' great.
That's great.
- I laughed so hard at that bit.
- I feel like they wrote a song for Katy Perry.
- It was so smart.
It was just the funniest bit.
But they were great.
They were so great to see.
- I could hear them from where I live.
'Cause Fremont Street is so close.
So there's a lot of times I can't go to bed early
'cause there's stuff going on.
- Oh yeah.
- This makes me so confusing.
'Cause I heard that concert and then I look out
and I see Disney drones.
And I'm like, God, I thought I got away from them.
- No, no.
(laughing)
- Fantasmic and the freakin' Bellatio.
I was like, they found me.
- Yikes.
(laughing)
- He gads.
Well, if you're ever downtown again,
you hear Bowling for Soup playing,
just come on over 'cause I'll probably be there.
- Yes.
- We're gonna play that one last.
It's our big song.
- That's very funny.
- Let me explain to you how show business works.
- You're gonna be on Disney for Thanksgiving
or you're gonna be on Disney for Christmas?
- I'm traveling to Disney on Thanksgiving
and I will be on Disney for Christmas.
- Oh, man.
- And New Year's Eve.
- What's the point of us becoming neighbors
if you spend all your holidays doing cruise ships, JJ?
- I know.
But I'm here December 3rd to December 13th
and then for next year I've taken off two weeks
of every month because my body--
- Smart.
- Apparently, my cortisol levels are 42
and they're supposed to be not higher than 28
and they're like, it's burnout and stress.
So I'm making my body--
- Oh, where's Dr. Mike?
We should have let Dr. Mike go.
We should have talked about your cortisol levels.
- Oh, Dr. Mike, I need Dr. Mike.
- What is a cortisol level?
What does that do?
- It's basically--
- It's a stress hormone.
- What regulates stress, I think, right?
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I hear people talking about it.
I don't know what it is though.
- I gotta tell you--
- You don't want a high cortisol level.
- Instagram says I need to treat it like crazy
in terms of targeted ads.
- Yeah, no, every targeted ad--
- That's obvious, though.
- It is obvious.
- It's obvious.
- Oh, the Instagram medical advice is not solid?
Oh, interesting.
- Not to be trusted, not at all, nope.
- It's very hard to treat your cortisol levels
with an herbal supplement.
I don't think we need Dr. Mike back on to tell you
that's true.
But I did switch to actually, it was a cortisol supplement,
but it was advertised to me as like,
if you're taking melatonin, you should maybe switch to this.
And I've been taking melatonin since the pandemic.
And then a study came out that was like,
"Hey, taking melatonin every day
might not be good for your heart."
And so I forget what the name of the study is,
but the study is the placebo's work,
even if you know the placebos.
Do you know the study?
- I mean, I know of studies like that.
I don't know with the melatonin, though.
- Well, it wasn't a melatonin-based study,
but there's a particular study that just basically said
that we're giving you placebos for the symptoms.
And people would knowingly take the placebo
and still report improvement in their conditions.
So I've switched to this herbal thing
and stopped taking melatonin,
and I've been falling asleep better
on this herbal supplement than this.
And I'm positive it's just the placebo effect.
I cannot positively endorse this product.
I just simply am happier that I'm not taking melatonin,
so I'll do it.
I'll take it.
- It's called Ambien.
- Yeah.
(all laughing)
- Matt's going to sleep really well
on this new supplement, Ambien.
- It's actually, it comes in a rock form
and you hit your head with it until it absorbs.
(Matt laughing)
- Wait, so you were taking melatonin on the bus?
- Oh, yeah.
- On the bus I was taking-
- Why are you always so tired?
- On the bus I was actually ended up taking Advil PMs,
which I knew is something you shouldn't take long-term,
but I was doing anything to fall asleep on that bus.
Yeah, I was never falling asleep on that bus.
- Matt, here's a trick that I've tried,
and it's worked for me that I just heard about.
Get yourself a cooling pad.
Do you have like little ice pack type things?
- I do.
- Okay.
And you got it where you can either wrap it in a cloth
or something where it could be safe for skin contact?
- Okay.
- All right.
And before you go to bed, once you're in bed,
just put it on your forehead for 20 minutes
and that will chill out your frontal cortex,
your frontal lobe and seriously send messages
to like go to sleep.
And so it really, really helps.
So try it.
- This is what you need.
- There you go.
- I was just about to say,
I know JJ invested in some old timey ice bag
and here it is.
- There it is.
- But here's the thing, here's the thing.
So if you're at a hotel, you can fill it with ice.
If you buy a drink at the airport,
before I get on a plane, I buy a fountain soda,
fill it with ice.
- There you go.
- Use it on the back, everywhere.
- Yeah.
- Cruise ship, fill it with ice.
- This is, I live by this.
- That's a genius idea.
- To be accurate, how much soda do you pour
into that ice bag?
(laughing)
- It's not none soda.
No, but that's a great-
- It has happened once when I was very tired.
- But that's great.
- And yes, I did drink it.
(laughing)
- Out of the bag.
- I assume you drank it.
- Yeah, that's awesome.
- Oh yeah, this is how I get water.
As soon as the ice melts, I'm like,
I'm not paying $6 for water,
I'm just drinking all the things.
- There you go, smart.
- Drinking out of a plastic ice bag.
- Genius.
- It works.
- That's how you get that sawdust in your veins.
- That's genius.
- Drinking out of plastic ice bags.
- You could hide alcohol in this.
- You absolutely could.
There you go.
- Yep, yep, yep.
- Genius.
Genius.
- You say that like you drink.
You don't really drink.
- No, not much, but I could.
(laughing)
- She just wants to have the option.
- Yeah.
- Guys, I'm icing down my knees every night
with old fashions.
(laughing)
- It really works.
- A little bit of this.
- It absorbs through the skin.
- Natural medicine, baby.
- Natural medicine.
- Oh, you don't know nothing about no natural medicine
and you don't know nothing about nothing
'cause it's Jack vs. Nerd.
- All right, you're gonna find out
who knows nothing about something.
- Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jack vs. Nerd.
- Explosion of me accidentally deleting the scooperty
before I got to it.
(laughing)
- We got a scooperty coming to us today from ML Kennedy.
The categories are how it started, dot, dot, dot.
What's their number?
Turkeys and potpourri.
Oh yeah, it's the Thanksgiving one.
Happy Thanksgiving, everybody.
- JJ, what's your Instagram?
- Wait, my Instagram? - Yeah.
- @JessicaJaneMagic.
- JessicaJaneMagic.
Give JJ a follow.
She always does. - Oh, yay!
I'll follow you back.
I put weird stuff up.
- You document your weird life on ships all the time.
It's a good follow.
It's good adventures of someone who lives on the road.
- I'm very honest.
(laughing)
- That's what I don't like about her.
- That's how I knew about the old timey ice bag.
- I do post that on my Instagram, like you guys,
but I'm gonna mention the alchohol thing now.
That's gonna be fun.
- Life hack!
Matt, you're up first.
What category do you want?
Oh, I have to put it back on the screen, don't I?
How it started, what's their number?
Turkeys or potpourri are the categories.
Matt, what you want?
- How it started, please.
- For 200.
This 1996 Tim Burton movie was based on a series
of tops trading cards from the 1960s.
- Hmm, I feel like this is obvious,
but I'm trying to think of tops trading cards.
- A league of their own.
- I know, it's like major league,
but that wasn't a Tim Burton movie.
That'd be a weird Tim Burton movie.
- That'd be a great Tim Burton movie.
- I'll pass.
- Oh, that passes to me.
I have no idea.
Pass, Paul.
- Mars attacks.
- Oh, sure, Mars attacks.
- Yeah.
- Good call.
That's from a trading card game?
- Ang, ang, ang, ang, ang, ang, ang.
- Oh, it's me.
I'll try, what's their number?
200.
The King of England during the American Revolution
was King George the,
I wanna say fifth. - Infallible.
- I wanna say fifth.
I'm gonna say fifth.
King George the fifth is what I'm saying.
Third.
- Oh, you overshot it.
Overshot it by two, Jacob.
- So close. - Yep, yep.
Wrong George.
My bad, George.
Paul.
- I'll try potpourri for six.
- For 600.
How tall is Hello Kitty?
Please give the answer in apples.
- Oh, man.
So Smurfs are three apples high.
- Famously.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna guess Hello Kitty is also three apples high.
- Okay, let's try it.
- Shit, she's five apples.
Of course she's bigger than a Smurf.
Fucking shit.
- Yeah, what are you thinking, Paul?
- At F1, there was a Hello Kitty booth this year
because it's so funny 'cause they added
this Formula One Academy,
which is all about training up women racers.
So they had a big Formula One Academy race
and they had all women drivers.
And so one of the sponsors is Hello Kitty.
So all these people who weren't aware of this new thing
were just like, what the hell is this Hello Kitty thing
doing here?
- Oh, that's great.
- They didn't like Hello Kitty?
- Well, they're just confused by it.
- A lot of basically car dealers who won some contests
that their dealership sent them to F1
did not appreciate the Hello Kitty thing, yeah.
- Well, then they're idiots.
- So they had Mickey Mouse in the gang and Hello Kitty.
- They're absolute idiots because any car dealer
worked their...
No, seriously, if you were lucky enough to be like,
let's just say a Toyota dealership,
and you were lucky enough to get like
a Hello Kitty limited edition Avalon made,
holy fuck, those would not stay in stock for five minutes.
- Good point.
- They have no idea what they're doing.
Fuck those idiots.
- From your mouth to Theodore Toyoda's ears.
- Theodore Toyoda, send me a message.
We'll talk, we'll talk.
- It's weird to have Paul Chris in my mouth
because I feel like Paul would get along
with all of the opulent people that go to F1.
(laughing)
- I would get along with the rich people?
- No, I'm being sarcastic.
- You'd be so mad the whole time.
- Yeah, I would be.
I'd be throwing shit in their face.
- You'd just be furious.
- I'd be throwing shit in their faces.
- Yeah.
- Matt, you're up.
- JJ, where should I go?
What's your gut?
- Ooh, ooh, turkeys for 400.
- All right. - All right.
- Turkeys for 400.
(laughing)
- The budget of this Gina Davis pirate movie
was around $100 million.
It grossed about $18 million at the box office.
(laughing)
- You know this, Matt.
You know this, Matt.
- I do?
- No, what is it?
- I know this one.
- JJ, you can tell me.
- Matt, you know this.
- You can just tell me.
- It's Matthew Modine.
- Gina Davis as a hot pirate?
- And Matthew Modine.
- Where do pirates hang out, Matt?
- As Matthew Modine.
- On a ship in a harbor.
- Yeah, and that ship takes them to a piece of land
that's in the middle of the ocean called a--
- Island.
- It's an island, yeah.
What do they do on that island?
- Look for treasure.
- Nope, they kill each other in a very specific way.
- Murder Island.
- Close.
- Getting closer.
- Who are you?
- JJ, you're a horrible lifeline.
Just tell me the answer.
We can move on.
(laughing)
- Actually, I forget.
I was just hoping you'd get to it.
- Matt.
- Shipwreck?
- Imagine you had to go down on a sword.
- Okay.
- Is there--
- What would happen?
- It's not twash.
- Cutthroat Island.
- There you go.
- Cutthroat Island is it.
- All you have to do with these clues
to get Matt to figure 'em out is reference fellatio.
- That's right.
- Got it.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- It is a good movie though.
- Come on now, JJ.
- I believe Cutthroat Island was the reason
that movie studio had to fold.
- Yeah, it's a terrible movie.
- It destroyed a movie studio.
- It's damn near unwatchable.
- It was hot.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, everyone's attractive.
The movie's terrible.
- What were you four when that fucking thing
hit the theaters?
You were like, wow, of course it was cool to a four-year-old.
- JJ watches that shit on mute.
She sips from her ice pack.
- All right, fair enough.
I mean, I ain't taking nothing away
from Gina Davis and big old pirate boots.
It was good stuff there, but you know.
- I'll try turkeys for 600.
- You would.
- This film, developed in part by the four-year-old son
of the president of Paramount, grossed $65 million
at a budget of $125 million.
It's about trucks with hive mind creatures
living under the hoods.
Oh, is that the, what was the,
it was like the Loch Ness monster looking thing.
- What does your, what did your wife work for
for a minute there?
- A pimp.
- Okay, after she got done being turned out on the street,
she decided to go get turned out on the tracks
with those machines.
- Was it just called Monster Truck?
- It sure was.
- Was that movie just called Monster Truck?
- There you go.
Monster trucks, yep.
Yep, there you go.
Paul, you're up.
- I'm gonna go, I'm gonna take turkey 800, please.
I gotta get back on the board.
- This 1999 movie based on Michael Crichton's novel,
"Eaters of the Dead" grossed about $62 million worldwide
on a bigger than $100 million budget.
I guess that was an unlucky number.
- I'm gonna tell you what,
this movie should have made way more money.
This is not a turkey, this is an exceptional film.
Antonio Banderas puts in a superstar performance
in "The 13th Warrior".
- "The 13th Warrior" is correct.
- It is such a good movie.
- It is good.
- I have that on DVD.
That is one of my favorite movies.
It's a great movie.
- JJ was just talking about
how good "Cutthroat Island" is, Paul.
Don't be too excited to be on her team here.
- Listen, man, I'm on team "13th Warrior".
I don't give a shit, "Cutthroat Island", whatever,
but yeah, "13th Warrior" is good.
- My favorite movie of all time is "The Phantom"
with Billy Zane, though, so please do not take that.
- Stop it, stop it.
He was the bomb in "Phantoms", yo.
- Anyone who's absolutely repping Billy Zane first
is an insane person.
- No, that's just, that was just--
- JJ, I know somebody else in town
that that is their favorite movie.
- I'm gonna make sure the two of you meet.
- Really? - Yes.
- Holy shit.
- Go, go!
- I'm gonna introduce you.
You don't know them yet. - Oh my god.
- Matt, you're up. - Oh, this is awesome.
- You're gonna, you're gonna,
you better be careful, Jacob.
You don't wanna get two zaniacs in the same room together.
(laughing)
- Mike a little too zany.
- It's Matt Franco.
No, um-- (laughing)
- It's always been Matt Franco.
- It's always been Franco. - Matt Franco.
- He's got it on a loop in his dressing room.
- Matt Franco and I literally can talk to each other
in quotes from '90s Magic Specials
and only quotes from '90s Magic Specials,
a full 20 minute conversation. - All right.
Raise your hand if you're surprised.
(laughing)
Okay, no hands for you. - Raise your hand
if you wanna be in that room, no hands for you.
(laughing)
- JJ, where do we go? - Matt, you're up.
- Where do we go?
- Maybe a how it started.
- How brave are you?
- Let's do it.
- How it started for 400.
This six film franchise originated
from an unused spec script for an episode of the X-Files.
It's latest entry grossed over $300 million this year.
- Six films, huh? - Six films.
An episode that involves aliens or conspiracies.
- Okay. - 200 million.
- Guy girl, guy girl investigators.
- Huh.
- Paul, you know this one?
- It could be something like The Nun.
You know, they have those one-off kind of ghosty stuff.
- Oh yeah.
- You know, monster of the week kind of thing.
But I'm thinking six films.
When was this, when was this a scooperty?
- It's recent.
It's a Thanksgiving, it's a Thanksgiving scooperty
for a commission.
- 300 million this year.
So it's a film that came out this year.
- Yeah. - That's part of
a school franchise. - So it's a horror movie.
- Is, what do you call it, up to six movies now?
Oh, you know what?
I think it might be Paranormal Activity.
- Oh, did that come out this year?
- I think there was another, I don't know.
Paranormal Activity or the-- - I'm gonna pass, we're passing.
- I'm definitely passing.
Paul, what is it?
I mean, Paranormal Activity or the Conjuring?
Is the Conjuring up to six?
- I don't know, that's literally the question.
- I'm gonna guess Conjuring, I'm guessing Conjuring.
- Let's see.
Final Destination.
- Oh, I eat my own butt, fart on a shit.
Okay, I should have known.
- Wait, my first ink thing was Final Destination,
but it initially bombed.
So the fact that it said it reached over 300 million,
I'm surprised because--
- Yeah, this latest reboot was really hot.
People were really--
- I think it got like a cult following thing
with the sequels and all, I think.
- It's just one of those--
- And it also got real viral, yeah.
- I thought it was opening weekend this week,
and so I didn't guess it.
- Millennials are desperate to get killed
by a log carrying truck.
- Who is it?
- Oh man, sign me up.
- I'll try potpourri for 800.
- Right back to zero, fart.
- This is the only current flag of a sovereign country
without elements in white, red or blue.
- I got this.
- White, red or blue.
- I think I got this too.
- Is it, I'll take a guess on this one.
Brazil.
Is it Brazil maybe?
- Jamaica.
- You don't think it's Brazil?
Oh, I think you might be right.
It is Jamaica, you were right.
- Yeah.
- I got that one wrong.
- Wait, did I get it right?
What the hell?
- You didn't pass, you jerk.
- I didn't pass, I just got it wrong.
- I don't give a shit.
I still want the points.
- I lost points.
I lost points, that's how the game works.
- Fair enough.
- Paul, you're up.
- Popery.
- 200.
This name later shared with "Star Wars" characters
was given to the Mohawk steel workers
who helped build modern New York City.
Ewoks.
- Ugnaughts? - Called them Ewoks.
- Sure.
- Wait, yeah, I'll go with ugnaughts.
- All right.
- Skywalkers. - Oh, Skywalkers.
- Right, right, right, right.
- That makes a lot of sense.
See Paul, since that was your turn,
I'm gonna address your points with that question.
There you go, you.
- Thank you.
- Matt.
- JJ, JJ controls me.
- What's their number 600?
- What's their number for 600?
Daily Devil.
- Oh shit.
- Yeah, it's on the line now.
- The current pope is Pope Leo the what?
- Oh shit.
- I don't give a shit about the popes.
- The American from Chicago.
- The popiest pope that ever pope.
- Oh, I love it, Richard.
- Pope Leo the Bears.
- I would rather be locked in a Scottish basement
than figure out whose pope is whose.
I will.
- If you would ask for his name,
I could not have given you Leo.
- Right.
- Like I said, I know he's from Chicago.
- I know he's Chicago, that's all I know.
- Yeah, I know.
- He literally had a rave at the Vatican like last week.
- I get it, JJ.
I hate people who try to make these popes hip and likable.
It's like, okay, okay.
- Yeah, but this pope has really good drugs.
- And good pizza.
- All right, six though.
- Matt, try six.
14.
- Oh, mystify.
- Mystify that much?
Close.
- There's been a lot of Leos.
- Good Lord.
- It's me, I'll try, I don't know how it started, 600.
This 1992 movie turned Tony winning musical
was originally conceived as an entry
of "Tales from the Crypt."
- Ooh.
- 1992 movie turned Tony winning musical,
"Tales from the Crypt."
That is of course, "The Lion King."
- The Lion King.
- Really?
- Huh, no, I don't know.
- Well.
- Oh, he's impressed.
- What do we got?
- Andy, she guessed Annie.
- '92.
- '92 musical.
- I think I got it, I think I got it.
- I mean, I gotta pass, Paul, it passes to you.
What do you think?
- I gotta guess "Beetlejuice."
- Yeah, as I guess. - Oh, okay.
That's gotta be it, yeah.
Oh no, "Death Becomes Her."
- Boo.
- "Death Becomes Her."
- I lied, more points. - He passed to Paul.
He lost the point.
- Even more points away. - I heard that show's
amazing though.
- SJ saw it right before it got nominated for the Tony.
So she saw it like with a half empty audience
with the original cast and was like,
"Oh, this is just spectacular."
She was so mad that I didn't see it with her.
- Oh wow.
- Paul, you're up.
- I'll do "How It Started for Eight"
to try and get back into negative nothing.
- Get in there.
This four time Golden Globe nominee
was originally cast as Sonya Blade
in 1995's "Mortal Kombat."
Unfortunately, or fortunately,
she broke her wrist while training for the role
and was replaced by that lady who married Pete Sampras.
- Right, this was...
- Kate Winslet.
- Carmen, not Carmen.
Her name was Carmen in that fucking thing.
- Carmen Electra? - Shit.
No, it's, there's something about marriage.
Cameron Diaz, Cameron Diaz, Cameron Diaz.
- Cameron Diaz is correct.
- I know my "Mortal Kombat" trilogy.
- Trivia. - Do.
- Yeah.
- That gets Matt all the way back to zero,
which puts him in the lead with zero points.
Matt is at negative 200 and I am at negative 400.
Thanks a lot, ML Kennedy.
Matt, you're up.
You got four questions left.
- It's anyone's game.
- I think there's a daily double left too.
- Let's go with potpourri for 400.
The roots of this ice cream come from Greek words
meaning new and city.
- The roots of this ice cream name?
- Mm-hmm.
- Huh.
Ben and Jerry.
- Hagen Daz.
JJ, you know any Greek words for new?
- Nope.
- Moose tracks.
- So I'm just repeating everybody in the chat.
- What's my yogurt?
My faille, what's on my yogurt container?
Or what do all the captains say?
You probably know some Greek.
All the captains are Greek.
- That's true.
- Is it Hagen Daz?
- Is this a--
- Hagen Daz is a made-up name.
- No, it's not a daily double.
- Oh, then what am I doing?
Pass, I don't give a shit.
- Yeah, I passed too, Paul.
- No, I passed, I have no idea.
- Neapolitan.
(all groaning)
- We're so dumb.
- If only any of us had thought about the show
that we're currently on.
Let's see, I'll try to get some points.
What's their number for 800?
The youngest of George Foreman's sons is named what?
I believe it's George.
- I think you're right.
- I think they're just all named George.
It's George VI, the little Joey.
- Little Joey.
Wait, do I get credit for George?
- Yes.
- Wait, no, it was in the category of what's the number?
- Yup.
- I don't know.
Was it?
If it was what's the number, then I got it wrong.
- Oh, 'cause what's the number?
- I did not answer a number.
- Oh, right.
- Oh, how it started.
Oh, no, it was what's their number.
It was what's their number, yeah.
Yeah, so no, I didn't deserve those points
and I didn't get them.
Paul, you're up.
You got what's their number for 400 or turkeys for 200?
- I'll try turkeys for two.
- This 2012 Disney movie based off a "Princess of Mars"
managed to lose somewhere around $200 million for the studio.
The movie isn't bad.
- John Carter.
- Paul has other thoughts.
- John Carter of Mars.
Yes, John Carter. - Oh, it was just John Carter.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so you got that wrong.
You said of Mars.
- I did say of Mars. - And that is incorrect.
And Matt closing out the category and the game.
Going for the tie.
- Going for the tie, high stakes.
- What's their number?
And it's a daily double.
- Oh shit.
- It doesn't increase anything.
- Oh, that's right.
- It doesn't.
The current King of England is King Charles the what?
- The gracious. - The King.
- Charles's have there been.
- Boy, if there was ever a time to start up
a new Charles in charge.
- Let's see, Elizabeth was Elizabeth the second.
So that would make King Charles.
- Scott Baio is King Charles.
- Oh, it's a daily double.
So I have to guess.
- The good thing is you know that it's a number.
So it's not like there are infinite wrong answers.
- I'll go with third.
- King Charles the third is correct.
- Wow.
- Well done, Matt.
That is the game.
Matt and Paul are tied at 200 points a piece.
I have negative 1200 points.
But since of course, Matt and Paul tied,
cat's game, I win.
- Jacob wins.
- Congratulations, Jacob.
- I know that's from ML Kennedy.
Thank you, thank you.
- I hope when they, 'cause we get updates
of who writes them, they score them, right?
But I hope they get it right,
where they score your win for Paul and I tie.
I hope that was part of the--
- Oh yeah, you guys get the points.
Yeah, you get the points in the--
- Right, in the points totals, but yeah.
- Yeah, but I should get credit for the win.
- That was a really good one, ML Kennedy, thank you.
That was an excellent scooperty.
- That was.
If you wanna send us a scooperty,
just like ML Kennedy did, heyscoops.com is where you can go.
Go over to heyscoops.com.
You can make us a scooperty.
You can make us a Price is Scryte jock versus nerd.
You can make us an Obelisk jock versus nerd.
You can do all those things over there at heyscoops.com.
You can also send us an email over there.
We read emails on the show from time to time.
Matt, I have a piece of physical scoop mail here for you
that a house guest of mine brought for you.
- Oh, well then there you go.
- My friend, Scott Burrell from Natchitoches
is in town right now.
And he brought you a Bruce Springsteen
and the E Street Band tour hat.
- Yes. - Wow.
- From their 1999 tour.
- That's so cool. - Or 1990.
- Yeah, 1999 tour.
- Wow.
- That was when they reunited.
- Yeah, so I've got a hat here for you.
- Freaking awesome.
- Yes, I'm very excited about that hat.
I wanna thank Dr. Mike for stopping by today.
- Yes, absolutely, thank you, Dr. Mike.
- He and I have been texting since he got off air.
Next time we do a double episode,
'cause when we do two episodes,
he can wake up at a reasonable hour and join us.
We're gonna do a Dr. Mike answers
all of our medical questions episode.
We'll tell the scoops in advance.
- Oh, good, yes.
- All the scoops. - That's a great idea.
That's a brilliant idea.
We should do that sooner than later, yeah.
- I don't know, I mean, I feel like
most of the scoops questions involved hemorrhoids
and I feel like we covered most of that today.
We did cover a lot of hemorrhoids.
- There's no doubt it's gonna be hashtag butt stuff.
That's, there's no doubt.
(laughing)
- Well, I mean, it's Dr. Mike's personal hashtag.
- Did we, did we, where did we come down
on the razoring your hemorrhoids or no?
Was that a-- - That's a bad idea.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Yeah, you're saying like it was up in the air.
It was always a bad idea. - I wasn't 100%,
I wasn't 100%.
(laughing)
- I also wanna thank JJ, Jessica Jane for stopping by.
Thank you, JJ. - Yeah, I love you guys.
- Thanks for coming by, JJ. - Jessica Jane Magic
over on Instagram to go check her out.
Give her a follow.
Don't follow her in real life.
Just follow her on Instagram.
If you follow her in real life, she's gonna,
she's gonna follow, you're gonna follow her down alleys.
You're gonna find single shoes.
It's gonna be a whole thing.
- Listen, I am so lonely.
(laughing)
Follow me.
- I was just gonna say,
if you think you're gonna follow her physically,
you would get in line.
There's at least, there's at least four other people
trying to do that.
- They're all magicians.
- Well, they're not trying hard enough 'cause I'm lonely.
(laughing)
- Please stalk and visit me.
- Please.
- For me, as your friend, the best I can promise you
is I think December 8th or 9th we can hang out
is the next time we can hang.
- Yay, okay, good. - Let's do that.
Maybe come over to, you wanna do a game night with the boys.
We should do that.
- Yes, that would be awesome.
I miss those little dudes.
- Yeah, they're not little, but yeah, yeah.
- They're big dudes.
- They're just dudes. - They're very big dudes.
- They're taller than me now, I think.
- I think one has got you.
I do think one has got you.
- Oh, chaotic clumsy.
The American healthcare system equals
showing a doctor from Australia
your hemorrhoids and rashes on a group Zoom
filled with other people yelling salt pork at the screen.
- You're not wrong.
- You're just absolutely right.
- And it hurts how right you are, chaotic clumsy.
- It's true.
- I will go to Europe.
Who wants me to go to Europe?
- Nobody wants you to go to Europe.
- Yes, I will go.
I will go.
Yes, and Andy, I am recruiting stalkers.
Just don't get me mixed up with Mike.
If he's dressed up.
- Mike.
- Or Dr. Mike.
- And we gotta get our castle show together.
All right.
Thanks for listening to everybody's,
no, we gotta thank people. - We gotta thank people.
- Nope, sorry.
- Yeah, yeah, we got Patreons to thank.
There are people here that supported us all these years.
All of these people know that you cannot get hemorrhoids
as long as you're wearing Spanx.
That's a Scoop of Saltwater, Scoop Skywalker,
Scoop T, Scoopaholic, Scoopa Troopa,
Scoop Paul's Drag Race, Scooped Mids, Scoop-a-Luga,
Scooper Metroid, Scooper Nova Girl,
Scoopy Loren, Scoopiter Ascending,
Scoop JD, Scoop Kada, Scoop Knack Paddy Whack,
Scoop Lachisa, Scoop Neon Black,
Scoop Nick, Scoop-o-Metrics, Scoops Ahazard,
Scoop Trek the Experience, and Scoopy and the Beast.
- The following people learned the hard way
that you should not razor your hemorrhoids.
Six-foot Scoop, Scully Wall Scoop,
Slightly Sleddy Scoop, Slurpee Kay-ay Motherfucker,
Smitty Scoop, Solar Powered Scoop,
Soulless Scoop, Sound Man Scoop,
Spring Loaded Scoop, Stab and Dash Scoop,
Stacey Coleman, Streets McGreets,
Stephanie Young, Stephen Clively, Stephen Landon,
Stephen Biggs, Stuart Wilson, Strange Uncle's Podcast,
Strap a Chicken on Scoop, Sugar Rush Socio,
Supergeek13579, Swedish Scoop,
Take It Evie Podcast, Tamara Hamilton,
Technical Scoop Hort, Temporary Dot Reality,
Pierce, Turn the Page, That Thing in the Attic,
The Bad Humor Man, The Sincy Scoop.
The following people all have a pickled graveyard
in their backyard because it's allowed by the law.
(laughs)
That's Scoopy Dooby Doo, Scoopy Ramone,
Scoopy Bartfast, Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess,
Scott A, Scott Andrews, Scott Ashlock,
Scott Headington, Scott Mulderig, Scott Schofeld,
Sean Kellner, Seanathan P, Sebastian Robbins,
SF, Sean, Shoeless Scoop,
Silicon Scoop, Silverfist Scoop,
and Sir Scoopy McScooperton the Third Esquire.
- The following individuals all have an elaborate shrine
to Billy Zane in their attic.
The Sincy Scoop, The Civic Crew Scoop,
The Damsels of Dorkington, The Devil's Lettuce Scoop,
The Digery Douche, The Famous Ball,
The Going Over Our Fred's Podcast,
The Ice Cream Headache, The Ice Cream Headache Again,
The Lapis Lagomorf, The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver,
The Nano Scoop, The SCOOP, Turn the Page,
That Thing in the Attic, and The Bad Humor Man.
- And of course I wanna thank all of these people
who have prehensile hemorrhoids.
That is The Salty Squid, The Scoop Lockian,
The Spirit of the Latin Club, The Upside Down Underscoop,
The Dirty Scoop, The Man, The Myth, The Scoop,
Thomas Beach Thunder, Cougar Falcon Scoop,
Timothy Sutton, TK421 Scoop Please,
Tom Kreiger, Tom Mankerdy, Tom Stott,
Tony Cowley, Tony Scuprano, Travis Jaguri,
Travis Murray, Tristan Guevara, Troy Anthony Tanzer,
Tuba Scoop, Tyler Bartlett, Tyler Scoop McDuck,
Udo Gearhards, Uncle Don's Woodshop, Warren Breaux,
Water Ice Scoop, Wendy Cooper, Wendy Bumgarner,
Wes Coughlin, What Was Like When Scoop, Who Dat Scoop,
Will Beardydan, Will Kelder, William McDonald,
and Wind Walker Scoop 23, thank you all so much.
You are all jewels in my eyes.
- Thank you all so much.
If you want to be thanked on air,
if you want all kinds of other rewards,
we have monthly and yearly options.
Yearly will save you some money
by committing to the year, you get a discount.
- That's right.
- Anything that fits your budget,
we could use your support right now over at preachingfun.com.
(upbeat music)
Come visit preachingfun.com
It's better than hanging with your mom
Out of the bed
- Or if you don't want to physically follow Jessica Jane
around town all the time, just send her a nice gift.
What should you send her?
Send her a fart in a bag, fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts
Farts in a bag.biz
- That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with,
what's the other one, preachingfun.com.
- JJ's all faster.
- JJ distracted me with her farts in a bag.
That along with preachingfun.com,
it takes you to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
Of course, we are funded by our Patreons,
so head over there, fartsinabag.biz, preachingfun.com.
Go over and do it now.
Another thing you can do after you have gone over
and given us most of your money at preachingfun.com
and fartsinabag.biz, if you have any of it left over,
you can go over to GoFundMe,
and they are funding the last of the Hey Scoops the Movie,
Help Finish Hey Scoops the Movie.
If you look up Hey Scoops, GoFundMe on Google,
it takes you right to the page.
The page is actually called Help Finish Hey Scoops the Movie.
They are currently 70% on their way to the goal.
- Yeah, so yeah. - But we wanna push it
past the goal, we wanna get it really--
- And we wanna go past the goal, of course, yeah.
'Cause there's gonna be more expenses and everything,
that it's gonna be a bit of a moving target,
but it's gonna be all reasonable and great.
So if you're interested at all in the Hey Scoops Movie,
go over there, yes.
- How big of a role does Vinny have in the documentary?
- I was gonna ask if he's in that day movie.
I mean, the day that they were filming the movie,
I'm sure he did.
- I think he's the narrator, right?
Yeah, he's like the-- - He's the narrator.
- He's the Jiminy Cricket, I think, of the movie.
- No, no, no, no, not okay. - No, no.
- Yeah, Happy Thanksgiving.
- Oh yeah, and just a shout out to all of those.
Well, I guess it's too late now,
but I'm hosting the Hangout tomorrow at seven o'clock.
- Oh yeah, it's too late.
- But last episode-- - Yeah, yeah.
- You would've heard it, but whatever, yeah.
- Good job.
(laughing)
- Put a button on that one.
- Thanks, guys. - Glad we circled back.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, I'm on top of it.
I'm on top of it. - Oh, right.
- Does anyone else have any announcements?
- Yeah.
- Tomorrow, Hangout, seven p.m.
But that's Wednesday. - No, no,
that was last week, Paul. - And this is going out
Thanksgiving, right? - Monday.
- This technically our Thanksgiving episode, yeah?
Okay, great. - This is our post
Thanksgiving episode, this is our Monday
after Thanksgiving episode.
- Oh. - We're all so full.
- This is our tryptophan episode.
- Yeah, yeah. - Yeah.
- So we hope that you use some song lyrics
if you got challenged to say grace at your table.
- Yeah, don't forget to do the--
- Bermuda, my mama, come on, pretty mama.
- Yeah, how far can you get into-- - The Kokomo challenge.
- The Kokomo challenge, how much Kokomo?
Can you fake for grace?
That's what, that's always-- (laughing)
- If you didn't do it at Thanksgiving,
Christmas is right around the corner.
- That's right, they always get a chance.
I want somebody to get through it 100% one of these days,
it's gonna be awesome.
- I think the Kokomo challenge is one of the funniest
things we've ever done.
- It is, it's pretty great. - It really is.
It really is, we should've stopped there.
- 'Cause a lot of it sounds like a prayer.
- Yeah.
All right, thanks for this, everybody.
Stay safe out there, we love you and we'll see you soon.
- We'll see you soon.
- That dreamy look in your eyes
gives me a tropical contact high.
Thank you, Jesus. (laughing)
(upbeat music)
Pass the gravy.
Freakin' fun
See ya!