Oh hello there I didn't see you but I'm so happy you are here because I'd like to
thank the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers
right now I'd like to thank Frankie "Sticky" Scoop, Fifi, Elton "Magic" Scoop, Dr.
Scoop Little, Dirty Old Scoop, Dead Lazlo, David Walker, Darth Scooper, Darren
Cunningham, Christie Salinas, Christine Elsesser, Chasing the Dragon Scoop,
Blue Line Scoop, and Bearded Scoop 3. If you want to be an ice cream truck driver
just like these fine folks head over to preachingfun.com. Preachingfun.com is
where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life
you save may be your own and now a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice
cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
it's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social sitting in Pittsburgh
Pennsylvania that's Paul Mattingly sitting at sea it's Matt Donnelly sitting
Las Vegas the bad-ass me check out the audio guy we're preaching fun fun I'm
doing wonderful I'm out on the the seas outside of Canada I said last week that
I was gonna go to st. John Newfoundland and I was so excited turns out Canada's
wicked wicked crazy with st. John's so it turns out it was st. John's New
Brunswick and not they're lousy with st. John's now I already have an affection
for st. John and the Virgin Islands right John's Newfoundland that I wasn't about
to get off the boat for this st. New St. John I was like I don't have room I
don't have room in my heart for a third st. John you have plenty of st. John's in
your life you don't need more do any of these locations go by St. John because
that's a real thing you know we're going from st. John's engine yeah well it's a
there you remember a air wolf right of course I remember air ball so string
fellow Hawk yeah he was always looking for his brother St. John and that is a
shortened way of saying st. John so there were kids that were named St. John
I just wondered if they ever if that ever applies to like cities I'll open my
porthole and ask okay anyone go by St. John I'm just kidding my porthole over
looks out into a wall so a wall in the boat yeah my porthole looks out into the
vast six feet away as a wall that's what I oh you're just docked right now no no
no no oh no you sure it's an internal hole it's an internal portal my god it
is a glory pole I mean he might be docking right now as well
oh yeah in a glory porthole that's cameras from the waist up so we have no
idea we never will know are you ever gonna be on boats with pipe to plane
again soon I don't know I'm on there they're joining the boat the ship that
I'm on right now next week okay so ships in the night we we would have
cross paths on the day yeah like I'm getting on the way I'm me getting off
except that I am and now I have to get off early right here's the thing so I'm
on the ship for four days and that's because originally they wanted me here
for the week but the week started at scoop fest and I said I can't do it I
got to go to scoop fest right then I got this offer for Virgin Voyages to join
Virgin and that was a two-week gig so I want to say yes to that and basically
saying told by agent I will I will let go of this gig if it means you know if I
have to just just to still do virgin right yeah and that would give me days
off after scoop fest that'd be nice so I was like there's no way they're gonna
agree just to have me on this ship for four days but they're just going to just
truncate the front and back end of the week and they did now you have discovered
the true infinite money glitch that is cruise ship lines apparently what also
meant and that means that I knew that I was getting on a performing like those
and I was doing shows right and so was it when you got on yeah I didn't do two
shows that night wow shows the next night holy shit dude how did that go
luckily you were nice and rested so yeah so at scoop fest I had the already had
this hard task of it that I've never go away for three weeks and I'm away for
three weeks and then on top of the three weeks I'm going for in cruise ships I
have two shows in Sparta New Jersey on October 16th and the improved jammer
Union on October 18th October 17th is the smartest shows and so I had to pack
for magic shows for all of those things plus materials you know I could go you
know I go through materials things like that and and and so I was already pretty
nerve-wracked plus I did magic at school fest which means I had to bring stuff
just school fest so I had to bring it I had to perform them bring it home or whatever so
the only chance I had to really pack with sanity was in the dinner break
between daytime scoop fest and nighttime scoop fest on Saturday yeah right which
was a two-hour break and it was like a true two-hour break because we finished
up right before the break started in the daytime session so like we actually had
about two hours between the daytime session and the Jog vs. Nerdball and
during ice cream social I was getting notifications on my phone from Air
Canada right and I was like that's weird I mean I'm flying tomorrow but I can
check in sure whatever and they were and they were inappropriate messages right
they were like dick pics and a lot of stuff yeah they're basically saying no
there was they were showing you show me mine they're saying if you don't respond
to these text messages we're putting these on the internet so you didn't
respond and now they're out holy Mike Johnson
but I don't know Paul Air Canada okay I've gotten an email like a week before
whatever and I saw that they were shifting the time of my flight like a
half hour earlier okay great what I didn't realize is that they also shifted
it to a day early day earlier than a half hour earlier 24 hours and a half
hour earlier yeah this is Air Canada not not not my cruise booker right yeah
right I think it was booked and then the airline moved the thing well they moved
oh it's Air Canada so the times are metric that explains it that explains
that explains the disconnect it goes by how long it takes ice to melt that's how
they ancient ancient Phoenicians had sundials most things in Canada are based
on how long it takes ice to melt yeah that's right so I just spend the dinner
break rescheduling my travel frantically just on the emergency line lines because
suddenly I was not on the flight that I supposed to be on right and and I should
have another like the whole that's the whole thing and so I could you know how
to take the reservation but you don't know how to hold the reservation and I
so I basically had to come back to the jock versus nerd ball without knowing
what I was doing the next day and then at the end of the costume parade I got
an email saying that I had to be on a flight at a 6 a.m. flight so I had to be
at the airport at 445 of the morning that is some shit bags bullshit and then
because it was a last-minute flight it wasn't direct so I had to take three
flights to get to Canada oh holy fuck man so I was three flights total of 15
hours by the time I got to my hotel they let you sit on the wing and then I'd
asleep and get up right away and just get to the ship oh and then it's like go
to the ship there's a guy on a bike he just goes Matt Donnelly he goes yeah he
goes forgive me it's my day off and he's just dressed in like head-to-toe and
beautiful biker riding bike outdoor gear right that's like forgive it stranger
yeah but they're waiting for you get in there and I was like oh I said I can't
have gone here any faster than me meeting my driver on time and my driver
getting me out of time I don't know what I could have done yeah step on it
waiting for me what yeah and then I see noted it for you if you get that get me
there in time for my show I get around to the port and the the pork is we have
no record of you being here I was literally just told two minutes ago and
a hundred feet ago that you were waiting for me inside yeah apparently not that
guy so finally a guy from business comes out and basically reprimands someone at
the dock for looking up my thing improperly that person being very
defensive and I was listening to a very snippy conversation guys guys guys
could you please have this uncomfortable conversation after I get on to the boat
I would like to get onto the boat you guys could have this conversation for as
long as you want after I'm gone and so this is like normal little gang way it
goes right up to the fourth deck yeah and then there's a zigzaggy gang way
really long gang way that goes up to the seventh deck and and the first of a
princess gestures me to the zigzaggy gang way that goes up three stories and
I have two giant banks and my my backpack in banks and I was like are you
sure I can't go up the little one yeah
yeah but there's like no that's where most of the guests are getting off to
go into it's a Saint John to Halifax and singe in Halifax and and so I go to move
like all my stuff and there's a guy you know working for the cruise like an
eager young young guy English other first language goes can I help you with
that I was like boy can you he takes me up but I'm in a crew cabin not in a
guest cabin yeah and so we get on the ship and I was like showing him my room
number and he's trying to get me to this the seventh deck where the crew for the
regular cabins right I'm trying to explain to him no no I'm in a crew cabin
yeah so he's stopping as he stops like a janitor and they and they speak Spanish
to each other and the janitor's like no follow me and I go through this ornate
path we're all set I'm like outside of the ship on this weird deck area where
I'm looking at the thing or I'm like I don't know if I this isn't supposed to
be here then boom I'm into a crew area and then into finally into my cabin and
the good news is my cabin is 50 feet from the theater oh that's oh that's
that's big that's big yeah yeah so I get all my stuff in the theater back in the
thing and then I realized I should go get like a cup of coffee or something to
eat or something and I am walking aimlessly in the crew area please
someone give me coffee try to find your way I was like yeah no one no one showed
me how to get out to the regular ship yeah and so I see two guys and I'm like
I'm just trying to get to like the regular part of the ship or like where
the passengers go or whatever and they go who are you are you supposed to be
back here what are you doing there is a there is a hard line like I said when we
were doing second city tours we had a very fortunate situation where we had
passes that were literally crew and passenger status right we had both so we
could we could go anywhere but yeah if you haven't been designated they get
snippy yeah but they figured it all out did you do a little quick bit of table
side honestly or did they harpoon you I straight up just I straight up just
walked away I walked up to another floor I'm good and then I went up to you just
left them arguing about who yeah I was like I don't want to I don't want to do
this and no that's awesome later that's awesome be another way you know what I
bet I can find it on my own see you guys have a good day never mind yeah so yeah
it was it was it was it was a it was a big adventure to get here and then just
do two shows right away and they were really well good I was like I was like
this could get this could have gone a lot better if I had those shows were
all right imagine if I had slept so listener Chris Lowry is on the the he
listens to the show and he and his wife book book travel for people yeah go
with Lisa.com that's where they help set up people want to see me on the ship and
stuff and so Lisa his wife is on on the ship and I met her before she's come to
my Elton shows they offered to take me out to dinner at the beautiful Crown
Grill nice on my on the second night I was on board and then they were telling
me about how they ran into people who saw my show on st. John and I was like oh
I don't think they're gonna tell me a story where they complimented me she was
like yeah one guy was like yeah it wasn't really for me mind reader guy or
whatever and I was like why are you telling me this story yeah what the
hell this next story super awkward then cuz I just saw several people that hated
your show I understand I'm not for everyone as I said as I said it's good
fest you know you know you're not for everyone but as soon as you hear it it's
devastating so very critical about my outfit that I was wearing at the time it
really hurt but they talked about how they basically said like oh we're going
to the embassy the Crown Grill but they said the other name for another ship's
stakeout so yeah Cagney's I think it was called okay and so then that so I go oh
so they were coming here to this thing tonight that's what they told you they
invited you to dinner to join them here and I go yeah so they're here yeah and I
go like oh okay and we look around or whatever we don't see them just now
getting back to my room from getting coffee for this episode I end up taking
an elevator and two guys are like oh you're the mindbender guy and I go yeah
yeah we saw you show the other night I go yeah and then nothing okay and then
the opera silence the guy goes I think we saw you the night at Cagney's you're
having dinner with Lisa and I go oh my god it's them it's the guys they were
talking to it's the eyes not for me it's not for me guy
amazing I'm face-to-face like a murder she wrote mystery novel we're like I
had the key I had the key that they right they named the steakhouse the wrong
steakhouse and it's the only thing they could have said to clue you in this
confirmed but it did not enjoy my show yeah we saw you show the other night
there were chairs and everything hey Oh Rica is making a great point in the
chat here she's saying Matt is upset that no complements his show but when
he runs into audience members he doesn't compliment them either and that's a
really good point yeah I have to go back and tell those guys nice hats nice hats
assholes let me have to do that oh you guys are great at Cagney's the other
night I saw you order that steak amazing work yeah well we got a Rica I'm not
upset that no one complements my show I'm thrown off when people insist on
telling a story that someone did not enjoy my show that is weird man that's
weird that was no problem hearing nothing that's different that's
different is that what is that where your brain goes after you've booked
people on thousands of travel experiences is that you just get to like
oh yeah well you know a lot of people just hate you and they don't really yes
I mean people definitely get into that state of mind of like none of this
matters to me so why would it matter to you right yes right comes right that's
the energy of like that we're just shooting the breeze I just know this I
know that yeah these guys hated your show but it like in their mind she's
sitting there thinking like oh Matt has done this show so many times well surely
people have disliked the show before it can't bother him it's just water off and
ducks back like who cares we're being harsh too wasn't that he hated it just
wasn't for him oh no no he actually sent me a message as well the way the story
actually goes is that the subtext of the stories was told to me it basically
didn't didn't believe I was an actual mind reader oh really well in that case
I've got good news for them they were they were right so this is Simon Cowell's
cousin and which is I should make no claims during my show that I like I set
the premise but I do I do know I basically like all of my stuff as if I'm
doing any mind reading bits it's all comedic right like I get the results
correct but all I'm trying to do is make sure it's funny along the way and that's
the it's the weird thing I imagine but you it's a you can't deny it if someone
goes like yeah I don't think you really do that you're like yep that's right
that's correct and so if you're upset with me for even towing the line for
claiming to have superpowers I could if that upsets you I get it like I can't do
anything about it it's it's it's it's the deal right all right I did it Jacob
nailed it I said Oh Rico's name correctly on air oh nice oh I am
impressed I know I am and I noted that I have never heard I'd never heard the
pronunciation correct and I was like oh yeah Rica yeah yeah took me 12 years and
and her something by African babble to get it right but that's what happened
perfect finally got it oh man Jacob you asked me for a sponsor and I can't
access my phone so I'm gonna go over to a web page and open it up there oh nice
well while you're doing that we'll just we'll just talk a little bit scoop fest
here we just had our big scoop fest it was amazing it was oh we are all almost
recovered and by all I mean like fucking everybody I imagine I mean I don't buddy
yeah everybody got beat I didn't get kovat this time well there's that that I
know of yeah but also like legit like I felt like everyone not just us I felt
like the attendees were like Jesus by the end of the yeah well actually I was
having a conversation with Ryre the night of the loadout because we even
commented during the during the show during the scoop fest podcast that the
energy you kind of like went weird in the room for a while and we were kind of
chatting about that and the energy of the of the whole thing and it really
seems like everyone came to scoop fest as you know in a way that you would
expect which is a relief you know they're coming to scoop fest as this as
a big energy relief thing and especially by the end of it everyone was kind of
like sitting in that lull yeah I don't know it was it was a it was an
interesting it was an interesting thing yeah I think I think so I think I think
this I really you know we talked about this in a few episodes back but like I
that is it is a crazy time yeah and I think and I think during Penn Sunday
School live like Penn really hung a lantern on it in terms of talking to his
children yeah you guys don't know that this actually is incredibly unusual
right and like what's happening is impossible yeah and so you know none of
this that is happening can happen it's none it's all impossible but it's
happening anyway yeah yeah yeah and the shows also 12 years old or whatever 11
years old and so are indeed our we've all gotten older we're older and so is
everyone else maybe the evening festivities started 7 and not 8 wrap up
around 7 I don't know I don't know about all that we're all gonna go to the
sizzler and have dinner around 4 bird no I mean like something who spearheads the
the the nighttime programming and stuff I was like panicking trying to add stuff
and then by the time it all went down I was like oh I put a lot of stuff up here
oh yeah we need we needed I did have I did maybe over program some some of some
nights it was activities no laws though that's for sure no I mean to go in
order a bucket show crushed so fun yeah big thanks to Brenna Mark Robert Mark
that was fantastic this again and like I had so many scoops coming up and saying
it was the first time they'd seen a bucket show and I was like well hope you
like that one because it's never gonna get any better than that
was actively telling people to not come back to future bucket shows because that
one was that was to be the best one I don't know if it went quite that far but
I just said that is the best it's close yeah as close if you came to see both
those shows shit I don't know man I don't tell you great we're doing we're
doing one at Tunis Tavern like real soon it's like October 23rd let's oh we're
gonna crush that one we already sold some tickets for it let's not no we're
gonna crush that one because that one was already planned that one was a was a
carve out in Paul's statement never see another one unless you've already planned
to see no it was just it'll be better it was just really it's just one of those
things too again and even like I was doing that interview for the documentary
and I recounted our first meeting Matt and how you had friends in the audience
that night after we'd done our show and they asked you how long we've been
working together yes it's just well it's just one of those things it just kind of
remind me again it's like we had two brand new people who we hadn't played
with in forever don't play with regularly and it was like you know forget
it I had never I had never coached Brenna's impromptu yeah or one with
Brenna yeah I just knew we just we vibrate Brenna obviously his podcast
co-hosts and friends and stuff and she always said like oh we should all just
shook around some time look everybody it's a cold runner and everybody hey you
wave to all the scoops she's got to go pick up our giz from the grandparents so
she's she's across the state to go grab the doggy yeah yes yeah rainbow bright
shirt represent be safe sweetheart holler if you need anything I love you
too all right did you guys have a favorite part of scoop fest no I mean
somebody else was trying to zip through an order because the next day was the
barbecue right and Jacob you cooked barbecue pulled pork and yeah my god
dude you fucking crushed that too oh it was so good I really wish I could have
gotten more of that pork but I I didn't get enough but it was good yeah the food
Alex Bartman made fresh pizzas for everybody oh yeah the pizza was great
yep the food was the food was all was all solid
SJ made SJ's famous mac and cheese that shit was great too yeah so we all we all
pitched in a little bit this year instead of doing any we didn't or last
year we cooked the main stuff and then ordered the sides and this year we said
now fuck it we're not ordering anything yeah we're doing it all it was really
good and it was it was nuts it was nuts for you guys to pull off all the stuff
you pulled off yeah it was windy that was the only thing we didn't account for
was wind I remember driving a day and it rained for like two minutes I was like
rain we have not we have no backup plan for rain dead if it rains I had a germ of
a plan but it wasn't a good plan it was not a good plan at all yeah yeah I mean
scuba nova girl in the chat is saying everyone cram into Jacob's house that
was gonna be plan B yeah yeah I feel like we were definitely just gonna get
the plan B well as funny as it was it was still pretty hot and the Sun was
pretty blazy and you know you had that shade wall everybody just rammed up
against the shade wall yeah and then I got really red to the point where scoops
were like are you okay I had to let them know that that's just what the
Mattingly jeans do I just get real red looking I'm fine I didn't I didn't burn
like you can see I don't have a sunburn yeah but I just I got really red I look
like I'm gonna explode when I'm mowing the lawn out here like if I come inside
just be at and hands it's like oh my god you're a lobster I'm like it's just what
I do my body just it gets it's you know that's how I'm getting the heat out it
comes to the front but yeah I do I really ate exactly a pine a plane played
the the barbecue they were fantastic that was the that was the biggest swing
I did I pulled for this one was that my friends from Ireland were all off they
weren't they weren't obligated to be on ships and so I said if you're available
let's get you in here and so they I flew them in from Ireland to be here is their
first time in Vegas and they just were absolutely blown away by they exhausted
and I had to write them a note being like you know it's very common that
people love Las Vegas and also think three days is plenty right oh yeah and
and that was the case for them they were definitely like just wiped at the end
sure but they yeah they crushed it at Jacob's house and they're they're just
that I love those guys so much and they're so charming and they're such
they're great at what they do and it's they have such different personalities
and they all find a way to really shine and it's really funny and I like them
and so yeah they I was I was very emotional watching them play in Jacob's
backyard that was yeah it was great it was a big carry deal for me and we were
supposed to have you you're talking about the wind we were supposed to have
another entertainer at the at the barbecue but the wind kept Michael Doe
from being able to juggle at the barbecue right so Mike no it's Parkinson's yes
and he asked it he said yes to do excuse us before he knew he had it right
his obligation and then he has to juggle you know 500 throws every day to make
sure he can keep movement in his body and be able to do what he does for a
living while he fights this vicious disease and then it's fucking windy as
hell yeah it's windy we might not go and I said oh you can't you don't want to go
he goes well I can do it the show will be funny but there will be no juggling in
it and then he said no successful juggling there will be throwing but not
catching not catching I said okay let's let's let's just call it so I was so
aggravated too because it was like it was perfect all afternoon and then like
20 minutes before Godot was was set to go up that's when the wind kicked up
yeah like it was it was and then like half an hour later it was it was back to
be in like there was a light breeze but it was fine after that still but yeah
it was crazy it was crazy for a minute yeah yeah and then but he still was
phenomenal yeah well and then he did the variety show yeah yeah yeah so then that
night we surprised the audience with a reuniting of two characters in a clown
shortly after the very recent breakup of the podcast to do a podcast battle Jimmy
Sonina dressed in full clown regalia he did was delightfully ironic because in
their Cirque show it's Johnny and RJ have to wear a lot of makeup and Jimmy
doesn't and so it was very funny for Jimmy to come in full makeup while
they were there goes and we had delightful trivia battle hosted by Mikey
for between between us and they won yeah they did spoiler because we're gonna put
those in our patreon feed like always and so that was really fun then while I
was doing my shows at the Magic Castle a month ago someone on my special
like touring company feed on my abracadabra which is a whatsapp thread
right I share my my all my all my adventures and someone said why aren't
you and Nick doing scoop fest and I literally just turned to him backstage
like good point Nick what are you doing this dates like when I was like all right
come out to scoop Nick and I did our pillar set in that we did the Magic
Castle at scoop fest which is so fun because in our set I get to do an
illusion with Nick that he normally does with his wife and I love doing this bit
it was great the whole thing was great that whole that whole show was really
really good so you make you make an excellent magic assistant Matt this is
this is a running gag right that was really funny that bit was funny
Alex Ramone had a bit in his show where he has someone called misdirection and
in his regular show he used to show girl as misdirection and we did the Magic
Castle I came out as misdirection and the foolers tour I came out as
misdirection and telling me to just improvise and dance and pretend I'm a
showgirl is not a tall not a tall ask for me in any way no I I will I will fake
dance until the Sun comes up and basically it's also me going like I have
no magic responsibilities great I'll be over here being funny yeah yeah you do
all the work I just have to pretend like I'm you know doing this or that no
problem oh and I still get credit great even better and so yeah we have to do
that bit and yeah yeah I the show Nick and I have done is really come together
now we've done it two different two different runs beach run is always like
15 shows yeah so it's really become like a really fun show to do I really enjoy
doing it and and that was fun and then Lindsay Benner I don't know dude and
Gary and let's even Gary and Emily when they're playing Gary I don't know how to
like tell people what you're gonna see right now because you're like I guess
she's a juggler but like sure really juggling show like it's just this
beautiful piece she does called the book of love and I know this because she ran
into this with it's now it's now part of the party over at Las Vegas at the
Cosmopolitan right and same thing where she said like hey you know I can do this
bit in the show and I heard she told me you know I hope I'm not portraying any
confidences but she said that they were a little like what I don't know or
whatever and she basically was like just let me do it yeah yeah because like
whenever she does she did she was part of like the magic live one year she had
the whole bit in the magic live and got like standing ovations for it it's not
him yeah it's just this beautiful really cool beautiful art piece get some of the
audience and does this whole arc of love with these juggling comedy bits and it's
just beautiful it's funny and it's and she's just a brilliant person it's funny
it's it's poignant and it kind of goes from from one almost variety slot to the
next on its own and it just it it flows and it works yeah and they're both they
were both so committed and fantastic oh yeah just yeah Gary comes out and it's
just and Gary is just a fucking icing on the cake with all of this it's it's so
good yeah and it's just and so yeah that crush so yeah that was and that was that
that was that was night one yeah which was it was a lot yeah and then we fell
over day two that one and then goes into day one technically yeah that was the
that was the extra that all right that yeah wasn't even day one that was just
the extra yeah that was the VIP yeah yeah let's do let's do a quick sponsor
and then come back and do day two today's show is brought to you by Bobby
but kisses kick butt buttery hello I'm Bobby but kiss and I got a kick but
buttery you want some butter for your butt for your buns I got bun butter I
got butter for cops I got big butter I got bitter butter some of my bitter
butter is comes in itty-bitty palates would you like some of Bobby but kisses
itty-bitty bitter butter palates for cops are too small for me the pallets
are too small yeah you want to try some of Bobby but kickers bitter butter bigger
pallets it's a bigger palette okay it's approximately four times the size of our
original Bobby butters bitter butter is like a bucket now that's a whole nother
product oh the bucket yeah we've got pallets we got buckets then we've also
got we've got ladies that's the other that's the other size what holy whole
lady size of whether it's just a lady made of butter that's right it's a it's
a man a margarine mannequin oh shit oh yeah I'm just here to pick up my lady
butter your margarine mannequin we were delivered to you you don't have to come
here for it my god well I have a gun what are you doing
oh my god whatever you want is yours oh god and her hey scoops a check out it's
really kind of the send the audio from that recording after that terrible
incident yeah we should not have aired that that was tragic yeah well that's
what you get for recording commercials on ring cameras it's very on tour but
sometimes every now and then you get a home invasion you know we're just trying
to do some ads here every now and then you get a home invasion what you're
gonna do so on today to technically day three day one yes yeah how this keeps
happening to us yeah is the variety show and this year was the most like frogs
in a wheelbarrow year ever you know for those expression with the trying to keep
frogs in a wheelbarrow they keep hopping out you know we try to get new people in
and and and still honor if other people want to come back and do it and you know
there are people that were on board up until like days before bailing out there
are people who wanted to do it but then like took jobs a month ago that left
town like and it just was like I just kept watching the thing and at one point
I was texting Jacob like days beforehand being like I'm really in my head about
this right this year's variety show and I was coming up with like backup plans
of maybe doing violin prob with Maeve Kennedy from the trio like I was like
really like what's happening and then some things just fall in our lap like
Stapes was still in town just around or what JD was like you know Stapes is down
I was like oh right we got Stapes that was great days before Harrison Greenbaum
calls me up as hey I'm gonna happen to be at the Rio this week are you gonna be
in town I was like well that scoop vest and of course Harrison was like yeah
down no problem yeah so good he was goddamn that was so good it's like
really happy about it and someone I've been trying to get to for years to do it
because we have a lot of friends in the burlesque community and like to go a
little burlesque in more Vegas we could throw in a little a little a little fun
burlesque although we are Kevin is always like hey as weird as you want to
be oh yeah like whatever shits like been too weird for other burlesque shows do
it do it here yeah go like I mean jumping ahead Hazel
performed and Hazel and I spoke a month or so or earlier and she was like I I
could do just like a classic burlesque thing and and just come out and be
pretty and and have pretty costumes and fans and everything I was like that's
great people will love it I'm sure if you do it you can also do your weird
stuff yeah the weird the weird stuff will play and she came out on stilts
dressed like a giant tree yeah she was a hint from Lord of the Rings and from
Lord learn she was treebeard a sexy stripping is sexy beard it was amazing
two tiny hobbit dolls that she made kiss and make out with each other and they
stripped - yep and but I finally we've tried in the past with our friend Nick
Byler came by who does this really incredible act in absent and he's just
and he's also in disco studies the the the host there extremely talented
fascinating guy he was great yes he does this really we did this really weird
thing in the show hot trashed or the pandemic where he tries to make a banana
daiquiri while trying to still hit a triangle on the notes during this one
song it's this conflict between trying to make the daiquiri and at the triangle
all while he's wearing just a banana a skirt made of actual bananas right and
it was great to have some equal representation from the male side of
burlesque world and then I had Jonas Wilberton and I forgot that I was also
burlesque yeah yeah but he was a very funny John John Mack and fro uh-huh
where he has the audience hit him with tennis balls and he does so he does a
seer wheel which you know those of you in the circus world are familiar but
those you may not be it's a big giant steer steel wheel it looks like a giant
hula hoop a steel ring that he is able to manipulate and swirl around and this
was a steel ring with a radius of about what six and a half feet or not a
radio yeah what's the thing across the circle whatever that distance is right
yeah this was the smallest stage he'd ever perform this yeah we only gave him
eight feet of space he had done it on a on a nine footer I think maybe mm-hmm he
he had kept asking me like there's a version I can do without the wheel I
said then let's do that and he goes we'll just send me the dimensions anyway
and I said in dimensions and he goes oh that's pretty small I go then don't do
the wheel just do the other part yeah and he goes okay well I'll bring the
wheel just in case and I go okay and then he sends me we load in and I see
it's a carpeted stage which is again not ideal for zero so it's carpeted so if
you don't want to do the wheel do not do the wheel and he goes all right I
probably won't but I'll bring it just in case yeah and then not only was it
carpeted but it had nth leaves and leftover banana daiquiri all over and
tomato juice yes it had tomato seeds banana juice had fucking leaves so I
would I had been sketching stuff away with my foot the whole time because I
knew that wheel was coming I was trying to make sure that was oh yeah but oh
y'all were we were all like try to clean the stage as much as possible I told
him afterwards I said that was fucking brave dude and that was amazing but it
was it was also really really funny and really really awesome yes one coming up
on in November he's doing a show over at the Vegas Theatre Company so we're
gonna have him on as a guest oh great great great great yeah yeah but yeah
Brenna did a more another goblin burlesque Stephen Roberts came by crush
doing stand-up yes not a not a show without Stephen yeah and without personal
highlight for me was Michael Gudeau yeah yeah and seeing Mike do it seemed like
you don't do it it was so good it was so funny and holy fuck yeah we talked
about it at the at the con but uh you forget we're friends with Michael Gudeau
we hang out we chat with Michael Gudeau we all forget that you get Michael Gudeau
on stage and he's a goddamn killer I mean it's just what he's gonna get on
stage just do it it's crazy to me too I was lucky enough to go see him with the
Lance Burton show way back in the day right and this is when I was first
working with Second City as a full-time Second City and class act that Lance
Burton is he called me out in the show had me stand up and wave to the people
because nice because Lance Burton knows how to be a fucking entertainer you know
we help each other we talk each other up right that's what it's about and that
that had that moment has stuck with me and just like the fact that Michael Gudeau
and Mac King both specifically came out to watch us do the bucket show I got I
put it up on our Facebook and whatnot Mac tweeted about it because he loves
come see us which is just so amazing to me because he's one of my heroes too we
have we have fucking strip performer royalty at this fucking thing yeah like
real deal you can't get any higher on the total poll how many shows did he say
he'd done it was 19 years 19 years thousands and thousands yeah I mean it's
nuts and I just forget like he just gets the audience right in that pocket
well he knows what he's doing and as soon as as soon as they're there you're
like oh I forgot it's just cruises yeah from here like it just he just is so
funny and there's so many gags and he just nails them and it just was like oh
god it was great he really you really that was the second time I was very
emotional at scoop fest was was that right there it was really awesome it's a
big moment it's a big moment I again I'm just I'm just honored that that not to
say that Harrison's ice stacking prediction via 9/11 theme didn't really
I loved that too my brother was involved in that trick and that made it even more
special for me it's only it's only appropriate because your brother was
involved in the in the real day too right involved involved is a big way to
say helped out with building seven but I mean you know you sure you say what you
want to say involved masterminded I know he won't take credit for the master
minding of it but that's only because he's modest then we had our mouth finger
bottle competition oh yes oh my gosh it gets better every year I so all through
scoop fest I make it a point so we you know our room there at the Orleans our
big our big convention room there at the Orleans it's right off the main hall in
their convention space there's other conventions going on while we're there
there was some religious thing going on on one side of us there was a family
reunion going on on the other side of us so I made it a point to as much as
possible keep those main doors open no no just during the whole goddamn thing
it is it is entertaining for me to watch people walk past those doors it's the
reason that I keep them open I love watching watching people look in and be
like I do it every year I love it during mouth there was a crowd of people at the
doors with just pure confused look it was great at one point I went to you
know use the facilities and I was in a bathroom stall in the men's room and I
heard two guys talking go like yeah they're not really checking any badges
over there that whatever that scoop thing is going on over there and then the
other goes yeah but like what the hell is going on over there what guys like
we could just go in there they're not gonna stop us and the other guys like
yeah but should we do I want to do that dare I dare I let my freak flag fly what
I'm trying to put an obelisk I believe inside of me I don't know how they were
gonna do it that makes me laugh they're not checking badges like you wouldn't
know like you wouldn't stick out like a sore fucking thumb if you weren't a
scoop or if you weren't at least down to clown this year our mystery our mystery
gift was a fez yeah where you could be jeweled so we had a bejeweling station
you could you could you could which was a stroke of genius by the way that
bejeweling station was that worked out well that goes that I mean he's here and
that goes that Michael Osroth is basically our director of scoop fest at
this point he really is he did a fantastic job with these these turned out
awesome he kicks everything uphill for us well we tried it well we all pull our
hair out trying to pull off school fest and and acts as a wonderful ambassador he
and Laurie in the party room to help really initiate and introduce other
scoops to each other in the party room really gets the conversations going and
that that vibe carries on to the show itself we were running into new tariff
shit we were running into all kinds of stuff yeah and I we really wanted pink
robes to continue the robe theme to figure out the Neapolitan effect we had
vanilla now we have a strawberry and and and then what's coming next chocolate
robes get warm and some experience pain I said I do an idea to mess with it okay
but but I don't remember the game of the idea of fans but then says I think I
think it was me it might have been you I mean we can look through that we can
look through the text but I think it was me I'm not taking I know it wasn't me so
that's I'll give you full credit okay it was me it was it was you or it was you
or Michael yeah me and Michael I think but Mike but again so many times we're
like oh because of this is getting expensive because of this we can't do it
or whatever and else from just kept after it yeah to make sure that we had
everything we wanted to deliver to the scoops the way we wanted yeah I have
ideas and Michael actually makes them happen
I'd yeah exactly ideas yeah those you guys listening just just picture casino
floor and a bunch of people in pink robes and maroon fezzes with a big not
occult on the back we're going in and out of the casino right it is the best
sight it is the funniest thing so funny it's just great so yeah and during all
this yeah I think we'd figure it out we had a documentary crew running around
during all this yes capturing all this madness yeah yeah it was just really
really great and yeah a supernova girl in chat saying the group photo never
happened yeah I just want to note an entire documentary happened so just just
yeah there's gonna be there's gonna be like just clear we really did cover it
yeah I mean if you really want to get technical like hundreds of thousands of
group photos happened as the documentary goes on we also we did a we did a group
photo with the at the ball too we did we did we did do that yeah yeah yeah yeah
we usually do one earlier in the in the event yeah but yeah we did one at the
ball this year yeah I have great news I just got a text message I'm being
offered it's not even it's not even asking me to to respond to it and to
apply for it I'm being offered a new job right now it's only gonna take 60 to 90
minutes a week some weeks at most 60 minutes a day $250 no they're willing to
pay me up to $3,000 a week get out of here yeah you have to murder
apparently let's see Paul Mattingly oh well I even know that guy I'll split it
with you yeah remote work I could work from anywhere let's see oh I get
instant I get several weeks of paid time off instantly with this with this new
position that's nice and no experience necessary so they're gonna give me
three thousand dollars a week and they don't even care that I don't know what
the gig is I it feels too good to be true but it must be yeah this is I mean
it is a hard time to be looking for work right now and yeah this shit happens to
us and we're not even looking for work right you know what I mean like fucking
every day it's fucking nuts I feel so bad yes oh yeah in the chat a wall scoop
says even if they crash scoop fest what would you have done if they were
enjoying themselves and not being disruptive excellent point and the
answer to that is probably nothing well that's why I just commented I said
exactly we just try to obelisk him yeah we give him some poker chips and say
please download our shit all day long man get out chips and hey check us out
yeah yeah it was nuts it was nuts no finger but whole oh those are things we
had a confessional booth set up oh I know our separate repeat I am excited to
hear those I haven't heard anything I don't know and one of our old friends
was a Piper was behind there helping out and I said are you having shoes there
and also you haven't fun just oh I'm having a blast just it is so great to be
in the room where I'm not the weirdest person in the room oh and I said like
think of it too yeah beautiful beautifully said and I was like that's
exactly what I want people feel like yeah they come you know it's like that's
exactly it's all about letting your freak flag fly man yeah we don't give a shit
it's like you know yeah you know we're welcome yeah very welcoming community
yeah look at that we're up to 40 participants that's a new record for the
chat guys we're doing it that's growing what else was it scoop fest we had the
mouth finger butthole tournament we had all of the quizzes with Mikey oh which
yeah yes oh yeah he outdid himself again this year oh uh we should say on
the show to several people asked about it at scoop fest people saw some medical
attendants checking out Mikey at one point that was just a it was a very
minor thing no big deal everybody is perfectly fine it was the casino being a
little overly cautious just having their people check check Mikey out after a
little slip and fall that we checked on him he was okay everybody's good they
were they were everybody was healthy and happy oh then we had oh Celestia thank
you scuba cabra in the chat for reminding me Celestia was there doing
caricatures yes jock versus third ball whole every time I walked over to see
what she had done for for a new group of people over there it was more
disgusting and more wonderful than anything I will say my brother was like
ooh we should get a we should get a caricature and so I did play my scoop
card and got cut sees in line to do a dare you I know but it was you know my
brother I see my brother maybe twice a year if I'm lucky in person so it was
really nice to actually get a moment to to have this and we've got a really
special year we have to get Celestia to do one of the three of us yes yes we
should well I mean shit she'll do that it's hard to go sit for anytime you know
what maybe we can have her do that during the zoom because we're having her
on soon maybe we can do that because I'd love to I'd love to get one and put out
put it up in the new chart well we'll talk we'll talk to her about that when we
have her on next and see if she can just watch us during a zoom if that would be
enough for her to get us I'm sure it would would work yeah so she was
incredible like and also I had a personal highlight with the Pollywood
Squares that fucking talk tell us about Pollywood Square what happened there so
I was a little worried because of the board I was kind of like all this work
into this fucking thing and if this doesn't go well it's gonna be the worst
but then Ryerson who fest I was like the only note I have was not enough Paul
my whole thing and so like like we did a lot of stuff a lot of things but Paul
you know was not I basically was like Paul is funny we're trying to get him
involved we were trying to get you to host a little bit of the trivia battles
and so the adjustments we made was let's let's take on everybody in trivia so
that it's right it's it's Paul and us against everybody instead of having two
podcasts face each other right and then my brain was like oh Hollywood Squares
but everyone's Paul it's Paul's characters all of Paul's characters and
I in we reach out big there's a way to do with technology but well I go no no I
want a physical clunky awkward big square yes where we have to move squares
around Paul and I got of course turn to Ryar Apple door and to be like you you
know what I'm talking about you know what this means so Ryar Apple turn made
the biggest clunkiest Hollywood Squares board that could even fit through the
door right with hangable X's and O's that was like nine feet what was it was
like nine it was huge yeah and and that was the thing Ryar and and Mike were
bringing it out and Ryar said they couldn't hardly fit it through the door
right and it started well they couldn't fit it through the door that's why they
had to come through the a different area they started from backstage on stage it
started to crumple and bend and fuck up and the moment it started to just fall
apart Ryar was just like oh this is gonna be perfect and he was right he was
right the stupidity of it all just added just layers of dumb and it just oh it
was so good it was down here you were Paul Lind Johnny Australia yeah Truman
Capote which is a new one earlier in the day mum-rah mum-rah my favorite Paul
Stanley vampire Bill Cosby yeah child barrel child yeah oh man and it was we
were just asking trivia questions and making Paul's characters answer all of
them Paul just came buckled right into the format of knowing how to play
Hollywood Squares and I've watched a lot as a kid yeah yeah and it was
hysterical it was so fun it's really good I was like and I was like you were
like I would know I was like this is I as soon as it came to my head I was like
hit it's in and it was floating is like I could we could do this multiple times
like I was like if anything falls short I was like yeah we could just do another round with more
characters even one point James like well if it's good and I was like no no
this is good I don't know why there was doubting I don't know why there was
doubting this pimping Paul nine times is exactly what the show needs and at the
end Paul was almost guilty about how well I went he said so it felt a little
self-indulgent and I was like right your festival it's true yeah yeah we're at a
festival of you it's talking about yeah it's all good we're at a festival about
you yeah and we are celebrating a show that has your name in the title it was
it's it's possibly a little self-indulgent in some way the whole
thing is self-indulgent it's now on the list right with mouth finger butthole
that is now just a it's it's just on the list yeah yeah it's like that could be
done at churnouts - yeah yeah well now I've got an idea for it for for zoom -
I've got an idea for it for on camera oh hell yeah yeah mini version that Paul
can just stick his head through that sounds fucking fantastic it's gonna be
great that is good good good it was fucking hot shit and it made me laugh too
so that was great yeah yeah I'll tell you what else Paul is gonna stick his
head through and that's the following sponsor pizza for your hands that's
right no more chewing with that pesky mouth of yours now there's pizza for
pants hello I'm Reginald Felicity Guinevere and I have invented pizza
mittens that's right pizza mittens cooked fresh every day made to order
slathered in the finest of pasta sauces and mozzarella cheese the mittens are
then placed on your hand piping hot and it's like the old Edward 40 hands days
remember those days remember being an Edward 40 hands do you ever have friends
do that to you and when 40 hands they would take a cold 40 of alcohol and they
would duct tape the 40 to your hand and then you had to drink the 40 because
it was so cold to drink the 40 quickly to stop all the coal so it gets you
drunk really fast there's a similar thing but with pizza as mittens and so
the pizza comes on it's pretty hot so you got to eat the pizza very quickly to
get the heat off your hands but then the heat goes in your mouth and you burn
your mouth but it's still really good it's still really really good yes yes
yes and her hay scoops to check out so then what else what else was oh Gabrielle
Lester just destroyed she just crushed Gabrielle yeah so fun and that was
Carrie's mom who was up there with her I believe she's just known as mama scoop
now yeah so so for those of you who don't know I hope I'm not putting
anybody on blast here but Carrie brought her sister and her mother which is great
and I think her sister spent more time than she thought she would hanging out
with some of the events her mom certainly did her mom wasn't sure she was
gonna enjoy it at all clearly she did oh by the end of it her mom was in yeah and
I thought even by the end of it halfway through it mom was in I believe this was
on Friday they got the hard news that their brother had suffered a stroke mmm
oh jeez yes and it's so that yeah mom was upset sisters upset carries upset
they're all fucking you know it's rough because it's in fees in Florida right
what can you do luckily scoop fest acted as a distraction and by the end of the
event his health had improved he was doing much better of course still you
know not an ideal situation but things are going better and yeah yeah yeah so I
think not only did it like it helped as a distraction and everything but yeah
it was really cool seeing mama scoop find out what this community is all
about and kind of just get with it crazy the shenanigans that is involved in this
community yeah yeah but yeah Gabrielle was was great and then we brought back
the pineapple and people to play for everybody to play for all the people not
just the barbecue and of course that culminated with sweet Caroline we finally
got to combine the the two bits the one the one that we do yelling fucking whore
in between the bits and then again a great time to be looking out of the
front door of the convention hall and watching the people walking by oh I bet
I bet did they lose their fucking minds I bet those oh pure confusion it's
wonderful and then adding in I don't believe you you're making it up and so
we finally got both bits combined into sweet Caroline yeah and well we were
shouting it Phil just turned to Fionn and said what is happening right now who
knows they were confused but they loved it right I mean they just yeah well
here's the funniest thing okay so one of the things that happened behind the
scenes was you know they say we'll take requests and we we had them take a break
to do Hollywood squares and so in the break people come up to me giving
different songs you know one of the things that what's it called Princess of
the City or whatever that's not the famous average song is by the Pogues oh
it's a what's it called a New York City fairy tale or something like that yeah
fairytale of New York that's what it's called very very New York it's a
traditionally Chris it's a Christmas song but it's it's crazy it's about the
deterioration of this long-term relationship these two people that grow
to hate each other and yeah it's really it's a beautiful song but it isn't
traditionally traditionally a Christmas song they're just cracking up going like
I guess we'll just play it even though it's a Christmas song Merry Christmas
yeah and then another song someone came up to Fionn and again just like you know
time and culture and everything else he's the he plays the flute in the band
and someone came to Fionn was like oh would you play like the orange flute of
blah blah blah or whatever I don't know the name of the song no that was it and
film just dead face was like ah maybe I don't know if we know that one and in
this face is that it is a song about the English like conquering the Irish like
the orange flute is about like the orange like yeah yeah it's like you
were not playing that it's like when I first when I first start when I was
first sitting there at the barbecue watching I was like I wonder if they'll
do like the the Outlander theme and I was like that's Scotland you dumb I didn't
say anything but I was like the Outlander theme that would be that's
fucking Scotland you don't even yeah shut your fucking yeah people who are
from Scotland do not want to be told they're from Ireland and vice versa and
vice versa it's very key thing I don't know why anyone would do it yeah very
crazy Ozzy no I'm not gonna I'm not gonna touch that so there we go and they
never played long distance no they didn't play long distance but we didn't
ask we didn't ask him to learn long distance that's okay I'm sure they know
it I'm sure I'm sure they've just picked it up by just hearing it on the radio on
the international radio stations all the time so that being like I can't believe
somebody's asked that's great basically get any other situation we would just be
entirely offended but it was like let's just let it go I'm sure it was just an
earnest request and not a lot of behind it not realizing what it meant and yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's amazing that's amazing yeah it's horrific and orange
flute that's it the old orange flute oh yeah yeah this is just this is about
this is a story of the Irish version of Benedict Arnold basically betraying the
Irish to the English yes so now so now it's not a song that they play all the
time is it but it but it isn't a traditional Irish song and not it did it
recounts a terrible time for the Irish but it is the one that I'm finding here
is by the Dubliners and it was done in 19 it was released in 1965 so that would
be that would seem to say it well it is a traditional Irish song but just of a
very sensitive topic yeah probably so it'd be to be a different thing if we've
gotten out we've gotten out of the knowledge that I have I okay I have is
entirely based on reading these lyrics here and that's it I love that they did
a Wild Rover because when I used to sing at the bar at Star Trek the experience
when I was doing I'd do a Klingon opera occasionally we would get some Irishmen
in who and we'd swap songs it was great and they did Wild Rover and I learned
Wild Rover yeah and so I knew Wild Rover and then but I knew a call for Wild
Rover it's an offensive call I don't know they were ready for it I don't know
if they've ever heard it but it's you know that I've played the Wild Rover for
many a year and I don't know this but but then it goes and it's no name never
right up your ass no never her no more will I play the Wild Rover no never no
more so but that I learned that from other Irishman so it is a legit call
response move for that song but yeah that was great they played that one too
yeah yeah they were just it was great and I sent them to they got to go to
Mystere while they were here oh fantastic did they get to do a backstage tour - no
they had to get back and play the show well at least they got to see it that's
cool I said I sent to Piff Piff the next day so you'd see Piff show the next day
yeah next day Penn Sunday School live if you it's coming out this week just just
check it out Penn coming back from England fighting a nasty nasty cult yeah
tough it out for scoop fest of him telling a story about Piff Piff is there
so Piff comes out from backstage and surprises the audience and it's Piff the
magic dragon and he's got a steel chair I got to do my if impression just spot on
yeah oh yeah yeah like Gudeau said and it was a really good it was a really
really fine episode of Penn Sunday School especially health is considered
Penn's health but it was it was great yeah then Piff stayed by he broke down
his appearance on Foolish with Hondreau yeah it was funny that's the funniest
thing is that you know Penn one Piff I know if Penn was sticking around Penn
couldn't stick around because he was sick you want to know if Hondreau's gonna
call in the Hondreau wasn't available to call in sent a small video but I was
like I was there I'll help or whatever and I just should know better by now that
Piff the magic dragon is always ten steps ahead of everyone has already
planned everything yeah and so I tried you'll hear if we play that if we'll
play it on those feet or not I'm not sure I don't think it's maybe it's good
audio without video but I tried to help early and then there's a point where I
just realized I should just shut up he's got it he's got it yeah yeah and and he
just it just did a very funny presentation of all of breaking down his
this is disastrous appearance it was a disaster it was it was funny to watch
live I mean it really is it's up there with your cutting the tip of your finger
off at that performance that you did I mean it's the same kind of thing yeah
and if I had a perfect sense of humor about it it was great oh yes and Hondreau
will probably develop a sense of humor about it one day well I mean he was good
enough to leave a message that was nice yes yeah that we do a trivia battle with
great night our epic battle continues yes you're now to what to know in our
last battles against great night it's pretty impressive if you don't have the
other battles that we've had against great night we are to and oh against
great night I'm telling you ever since Ryre made that badass fucking belt
that's ours baby that championship now we've got something to fight for yep
yep and we and might I say I'm pretty sure I put us over the line with
Blueberry Hill that's right you sang us you sang us into victory last year it was
because the movie was one that I had actually seen before the terrible movie
was one that I had actually seen before this year Paul Golden pipes Mattingly
Blueberry Hill there it is and the ice cream social live you'll hear it that's
the episode that just went up yeah and so that's there and so we go to the
jock vs. nerd ball for baby probably the one of the best years ever man it was a
solid jock vs. nerd year the foolers were there unbelievable including math
the mind noodler it Michael Elsroth dressing up like Jessica
Jane Peterson from head to toe from the foolers tour was really something else
all weirdly accurate outfit we're the accurate great well for a minute I
thought she was here I thought that was her I was JJ got tall what the hell yeah
it was pretty great yeah turn to Michael's thing I got us in the photo to
JJ and him going I hope she's not offended by anything I've done here and
I said are you kidding me she is what Jessica Jane I found these shoes on the
strip Peterson offended by yeah I mean if you put on Vegas stray shoes get the
fuck out nothing nothing can faze you you're beyond the human capacity for
phasor at that point I can't fathom that process I'm still thinking about that
from last school fast clearly I am she's not she's not of this earth I don't know
why you're yelling at me about it Paul said Jessica Jane got something else
going on she's just a little wood nymph it's amazing yeah so funny see and then
I said to the whole foolers thread so Christine just up as Alex as Vinnie
Grasso with a bald cap on great helping people with cards left and right yeah
it's really funny yeah really got good at that Amy was just as me as hillbill
which is very good Amy did a card trick for me at one point as hillbill it was
Amy had me pick a card and then she flipped me off and said fuck you I'm
from Jersey
the Alex remote would just Alex with abs just an ab shirt and a stuffed dog and
just Alex wrote me saying thank you for the abs thanks for giving me abs and
just know everyone can I get over Michael Osruth is Jessica Jane Peterson
well and then and then to top it all off we had Penn and Teller for fuck's sake
yes to introduce the whole thing yes Rock and Carl being Penn and Teller
those are those are I want to ask about those suits they were legit suits they
were nice suits bespoke yeah those are I think they just went and had suits made
for themselves no joke like to me bespoke yeah Oh Kurt says Amazon specials
well there you go oh man really good Carl and Brock crushed that look that was
awesome and and of course the winner of the costume contest the tickle house
tickle house damn let's all go to the tickle house such a cut that's the
tickle house repair gardeners Chris angel was yes also excellent multiple
pig assist with someone dressed as a Ghost Busters people came with awesome
awesome constant on the road who that go really great who that goat that goat oh
yeah oh man I came in with a hood that goat was amazing it was like a really
right now I think yeah professionally applied thing now Colton nailed that look
and and that's the other thing too just the it's so fun at scoop fit I mean
first of all the costume contest always blows my mind because we see bits we see
bits from the entirety of the run old stuff new stuff it's just we bits that
remind us of the bits exactly the horse that can see nine times oh yeah the the
girl who wanted you to watch the balloon Jesus Christ Nick my balloon girl was
there damn that was so funny that was great bananas burlesque bananas yeah
Mario and ready yeti throwing confetti spaghetti and ready and yeti spaghetti
confetti it hit it was so good it's just all good man everything everything was
great it is so fun so fun and and and just seeing also just during the during
the week all the t-shirts and stickers and hats and different merch that we've
made it's been a we we've been doing this for a minute now right like we got
yeah stuff there's there's these really nice social baseball jerseys and I was
like whoa oh those were great yeah those were so great oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
uh verminous coupe had that right was it verminous coupe with the patch which
patch the patch on the on the sleeve of that one of those it was just a really
great patch the three of us yeah yeah yeah it's fucking great man those those
jerseys were all great yeah yeah oh there was informative Lemmy informative
and I had all the all the facts written on yeah that was great that informative
Lemmy was really good too yeah oh man yeah so good it was back from like some
of the facts were like from the scoop fest is so funny right yeah so many so
many anyways yeah so it was just a beautiful beautiful event crazy great
everyone come out yeah we can't do this without our community it's just
incredible and fingers crossed for where the documentary goes thank you all for
participating in that oh thank you to our safety cones we could not do it
without our safety no geez that's the whole thing man oh yeah my lobster club
barista guy was there oh yeah yeah yeah yeah so fun so fun we look as true
country scoop we learned that Krypton is the eighth most common gas in the
atmosphere and that was one of informative Lemmy's cards mm-hmm
amazing yeah and by learned that I mean Mikey told us that and we all took it as
truth and none of us have done any further research I believe Mikey 100% oh
me too clearly Mikey yeah I'm fine with this I'm just narrating but it was great
and then had a wonderful time over at McMullin's McMullin's actually worked
out this time this was a good good yeah I think yeah did you guys like a
revamp or whatever like their staff was on point did you see that does the staff
had a scoop hat on they somebody got got one of the waiters a scoop hat or they
got I don't know how they got it but they had a scoop hat on yeah while they
were serving on on Friday night country scoop in the chat gave him gave that to
the bartender yeah he was oh man and he wore that for for at least the rest of
scoop fest he was well done country days that was really really kind of you it
was incredible and and and like always the scoops treat everybody really great
tip-heavy bought me food bought me drinks it's great yep just so oh and if
anybody wondered if the Irish trio pint of plain went to McMullin's and tried
Irish nachos yes yes and they loved them oh my god yeah I said I said I was
afraid to even show you this whether you think it was like offensive to you or
whatever oh and they go well there's nothing like that in Ireland but boy
there should be this is really good they're really blown away particularly by
the nacho beef the beef that goes on the Irish nachos right and it sounded
like an Irish stew beef the corn beef the nacho beef yeah no it wasn't corn
beef just the regular ground beef oh okay they're spiced ground beef yeah oh
but the way they make it at the at the McMullin's they're like this tastes
like Irish like stew beef this doesn't taste like nacho beef and they were like
flipping out about it oh that's cool devoured two plates of Irish nachos
blown away yes though three who's super that was that was my favorite but I sent
them a picture with them in front of the plate I said my four favorite Irishman
it was the three of them in a plate of Irish my favorite Irishman and my three
friends from Ireland the country's not chiming in it's the same beef they use
in their Shepherd's pie there yes and this way it's like it's like it's
actually why I like I like that we do every year and a half for a variety of
reasons one is right now to give us breathing room to not think about the
next one oh to like that extra six months like our lives change enough that
different people come into our lives to bring to scoop fest yes you know we get
to include different people in it and so that's like really always kind of
exciting to do and and and also we lose track of how many we've done so it makes
them all really special because I'm like I don't know how many like how many
businesses I'm like I have no idea I don't know and how awesome I think it
was was it you Matt or Jacob one of you two what me came up with the thought of
selling twenty twenty seven scoop fest
nothing to see here I don't think that should be said on air but yeah I hear
your buddy and I appreciate it okay they're not for sale right now so no no
no no I'm not saying I'm gonna be an edit yeah yeah but yeah yeah it's all
good yeah that's fine all right well we'll say it out loud now people at
scoop fest were able to buy super early bird tickets or the next event yeah yeah
yeah but that just now I was one to say with that was that it just to me speaks
so highly of people trusting us and then being enthused about this event yeah
that's not even announced yet right well the people that basically okay the
people that come a year after year after year and I really wanted to reward them
yes we're doing that yeah and so we wanted we wanted to give people a
special discount on early bird even though we haven't figured out where it's
gonna be there's no the time frame of where it's gonna be we know it's gonna
be a year from late April early May yeah inside the actual specific dates yeah
we've got a window yeah and and so basically if you were willing to roll
with the punches we want to reward people who come year after year and so
we give you a special a special ticket so they're there each everyone else and
we'll get everybody else we get early bird tickets out and at some point in
the in the future as well once yeah once we figure more of our ducks out exactly
yes yeah yeah we usually announce it about a year out yeah I'm trying to put
anybody on blast but yeah do you understand it to the listener this could
not be the best news do you understand why I was trying to not do it no okay
not everyone had the opportunities to do it people who are listening to the show
weren't all at the show right all right no it's great but and we will we did we
did discount for the people there we'll do a different early bird discount for
everyone when we get the the tickets up to yes yeah we're gonna take care of
everybody as much as I can it could be a bit of a sticking point for some of our
international scoops as I'm seeing Bozzie right now but that's not our
doing per se yeah yeah yeah well I mean we did vote for him twice some people
three times good lord but yeah yeah it's gonna be great we're looking for the
next one do you have any kind of trivia we have we have talked everybody's ears
off at this point I think it's time we give them a break we've done a full show
here we've done we've done all this talk and everything do we want to do do you
want to do a quick scooper T you want to race through one sure yeah yeah let's
race through one here's a lot of Jack vs. nerd break something fresh off for the
listener we got scooper D from silver fist scoop categories
are one hit artists one hit albums one hit songs and one hit music videos Paul
you're up first I'll try one hit music videos for 400 artist the Buggles video
song what is it fish no wait is it fish heads was that the Buggles no that is
that the Buggles shit that's the entire question I know
I'll go with fish heads all right now the radio star it wasn't fish heads it
wasn't I knew I was wrong but I'm still got it wrong what an asshole that's me
I'll try about a one hit songs 400 artist Michael Sembello album bossa nova
hotel song I don't know Matt poop Street Blues it rolls downhill
oh I will pass let's see here Oh maniac from flash dance that is a good one Matt
one hit songs for 800 artists Stacy Q album better than heaven what's that song
pass Paul
I believe that's I don't want to fall in love all right let's try it oh fuck it
was that one oh I don't want to fall in love from Stacy Q no it's not Stacy you
had some other person Paul you're up geez I gotta try and redeem myself I'll
try one hit music videos for 2,000 all right points back on the board from
musical youth what is their song video musical youth Oh pasta duchy
redeemed redeemed that is correct Paul has taken the lead yeah what a turn around I'll try one hit
albums for 400 it's a daily double still just for 400 the waitresses song I know
what boys like and what is the album also have to tell you the name of the
album this is gonna be a terrible category oh and it's a daily double I
can't even fucking pass it um that album was called tips are for losers wasn't
tomorrow wonderful I was so glad I was just confused tips are for losers was
the follow-up album what a cute thought I was a waitress
Matt Europe no one's gonna know any of these a lot of miles song black velvet
what was that album called Matt or Paul I think it's black velvet but I'm gonna
pass I'll guess black velvet oh no just self-titled six one eponymous Paul Europe
I'll do music videos for 1200 let's see here a flock of seagulls what is the
song and it must be the full song title I ran I ran so far away I ran so far away
yeah sorry you did two Iran's Paul one Iran is enough they could never have
enough Iran's oh no no there goes our podcast yeah I'll try one hit artists
for 400 album somebody's watching me song somebody's watching me
artist who the fuck did that song he he worked with Michael Jackson on that track
yeah that sounds familiar yep that's Michael pass doing the thing
yes Paul it's like Mac Dylan or some shit make me clump mcclumpy I can't
remember it exactly so I have to pass all right rock rock well rock well you're
or or mcclumpy as I call him yeah all mcclumpy Matt let's get let's keep I
says I know none of these I'll go with albums just to get it out of the way
great the vapers song sorry the vapers is the artist turning Japanese is the
song what is the album pass Paul oh it's a filthy title but I can't remember it
off past I yeah it was like cunt wallet or something like that something like
that yeah new clear days oh my god Paul music videos out of my head the video is
Mickey the saw the video song is Mickey the artist is Tony Basil Tony Basil I
finally knew one and I didn't get it I did you know she choreographed once upon
a time in Hollywood for QT she did yeah that amazing that she's still fucking
kicking ass all these years later still working yeah that's me it's me I'll try
doesn't matter one hit albums 2000 Jermaine Stewart to the song we don't
have to take our clothes off and that's off of the album
now Matt who knows this somebody it is tall I'll pass I don't know frantic
romantic oh wow someone knows it Matt you're up you got one hit artists or one
hit songs when they hit artists 800 please the an emotion song is the I'm
sorry the an emotion is the album the song is obsession and the artist is who
make not who that's a different man pass Paul my obsession who do you want me to
be to make you sleep with me I have to pass me too oh it's an emotion there you
go that's the name of you as well Paul what would you like what he has
originally Hulk Hogan's walkout music right it was it's for 1200 please who
do you want me to be brother to make you sleep with me brother no there's a
Saturday night whatever the same age as I was like that there's a part where
W just used music recklessly and yeah right ask for rights and that was the
original Saturday night I bet you're right the Saturday night's main event
that was there I got it oh yeah that was the artist is Paul Hardcastle the album
is Paul Hardcastle what's the name of that song I have no idea at the pass
camera what he did Paul's Hardcastle boy they just add an apostrophe yes oh that
passes to me I don't fucking know pass passes to me oh my god that's that sad
Vietnam song well there's a couple there's a couple fun ones because I'm
surfing in Vietnam everybody surfing surfing be surfing for Vietnam I'll tell
you Charlie don't surf but that's a lie Charlie will serve come give it a try
artist swing out sister album it's better to travel and the song was Reno
when Bruce Springsteen did it later it was actually a cover of the original
swing out sister song ain't the best we've ever had that's right
it's breakout I was confused I was good for us but this one is breakout I was
confusing that Reno I don't remember breakout when you ask for a quick
scooperty I guess you got your wish and that we don't know any of these that's
it that's it so there you go it moved them it moved the line yeah let's see
Matt oh do a quick score check before these last two questions Paul is
currently in the lead with 2,800 Matt is in second place with zero and because of
two daily doubles I'm in third place you know that to two scoops at least two
scoops reported the same tactic for mouth finger butthole where they threw
mouth every time and that's what got them further away and the thing they
threw mouth every time our mouth does the trick yeah and I bring that up
because I passed the whole time I'm coasting in a second place no problem
yes oh my god - I just got both daily doubles I got stuff we need a new shirt
design for mouth finger but whole mouth finger but whole on the front and on the
back I'm throwing mouth that and it's like to know it's like I'm serving cunt
but it's I'm throwing I'm throwing mouth I like it yeah Oh Brogan's doing it yeah
Brogan Brogan take the wheel thank you bro that you want one hit artist for
1,200 or 2,000 you're gonna know one of these I'll go I'll go I'm a 2,000 just
because it's more fun to pass that one let's see it album living in a box song
living in a box by the artist box or Willie living in a box I'm a living in a
cardboard box I'm a living in a box I'm a living in a cardboard box it's some
dude I can't remember his name though show me some dude oh no I'm sorry it's
living in a box his name was living in a box get the fuck out of here artist name
is also living in a box that's really funny that is Paul closing out the
category and the game one hit artists for 1,200 their commissar is the art is
the album the song is there commissar the artists what's his name Paul what
were their name
Stalingrad or some shit I think it starts let's see Stalingrad oh no I'm
sorry Paul it's after the fire sure of course after the fire of course after
the fire I had to make a guess just for sportsmanship that's right Paul still
wins with 1600 Matt congratulations you got second place with zero and to me go
fuck yourself I got negative 3200 and that's from silver fist scoop thank you
silver fist scoop if you want to send us a scooper to yours or a price of sprite
jock vs nerd or an obelisk jock vs nerd head over to hey scoops comm you can
also send us some scoop mail from over there hey scoops comm do all the things
right over there right now I was just about to say you can go there and get
your tickets for scoop fest that's not true anymore oh that's right that's not
true that's not true right I'm gonna think Ben Jeff creating this podcast
thanks Ben I want to thank the following people who all these people they all saw
living in a box and concert you know before they sold out Peter Sands own
petty officer scoop Phil Rendley Phil Tomlinson Phil Guyton pick it up pick it
up proper scoop proto scoop pyro quiet quiet scoop radioactive scoop raggedy
girl Ralph Barrett Randy Randy Glenn refrigerator Perry scoop remember the
Allah mode Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster
Richard Dunn Richard Dunn Richard fast not rich graffiti Richard Hill Robert
Paul's robots ahoy and Rodimus scoop the following people even though it goes
against all warnings did in fact go in the tickle house scooped mids scoop a
Luga scooper Metroid scooper Nova girl scoopie Lauren scooper ascending scoop
JD scoop Kata scoop knack patty whack scoop block keysa scoop neon black scoop
Nick scoop a metrics scoop so hazard scoop Trek the experience scoopie and
the beast scooby-dooby-doo scoopie Ramones scoopie Bartfast scoopie scoopie
Jess Jess Scott a Scott Andrews Scott Ashlock Scott Ashlock again Scott
Headington Scott moldering Scott Shofield Sean
Kellner Seanathan P see Baskin Robbins and SF the following people will all
tell you to take that orange flute and shove it right up your ass about the
Roger Edge Ron Heck Rose Ryan Hayward Ryre Appledorn second mingle salt
scoop Sam Reed Sonya Petrovich Sarah Boyle sex guy Jimmy D scoop scabby the
rat scoop scoop Brady scoop scoop Bucky scoop Chang the Beijing bugle scoop
Dave ill scoop Emily scoop it real good scoop DeJure scoop Jesus scoop Lindsay
scoop Lord Tristan scoop Mipha scoop nurse scoop of salt water scoop
Skywalker scoop T scoopaholic scoop a trooper and scoop Paul's drag race who
once again crushed it at the jock always and gorgeous Jake got there early this
time yeah it was great they were able to really take it in this time was
wonderful yeah the following people have decided to prove that they have even
more bravery and skill and have taken their CEO seer wheel onto a three-foot
stage Sean Shula scoop skill in scoop silver fist scoop sir scoopy mix
scooper tin three as choir six-foot scoop Scully Wally scoop Scully wall
scoop slightly slutty scoop slurpee Kai a motherfucker
Smitty scoop solar-powered scoop soulless scoop sound man scoop spring
loaded scoop stab and dash scoop Stacey Coleman streets Mcgreet's Stephanie
Young Stephen Clively Stephen Landon Stephen Biggs Stuart Wilson strange
uncle's podcast strap a chicken on scoop and sugar rush socio and the
following scoops are all the answers to all of Chris Angel's questions that's
super geek one three five seven nine Swedish scoop take it easy podcast scoop
Tamara Hamilton technical scoop port temporary reality Pierce turn the page
that thing in the attic the bad humor man the sensei scoop the civic crew scoop
the damsels of dorkington the devil's lettuce scoop the didgeridoo sh the
famous ball the going over our friends podcast the ice cream headache the ice
cream headache the lapis ligamorf the lost ice cream truck driver oh you're
lost I'm sorry get found the nano scoop the SC double OP the salty squid the
scoop lock in the spirit of the Latin Club the upside down under scoop I just
lost my place that's a shame the man the myth the scoop Thomas Beach Thunder
cougar Falcon scoop Timothy Sutton tk421 scoop please Tom Krieger Tom Mankerdy
Tom Scott Tony Cowley Tony scuprano Travis Jiguri Travis Murray Tristan
Guevara Troy Anthony Tanzer tuba scoop Tyler Bartlett Tyler scoop McDuck Udo
Gearhards uncle Don's wood shop Warren bro water ice scoop Wendy Cooper Wendy
Bumgardner Wes Coughlin what was like when scoop who dat scoop will beardy Dan
will Kellner William McDonald and wind walker scoop 23 we love you all sexually
and thank you so much all right thank you all so much if you want to be
thanked on air if you want invitations for our zoom meetings if you want a
plethora of other rewards get involved support us today with whatever way that
fits your budget at preaching fun calm
it's better than hanging with your mom
and if you're definitely going to come to scoop fest next year because this
story made you jealous head on over to farts in a bag dot bill
that's farts in a bag dot business that along with preaching fun calm it does
take you over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month
you can help keep this show on the air we are able to do this show entirely
because of our patreon backers so if you think this show is worth more than zero
dollars please head over to preaching fun calm farts in a bag dot biz and
there's new shit coming to those real soon yes so I go check them out all
right thanks folks everybody say see if out there we love you and we'll see you
soon
thank you again for another amazing success with scoop fest thank you jacob
and matt for all your hard work organizing for that event
love you see you bye