Oh, hello there. I am so glad you're here because it's time to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Why, these are the folks who deliver that ice cream straight to your ear holes.
Right now I'd like to thank Sarah Boyle, Richard Dunn, Pyro, Paul's brother, Mike, Malia, Leon Kasab, and Lori Ellsworth.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver.
And who knows, the life you save may be your own.
Here's the show.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
[Music]
Just got a video message from my friend Alex Ramone.
Oh yes?
Because he's out in New Jersey at something called ProfitCon.
Nothing scratches me wrong about that in any way.
Heading out the old ProfitCon in New Jersey.
P-R-O-P-H-E-T?
No, no, no. I wouldn't have outed him if he was at ProfitCon.
Alex Ramone is the returned prophet for a group in New Jersey.
If anyone could pull off a cult, it's Alex Ramone.
That is true, that is true.
Let's not get it twisted, MJ can pull off the cult.
He knows where his bread is buttered.
MJ would be on all the merchandise.
Profit like money, profit like money.
Profit like money y'all, that's the name of this episode.
Profit like money.
They should have just called the con Step 3.
Right.
We could start doing a Step 3 con.
Super expensive tickets, nothing really happens, it'll be great.
He said he was a magician.
And the woman goes, "Do you know someone named Matt Donnelly?"
And he goes, "Yes."
And she goes, "Well, I know him, but I really know his wife Sarah."
I was really good friends with Sarah and her friend Jen.
And so he pulled out his phone, they made a video, shot a video to me.
And it is the woman who booked Sarah and I on a Valentine's Day morning show when we were first dating.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
She was a TV producer.
I remember this.
Yeah, she was a TV producer.
Because SJ and I were supposed to, I don't know, this was a different thing, right?
I think I'm getting confused with something else.
This was way earlier, this was back in New York.
Because there was another thing that happened like this in Vegas.
Didn't you and Sarah shoot like a Valentine's thing in Vegas one time?
Yes.
And Jimmy and Robin were in it.
That's what I started thinking of immediately, Jacob.
I was on your page, but then this is even earlier.
There have been conspiring forces all around you for decades to make sure you and Sarah are a thing, huh?
I think it's possible that's the only reason Matt and Sarah are together.
Because the universe forced Sarah into it.
Yeah, I mean the second one of her friends goes like, "Sarah, seriously?"
And then she might just like come out of it like a hypnotist.
Like, oh shit.
Oh God, what have I been doing for all these years?
I have children.
He's hideous.
No, no, so when we first started dating, we were hanging out, having drinks with our friend Jen.
We're still very good friends with Jen.
Jen and Andy, her husband hired me to do handiwork when I had that job destroying offices and painting walls.
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I thought you were referring to close up.
And Jen was in Miami with Sarah out here in Vegas.
She later did Miami on Broadway, did Kinky Boots on Broadway, still lives in New York, good friend of ours.
Definitely tried to cock block us on our first date, which I always think is very funny.
Not like she wanted me, but she just wanted the date to get awkward.
She came and mess with us.
She was at the bar and she got hammered.
It kept being like, "So you really like Sarah?
Are you going to mess with her?
What are you going to do?"
And really out loud in front of Sarah and I trying to destroy the date, all the chemistry.
Great.
And I doubled down and go like, "No, I really like her.
Yeah, no, it's great."
And I just turned to Sarah and was like, "I really like you.
I really want to keep dating."
And so I just was like eating all of her things to destroy it and be like, "No, I'm going to stay confident."
And be like, "I like this gal."
Yeah.
So then we ended up becoming all drinking buddies as I continued to date.
And then we had beers with this woman, Liz, who is a producer.
And she then goes, "Oh, I need couples for a thing on Thursday for Valentine's Day.
We need couples competing for a travel sponsor.
We want to do a getaway or whatever."
And so I was like, "Well, we're not close to married.
We've been dating about six or seven months or whatever."
Right.
Because we'd only been dating for six or seven months, we crushed it.
Oh, because you just knew everything about each other.
We knew everything about each other.
We knew everyone's favorite colors.
And hadn't had time to forget it.
Favorite movies, favorite whatever.
Yeah.
All the things that you forget over time.
It went to my head.
I could not tell you Sarah's favorite color or favorite movie.
And she could not do the same for me.
Oh, Sarah's favorite color is blue.
Yeah.
And her favorite movie is being John Malkovich.
All right.
Jacob, you and Sarah are going away to Maui.
Maui!
Ann's favorite color is red.
I don't know that she likes movies enough to have a favorite.
But I don't know.
Maybe "Step Brothers" like me.
We both love "Step Brothers."
So we one tied with another couple.
And so we had a tiebreaker.
And I lost the tiebreaker because it's for a travel website.
And they asked how many destinations does the travel website go to?
And I was like, I don't know, 1,000?
And the sponsor was like, what?
And the answer was like 100.
I was off by an order of magnitude.
Yeah.
I was automatically the sponsor.
I did.
So instead we got like--
I don't know.
All of them?
Spin the globe and just hit--
Just three places in Arkansas.
It's only three places in Arkansas that our company goes.
Oh my god.
Throw a dart at a map.
I don't know who this guy is.
So we ended up with-- it was something like a $300 voucher or $500 voucher
or something like that.
Oh, that's pretty nice.
In second place, yeah.
First place was like thousands of dollars in a real vacation.
But you probably had to pay taxes on that.
Maybe, yeah, maybe.
All I know is that--
I think it was like $300.
Because Sarah and I were so broke that we couldn't use the $300 as a base point.
We had to use $300 as our budget.
Yeah.
Right.
You now have a budget of $300.
You've gone from having a budget of zero to having a budget of $300.
Exactly.
So we did a getaway to a hotel just outside of Philadelphia from New York.
And we spent a weekend in Philly.
Perfect.
That's pretty good.
The Paris of Pennsylvania.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good Lord.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
We did have a good time.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah, yeah.
I miss the days of just like, well, we're going to do something.
Yeah.
We don't have any money.
There's a hotel down the road.
Let's go stay there.
I know.
It really is.
I do miss those days.
That was the plan in Vegas.
When you're living in Vegas, what else are you going to do?
Just go get a hotel deal.
That's right.
Yeah.
Staycation, baby.
Well, we were out last weekend.
It was one of my son's birthdays.
Okay.
And he and his friend, when they were young, they used to always do joint birthdays because
our friend Danny and Jason, they're kiddo.
They're kiddo.
There's no popular person on earth than their child.
Like, every time they start saying a new expression, it's like, oh, you've been hanging out with
Danny's kid again, you know, kind of thing.
And suddenly they want a new game.
And the best was, okay.
This is her, we're being coy about the names because it's people's children, but we know
these kids.
This is Danny's oldest son that you're talking about, right?
No, their youngest.
It's the same age.
Oh, the youngest.
The youngest.
Their oldest, they think he's cool as hell, but he doesn't spend a lot of time.
But he's a little older.
He's a little older.
Yeah, yeah.
But their youngest son is the same as my oldest and they're only nine days apart.
And so they used to do joint birthday parties, then different schools, different whatever.
We finally decided like, let's do it.
Let's get together and do a birthday party.
But I'm going to take a side note here to be like, I've now officially encountered my
first, like I've been out of touch with slang that we brought up on this show, but my kids
have now just started saying this expression that I am like, what?
And they won't stop saying it.
Are they saying for shizzle?
They're saying for shizzle?
Can I, can I take a guess?
Yes.
Is it six, seven?
Oh, they do that before every photo and I ask them what it means and they don't know
what it means, but they do say six, seven.
I love kids saying things that they don't know what it means.
It's my favorite thing.
Yeah.
Do you, do you know what six, seven is from Paul?
I have dug up a couple of things.
Yeah.
So it's, it's Levar Balls height.
Okay.
Or LaMelo Ball.
LaMelo Balls.
LaMelo Balls height.
Charlotte.
And then it, it's sort of like, oh, I would like to be that, you know, like, like to be
six, seven or whatever.
Yeah.
Like that would be cool.
But it's also can mean mid in certain situations.
Okay.
Like it's only six and seven out of 10.
Yeah.
Like that it's, it's been co-opted to that sometimes, but it, but it's, but also Jacob
more to the, mostly it's people don't know what the fuck it is.
They just say it.
Yes.
Cause everybody says it.
If it comes up like in a thing, six, seven, six, seven.
Yeah.
They just yell six, seven.
Like you guys take a photo.
They go, okay.
And I'm gonna go six, seven.
And they laugh.
Yep.
And that we don't know why.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's a reference to basketball players height and some other weird meanings that have been
attributed to it.
There you go.
So they say bet.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Bet.
That's back now.
That's back.
Oh yeah.
Bet's bet's back.
Wow.
You know what else I heard that was back the other day?
I was watching a video of kids getting their hair cut.
What's that?
You know what this kid said?
Getting haircuts has been around for a while, Paul.
Okay.
This is a viral barber shop where the kids on their summer vacation can spin a wheel and
get crazy haircuts.
Okay.
Oh, I like that.
And they dare their friends to spin the wheel and go for the crazy haircut, like half shaved,
half on, or old man, where they cut off all the back hair and just leave the horseshoe
rim and all that kind of stuff.
Good.
So these kids, these young kids are getting these wild haircuts, this thing.
But this one kid spun it and he got the half on, half off, right?
Yeah.
Good.
Right down the thing.
But then the fryer tuck, that's one of them they're getting.
Yeah.
He's getting it done.
He's like, he's liking the look.
And he says, oh, that's tough.
Tough is back.
Whoa.
Fucking greaser.
I haven't heard tough in forever.
Sorry.
I have to go fight with the socias.
Dude, like for real, tough.
That was such a thing when we were kids.
For me, anyway, everything was tough.
Yes, it's from the outsiders.
No, but no, it's even before that.
It's like, oh, that's tough.
It was like, cool.
Yeah.
I mean, it was written about in the outsiders though, in the famous book, The Outsiders.
Oh, I guess.
Yeah.
And it was kind of immortalized in that.
But yeah, I mean, it was around, the author wrote about a thing that was just around at
the time.
Yeah.
So my kids are saying, oh, bet.
Like, yeah, good.
Let's do it.
It's on.
Yeah.
So they're saying dubs or W, like win, like that's a win.
Uh huh.
Getting some dubs.
Yeah.
And also just going like dubs.
Let's do it.
Be dubs three.
Then they start saying, oh, bet.
Well, a couple of things about that was one was like, we had the quintessential what happens
with parents.
Like, I couldn't believe like this conversation was happening because it's like, it's as written
as every parent should.
Yes.
So I said, when did you guys start saying bet?
And my oldest was like, I've been saying it forever.
No.
Forever.
No, you haven't.
That is simply not true.
We're very aware of your speech.
We have paid, over the years that you have been alive, we have paid a lot of attention
to you.
Exactly.
I was like, what?
No, you have not.
You have not.
That was 80s.
You weren't saying it yesterday.
That was 80s hip hop slang.
Oh yeah.
Bet's been back for a couple of years.
Bet's been back in a hard way for a couple of years.
Crazy.
And so anyways, we decided to do a joint birthday party.
We went out to Sandy Valley.
Sandy Valley Ranch.
Oh, not the strip club.
No, no, no.
I mean, it was just across the street.
Yeah.
But it was actually driving up.
I was like, I did see like ranch, ranch, ranch.
And I was like, wait, where am I?
And I was like, oh, I'm in California.
So there's no bunny ranches.
No whatever here.
But you drive out the Gene Goodsprings exit off of the 15 on your way out of town.
And then you just drive forever out in the middle of the desert.
And then suddenly you pop a bunch of ranches.
And I think we would categorize it as glamping.
Yeah.
All right.
So there's a giant teepee where the kids all piled in and stayed there or whatever.
Good.
Sarah, Danny, and I have the covered wagon.
And we gave our friends, the younger couple with the two more kids a mini house, full mini
house for them.
Great.
Are these outdoor little like, you know, kitchenette areas where it's, you know, it's a gas stove,
propane pens for showers.
So these are pretty permanent structures.
They're not like tents.
No, no.
They're permanent structures.
That's it.
That's what I mean.
They have locking front doors.
No.
Oh, yes, actually.
Yes.
Not the teepee.
I can't lock down the teepee.
Oh, really?
Oh, not with that attitude.
No.
You're out, Paul.
If you can't lock the teepee, you're not going.
I can't lock my teepee.
I'm gone.
Because I used to have nightmares about, I used to have nightmares about that all the
time.
How about people breaking into your teepee?
No.
Why?
Well, one, people would break into my teepee and then break into my wigwam.
And I was like, and I was like, fuck, doc, what am I supposed to do?
And the doctor said, you're too tense.
You know who else was just made a little sad by that joke?
The following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Bobby Butt Sticks Boulangerie and Lingerie Shop.
That's right.
From Dave Sorensen in 2024.
That's Bobby Butt Sticks Boulangerie and Lingerie Shop.
Boulangerie.
What's Boulangerie?
I think it's a type of restaurant, but let me look.
Yeah.
Let me look it up for you.
Let me look it up for you, Bobby Butt Sticks.
Thanks.
I'd like to advertise my establishment, but I need to know what I am.
It's a Belgian bakery.
There we go.
It's a bakery.
Okay, great.
Yeah.
So it's a Boulangerie and Lingerie.
Hello, I'm Bobby Butt Sticks.
Where did this voice come from?
It came from me, Bobby Butt Sticks.
I started a French bakery years ago and I had nowhere to put my buns.
So what I decided was I would also sell lingerie and I dress my baguettes in badonkadonk thongs.
That's right.
You can buy the finest loaves and titty holsters at my place of business.
Bobby Butt Sticks, Boulangerie, come get it.
Boulangerie shop.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
You heard me.
You heard it.
You know what I said.
So also I have sweet buns.
I have hot cross buns.
And if you're lucky and you buy something very tantalizing, you'll get sticky buns.
That's the Boulangerie, Bobby Butt Sticks, Boulangerie guarantee.
Yeah, oh wow.
I'm getting notifications from the ugly old woman in the kitchen that something is cooking
and done.
Hello, ugly old woman in the kitchen.
What do we got?
Oh my God.
The ugly old woman found the lingerie and she put it on and she's transformed into a beautiful
lady.
Oh, she's gorgeous.
We're going to go and get married.
I'm sorry, I'm closing the restaurant and lingerie shop to spend the rest of my life
with the ugly old woman who was my cook who only needed some TLC and some nice lingerie.
Oh boy, my life has changed forever today.
Thank you me for selling the things that made the ugly old woman in my shop pretty and I
can marry her.
Happy Thanksgiving everybody.
Don't enter Hayscoops at checkout.
No, because we're done.
The store's closed.
The store's closed for marriage.
We're turning it into a house.
This was an odd commercial to pay for.
We charge a lot of money for these commercials.
It's weird that they're paying for this commercial just to tell us that the store is closed down.
I'd like you all to meet Mrs. Bobby Butt Sticks aka the ugly woman.
There she is.
Hey, hey.
How's everybody doing?
Oh, she's so beautiful now.
It's a real pleasure to be here.
Now don't you give her sass because she's wearing lingerie around the town.
That's how she does it.
It's the only way I look good.
That's right.
If she takes off her sexy lingerie.
Until this I was an ugly old woman.
She takes off her sexy lingerie.
It's like a magic spell.
Did you guys watch any of the newest fight of the century?
What?
Is Canelo, Canelo Crawford?
Canelo and Bud Crawford.
Who?
I don't get to watch any of it but it was the big fight that was on Netflix, big boxing
fight.
Yeah, it was the big boxing fight.
So you had Canelo, the reigning defending champion and you had Crawford who came up
in weight to match Canelo to do the fight at all.
It was weird.
They were talking about it because it's like the end of both of their careers but it's
the biggest fight that Crawford has had to date.
He's been a really renowned fighter and a crazy respected boxer but never had any star
power.
This was his third weight class.
This is a fight that they've been trying to make this fight happen for a few years.
It was the first boxing fight in years though that has actually lived up to the hype that
came into it.
It was actually a really good, fun to watch event.
Yes.
Well, I didn't watch the whole event.
The whole event was like 6 hours long on Netflix with all the pre-fights and our friend Mitzi
was texting us during the first fight and saying there were more people in the ring
than there were in the stadium because it was in Allegiant.
It was in the huge stadium.
They set a new attendance record in Allegiant Stadium where the Raiders play, 70-some-odd-thousand
people.
Oh my God though.
I really liked this fight.
I watched the whole main event fight.
You had all of this Saudi stuff and the Saudi Crown Prince got introduced before the fight.
They did a special thank you to the Saudi Crown Prince who was in attendance at the
fight because I think he had given a lot of money to make it all happen.
I think he was part of it and the crowd of 70-some-odd-thousand people loudly booed the
Saudi Crown Prince live on Netflix and it was pretty hilarious.
This is a very strange thing that's happening.
Did you guys see the announcement that WrestleMania 43 is going to Saudi Arabia?
Yep.
Dude, Tom Brady just signed a flag football thing to play flag football in Saudi Arabia.
Good grief.
I need a Saudi Prince to get into podcasting, improv and magic like yesterday.
Yeah.
Oh, it would be great.
I don't know.
It seems really scary, all of it.
I mean, it seems like there is enough money involved that no one who is tempted by that
money remotely gives a shit about the optics of it.
Well, I mean, they got CM Punk, he flipped.
Well there you go.
There's the proof.
I told you.
What more proof do you need?
No, but I told you about that a couple of years ago when he was out on the outs with
WWE and he had an argument with one of the other guys who was going to go perform in
the Saudi Arabian and he said, "Go suck a blood soaked dick in Saudi Arabia," and he
had to apologize for it this year when he went.
Because he's taking money.
He went to hell with money.
Yeah.
It's weird.
There is, there just simply isn't an amount of money where we don't care about the murder
of a journalist.
That's it.
It is, "I murdered a journalist, but I would like to give you money.
I'll give you 50 million dollars and you just won't mention that I murdered a journalist
anymore."
Well, I mean, I still go like, I can't believe that Dana White being on film smacking a woman
did nothing to him, nothing.
He didn't apologize, he didn't have to apologize, and it didn't stop him from being invited
to speak at the Republican National Convention, to speak at like these higher, he gets these
high paid speaking engagements, like it stopped, it thwarted him in no way from accomplishing
everything he wanted to do.
It's because his name is Dana and when your name is Dana, people feel like they can't
pick on you about other things like beating women because you've already had too difficult
of a life being named Dana, and so they just don't want to make it any more difficult for
poor Dana.
It's so strange to me, but yeah, that's it, is that like we cared about Jamal Khashoggi
for like six months.
Yeah.
And then we're like, "Ugh."
Like the same thing ended Ray Rice's career.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All pro football player did exactly the same thing that Dana White did, and it ended his
career.
Yeah.
As it should, by the way.
If you're saying this as something that should be an outlier, that's how that should work.
Yeah.
No way.
You act like you still didn't draft Ray Rice on your fantasy football team in case he came
back.
Come on.
Drafted him this year, motherfucker.
This year.
Don't call it a comeback, he's been here for years.
But yeah, no, the fight was supposedly a great fight, I haven't watched it, but it apparently
was very good.
Yeah.
It's really good, it's really fun.
And watching the Crown Prince of Saudi, watching him get booed, and he got booed while he was
standing in the middle of the ring, they had invited him into the ring, so the camera is
just on him, and he's got this deadpan expression trying to ignore 70,000 people booing him
really loudly.
He literally whispered to someone, it's like, "How much to pay the people to applause?
I'll pay it.
$1,000 a person?
Yeah, yeah.
Let's write the checks right now.
Let's do it.
Yeah, I think for the ticket price that was at that event, I think it's more than a grand
a person.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Based on how much those people paid to be there, it's more than a grand a person.
There were so many people in town.
Now, how many people were booing because of Saudi Arabia's policy towards women and other
disparaged minorities?
And people that they fuck with.
Yeah.
For some people, just out of racism, just saw a brown guy in a turban and were like,
"Boo!"
So, what do you think?
What do you think?
It's not 100% to 0%.
I was saying, "Boo-erns."
I was like, "Oh, oh, was anyone else saying boo-erns?"
I was saying boo-erns.
Nick Newman in chat says they were saying, "Bruce," because he was Prince Bruce.
Prince Bruce.
Prince Bruce from Saudi Arabia.
I want to hear that version of my hometown.
You know, maybe the solution is, the next time they introduce him, they start playing
old Ray Stevens and he had the A-Rap.
That's his intro music.
That's it.
Not just the streak.
The Sheik of the Burning Sands.
Oh my God.
I had to – I didn't have to, but I did.
I took my wife to the airport the next morning because she had an out of town gig and neither
of us really thought about it.
She had like a 7 a.m. flight out of Vegas and so driving her to the airport, there was
suddenly a line for miles of cars trying to get to the airport the morning after that
fight.
Oh, jeez.
That early, too?
We pulled it.
Yeah.
And both of us were like, "Oh, oh shit.
This is a thing."
Did you do the old Mattingly Donnelly flip around?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, we did all the back things and we were in the truck so I could get off the road a
little bit, the dirt patch and everything.
Yeah, we did the whole thing.
But yeah, go ahead and pick her up the next day.
It was just as bad.
And I was trying to get to the pickup area.
I'm on the phone with her and now I'm stuck.
Even now, I can't do any kind of flippy or go anywhere else because I'm stuck on the
road.
But I'm texting with her and she's like, "The passenger pickup area is empty.
I don't know what you're talking about."
And it was all people going to like long-term parking in the valets and all of the wealthy.
People getting out of town.
Muck to mucks.
Yeah.
Just getting out of town.
Yeah, yeah.
That happened the same.
Yeah, went to pick me up and I was like, "Passenger picker, there's no one here."
She's like, "I cannot get in there."
And I was like, "Weird."
Yeah.
And it was just, I was coming in on a day where most of them were leaving town.
So all the locals were clogging up the affordable rates of overnight parking at the Vegas airport.
That's right.
The very affordable rates.
The bad thing is there's one road that leads to passenger pickup in the A terminal, the
main terminal.
There's one road that leads to passenger pickup, but that road also leads to long-term parking
and economy parking and valet.
And then there's one fork off that goes to the departing flights.
Yeah.
I mean, that thing was designed for when we-
When you got all those things going.
We were still calling Vegas Hotels carpet joints.
Do you know what I mean?
Like that's how long ago that place was designed and it's not-
Yeah.
I will never-
Modern traffic.
I will never understand.
I mean, I understand it, but man, they should have put that modern rail to the damn airport.
And now it's Elon Musk is taking on the cab union.
Of course.
Yeah.
He's trying to get the boring company to make it to the airport.
Well, are there like two people left in the cab union now?
That's it.
But they are mad.
Well, I mean-
Those two people are really pissed.
Maybe the power has shifted.
Maybe they are coming back because I know there's been a lot of backlash with Uber and Lyft
too.
Nah.
So I don't know.
We're not going back.
That's not how things work.
chaotic is right.
You got to play Vegas parking weather.
We're crushing it right now.
Oh, that's true.
Vegas parking and weather.
No one does it better than ICS.
Oh, speaking of weather-
You know who else knows everything about Vegas parking and weather?
Hold on.
We're going to come back to that.
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by- Nope.
That's me looking up the laundry.
Today's show is brought to you by Henry's Hobo Cafe from Dead Laszlo in 2024.
That's Henry's Hobo Cafe.
Yeah, alright, uh huh, all night.
My name is Henry.
I'm a hobo.
I got hungry sitting on the street.
I said, Henry, time to grab some gumbo and find a place to eat.
So I grabbed my gumbo and my bendle and I went on down the road to find a spot.
I happened upon this old abandoned hotel full of ghosts and a cooking pot.
So I asked the ghosts, you want to work for me?
My name's Henry.
They said, we'll work for free.
So now you can come into my house.
That's not really a house.
It's a place on the middle of the street.
It's full of ghosts and me.
You can get some old cooked meat.
Come on down to Henry's Haunted House Hobo Havel.
That's right.
It's full of ghosts and also garlic toast.
Come on down.
Get your fill.
Henry's got ghosts that will kill.
That's right.
I didn't mention, but they're deadly.
These poltergeists will eat your soul.
They also make you into food and you are what becomes in the bowl.
You're what we serve for lunch and dinner.
If you come to eat, you get eaten.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Anybody who comes to my place is killed and eaten.
That's what happens.
I'm a cannibal.
I'm Henry the Cannibal.
Henry the Cannibal.
Come on down and get eaten up by me and the ghosts.
One of the ghosts is little girl.
Do you think she'd be fine?
But she's not.
She's mean.
She's meaner than anybody.
Oh no.
I hope it's not the girl.
I'm just here for lunch.
Can I get seated for lunch please?
Come on in.
I'll be happy to seat you.
Oh no.
Now it's a little girl ghost and she's murdering me.
Oh, she's eating me.
She's starting to get my feet and eating her way up.
Oh no.
Oh man.
Enter Hayscoops to check out.
There you go.
What were you saying, Paul?
Oh, I was saying, speaking of weather.
Uh-huh.
Speaking of the biggest weather.
How's our outlook looking as we approach Scoop Hatchery?
Oh, I think we look great.
I think we're looking really great.
Yeah.
Here.
I'll pull up the actual Vegas parking and weather.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
We're in the middle of it.
So yeah.
Actual Vegas parking and weather.
Uh, yeah.
No, it looks like we are, oh, mid to low nineties, mid to upper eighties.
That's great weather out here.
That's gold out here.
Yeah.
No, we're going to be perfect.
Sunny.
Sunny the whole time.
It's going to be so nice.
Very, very nice.
It's not too late, by the way.
Scoopfest.com.
Go ahead and buy your tickets.
Come join us out here in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Enjoy that fantastic weather.
Come hang out with us for all three days.
Uh, there are barbecue tickets available.
There are VIP tickets available.
It is going to be a blast.
I was talking to, uh, a performer last night that is going to be performing at part of
Scoop Fest and they were super excited about it.
It is going to be so cool.
Scoopfest.com.
Uh, head over there.
Get your tickets to Scoop Fest.
Come see us.
It's only going to take a week and a half.
I don't know.
It's soon.
It's soon enough that, uh, I am no longer getting anxious when someone mentions Scoop
Fest to me because I am already in that anxious cloud.
There you go.
We're in it.
We're dialed in.
Yeah.
I just live in it now.
Yes.
Same.
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
It's going to be fun.
We have some surprises on top of the surprises.
It's going to be great.
It is.
It's going to be so fun.
Jacob, hold my calls.
I'm doing a podcast.
Sorry.
I'm busy right now.
He's doing a podcast.
Professionals, everybody.
Pro aficionados.
We were laughing the other morning, the whole family were having breakfast and, uh, my wife
told a story about her dad doing the pull my finger gag.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
She said she pulled his finger, he farted, and she was shocked and upset as a nine-year-old
girl was just furious.
Like, why?
Absolutely not.
That is not appropriate.
You monster.
We were laughing cause I said, you know, it's funny now that we're older, you know that
later on he was like having a beer with a buddy going like, man, daughters are different
than sons, man.
Yeah.
Daughters just don't.
Not the same thing.
Like she was not, she didn't think it was funny.
No.
Yeah.
Well, did she think she caused it?
I think so.
I think she didn't want that responsibility.
Yeah.
I think she was like, I don't want to have this power.
And, uh, I mean that also, I think, uh, for girls, again, I can't speak with any kind
of authority or experience, but I, you know, girls have a whole different road to go down
when it comes to discovering bodily functions.
Yeah.
And if you suddenly throw into the mix that the pulling of a finger can cause a fart can
trigger.
Yeah.
It's like one more thing.
It's like, what the fuck is this flesh cage that I am trapped in?
What kind of disaster area have I been born unto?
How many booby traps are in this thing?
You think this child was upset because she had learned something about the human anatomy
that she didn't know previously.
Right.
This is just too much.
This is one more fucking thing, one more fucking thing that can go wrong with human bodies.
This is just, add it to the list of the terrible shit that goes on with these meat puppets.
Chaotic and clumsy.
What the fuck is the flesh cage I'm trapped in is when I yell every time I'm in a store
changing room.
No, that's not even what we were talking about, the reputation of women and wives watching
true crime and true crime podcasts and true crime documentaries.
Right.
And I was like, let's just straight up staying coached up on their most likely natural predator.
This is all it is.
Yeah.
This is all just, it's just absolutely just staying on top of, it's like why men watch
Shark Week, the same exact reason, we're just staying coached up on our predators.
That's all.
That's why we watch Shark Week.
That's all we got.
When I get in the water, when I put one toe in the water, I am no longer at the top of
the food chain.
I need to, I need to educate myself to watch Shark Week.
Or in the case of that little girl, Shark Week.
Yeah.
Shark Week.
But I was like really, like really meditating on this pull my finger gag.
I was like, wait, someone did it first, right?
Right.
Like someone was like, oh, I got to fart.
I can't come up with a noise.
Let me just, let me, if I come up with a joke, I can fart in public, no problem.
This is, it's a, it's a, it's a little known fact.
It is the second most famous thing that the Earl of Sandwich did.
He invented the sandwich and he invented this bit.
But that's it, right?
How old is the gag?
Right.
Because that guy could be very old.
I just saw a crazy TikTok with this lady talking about, she came home and her husband said
he had a surprise for her and the afternoon before she had eaten a bunch of beans at a
taco joint.
Oh no.
And she knew she shouldn't.
This is the kind of humor that my wife does not enjoy.
She knew she shouldn't, but she did it.
She ate a bunch of beans.
And he blindfolds her and sits her in a chair in their, in their dining room.
And she's sitting there and the husband says, oh, I, I'll be right back.
I forgot something and she can hear him leave and she's like, oh, I gotta let one go.
So she lets out a toot and then, and she's like, oh boy, that's a, that's a, that's a
real winner there.
That's a woof.
And then she does another one and she still doesn't hear him come back yet.
And then she has like three or four and she's like, oh geez.
So she keeps the blindfold on, stands up and gets like a pillow from her chair and starts
woofing it around to try and dispel the stink, you know, and then sits back down.
And then finally her husband comes back in, she's still worried that he's going to smell
it or whatever.
He takes a blindfold off and it's her whole family there for a surprise birthday party.
Yep.
What is this unsliced cheese doing here?
Oh my Lord.
Can you imagine?
Oh, according to this, the first time the pull my finger gag happened on film was in
1959.
Oh, right.
But I'm saying we're going to get some like, you know, half ape, half man out of ice one
day, revive him.
Someone's going to do the pull my finger gag in front of him while they're studying him
in a cage or something.
And he's going to be like, you guys are still doing that gag?
Yeah.
Is that gag still alive?
And we'll be like, yes, unfrozen Brendan Fraser, it is still alive.
No, like we, we, we as comedians, we don't, you know, we say like, oh, we do is silly.
It doesn't matter.
We don't change the world or anything.
We just make the, make the day a little easier for everybody.
Right.
That guy changed the fucking world.
That guy created a fart joke.
For better or worse, just as, as just the world is a different place from the one that he
found.
It's the truth.
Yeah.
He left it better than he found it.
And Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Yeah.
I put the right neck and neck.
Totally the same.
So I've been watching, I've been watching a lot of a weird reality TV lately, especially
bad reality competition shows.
This has become my late night watch while I'm, you know, sending emails and half paying
attention to it.
But it is, it is fantastic.
Okay.
I've been watching one, I finished watching it now on Netflix called Outlast, which is
they just take a bunch of people and drop them in the Alaskan wilderness and they have
to form teams and they, and they survive out in the Alaskan wilderness until the other
teams give up.
And so it's an open-ended game.
It lasts as long as it lasts until enough people give up.
And then there's a group that wins.
There is one dude who was on this show though, that all I could think of the entire time
watching him was if Paul Mattingly were really good at outdoor survival, this would be him.
That's a big capital I, capital F pal.
It sure is.
It's a whole big old if, but I'm telling you, if Paul Mattingly had made a couple of different
decisions in his life and we're now just an outdoor survivalist guy, this would be him.
And I'm going to tell you why.
So to win the game, one of the rules, one of the only rules is to win the game.
You have to be on a team.
So a team has to accept you in to be, to be even for it to even be possible for you to
win this game.
Got it.
So at one point he is changing teams.
He all of his team is gone.
He's the last person remaining on his team and he's going to change teams.
And he knows that one of the other teams is going to come along and loot his camp that
he and his team had built up for themselves.
They're going to come loot his camp and get his resources and everything after he leaves
taking what he can to the, to the new camp.
And so this motherfucker in, I believe what would be the ultimate Paul move burns his
house down so that the other people can't come in and get it.
Now hold on, you think that's what I would do?
I think if you had made the turns in life to become this person at all, I think you
might have a little bit of this in you.
Oh, I don't know.
I think you'd be, I think you'd be like, because it's a game.
So it's all, it's all a game and it's a game that now people are taking a little too seriously
because they're in it and they've been doing it for weeks and they're starving and they're
outside and so they've, you know, part of their brain has forgotten that it's a game
and that it's not really real.
I don't know.
This guy just struck me as, I didn't dislike him either by the way.
Was he a, when I watched him burning his house down, what made you think of me?
It was, it was his mannerisms and, and just everything about him that it was, cause it
really wasn't, there wasn't an A to A line to draw between the two of you because you're
so, you're so very different.
You just think this is alternate universe me.
I think this is just alternate universe you.
And he was, I should say too, I should say too that I liked this person.
Okay.
So he was, he was burning his house down.
I got it.
I understood why he was doing it.
Everything about it.
I was like, this is, I like this guy, but he is on a different wavelength entirely from
where I am.
And I'd like to think that if I really put my mind to it, I could survive in the wilderness.
Oh, I think you could.
With a couple of tools and whatnot.
I don't think you're a useless person.
I would hate it.
Yes, you'd be so mad.
I would hate it so bad.
You'd be so mad the entire time.
That was just it.
That's why I quit Boy Scouts after getting Life Scout.
I was like, I can't in good conscience even go through with this Eagle Scout shit cause
I despise the out of doors.
I can't in good conscience.
Not really.
As a kid I was just like, I was like, this is like, this goes against who I am as a human
to even purport to enjoy camping in the least.
I don't.
I hate it.
I hate everything about it.
So I want you to watch this show, Paul.
It's outlast.
Oh, I'm sure I'd have a great time.
Paul is a clamper.
Temperature controlled covered wagon.
I don't think I've been camping in 30 years.
Yeah.
I could say.
Is it 30 years ago you drowned that kid in the lake?
Was it that long ago?
Holy shit.
I didn't consider that a camping trip.
Okay.
That was just an afternoon.
That's true.
Yeah.
It was just an afternoon.
It's true.
You didn't sleep outdoors then.
You just were outdoors.
I was just working.
Yeah.
That's true.
My wife asked me to take out the trash, so here I go.
That's a good Saudi money, man.
You can't pass up that Saudi money.
I didn't realize she hated that neighbor kid so much.
Saudi Prince was like, "Drown that kid."
You got it, Paul.
I was like, "No way."
He's like, "Here's a dump truck full of cash."
I'm like, "Okay."
Do I get to keep the dump truck?
Yes.
I'm in.
It's a tax write-off.
You had me a dump truck.
I don't know.
I don't like camp.
I don't like anything about camping.
Well, when we got home, we borrowed sleeping bags from my neighbor, Gary, who loves to
camp.
He takes his own tent and sleeping bag on a motorcycle and just goes out in any direction
and just finds places to camp.
He loves it.
I've got a sleeping bag you guys can borrow.
I've got a big double, like a two-person sleeping bag if you guys ever need it.
We did.
We should have gotten it.
Yeah.
It's zero degree, too.
It's fucking hot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Perfect.
I'm really surprised Paul hates camping.
Leon Kassab.
Leon, he's talking to that.
It's the only time I've ever been able to read sarcasm in the chat.
No problem.
Yeah.
Yep.
Now, do you know what I do like?
What's that?
The idea of having a sleepover in the house.
I like the idea of people setting up sleeping bags on a nice cushioned floor, watching TV
until you fall asleep, playing video games until the wee hours.
I like that.
Speaking of camping, I was just talking to somebody the other day about Airbnbs and they
were saying that they had had some bad luck with Airbnbs and I said, "Yo, Matt and Paul
and I had bad luck with an Airbnb one time.
I think it was in Jersey."
Yes.
And it had been listed as like a three-bedroom.
And we got there and one of the bedrooms was just a child's room with a pair of like Ninja
Turtle bunk beds or something.
Yes.
Now, that was Austin.
We would have been so aggravated.
Was that Austin?
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, because Brushwood came back.
We would have been so aggravated if it wasn't for the fact that Paul was there and was more
than happy to sleep in the children's bunk beds.
Oh, yes.
The Turtle bunk beds were in Austin.
We did have bad luck with Airbnbs in Jersey.
We had a weird Airbnbs in Jersey.
I think I'm conflating you.
We were on the third floor of a house and the people were definitely living in the house
below.
We were trying to leave.
Oh, that was just the three of us.
Yeah.
We were in and out of that place in like seven hours.
Yes.
Yeah.
We used that place to barely sleep and take a shower.
That's because we took an overnight red-eye flight home on Spirit Airlines on their deck
chair that they got in first class.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We were trying to leave to go to Tierney's and it was like they had like a birthday dinner
or something, like one of their kids or something.
Yes.
We couldn't leave.
We felt like we were going to their backyard.
We had to leave.
We had to walk through their children's birthday party to get to our car.
We had to walk through the party.
It was terrible.
No good.
Oh, so funny.
Oh, we returned our sleeping bags to Gary, he goes, "You like it?"
And they both go, "Yeah.
Yeah.
We love it.
It was our first time camping."
And I was like, "Oh.
Oh.
Bad dad alert.
Bad dad alert."
It did not occur to me that that was the first time camping at all.
And that the first time camping was this really nice Sandy Valley Ranch glamping.
I was going to say you have ruined your kids now.
That's not bad dad alert.
What are they?
Eleven and ten?
Eleven and nine?
What?
They're twenty-four.
No.
You take kids much younger camping.
You risk a hawk stealing them.
It's not, you know, this is not-
That is true.
Yeah.
Good dad alert.
Good dad alert if you ask me.
Exactly.
Snakes could eat them.
Hawks could snatch them.
How many of your children got stolen by hawks, Matt?
That's zero.
Good dad alert.
I mean, seriously, you watched some of these, what was it, the missing 411 stuff?
All the people that go missing in the woods?
That's scary.
Yeah.
All those hawks.
Paul's drawing from experience.
He went to drown that kid and a hawk took him away and Paul was like, "Fair dinkum.
Fair dinkum."
Well, he pulled the-
And dinkum.
The kid grabbed him out of the water thinking he was a fish, I guess.
And the kid wasn't drowned.
So I was like, "Ah."
So I had to train on the hawk until it got high enough that I was like, "All right.
This fall is going to be fatal."
So then I shot the hawk, he dropped the kid, bam, done and done, done and done.
You know, that was the original ending for Lord of the Rings.
Almost exactly.
It was Gandalf up on the eagle, bang.
One shot.
There's stories like that that make me think you could run UFC, Paul.
No problem.
Oh boy.
Well, I guess you get that government contract, do the big fight on the West Lawn.
Oh, right.
What the fuck?
What are you talking about?
That is actually happening.
That is going to be ... That's the thing that's so fucking crazy.
That's a big part of why I'm-
Yeah, that's it.
Well-
That's the one thing.
I can't really watch wrestling anymore.
I've stopped listening to my wrestling podcasts.
I don't really watch live.
I watch Botchamania and that's about it.
But it's just, you know, it's too crazy.
It's the same ... It's the government.
That's our government now.
It's the government.
It's WWE.
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
That's them.
Yeah.
Well, on our way out, we knew one of the women who lived in that area, she came by to visit
on a golf cart and the kids took turns driving the golf cart.
Oh, fun.
Now, that's fun.
Good.
And I was like ... I turned to Sarah and I was like, "This is all they're going to remember.
This is all they're going to remember."
Yeah, yeah.
They're going to be like, "I love camping because we drove a golf cart around."
In a couple of years, your youngest son in the middle of a conversation is going to mention
that he's a really good driver and you're going to be really confused why he's talking
about that and then he's going to mention the golf cart and you'd be like, "Motherfucker,
you're talking about that goddamn golf cart."
Yeah.
We got to feed.
They were feeding the horses.
We fed donkeys, goats, chickens, pigs, and there are these horses that look like cows.
They're fat horses?
Are they ponies?
Like it's a cow patterned skin, you know, a cow patterned hair bone.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's like a mottled, a mottled-
Palomino.
Palomino?
No, no.
Is that what it's called?
That's the club, Paul.
They're called-
That's the club that you love going to, Paul.
You're confused again.
It's called a palomino, right?
Isn't it a palomino?
No, I believe so.
Newman says, I don't know.
He says, "I quit."
It's not a palomino?
I was going to say, we're getting palomino and of course, anti-cheat guest horses, which
is also a great name for them as well.
Is it a calico?
It's a calico horse.
Calico horse?
Palomino is a horse breed characterized by a pale, creamed, golden coat or a white and
silver mane and tail, so that's not it.
It's not a palomino?
No, no.
Nick Newman's saying we host a horse podcast together.
It's true.
Yeah, but I don't know from a fucking palomino.
That don't mean we got any horse since.
Okay, I don't think-
El Camino.
It's an El Camino.
I just saw a cow for the first time in my life.
There's an El Camino because of big cow-sized horses.
Yeah.
Newman, unmute yourself.
There's one.
There's a swayback El Camino right there.
Yes.
There you go.
Is Newman, if this is what you can, unmute yourself or no?
Who can say?
I can unmute myself.
Hi, guys.
I'm not mad.
I'm just disappointed.
Newman, tell us about these cow-looking palominos.
The front is like a horse.
Those are beautiful.
The back is like a truck.
The front is like a horse.
The front is where you ride.
The back is where you fuck.
Is the picture in the chat what you saw?
Similar.
It was maybe more brown and black skin-based, and it was more of a ... It wasn't a race
horse, but it looked more athletic-looking than that.
Oh, a horse with spots is most commonly called an Appaloosa.
You either saw an Appaloosa or you saw a good old-fashioned American paint.
Oh, yeah.
American paint.
And that's not because they actually paint it.
It's because that's what they call it.
No.
That's a Sherwood Williams, they call it.
That is an American ... Probably what you saw was an American paint.
Okay.
That is ... Okay, because what I didn't get into is that I met a guy who'd been working
around the ranch for 27 years who called himself Bones, and-
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, I need to know everything about Bones.
Everybody shut up.
This is the rest of the show.
We're going to talk about Bones.
I need to know about this man.
And he was like ... So I said, "Oh, we've got to head back to Vegas."
He goes, "Sorry to hear that.
I got out of that city 27 years ago and never went back.
I came out here to help my friend move and never left."
Oh my God, my spirit animal is gunning Bones.
Well, she was an American paint, had a face like Sarah Jessica Parker.
Oh, jeez.
Harry on bread chop.
He was joking around with me so much.
You know when someone has so many bits in their head?
And then I laughed at one of his bits so that it was something that he was rapid fire, but
it wasn't-
Now it's on.
Yeah.
And in a hurricane of information, he'd used the word paint.
And I literally was like, "Are you saying paint like paint?"
And he was joking like, "Yeah, we paint them or whatever."
And he was like, "Hey."
And I couldn't get to pass his crazy-
You were like, "No, no, I needed the real answer."
I couldn't get him to stop doing bits.
And so when he said paint, I was like, "I think he's fucking with me and I don't know
what he's saying.
And I can't believe ... I now can't believe any information he's telling me about this
horse."
But he was saying what it's called.
It's called an American paint.
That's what it was-
Ah!
And here's where it gets more confusing.
Different breeds can also be classified as paint horses by the American Paint Horse Association
based on their coloring.
Okay.
So it doesn't have to be the caliphate.
Yeah.
So we had a thoroughbred named Marketry.
Okay.
And Marketry's coloring on his leg went above the knee, which is part of their requirements
that the judges for this paint horse thing have.
So he actually was dual certified as a thoroughbred and a paint horse.
Wow!
I know.
His name is Marketry and it was a bad joke because that is a French woodworking term
for when you use glue made from horses to do inlays.
Boo!
Boo that name!
That's fucked up!
Yeah.
Isn't that bad?
We didn't name him that.
I like it.
It's macabre.
I was like my buddy who had a rabbit named Hassenfeffer.
I dated a girl that had a rabbit in a room in a cage.
And first of all, there's an odor.
It's mostly cedar chips, but there is an odor.
This, Nick, was this one of those things where as I've heard in apocryphal Aerosmith songs
that she perhaps utilized this rabbit for pregnancy tests.
The rabbit done died.
That's right.
Was she so promiscuous that she had several bunnies by her bedside to test whether she
was pregnant?
Is that what's happening?
If I made it up them stairs to that bedroom, I'm sure I wasn't blazing any trails.
That's what I'm saying though.
But so do you think that's what was going on?
She kept the rabbit.
Yeah, that's what was going on Paul.
That's definitely what was happening.
I have not read nor have I seen, and still to this day, a work called Watership Down.
You've never seen Watership Down?
No.
It's a book and an animated movie.
And it'll break you.
The name of the rabbit was a reference to that.
Was it a number?
It was a number.
Okay.
It was a number?
Fiverr.
This is my rabbit.
Unban scooped and the chat says fiverr.
That's fascinating.
Do you know that girl?
Siege?
I wasn't the first.
There it is.
No.
Okay.
He knows that girl too.
Yeah.
The chat knows everything.
You all got those rabbit girls.
And she was kind of shitty that I hadn't seen this.
Yeah.
She's right to be shitty on that.
You need to see that, and then you need to see plague dogs, and then you'll never have
to smile again.
I'll save a lot of time.
No, I just listened to that REM song everybody hurts on repeat in my car.
Seriously though, plague dogs is the same animation house that did Watership Down, and
it is the most devastating thing I've ever seen on film.
Plague dogs?
Plague dogs.
Yep.
Okay.
That's how much I...
Devastated!
Thanks for having me.
All right, buddy.
Thanks, Nick!
We appreciate your horse sense.
Well, let's do a little Scoop Mail.
Message for you, son.
We got one here from the Salt Lake Scoop.
Hey guys, I thought I would share something from a recent Vegas trip to let you comment
on it.
We went to Brad Garrett's Comedy Club recently, it's over in the MGM Grand.
Just a quick summary of the format of the show.
Brad comes out and tells some jokes, then he introduces the first comedian.
Then Brad comes out and tells a few more jokes, then he introduces the second comedian.
Brad told a few jokes indicating that he was not a big fan of Trump, he did a Trump voice
and did the Trump dance and said it looks like he's jacking off two guys.
Brad made a few other jokes at Trump's expense, he did more Trump material than I thought
someone would do at a Vegas show.
Yeah, Brad is a very anti-Trump fella.
We were at the show two days after Charlie Kirk was murdered during Brad's second set,
a woman across the room stood up and addressed Brad.
I thought I heard her say, "Can we have a moment for Charlie Kirk?"
Is this Brad Garrett?
Brad responded...
Yeah.
Okay.
Is Brad Garrett on stage at the Brad Garrett Comedy Club?
I thought I'd say, "Can we have a moment for Charlie Kirk?"
Brad responded by saying, "A moment of silence for Charlie Kirk?
You know this is a comedy show, right?"
But then he quickly followed up.
It is tragic, everyone should be able to say whatever they want without that happening
to them.
With that comment, about 70% of the crowd applauded and Brad had won the crowd back.
At this point, the staff began to move toward this woman.
Brad said to the staff, "No, no, no, she's okay, just leave her."
Indicating that he didn't want her kicked out.
Brad then went on with his jokes, his show was almost completely derailed by that woman
and he got the control back so quickly.
It was fascinating.
I went from cringing to applauding and back to laughing in less than a minute.
A few questions for you performers and Vegas insiders, was there any chance that this was
staged?
No.
No, no, no.
No way.
You're just looking at a guy who has dealt with this shit.
I just saw Mark Maron talking about hecklers and crowd work in general.
I can't recall who he was talking with now, but he was talking about crowd work as it
being something that's currently hot right now.
A lot of comedians are being praised because they do awesome crowd work.
Maron was like, "Hey, it's important to the degree that you're able to quickly address
a heckler and get your shit back on track."
I don't think making your career on crowd work is really that laudable per se.
I think what you saw there was a very experienced professional who was able to very quickly
turn it around and get it back on track and reset the mood.
That's experience, man.
I mean, that's the goal too.
It's just a reset.
And the brevity of it.
That's the other thing, able to do it quickly, just like, done.
You don't even realize.
Yeah.
No, I mean, it's a weird ... The internet makes things change so fast, and so at first
standups felt like they were really hampered by social media because they couldn't put
their best material online so they consider it burned, something they can't do again.
And so then they started realizing that younger people started realizing faster.
They just did crowd work and put crowd work clips up, then they could protect their best
material and just do crowd work.
But then crowd work clips just became so much more popular and so much more viral, then
all of a sudden you had all these people purposely putting comedians on the spot and doing those
kind of contests.
There was crowd work shows and all kinds of other examples of it.
And so crowd work just has become this version of it, and even stranger, and I've talked
about this with magicians and comedians, is how much an audience now is just prepared
to talk to the person on stage.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh, it's amazing.
They're ready, like, back in the '80s and '90s and even early 2000s, if a comedian started
talking to someone from stage, that person would be embarrassed.
Yeah.
Yes.
They would recoil in fear.
It was a conversation.
No.
And now it's just like, "Yeah, yeah, I'm ready to talk.
What are we talking about?"
No.
That's why they're going to comedy shows to become part of the show.
It's...
Right.
...fucking weird.
Krista Hendrix, who's crushing it, right?
She figured it out.
This is something that happened to her.
She wanted to do crowd work, so she went with the burner magic tricks, and people liked
her crowd work so much, she had to keep eliminating magic tricks in her show.
Right.
She had to do less and less magic tricks.
And you can watch now in her more recent clips, when she goes to talk to the audience, they're
just ready.
They're ready to talk to her.
They're ready to give her the answers.
They're ready to talk about their occupation or the specifics of the situation they're
writing about.
They have no problem talking to people now.
They know their job.
It is...
They know their part.
It's wild.
It is bizarre.
Nope.
That's from Saltlick.
Thank you.
Thank you, Saltlick.
Scoop.
Did Newman plug his podcast before he went?
Sorry, I had to take his call, and I was gone for a minute.
Oh, no.
He did not.
He's relaunching...
What's Newman's new podcast?
He's relaunching his podcast, Newman Unleashed, on September 25th.
You can start listening to his solo podcast.
There you go.
Check it out.
You can listen to Newman, if you hate yourself.
Get that horse sex.
Wait a minute.
Here's some Jock vs. Nerd.
You wanna do a little Jock vs. Nerd action?
Oh, am I?
Fuck yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Expunge.
We got an old school Jock vs. Nerd coming at us from Nesticle, Scoot.
Oh, nice.
Nesticle sent this in a while ago.
He reconstructed it for me because I missed it back then.
Here are a dozen episode titles from our show, from our very own beloved Matt and Mattingly's
Ice Cream Social.
Here are a dozen episode titles.
The question is very simply, figure out which of these titles are real and which ones Nesticle
Scoot made up?
That's it.
Easy game, fellas.
Easy game.
I'm going to tell you a title.
You're going to tell me, is that a title of our show that the three of us produce and
put out on the air?
You're just going to tell us, is that a title that we produced or is that just a made up
thing?
First one.
Paul, I'm thinking of a number.
What is it?
Two.
That's it.
That's exactly right.
You're first.
Bleach Thy Crevices, Bleach Thy Crevices.
Is that an ICS title or is that made up?
Made up.
Matt, is that an ICS title or is that made up?
Say it again?
Bleach Thy Crevices.
I think it's made up.
It is made up.
Good job, both of you.
All right.
We've played a game like this before and I have an unfair advantage that I go back and
forth with Slaking Fool about titles for each episode before they go up every time, and
I'm the one who uploads the episode, so I type it twice before I put it out into the
... This is on a curve.
I usually retweet it and I usually see it, so you know.
That's true.
Oh yeah.
I usually pay some measure of attention to it.
Rich Men Knit, Rich Men Knit.
Real or fake?
Rich Men Knit.
Matt, you want to go first on this one?
Rich Men Knit, K-N-I-T.
Fake.
Paul.
It sounds real to me.
Point for Paul.
That was episode 602.
All right.
Rich Men Knit.
The Twerking Disaster.
Real.
Shout them out.
You know them.
Real.
Twerking Disaster.
I'll say fake.
It is fake.
Two points for Paul.
Pete, Pete Seging Missiles, S-E-E-G-I-N-G.
That's real.
That's episode 780.
Yeah.
Chilele leg.
Paul's up by two now, yeah?
I think so.
I think Paul's plus two.
Yeah.
Chilele leg.
True.
Yeah, that's a real one.
That's a real one, 733.
The Moist Horizon.
Oh, that sounds like us.
It does.
It really sounds like us.
But it doesn't ring a bell.
Yeah, right?
I'll say fake.
Okay, Matt.
I still say fake.
I should do it for gamesmanship.
I should change it up, but I think it's fake.
It is fake.
Good call, buddy.
Good call.
The Androgynous.
Fake.
Oh, I think that might be real.
It is real.
1081.
That's lazy.
Ah!
That's a lazy title.
That's exactly what I thought when I saw it.
I was like, "The Androgynous?
That's not real."
I scrolled down and said, "We have a show called The Androgynous?"
The Gospel of Jacob.
Hmm.
I mean, on a chat GPT level, we must have, right?
Right.
That just seems like at the end of a thousand episodes, we must have done that.
The Gospel of Jacob?
Yeah.
The Gospel of Jacob.
Did you say real, Matt?
I said real.
I'll say real.
It's fake.
We never did The Gospel of Jacob.
Out of town.
Let's call this episode that one.
The Gospel of Jacob and the moist horizon.
We didn't use both of those.
Chili Chilis.
C-H-I-L-L-Y.
C-H-I-L-L-I-'s.
Chili Chilis.
That's real.
Oh, that is fake.
What?
That is fake.
Stop it.
I know.
That's fake.
That's three that we have to use now.
My brain is confusing.
Porn sniffing dog.
That's real.
That's definitely real.
Yeah.
That's episode 679.
The fifth nugget hits rock bottom.
I'm already upset with how poorly I'm doing on this, by the way.
Three wrong is unacceptable.
Matt, it's not like you gave a speech talking about how you had an advantage in this game
at the beginning of the game, though.
I think that's real.
Exactly.
I was putting myself on blast on purpose.
I wanted to stay sharp.
Yeah.
I'll say real on the nugget.
What is it?
Oh, Paul says real on the nugget.
The fifth nugget hits rock bottom.
I'm going to say false.
It is real.
Episode 1133.
I'm running away with it, Matt.
I'm running away.
That's a recent one.
Yeah.
Paul's destroying me on this.
1133.
You say recent, Matt.
That's like three years ago.
Maybe four.
It's a year ago.
No, it's like six months ago, right?
No, no, it's not.
It's not.
I don't know what number we're on now.
What number are we on now?
What number is this show?
We're on 1240 something.
Yeah.
So it's been about 100 episodes.
Yeah, it's been a year.
That's a long time.
This is the last one, and of course, as tradition dictates, this one is worth 18,000 points.
Don't leave me gross.
That's real.
We both get 18,000 points, but Paul wins by three.
That was episode 454, and that is from the Nesticle Scoop.
Thank you so much, Nesticle Scoop, and thank you for rebuilding that Jock vs. Nerd that
you had made a while back.
We really appreciate it.
If you want to send us a scooperty or a Price of Skryte Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jock
vs. Nerd, or just send us an old school Jock vs. Nerd like Nesticle Scoop just did, or just
go over there and send us some Scoop mail, you can do all those things over there at
Hayscoops.com, head over to Hayscoops.com, do all those things.
It's going to be great.
Buy yourself tickets to ScoopFest.
Yes.
You don't have to hear us.
Plug ScoopFest a whole lot more coming up in the next couple weeks, so get them now.
Do it.
You're going to miss it.
Awesome.
Who sent that in?
Nesticle.
Nesticle Scoop.
Thank you, Nesticle Scoop, for making me doubt myself.
Really now.
I'm a terrible podcast host.
I don't think that's why you're a bad podcast host.
Thank you, Jacob.
Those were great, though.
Even the made-up ones were really tricky.
Oh, there were, like the made-up ones, I'm just upset that we haven't already used them.
Jacob, you're right.
Why I am a bad podcast host is I muted my Zoom because I had to take a call, but then
I didn't mute my recorder.
Oh, no.
So, in the middle of the Newman interview, you have to figure out, bro.
It's where Newman's talking, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I got you.
I got you.
I'm just going to make a note about that right now.
It'll be fine to just hear Matt's rando conversation in the middle of the interview.
With my corporate magic booker.
That'll be great.
Yeah, that'll be great.
Professionals.
That's right.
Nicholas Newman in the chat.
Great time to take a call.
Yeah, yeah, Richard wants us to leave it in.
Thirsty Scoop wants us to leave that in.
There's a Patriot level.
I do notice, and I don't know what to do about it because I don't know how to mute the recorder,
so I just leave the room.
So, it's only the beginning of the conversation before I leave.
It will not be hard to find.
When you hear a different voice on the phone on my audio, you'll know.
That's it.
And that's why I'm not a good podcast host.
Other reasons.
I want to thank Ben Jalef for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I want to thank the following people, all of whom, consider glamping their first-time
camping.
Yeah.
Dan Martin, Daniel Loeser, Danielle Matias Ferrer, Danny Olwein, Darren Cunningham, Darth
Scooper, Dave Serial, Dave Hanson, Dave Slusher, David Johnson, David A. Small, David Gravel,
David Kay, David Peterson, David Sorensen, David Walker, Dan Laszlo, Derek Josier, Dole
Whip Scoop, Dippin' Dots Jack, Dirty Old Scoop, and Distiller Scoop.
These wonderful people refer to themselves as paint horses.
Edward Bender, Alyssa Walsack, Elkton Magic Scoop, Eric Nilsen, Erotic Scrape Scoop, Evil
Monkey, Fade Out Scoop, Fifi, Finn Steffensen, Flat Kidney, Frankie's Tiki Scoop, Freehold
Scoop, Freeze Dried Scoop, Frozen 49th Scoop, Frozen Cusser, Fudgy the Whale, Galoosha
Scoop, Galactic President Scooperstar McScoopsalot, Galen Diggs, Garrett Godfrey, Gas Man Scoop,
and Gazpacho Scoop.
I want to thank the following people who know the old song from the Half Cow, Half Horse
Show, of course is of course, of course, of course.
That's Doc Scoop, Don Donnie, Don't Say Scoop Name, Doug Lay, Dr. Science Scoop, Dr. Scoop
Little, Dr. Tobias Scoopay, Duck Flambe, Duke Scoop, Dwayne Webb, Ed Short Arms Marcus,
Ed Ondrick, Ed Wagner, and Ed Les Scoop.
Big thanks to these individuals who have far better bathroom luck than Jacob usually does,
even though we didn't have a fun Jacob bathroom story this episode, I'm sure we'll have one
very soon again.
The Gospel of Jacob!
Yes.
Gelato Problems, Gelato Steve, Gene Zink, Genetic Scoop, George Guskov, Gerardo Garcia,
Gizmo Scoop, Greater Sunday Scoop, Gravel Scoop, Green Wolf Scoop, Grill Sergeant Scoops,
Guy Wade, Gwarthok, and Hatchet Scoop.
And I'd like to thank the following scoops, I'd like to thank Heather Divine Hanson, Holly
Marshmallow Lightly, Horse Dad, or House Dad Scoop, not Horse Dad Scoop, that's a whole
different person.
Hilly and Scoop, I Don't Have a Scoop Name, ENA Chapman, Ian Soto, Ice Cream Manwich, Ice
Blue Scoop, I Want a Scoop Baby, Jacob Dinklater, Jake Schneider, James Dawson, James Hubbell,
Jameson Fisher, Janine Lankard, Jason Klepper, Jason Horkostas, Jason Specklin, Jason Street,
Jason Vasquez, Jason Victor, Jason Yenowitz, Jay Shapiro, Jed Taxon, Jeff Faust, Jeff Harris,
Jeff Libby, Jeff Loomis, Ginny Ebarb, Jeremy Hudson, Jesse Rain, Jill Short, Jimmy Sloanina,
John Carter, and John Bloor.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do love you.
Thank you so much.
If you'd like to be thanked on air, if you want to hop on our Twitch broadcasts, all
I'm going to do is get on over to, why can't I finish this plug?
It's the thing that pays us, go to PreachingFun.com so that we don't do this for free.
Or if you want your kids to sleep in a teepee while you sleep in a chuck wagon, head on
over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Like Matt said, that is how we do the show, it's what makes the show possible.
So if you think this show is worth more than $0, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those
are the places that you can go to support this show and get some cool stuff.
Like you get to hang out in the Zoom with us.
Our Zoom attendance today got full on spoilers for ScoopFest this year, just in the pre-show.
So there is something worth coming over and hanging out in the Zoom chat with us if you
are on Patreon, so do that.
Look at your Patreon messages, we send out the Zoom link twice a week, every week, no
matter what.
Well, unless we're not going to do it and then we wouldn't send the link out.
But other than that, no matter what.
Yeah.
Right.
All things considered.
Pretty much all the time, though.
Alright.
Usually.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
We'll see you at the cone!
Jeff Loomis points out that the phone call was probably not that entertaining since Matt
came back on the show after the phone call was over.
We're Preaching Fun!