Oh, hello there! I am so happy you're here! I want to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Right now, I would like to thank Malia, Mike, Paul's brother, Pyro, Richard Dunn, Sarah Boyle,
Sax Guy, Jimmy D, Scoop, Scoop Brady, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Cotta, Slippery Kie, Motherfucker,
Thunder, Cougar Falcon, Scoop, and Travis Jaggery.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks and help deliver that fucking ice cream
straight into people's fucking ear holes, head over to PreachingFun.com!
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up and who knows, the life you save may be your own!
Now here's a show!
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Happy New Year, everybody!
Happy New Year! Start off the New Year right.
A guy was just awarded custody of his brother.
Here in Nevada, I think national news because he was sexually abused by his brother when he was a kid.
Turns out he was the father of his own brother.
Happy New Year!
This time, we're Matt and Maddly's ice cream social!
Sitting in a pool in his own mess, that's Matt Donnelly!
Sitting in a pool in his own mess, that's also Paul Maddly!
I'm Jacob, we're PreachingFun!
I was looking at the trending news in Nevada and...
I shouldn't laugh, that's terrible!
It is terrible. It is absolutely terrible.
A man awarded custody.
It's horrible, but it's also horrible.
I'm only asking to empathize with me scrolling to be stopped with man awarded custody of his own brother.
And then you go to click the link, it says like a warning, sensitive material.
And that just was like, good lord, that's a hard guy to go on a first date with after this, you know?
Oh man!
So tell me about your life recently!
How old is this boy now?
The child that was awarded custody is early teens.
Okay.
The gentleman is in his 20s.
And the mother is in jail.
Good! Good!
I'm fine with that.
Honestly, I'm not even fine with that.
I don't want her to be in jail. I want her to be getting help or something.
It's not a crazy sentence.
It's like an eight-year sentence with parole kind of thing.
Good, good, good.
I mean, I say that as if I would last a week in prison.
Right.
I'm just thinking, what are the odds of her being a repeat offender?
I could do a dime standing on my head.
So yeah.
We're not all strong like you, Paul.
Also not all as strong as you.
Did we miss technicalscooport on the chat for the truck drivers?
I don't know.
Technicalscooport.
Shout out to technicalscooport for the truck driving.
If indeed we did not have your name on the list.
Might just be another list.
What are you talking about?
Technicalscooport in the chat was asking about you didn't hear his name on the truck driver.
Oh, I missed that.
Technicalscooport, thank you very much.
If I missed you on the list, I apologize.
We appreciate each and every one of you guys just being a crybaby.
No, not at all, technicalscooport.
That's what you pay for and we appreciate you guys so, so much.
And we also, you paid for us to change the subject.
Perfect, perfect.
Yeah, no, that was great.
That was my secret intention.
Coming up, there is a news article I read here.
I don't know if you guys have heard of it yet, but a man in Nevada was awarded custody of Big Brother.
And it turned out there was a twist that no one saw coming.
Oh boy, oh boy.
You know what the real twist is?
What's that?
Personal trainers hate him.
I did the, you know, you're singing a song to somebody else and they hear you do the wrong lyrics and they make fun of you for that?
Yes.
I did that to myself in the car the other day.
What'd you do?
You caught yourself singing the wrong lyrics?
I caught myself.
I was like, that can't be the right lyric.
I had the 90s station on and it was playing, oh, what's that song?
Everlast, then you really might know what it's like.
You know what I'm talking about?
No, no, no, that's not Everlast.
Yeah, that's Everlast.
That's Everlast, right?
That's Everlast, yeah, yeah.
I don't remember the name of the song.
God forbid you ever have to walk a mile in her shoes.
That one, yeah.
'Cause then you really might know what it's like to have to choose.
So I had the 90s station on and I was doing what Paul's doing.
I'm just singing along with it.
I'm like, yeah, this jam.
I remember this jam from like '96 or so.
This is awesome, yeah.
And the hair on his face was dreadlocked for the mange.
Dreadlocked for the mange?
Dreadlocked, yeah, for the mange.
I was like, oh, this man had to dreadlock the hair on his face
because he had such bad mange is apparently what I thought in the mid-90s.
No, that's not how it goes.
It's close.
Correct, it's not how it goes.
How would you handle the mange, Paul?
You don't want to have to comb it out every day.
No, but I'm thinking topical ointment.
A salve?
A salve before dreadlocking it.
Yuck, those things are going to come out in clumps.
Yep.
That's going to just fall right off your face.
Also, it occurred to me as I was thinking about this in the car as I was driving,
dreadlocking hair wouldn't help with mange at all.
That wouldn't even be a good solution for mange.
No.
Well, we do plenty of things in our lives that don't help
with the things that they're supposed to.
Well, that's true.
That's true.
All right, I'm back to dreadlocked for the mange.
There's dreadlocks for the mange YouTube page, which swears by it.
Oh, yeah.
People who said they'd done their research and they have different doctors
to testify that dreadlocking for the mange is perfectly well suited.
What is the actual lyric?
I'm looking it up right now.
It's just like hair full of mange.
The hair on his face.
Oh, I was much closer than I thought I was.
I was going to say you're very close.
Dreadlocked and full of mange.
Yeah.
I'm not as far off on this lyric as I assume.
No, you're being too hard on yourself in that car.
You got to go back there and say, I owe you an apology, Jacob.
Yeah, I owe past Jacob an apology.
I was too harsh on him.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are other lyrics in this song.
If I go through all the lyrics in this song,
I'm sure there are others that I'm just absolutely wrong on.
If there's a chance you might get interrupted,
I might have to leave to show a plumber my toilet that's not working.
No.
Matt has to go fuck a plumber.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
But nonetheless, I have another story.
I've had so many lately, the man of the hour intro.
Oh, the man of the hour.
I haven't gotten over the man of the hour.
We'll get through this.
The guy complaining about me in front of me, the cruise ship thing.
That's good.
My debacle as a soccer coach.
I saw your wife the other night at the show,
and I did something that I rarely do, which I stood up to give her a hug.
I felt like she needed it after having heard the boys' soccer story.
I was like, you don't know why I'm giving you a hug,
but I feel like you just need a hug.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're closing out the year strong.
Isn't that what they say about the new year?
When it goes to shit, then the rest of your year is going to be,
your new year is going to be good and that kind of thing.
I hope so.
That's an assumption, right?
I mean, as Matt Donnelly, famous set in 2019,
next year's got to be better.
I believe I did say that, right?
I think that's a legit, that's a legit quote.
I have a neighbor who's a douche.
Okay.
And I don't think I've talked about too much on the pod.
No, you don't want to put your neighborhood on blast.
How far down is he?
He's across the street and down two doors.
He's on the corner.
It's not Chad's old house or anything.
No, no, no.
Across the street.
So it's not a direct neighbor, which is good.
Yeah.
Close enough.
Adjacent.
You can see his home from your windows.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
From my driveway, you can see his house.
His house.
You know, we're catty, whatever it is.
Yeah, catty corner.
Matt can throw a cat in his house.
Yeah.
Ain't that far.
And so in the past-
What did this douche do?
In the past, he's yelled at children in the neighborhood.
Oh.
For things going on in his yard.
Oh, this isn't the no-cones guy, is it?
No, right?
So the no-cones guy, I think, either moved or just accepted that maybe-
Gave up.
That maybe he was possibly going to run over children and maybe chilled out.
I don't know.
One or the other.
Maybe he got therapy.
And once again, my kids got older and more agile.
So it was like-
That's true.
It was less of a deal.
They don't need the cones as much.
And no, this guy's yelled at children in the past, but not my children.
And so I've heard tales of him yelling at children before, but I never came to it face
to face.
But I was at the grocery store, and then my wife and I missed cross-hairs text, so we
ended up both at the grocery store together getting last minute things for a party we're
going to throw tomorrow.
Don't.
We're going to do your run tomorrow, but three to five for having people over.
Oh, nice.
And Paul, you're not invited.
And-
I knew it.
I fucking knew it.
And she's like, "I guess the neighbor's just cursed at our kids."
And I was like, "Oh."
Oh, no.
And so I was like, "Oh, I got it."
I was like, "Well, that's not okay."
Yeah.
And I was like, "I guess I should go talk to them."
How much of your inner monologue at this point is, "Can I get away with not dealing with
this at all?"
Well, this is, you know, I mean, I'll say that's always my first instinct, right?
My first instinct is like, "Oh, hide and do nothing."
Right?
Because I mean, this is not going to be a fun conversation.
No, I don't anticipate it going well.
No, I don't.
Because he has been across from us like, you know, I mean, this is no surprise to you.
We are neighborly, especially my wife.
We know all of our neighbors.
Y'all know your neighbors.
And these guys have been here for the whole time and we do not talk at all.
And they've ignored us every time we try to hide from them in the past.
Real grumpers, eh?
Just total grumpers.
A lot of people go in and out of that house who don't even know if there's one or two
families in there.
It's just one of those that goes on.
It's that kind of situation.
There's something, there's fishiness and that's why they're all standoff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You think it's a bunch of mobsters going to the mattresses for a potential mob war?
You think that's what's going on in there?
I noticed there's a lot of distribution of ammunition and different guns from the trunks.
I've noticed a bunch of Tommy guns being passed out over here.
You joke, but there's some shit like that that for real goes down out of these Vegas
residential.
It's no joke.
There is.
It's kind of a joke.
Yeah, this kind of seems to be like in his own business, his own, whatever, any man,
something, some kind of business, but he has two big trucks.
He's loading in and out all the time with different stuff, but yeah, so a good neighborhood
kid overthrew my son and the ball rolled off the street up onto his driveway underneath
his truck and he came out and screamed at my children to keep their shit away from my
shit.
So there was a ball on his property?
Was a kid trying to get the ball at this point?
As a matter of fact, because of the past, my son was waiting for the ball to roll back
down the driveway in which it did.
So he was even doing what he's supposed to do?
Yes.
Oh, come on.
When we first moved into this house, the house that we live in now, we have close neighbors
and we're in a cul-de-sac and the neighbors that we had when we first moved in, kind of
kiddy corner across from us, they had a bunch of kids and the kids were always out.
Our big cul-de-sac is not technically a street.
It's technically a shared private drive between our four houses right here.
And so, and obviously it's a cul-de-sac because it's done a lot of traffic.
So the kids would be out riding bikes and skateboarding and doing all that stuff all
the time and one of the younger ones, because we have kind of a circular drive in front
of our house as well.
And so they would cut through the circular drive all the time.
Not a big deal.
Who cares?
But once or twice, one of the younger ones would come up like all the way up to our front
porch and you know, just skating around doing whatever because there's concrete all the
way up there.
He wasn't doing anything, but he'd just come up, he'd come all the way up there.
And so one day I had to go over and talk to his parents who were very nice people.
Just a giant Mormon family.
So they just had kids everywhere.
They were just quiver full.
Yeah.
I think there were like 12 people living in the house at one point with this one with
this one family.
That's outrageous.
But they were lovely and they were a very, very, very, very nice family.
I miss them.
They're, they're great.
They were, they were good neighbors, but like I had to go have the conversation with the
dad who's just standing outside, it's like, Hey, maybe just ask your, your kiddos to not
like if they're in the driveway there, I don't care if they're in front of the house.
I don't care if they're in front of the garages.
I don't care.
The front porch, like their windows straight into the house there.
I don't really want them right up there.
Yeah.
So maybe, maybe talk to them.
And that was an awkward as fuck conversation.
Yes.
And we were both being very civil and I didn't like it at all.
Now this guy's just yelling because a ball was in his driveway for a minute and it removed
itself seemingly of its own accord with, with the assistance of gravity.
It removed itself.
So I was like, it's time to go talk.
That's a lot of, that's a lot of anger.
I know.
And this thing is like, and I'm, it's my neighbor, right?
So the whole point, tell him I had, I'm like, I have to, one, he's going to yell at me.
I have to prepare myself.
He's going to yell.
He's not going to be like, Oh, he's not going to be a two-faced person.
Which I'm like, Oh no, me.
I love those kiddos.
Like he's that fucking.
His voice is going to be raised.
My first thought would be maybe take him a gift.
Um, well, that wasn't, that wasn't my thought.
But uh, uh, uh, I baseball is a baseball because it's been a few incidents over the years.
Not a lot, but a few years, I don't know if adult ever got involved before.
So I was like, I have to just go over there and have a conversation with him just to know
that adult is, is, is also part of this conversation, right?
He had been hanging out in his car when it happened and he was hanging out his car.
When I went over, he'd been hanging out his car all day doing business from his car.
Oh, Oh, this is not a happy person.
No.
So I thought I was going to go to the front door.
He was already in his car and he rolls down his window.
And I said, he doesn't get out, he just rolls down the window.
Yeah.
And I said, Hey man, you can't be cursing at children.
And he goes, I didn't, I didn't curse it.
First of all, I didn't car.
Boom.
He's out of his door, uh, in my face and tell me I didn't curse it.
Any children.
And he goes, I have, I record everything.
He points, he gestures as if he has cameras all over his house and his car says, I recorded
everything.
And I said, great.
Play it.
And I said, awesome.
Play it for me.
And I'll apologize.
Yeah.
And he goes, I have to fucking play, fucking play anything for you.
Fuck you.
Like I am ready to be wrong.
Show me that I'm wrong.
I'm ready to be wrong.
I will, I will yell at my kids.
I will, I will beat them to with it for lying about you saying shit to them.
Show me the video and I will beat my children.
No.
And he immediately starts cursing a lot.
So I'm like, I'm skeptical that he didn't, he didn't curse it.
I'm skeptical.
If someone comes to me and says, Hey, you can't curse in front of X, I assume that I
did indeed curse, whether I remember cursing or not, that's where I start from.
And he then he's like, you had never talked to me until this moment, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, which I was like food.
I've tried to say hi to you like a million times and you've ignored me.
So I was like, check the recordings, man.
Exactly.
So I let that pass.
And then I was like, I was like, I was like, and I basically was like, you, you, you can
have everything you want without screaming at kids.
That's been my whole point.
Yeah.
You can keep the kids out of your property.
You can do that without screaming and cursing it at my kids, but he's getting, he's getting,
he's getting music.
You come over here.
You're going to get in my face.
You can just see this, you know, whatever.
He goes, kiss my ass, kiss my fucking ass.
Kiss my ass.
I say, I say if I kiss your ass, will you be nicer to the kids?
Nice.
That really threw him.
I'm sure.
And he said, but, and I said, if I kiss your ass right now, will you be nicer to the children?
What if I spin you around?
What if I, what if I give you a blow job right now?
I will, I will blow you in this driveway.
He literally like got jarred by that, that he actually like instinctively turned his
butt towards me.
Like while he was still being angry, he was like, Oh yeah, he wanted it.
So then I, I bent over, but I kissed my hand.
I kissed my hand and I, yeah, boop.
I touched his butt.
Tapped him.
Yep.
Yeah.
I gave him a little.
There you go.
Good.
Which triggered his gay stuff alarm.
And then he got even more angry again and was like, don't you fucking touch me.
You fucking touch me.
Fuck away from me.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
He, yeah, that, uh, Mark in the chat, that was a Freudian turn on the neighbor's part
for sure.
Oh, a hundred percent.
For sure.
This guy's filled with self hatred.
This is becoming more and more apparent.
The, the more we look into all of this stuff and I can speak personal, not personal, but
interpersonal experience.
A lot of this shit is coming from repressed gay people.
Oh, sure.
Don't have a way they, and it just, the self hatred that gets festered in.
Repressed anything.
Like there's, there's something.
Anything.
Yeah.
There's something inside this guy that he's, that he's furious about.
You know, the Kinsey scale is not exactly the most accurate thing in the world, but the
idea that we have different wavering amounts of.
Oh, absolute.
We're all on the spectrum.
Bisexuality.
Right.
So you gotta be aware enough to be like, oh yeah, there's, I mean, there's a needle that
moves when Trent Reznor comes into the conversation.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
I've asked you over and over again, not to refer to your dick as a needle.
Don't, I want you to be happier about yourself.
Oh no, no, no.
It's, it's, there's more girth than that.
I'm not, we're not, we're not playing records.
Okay.
Good.
I mean, it's, it's a success because he was a piece of ass and men like it's going to
see him in concert, but it was, he was an attractive guy.
I mean, the, the, the, what the album cover with his dick on it.
Yeah.
There's an album cover.
It's just like zoomed in on his, on his crotch.
No, you zoomed in.
It was a regular shot.
You zoomed in on his crotch.
Oh, I wondered why a magnifying glass was taped onto that album cover.
No, that's what I mean is like, yes, I do.
I do believe Paul.
I actually do.
It's like, it just, it's just this gay hatred stuff just really, really comes from really
straight quote unquote straight men, hating gay men and gay activities.
Right.
And that's why transfers to trance, because if you were actually attracted to someone
presenting female that was born male, then suddenly you think something's terrible with
yourself.
Yeah.
It's like they just, it's jealousy too.
It's like, how dare someone live their life open and free, embracing their identity.
I don't get to do that.
And that was the thing I mentioned this before to Jacob the other day.
Were we talking about, it's not a podcast or whatever it was, but how, when it gets
to a certain point.
No, no, that was just a FaceTime that you and I had a late night, our, our, our no pants
FaceTimes.
We were talking about how, uh, I got disinvited to no pants FaceTimes.
When did I lose my invite?
No, no, we're just, we're splitting them.
We're just splitting them.
Disinvited is a strong word, disinvited is a strong word.
We agreed, Jacob and I both agreed that we got a little turned off the last time.
Uh, so we wanted to keep it.
We wanted to keep it a little more spicy.
Just me and Jacob, uh, no, uh, this is the thing, uh, when a lot of, uh, hardcore religious
types want to adamantly say that sexuality is a choice that is coming from their reality
in which they must choose to repress their natural instinct.
And they think everyone has to undergo that same choice where we do not, it is, you know,
and yeah, it's just, it's hard.
No, I mean, I think there's like, like, uh, um, uh, my buddy Mike Mills, who's producing
the joker's tour.
He's also producing this documentary, um, anyhow, I can't, I don't think I can talk
about what it is or what it's about, but, uh, one part of it that he was talking to
me about was the studying was basically people did, uh, study, um, uh, basically hook up
meters to people's, uh, penises to show them pictures to like about twinges when they saw
stuff.
Yes.
Oh, that was, that was an official study.
That was an official study.
So if you've been doing on your own, Jacob, you need to share that data.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I had no idea.
Does my tongue count as a meter?
Yes.
It does.
Okay.
It's a meat.
All right.
So that and how you eat a Reese's peanut butter cup is intense, Paul.
It's intense.
We should talk about it.
Brother.
I put the work on them Reese's they're never the same.
So I was like a typewriter, but, um, typewriter and two bites and that's it.
So there's a legit, basically just say there's legitimately studied the kind of like self
hatred of feeling gay feelings is a real, is a real thing.
Yeah.
And I, and I guess much more prevalent than we ever think about, right?
That's the thing is that it's more, that's, that's what always blows my mind.
It's like, they keep putting out these studies like, Oh, 10% of the population.
Bullshit.
That's low.
That's right.
That's way, that's gotta be so fucking low.
That's low.
Right.
But that's not always been the statistic that we've always had the people.
If you just count the people that get on television and yell about how evil gay people are.
If that's more than 10% of the population right there.
I mean, if you involve yourself with theater for 10 minutes, you go, Oh yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Yeah.
This is cool.
But 10% no, I don't think so.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Service industry, Sean in the comments saying service industry.
Anywhere, anywhere.
That's the other thing.
It's not even just, it doesn't have to be theater.
It doesn't have to be services, any, any job you go, Oh wait, there's more than 10% here.
Okay.
Do the math, but we can't do the math because education has been completely systematically
defunded.
We have to bring people in from other countries to do the math.
We can't do that anymore either.
Nope.
God damn it.
They don't like us.
Oh, not only that, that is not allowing it.
No, I guess our shouting was creating a commotion in the neighborhood as, as I was trying not
to shout, but I raised my voice a few times, but both of course, but, but the one time
I was, the most I yelled was when I was going, I am trying to deescalate.
I'm trying to make this more chill.
I am not trying to be in your face.
I don't know how I would react if someone cursed at my children.
So it was really, I mean, I was drove home steaming.
I was really, really angry.
I wouldn't react well if I, if somebody told me that somebody cursed at your children.
Right.
Exactly.
Like if somebody was like, Hey, that guy just yelled at Matt's kids and be like, God damn
it.
And you have to like, uh, like, you know, it's a neighbor.
Right.
And we both been there for a long time.
And yeah, that's not going to change.
So you got to watch it because you don't want to just not, yeah, you don't want to be coming
home to do not call this.
Yep.
Do not call the registration car hotline.
Oh my God.
Right.
Can you imagine?
Yeah.
Oh, Myra in the chat wants to know, did your discussion get reported in the, in the nosy
neighbor board?
Oh, I, you know, I honestly have to go check cause I, I, I always end up, I click on one
thing and also they get like a thousand emails and after like a week, I'm like, wait, I want
to stop all these emails and I unsubscribe it is, it is the flow that we all go exactly.
So I have to go back, but uh, I mean, multiple neighbors were texting, but I'm yelling in
the first place.
And then obviously when I was screaming, but my wife came out and said, all right, basically
in the net, no, no, just loudly goes, all right, she, she goes, all right, you tried,
you tried to do the right thing and just said it nice to him and we just walked away or
whatever.
But, uh, it was, it was Sarah's just the best man.
Yes.
I was about to say, there are so many things that I can think of that I would rather have
happened to me than be the neighbor of Sarah Lowe and have her, have her mad at me.
Well, you know, she'll win.
Like she has the whole neighborhood wrapped around her finger.
Right.
Exactly.
No, I mean like she could probably sell his house, Leon in the chat, you tried the right
thing.
That was actually the only like comforting thing is he, he seems, he's always been very
intimidating from his truck, but when he actually got out and got in my face, I was like, Oh,
there's a reason why you stay in that truck, buddy with big old truck.
What do you know?
So you shouldn't try to give him a hug.
Look, I hate when you hug him.
I went further than I thought.
Yeah.
That was pretty far.
That was kissing ass.
That's pretty far.
I'll tell you who else tried to give their neighbor a mouth hug on his butt and that's
the following sponsor.
Today's show.
Man Manley's ice cream social is brought to you by Karen's cakes and cookies.
That's right.
From New Hampshire caveman in 2023.
That's Karen's cakes and cookies.
Hey, I don't know who made this, but it's not right.
It's just off something that's sugar, too much sugar in the mix or something, but the
icing is just a little bit runny or who knows the colors just a little bit off.
Hi, I'm Karen for Karen's cakes and cookies.
Every time you order, you're going to get something a little bit wrong.
It's not going to be quite right.
You're going to have to speak to the manager.
That's the Karen's cookies and cakes guarantee.
You will always have to speak directly to someone in charge to fix the shit you got
from your order.
It will never be right.
It will always have a mistake.
I promise you that or I'll talk about your fucking hair, bitch.
Get out of my store.
I can refuse you.
That's right.
Better a scoops of check out.
I just wanted cupcakes for my kid's birthday.
Well, you know what?
People wanted to not stare at that fucking bird's nest of a bullshit beehive you got
going on.
Get the fuck out.
I can have done the salon every week.
Whoa.
Oh, salon selectives.
Where are you going?
Is that salon deon?
Salon deon.
How is there not a salon deon in Las Vegas already?
I don't know.
Well, there is now.
I'm sure I've put it out there in the zeitgeist.
It'll happen.
Come on, people.
Hey, Matt.
Far across your hairline.
Okay, go ahead.
Oh my God.
There should be a salon deon.
Why is it not?
Oh, that's so perfect.
And follicles between us.
Yeah.
Salon deon.
Your extensions will go on.
Man.
Forget it.
Your extensions will go on.
It's right there.
That's all right there.
This is give me shit.
Right there.
Matt.
Yes, sir.
Speaking of your children.
Yes.
I have been watching Keeler in Pluribus.
I have been holding off because my wife watches like two episodes and I have a year.
Her year's resolution is to watch television again.
Like she has stopped watching.
So when you guys want to watch Pluribus, when you guys watch Pluribus, there will be moments
where you go, our son is starring as an angry, lonely lesbian, fighting a world plague.
It's pretty amazing.
I didn't think about it.
I didn't think about it until Paul said it.
We're two episodes into Pluribus.
And Paul is just correct.
I'm right.
I mean, I'm not out here to talk shit.
I'm not talking shit.
He's got a handsome lad.
He's got, he's got movie star looks clearly.
He is.
He is right now.
TV series looks.
He's currently, he is currently Bowie ask.
So I understand what you were saying about him.
Yes.
He's got the longish hair.
Yeah.
He's got this kind of thing going on something about the facial symmetry with this woman
in this movie.
When he was younger, he looked exactly like Charlie from Charlie and the chocolate factory.
Right.
Yes.
Really weird thing from the Willy Wonka, the chocolate factory from the old one, from
the Gene Wilder one.
Yeah.
Your son is absolutely Carol.
If you're watching pluribus and you don't know what Keeler looks like, yes, you do.
Yeah.
That's it.
Yes, you do.
That's exactly.
If my son can act half as good as Ray Seahorn, then we're in the money because Ray Seahorn's
absolutely amazing as an actor.
So no problem there.
No, no.
I am.
Where am I?
I finished up.
Oh, mayors of Kingstown.
Oh, good.
Probably the best season is the first season, season three and season two and three were
a little wonky, but season four was really good.
But it's still hilarious.
Like these shows, these Taylor Sheridan shows, like when you can commit mass murder and then
like just go eat afterward to be like, oh, now that that's over with, let's, let's chow
and talk about that some other time.
Because I was like the funniest thing to me, not like we should seek trauma counseling or
whatever.
But
I would love it if Taylor Sheridan shows just got really real, just really real.
I'm only one episode into the low down.
Have you guys been watching that at all?
No.
What's his name?
Ethan Hawke.
It was on.
It's on Hulu.
Okay.
Oh, my plumber's here.
All right.
Good.
I was only talking about TV show, so it should be, it should be hard to hand this off.
Okay.
All right.
Paul.
Yes.
Rating the rock vault closed last night.
Oh, you know, and it really broke my heart.
I saw all these postings from SJ and other folks because I follow a lot of rock vault
people and rock vault itself.
I did promotional work for them for a couple of years.
Got to see the show many times early, different iterations.
Then got to just see it as a fan to go see SJ a couple of times.
This is heartbreaking.
This is definitely a...
It's the end of an era.
It's a victim of where Vegas is right now with the decline in tourism.
And I think, you know, just shifting trends like always.
What's your take on it, Jacob?
I mean, I think it's part of that.
I think it's certainly part of that.
I think that has to do with it.
It's also, I mean, when we first moved here, all the shows at the big casinos here were
Broadway shows.
Right.
Yeah.
The first show I did out here was Spamalot.
And then the kind of new wave of shows came in and Absinthe was part of that new wave
of shows coming in back then.
And rock vault was as well.
Rock vault was part of that class.
Yes.
They were just a year or so after Absinthe.
I mean, they were real close.
And there aren't many of that class of shows left in town.
No.
Part of it is just the time.
I mean, it's so goddamn hard to run a show here, especially a show of any size where
you're trying to get hundreds of people in every night to come see it.
There's so much competition.
There's so much competition for people to spend entertainment money on here between
other shows, clubs, gambling, celebrity chefs, all these things.
But yeah, going and watching the end of rock vault in Las Vegas last night.
And they're supposed to go on tour.
They might do a little bit of touring here and there.
I know they're going to do some touring coming up.
I don't know just how long that's going to last.
But yeah, I mean, it's definitely the end of a crazy long thing.
Matt's back.
We're talking about rock vault closed in Las Vegas last night, Matt.
Oh yes, yes, yes.
End of an era.
It's heartbreaking too because losing that stratum of show, losing more of those kind
of shows, because for a long time in Las Vegas, shows and entertainment in general was considered
something of a loss leader.
It was a way to get people into your property.
You would just, you know, comp some people tickets, charge low fees to have folks come
and watch the show for a little bit.
And it just got foot traffic into your venue and then got people gambling.
That was the thing.
Now it was, you know, it was the, the building that you were in owned the show that you were
seeing in that bill.
Right.
And it was all, it was all part of the same ownership group that was doing everything.
Now everything's four walled, if that, and you're still being treated as a loss leader,
but you've got to try and make profit for yourself.
And it's just kind of the whole, the whole thing is backwards.
How did you know?
Because now instead of Sid Caesar sitting up in the, in the office at Caesar's palace,
I assume he owned Caesar's palace.
It was Sid Caesar.
Yes.
Yeah.
Instead of Sid sitting up there saying like, this is going to be here and this is going
to be here.
You know, he's just up there renting out rooms and like, Oh, you can come rent out my show
room and put on a show and you can pay me a lot of money per week to use my show room.
And I, I sure hope you sell tickets and you're able to make money and keep on paying me my
rent.
Right.
Because that's what I care about.
Good luck and God bless.
Yep.
They don't give a shit.
Uh, and, and that's, that's just more bullshit because it's just different.
I don't even look at that as a bad thing.
I just look at that as a different thing.
I look at it as a different setup.
The thing basically like, um, the problem is all these casinos that are still operating
are holding on by a threat right now.
Yes.
No, that's it.
And so like, there's no place to innovate or invest.
And so they're all just saving their own asses.
And so like basically innovation part, I think we're, I think we're hurting from the lack
of innovation now.
Someone new needs to see an opportunity in this space, specifically in Las Vegas strip
to come in and do something crazy.
The last person I tried was resorts world, which their big innovation was three hotels
or one hotel Voltron Voltron was their plan.
Remember the original plans for their resorts world.
Remember they had a Panda habitat.
They are going to have a stadium.
They were going to have all this stuff and then all of a sudden when Bush came to shove,
it was just three hotels.
Yeah.
And, and so like it's going to take like a big sweeping thing from an order of magnitude,
but basically these companies have all found a way to not go away.
Like normally some of these companies would have shuttered in the past, which would have
let someone else come in and dig over a big exception is what's happening at the hard
rock, uh, which Jacob point out before the show came on where they're building a giant
electric guitar tower.
That's going to change the look of the strip or whatever.
That's that's a different, totally different casino company than the ones that have come
in in the past.
That's the, um, seminal, right?
The seminal, the seminal tribe, I believe.
Yeah.
They own the hard rock, but even they like they're doing something like what they're doing.
It's the old Mirage.
It used to be the MGM Mirage and they tore down the volcano and everything in the, in
the front of it.
And they're building a giant guitar shaped, uh, tower of a hotel suites there in the,
in the front.
And then they're going to revamp the Mirage towers as well and make that part of the hard
rock and, uh, for people who don't know.
But the guitar, even that's not even exactly innovation.
That's something new in Vegas, but they're just copying something that they've already
done in Miami.
Right.
They also had a big ass guitar in Vegas a couple of years ago.
It wasn't as big, but they had, that was a big one in front of the old hard rock, uh,
casino.
This is a, yeah.
Yeah.
This is a building.
No, I know.
It's a, it's a mega structure at this point.
Yeah.
This is like, that was a big guitar set up in front of a building.
This is an actual building.
Yeah.
It's pretty crazy.
It's shaped like a guitar.
Yeah.
Anyways.
But rock rock fault is closing up, which is such a shame.
I just went saw disco last night.
Disco is closing this weekend.
Um, and, uh, but these are shows that, these are shows that would have worked in the past
where people are coming here going like, what should I do?
What's around, you know?
And, uh, it's just not, it's just not the way Vegas operates anymore.
So in the short term, it would help is, uh, right.
Maybe if foreigners didn't hate coming here, that would help a lot.
Yeah.
That might be a plus.
And I think they said, uh, November was the, uh, the biggest decline in air travel to Las
Vegas since they started, uh, keep checking those numbers.
Yeah.
No.
That's rough.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
And the big picture thing is just a matter of it.
Like we have, uh, we, with the sphere of the radar stadium, we have F one ourselves all
the time.
It was basically like when, when, when the whole, uh, when the whole town is taken up
by one event that really hurts these side endeavors, because now it's whether the crowd
that's going to that one event also likes this.
So does everyone going to see the wizard of Oz also want to see rock vault?
I don't know.
So then it's not that weekend that weekends out for rock vault, right?
Like it's just a, it's just a weird thing.
Uh, and I guess we also just say that we also are speaking from entertainers perspectives.
Like we're, we're, we're pro entertainment.
Of course.
Um, because like, uh, uh, Leon brings up Macau and Macau has never been an entertainment
space.
It's always just been a gambling space that shows the shows, the shows in McAlvin of Torsi
done terribly.
Um, even way back in the Dragoon's company, they, they had a show over there for a long
time that was spectacular.
I mean, they, they had a, uh, I forget what the name of the show was, but it was, it was
such a great show.
I knew a lot of people in it, uh, just, just hella talented people over there.
And boy, they just could not, they couldn't pay people to come watch that show.
And it was like a, a job, it was basically a giant Cirque du Soleil show.
Uh, it was super impressive and they just couldn't get butts in the seats.
No, and it'd be more gambling beyond that.
Yeah.
Beyond that, it was, uh, even the restaurants were doing well.
Uh, it was the food court, the food, if you were, if you opened up a spot in the food
court, you're making money hand over fist because that's what the gamblers could go
there quickly, get food and come back or have some of the food court, bring the tape, bring
it over to their, uh, bring it over to the table and eat at the table, get the food runners
going.
Yeah.
Uh, which is still, it's a little different than, than here, but we'll see.
I mean, the truth is that like, um, uh, tourism is down all over the place, you know, and
that's because people below a certain class are experiencing a recession.
People above a certain class are, are not, and, um, and so it's, it's a, it's a weird
time.
Uh, it's a great time for the rich to get richer, which is like, thank God, cause I'm
really as a, as a low end podcast, I'm ready to make a move, you know, but, um, I gotta
shift these $10 around.
Oh, this is a good time to bring up our scientific study.
Give each of us a billion dollars and we're going to see if we can do better.
I knew better than the current billionaires.
I think we really, really could.
I really, I really believe in me.
I think we could do it.
I, I'm, I'm very optimistic about us.
I've, I've, uh, uh, you know, it's funny is like, uh, what comes to like something does
come to mind for me when I, when I do hear that, uh, basically Tony Shade's vision for
all the downtown motels, uh, you know, that's all going away, right?
They're about to demolish all those motels, but I really think there's a way to revitalize
like a small downtown motel areas to do like really cool, distinct things with each motel
to make it much more of like a kitschy place to come visit bar crawl and like, and spend
some time and be away from resort fees and things like that.
Um, but, um, so there you go.
So that's plan a for my billion dollars is, uh, is, uh, pick up Tony Shade.
We're Tony Shade left off with the downtown motel.
Be a hotelier.
Yeah.
I think it'd be fun.
I think so.
Uh, you know, who else I think would be fun to, uh, have them die and then take over their
dream.
Yes.
And that would be the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by a compilation narrated by Jeffrey Jones.
If it's okay, if this is too dark to air, but it's a long shot.
Wait.
Oh, sorry.
I don't know if I understand this joke.
I don't get it.
I do.
Is this too dark to do?
Well, Bob crane was the star of Hogan's heroes and infamously a porn fanatic and made his
own porn.
And uh, Jeffrey Jones is the principal from Ferris Bueller and the dad from Beetlejuice.
Oh, okay.
Been outed as a nefarious, uh, child.
Yeah.
And bad guy.
Uh, they won't move along.
So yeah, we'll, we'll, I mean, it's a funny idea.
Yeah.
I don't know that I can execute it eloquently enough to make it funny and not.
That's it.
It's, it's, it's, it's all right.
Hey, scoops at checkout.
Fair.
Today's show is brought to you by PTSD is Barnum and Bailey's all veteran circus equally
dark.
What was that?
It's the circus.
It's here.
Stay very quiet.
Don't get out of the ring.
Never get out of the ring.
Barnum and Bailey's PTSD circus is here to entertain you quietly.
We guarantee no explosions, no animals.
Nothing exciting or scary will happen in the PTSD circus.
It's just clowns with no face paint falling.
That's it.
They just fall.
They just walk out onto the stage, fall down and they get, they get back up and they say,
speak.
They say, Hey, I'm okay.
So you remember when you lost that good friend in Da Nang, he went down.
He never got back up.
These clowns, they're going to stand up again and they're going to look you in the face
and say, Hey, I'm all right.
It's okay.
We can go home together.
No, no, that's too much.
That's too much.
Letting people off.
Calm it down.
Never leave the ring.
Never get out of the ring.
That's pretty dark, but not as dark.
I don't know.
Maybe not as dark.
I don't have PTSD from war.
Thank God.
It or hate scoops of checkout.
I guess.
Let's do a little Scoop Mail.
Physical Scoop Mail.
Zip-a-dee-doo.
We got mail in a box.
I love it.
We love it.
We got mail in a box.
Zip-a-dee-doo, we got mail in a box.
I love it.
We love it.
We got all our holiday cards here.
Happy New Year, everybody.
Message for you, son.
Oh, oh.
While we're in Scoop Mail, shout out to Craig Ruth, who just went up to the, went from the
low tier to the $20 tier for the year on Patreon.
Oh, awesome.
Hell yeah, Craig.
Thank you so much, Craig.
Thank you, brother.
Yeah.
Thank you, Craig.
We got one here from the Mass Hole Scoop, Happiest Holidays.
We love getting the card from the Mass Hole Scoop there.
These are great.
I love getting these.
The Maynards.
We got a great-looking family here, Season's Greetings.
We got a dog with possibly a Hawaiian lei or something like that around its neck.
I like it.
Whatever it is.
That's adorable.
I'm a fan of it.
That's from Frozen Cusser.
Let's see here.
Merry crisposh to you and the guys in the churn and to your families, oh yeah.
Thank you.
So nice.
This is from, oh, that's from the Maple Raisin Scoop.
Very nice.
Let me see if I can get it on the camera.
There we go.
Kinda.
Good.
We did.
We got a lot of crisposh cards this year.
We got, oh, I like this one.
Peas on Earth.
It's caroling peas.
Cute.
Very nice.
Oh, that's from Tess, the Slightly Slutty Scoop.
Sitting you and yours, the very best for the holiday season, thanks for all you do for
this amazing community, wishing you a merry crisposh.
Thank you, Tess.
What were you saying, Matt?
Oh, just a lot of iron content in that, in the peas chorus, a lot of good iron.
Oh, yes.
Peas chorus hot, peas chorus cold, peas standing on your doorstep singing songs of old.
We got one here from the Nielsen family.
Love that.
Very cute.
Matt and Jacob Paul got his on his own.
We wish you a sweltering and sweaty quick crisposh.
We do have that.
May the new year be lucrative and sexy like your wives fucking you in the face.
That's the Nielsen's.
Hell yeah.
And their pets.
Well, we got a great one from LAJ, from the big twisty road in San Francisco.
Thanks LAJ.
That's a cool looking print, man.
All the best for 2026.
Hope you're doing good, LAJ.
Yes.
Let's see, we got one here.
There is a Snow Bucks coffee and let's see, we got a snowman has ordered a hot coffee
and he is back at the counter wanting to exchange it for an iced coffee because it has melted
the front of his face completely off.
Wishing you the best holiday season, merry crisposh.
Wait, maybe despite being T DeVore, have we not been saying your name?
I don't know.
You also didn't put your name in this card.
You said, I haven't been saying your name as a Patreon member, but then you didn't sign
your name in the card.
So I'm looking at the return address, T DeVore.
If we haven't been saying your name, maybe it's because you haven't given me your name.
That's Travis.
Oh, Travis.
Have we not been saying your name?
Well, let's make sure we get that.
I got to look at the list here.
Travis, we're sorry.
How is that possible?
We have a list that downloads from the site.
I don't know.
It's annoying.
I'm going to tell all the listeners right now.
All you Patreon supporters out there and anybody that's ever been a Patreon supporter of us
and anyone that ever might be a Patreon supporter of us, when you tell us something is wrong
with Patreon, 85% of the time, we are as confused as you are.
15% of the time, we fucked it up, but 85% of the time, we are just confused.
Yeah.
I was doing the newsletter again, and that newsletter format is bunk.
It's bunkaroo, but I have to use it to include enough images.
I don't know.
It's weird.
Right.
This stuff is not at all conducive to anything, but Travis, thank you for the card, and we'll
try and make sure we get you on the list.
We got this one.
This is a great one here.
Much love to you and everything you do.
Luke, Angie, Pierce, and Frank.
It is a great, a great Chris Bosh card.
Their card.
There.
I got one of their cards too.
That was an amazing Christmas Chris Bosh card this year from them.
The Andersons.
I love the Andersons.
They sent us a great Chris Bosh card as well.
And the Drabillises.
We got one from the Drabillises, so Amy and Carl and kids.
And they got them next to the Dippin' Dots on the back, right?
Oh yeah.
They're standing next to the Dippin' Dots stand.
Yeah, I love that.
Jake, did you talk about how SJ is playing New Year's Eve tonight over at the Virgin?
I haven't yet.
Yeah, she's over at the, well she's at Jason Aldean's bar at the City Center first.
And then the Spice wannabe show, the Spice Girls show, they are playing at the Hard Rock
on the Strip tonight.
That's pretty impressive.
Oh yeah.
That's a big deal.
Yeah, they're booked there.
I think I'm going to run over and see at least the second half of the show.
I think it's going to be great.
That's going to be a good get.
It's going to be a big, big get.
Yeah, I think so.
They've got a lot of tour dates and everything this year.
I think they've got some new dates coming up here.
It's going to be good.
It's a great show.
It is.
They work super hard on it.
Let's do a little jock versus a nerd.
I always say Amy and Carl's last name wrong, Rory is fussing at me in the chat about saying
their last name wrong.
I always say her wrong.
Explosion of people saying last names wrong.
Well, part of it is I hear it said.
It's one of these things.
I hear the name said and I can say it.
But then when I see it written out, it fucks me up again.
I can't see it written out and say it.
Yes.
Anyway, we've got a scooper coming to us today from lemur screamer creamer.
The categories are animals in camo sounds the same mommy and milk dance with the cane.
The categories dance.
Yeah.
Categories dance.
Matt, you're up first.
What you want animals in camo animals in camo for 400.
The jackpot reached a million dollars.
What animals and animals in camo again, there's an animal in here.
Oh, I see.
Oh, this has become like a real gentleman's created a monster here.
I see it.
I found it.
It's just in one word.
Okay, doll doll jack, the infamous doll.
Don't go near the doll enclosure.
It'll bite your fucking face off.
Actually I've worked in the doll enclosure at the haunted museum.
What can I say?
That's what happened to Paul's face.
That's what happened.
Peggy got me.
Oh, lion.
There it is lion and a million lion, lion, a million.
You lie.
I'll do sounds the same for 400, a bucket lacking color.
Oh, I, a pale, a pale.
It sounds the same.
Yeah.
Paul, I will go with, sounds the same for eight, please.
All right.
A type of tree and by the seashore.
A type of tree by the seashore.
Oh, a beach, beach tree, beach nut, beach tree.
Yeah, absolutely.
I did not know that a beach tree and a ocean beach were not spelled the same.
I'm just learning that right now.
Only way I know it is because of all the baby food that beach nut, B-E-E-C-H.
Oh, Paul loves his baby food.
Yeah.
I mean, I just unload fuck tons of it every week, that's all.
I see it going through.
Put it right into a package for Jeffrey Jones and then mail it off.
Oh, Rose, Rose, Matt, you're up.
Dude, sounds the same for 1200, I would probably be doing a lot better if I was eating just
baby food, daily double, a corridor or to drag card cargo hallway, all the way.
Oh, a hall.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, hall and hall.
That's what Darryl Oates fears the most dueling holes and what is the status of their lawsuit?
They were in a nasty lawsuit for.
They are still very acrimonious.
They still hate each other.
The one guy bit the other guy, no, no, allegedly, no, uh, Hall is just like, Hall is just like,
I just want to be Darryl Hall and Oates is, but, but me, but you need the Oates.
Oh, the lawsuit ended in August of 2025, Darryl Hall voluntarily dismissed his legal action
against John Oates following private arbitration that resolved their disputes over Oates attempts
to shell, to share or to sell his share.
That's their greatest hits album.
It's called private arbitration.
Yeah.
So apparently Hall dismissed the lawsuit against Oates.
Private arbitration is how we settle our differences, me and Darryl Hall get along again.
Private arbitration.
Yup.
Clap, clap.
I'm still mad at them for writing man eaters.
So I don't care.
Uh, I'll try.
Sounds the same for 200, 2000.
Writing man eater.
I'm still mad at them about man eater.
So, uh, fuck them.
Permitted or in a whisper.
In a whisper.
Don't you know talking about a revolution permitted in a whisper.
I'm not trying to give you a hint, Jacob.
I'm just doing a Tracy Chapman reference.
No, no, no.
I caught that.
You weren't helping there, uh, permitted or in a whisper.
Is this allowed?
That's what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
But in a, in a whisper is confusing on.
But I mean, it's, it's, you know, instead of, yeah, instead of silently.
I guess so.
I guess.
Yeah.
I'll try that.
Allowed and allowed.
Yeah.
There we go.
There it is.
In a whisper.
Uh, Paul.
He is a Wafartian.
Uh, I'll do mommy for 400.
Daily double.
Mommy.
The Catholic nun won the Nobel peace prize in 1979, Mother Teresa, Mother Teresa.
That's right.
Mommy.
Matt.
You're up.
Um, I'll do, uh, what an undeserving bitch.
800.
She's a total shit.
Bracelets were handed out at the carnival.
The prize bracelets were handed out at the carnival.
Zebra.
It is zebra.
Yeah.
Zebra.
It's me.
I'll try.
Man.
You guys are so much better at that animal one than I am.
I'm going to try milk for 400.
Milk.
Pecorano Romano cheese comes from this animal.
Is it not a cow?
It's a mouse.
Probably not.
Is it a goat cheese?
The tit milk of mouse.
Pecorano Romano.
Pecorino.
Maybe it's a sheep.
Could be.
Uh, or is this one of those, uh, like you, you get a cheese from the, uh, from all the
lady bacterias that are down in the lady bits.
It's, uh, it's Pecorino Romano from under cheese.
Is it from under cheese, lady bit cheese from under cheese.
That's why I don't eat that Pecorino Romano.
Uh, I guess I'll pass.
Paul.
Hey, uh, give me some of that from under.
Um, I'll have a smear of that on my bagel, please.
Oh, here you go, Pecorino.
Oh, my brother is huge and wants to fuck my wife.
Um, I pass.
Uh, Matt.
Pass.
It's sheep.
It's a sheep cheese.
Sheep.
Sheep shenanigans.
Um, I'll go on with mommy, please.
Mommy, this board where electronics are mounted.
That's a motherboard.
That's a motherboard right there.
Get down on it.
I want to do animals and camo for 2000.
The simple mural brightened the whole space.
Lemur.
Yeah.
Wow.
Nice.
Good job.
That's me.
I'll try.
Um, I don't know.
Fuck that animals and camo bullshit.
Mommy.
1200.
Uh, however the fuck you say her first name, Daenerys Targaryen.
Yeah.
And I believe that is the mother of dragons.
Mother of dragons.
Yeah.
Mother.
Are you the mother of the dragons, girl?
Do you want to take over?
Oh, mother.
Father.
Uh, mommy, please.
Do you want to see dragons tonight?
Chris Jenner.
She is the mother of the Kardashians.
Also known as the hell mouth beast Satan herself.
The momager.
Oh, the momager, the momager, she's the manager and mom.
Yeah.
I'm glad I don't know that as much Kardashian shit as I've seen, fucker.
Well, then I don't feel bad about you getting there.
No, no, no.
She's trash.
Matt, you're up.
They're all trash.
Uh, see, I like animals and camo because you have to know stuff, just to see stuff.
Right.
Yeah.
Animals and camo for 1200.
The hijack almost succeeded.
Oh, wow.
It's a Jackalmo.
All right.
Big talk about animals and camo.
I'm a second ago.
Jackalmo.
It's me.
I'm in second with 3600.
Paul is in third with 400.
There are no daily doubles left.
There are three questions left and they're all about milk.
Mm, mm, milk.
Oh, let's see.
I have 2000 points and behind Matt, I guess I'll take milk for 2000.
What animal produces the most expensive milk in the world?
Cats.
Your mom.
By ounce?
My guess?
I like that I have a clarifying question to a question I have no idea.
Sure.
But let's measure it by ounce.
I'm fine with that.
Let's see.
Whale.
Someone wrote in the chat, human, which is like, buddy, go on Craigslist, I'll tell you
right now.
Human milk is not--
You're overpaying for your human milk.
Not that expensive.
But is it more expensive than other mammals?
I don't know.
Like whale, whale milk, don't platypuses, don't they have a nipple?
Don't they do milk?
They cut themselves as a very expensive milk.
Are they a mono-tream?
They're a mono-tream.
They are.
And they do produce milk.
Right.
I'll guess platypus.
All right.
A donkey.
Boy, that's one of those questions is that if you just don't know it, you just don't
know it.
Paul, you're up.
Who's donkey milk for?
Where's donkey milk popular?
Dan's the reason-- it's more commonly known as asqueezins.
And that's why you didn't recognize it.
Asqueezins are real--
Bam-a-lam.
I see.
Whoa, asqueezins.
Bam-a-lam.
I see.
He hauled that milk.
Bam-a-lam.
I'll go--
With smoothies and silk.
Bam-a-lam.
Ooh.
Asqueezins.
Donkey milk.
I'll go with milk for $1,200, please.
This animal's milk is popular in the Middle East and very salty.
Gotta be camel.
Gotta be camel milk, right?
Camel milk.
Yeah.
Camel milk tea.
Camel milk.
Camel.
And Matt, close it out the category and the game.
He's got the win.
Madden is at least, Madden is leading, milk for $800.
The fattiest milk overall is from this animal.
Oh, so there's an animal hidden in this clue, right?
No, I think this one is the--
I think this is--
No, this is--
This is just milk.
It's just a question.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm just used to hunting for animals in the--
The blue whale?
I think this could be the blue whale.
The fattiest milk overall is from this animal.
Your mom, that ugly bitch, final answer.
There you go.
Pass.
Paul.
No, sorry, me.
Fattiest milk overall from this animal, elephants, seal, the hooded seal.
I have fat in my milk all day long.
That's the game.
Matt wins with $5,600.
Paul is in second with $1,600.
I'm in third with $800.
That's from lemur, screamer, creamer.
Gosh.
Thank you so much lemur, screamer, creamer.
If you want to--
Milk's a real blind spot in our household, huh?
It really is.
Yeah.
If you want to send us in a scooper to your price of sprite jock versus nerd or an obelisk
jock versus nerd, Hayscoops.com is where you can go.
Head over to Hayscoops.com right there on the homepage.
Make us a jock versus nerd, send us in some scoop mail, do all the things right over there
at Hayscoops.com.
Do it now.
Do it.
Thank you so much.
Hey, this is not my time where we thank our latest people on air.
Did you send us a list, Jacob?
Right?
No, we--
I just sent it to you.
It's not a new month.
It's an old month.
It's still December when we're recording.
So we have people to thank here.
And all these people know that well milk is actually quite trim.
That's Matt McKenzie, Melissa Arachiga, Michael, Michael Martin, Michael Shaw, Michelle Yiser,
Mike Six, Mohan Nair, Manan Noxcoop, Monica Day, Nathan Clay, Paul Hoserscoop Luxton, Peter
Bougie, Peter Hines, Peter Sansone, Phil Rendley, Ralph Barrett, Randy, Randy Glenn, Richard
Dunn, Richard Fastot, Richard Hill, and his name is Robert Paulson.
These people will not be nice to your kids even if you kiss their ass.
Signature Curl Scoop, We All Scream 4, Mark McLean, Alice Scoop 6, Alice Scoop 6666, Corny
Scoop, Cup-A-Scoop, Dr. Science Scoop, Duke Scoop, Gizmo Scoop, Holly Marshmallow Go Lightly,
I Don't Have a Scoop name, Ice Cream Manwich, Kimchi Douche Scoop, King Scoop, Marble Tulip
Scoopy Tree, Miss Johnny Australia, Neck Pubes, Proper Scoop, Proto Scoop, Raggedy Girl, Scoopa
Troopa, Scoopia Lauren, Scoopy J.D., Scoop J.D., Scoopy and the Beast, and Silicon Scoop.
I like Scoopy J.D.
And then the following people here, I have more to say here.
These people all would physically kiss the ass of a stranger to help all mankind.
Whoa.
Ryre Appledorn, Second Mangle, Scoop Lindsay, Scoop Neck Paddywhack, Scoop Ramone, Scoop
Ashlock, Scoop Ashlock, Scoop Muldering, nope that's Scott Muldering, Scott Schoedfeld,
John Kellner, Sound Man Scoop, Steven Clively, Steven Landon, Stewart Wilson, Strange Uncle's
Podcast, Temporary Reality Pierce, Timothy Sutton, Tom Mancreddy, Travis Murray, Tristan
Guevara, Tyler Bartlett, Tyler Scoop McDuck, Warren Bro, Wendy Bumgardner, Wes Culligan,
Will Kellner, William McDonald, and Neil Fleish.
The following people saw the final performance of Rating the Rock Vault, Long Live Rating
the Rock Vault, Silverfist Scoop, Scally Wall Scoop, Turn the Page, The Damsels of Dorkington,
The Devil's Lettuce Scoop, The Going Over Our Friends Podcast, The Ice Cream Headache,
The Ice Cream Headache Again, The SCOOP, What Was Like Scoop, Angry Face Scoop, Ben Smith,
Bob, Brad Martin, Brian McLeod, C. Wick, Charles Jachecky, Chris Jorg, Chris K, Chris
Meloncon, Christine Starr, Christopher Huff, Chronicler Scoop, Clayton Shoney, Clown in
a Brothel, Colleen Fisher, and Craig De Farmer.
And the following scoops all have a healthy fear of Sarah Lowe being angry with them.
That's Chris Mayer, Dan Martin, Daniel Mattis-Ferrer, Doug Lay, Ed Underarms, Marcus, I don't know
what all that says, Edward Bender, Aliza Walczak, Flat Kidney, Guy Wade, Ian Soto, Jamison Fisher,
Jason Victor, Jay Shapiro, Jed Taxon, Jeff Faust, John Lord, John Holshan, Justin Robert
Young, Kay Mathis, Lee Forrest, Mark Cohen, Mark Gates, Mark Wilson, Mike Federley, Nathan
Hooten, Nicholas Petty, Nicole Busenbach, Nicole Levin, Peter Burford, Philip Guyton,
pick it up, pick it up, pick it up, Ron Heck, Rose, Ryan Howard, Sam Reed, Scott A, Scott
Andrews, Scott Heddington, SF, Sean, Stacey Coleman, Steets Magrits, SuperGeek13579, Tamira
Hamilton, Troy Anthony Tanzer, Udo Gearhards, Uncle Don's Woodshop, Wendy Cooper, and Natalie
McGillatine.
Natalie McGillatine!
I like you a lot!
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air or get all kinds of different rewards that we offer,
head on over to PreachingFun.com and look at the tier that fits your budget today.
Or if you, like me, were a little upset that Howard Leese wasn't wearing his enormous knife
on his hip for the last show of Rock Vault, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com takes you over to our Patreon page where for
as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon supporters, so you are really helping keep this show truckin'.
If you like this show, if you think it's good, head over to PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz.
Like I say, for as little as $3 a month, and you can do it yearly if you want to do that,
you can do your whole support for the year, you don't have to do it monthly if you don't
want to, and you get a bit of a discount if you want to do it for the year, if you want
to sign up for all of 26, you can do that.
You can do it month by month, that is perfectly fine.
And you can give gifts, you can give the gift of a Patreon subscription to someone that you
either love or hate, depending on how you think they will like this show.
You can give them the gift of us for all of 2026.
That's right.
All right.
Well, thanks for this, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
Happy New Year, everybody.
Happy New Year.
We need to go over our big resolutions.
This is a big deal.
Oh, yeah.
Any quick ones?
Resolution speed around.
Spanish.
Oh, 1080p.
Eat better after 10 p.m.
I'm clearly going to have the highest resolution.
I think so.
1080p is pretty high.
It is pretty high.
It's pretty high.
None of us wants.
None of us want to see us in 4K.
No, no, no.
That's why I didn't go there.
Who's watching movies for nose hairs?
I mean, come on.
We are not made for high def.
What are we doing?
Pop the box.
Every time I see like, you know, they take the old footage and upgrade it and make it
all high def and everything.
I'm like, oh, you were, you were just hurting these performers who never thought they would
be seeing this clearly.
There is something to that 30 FPS.
Great.
Film quality that makes it so much more theatrical, like fairy tale, dreamlike, it removes it
from reality.
It looks like a movie and I mean, maybe it's what was raised on, but it looks like a movie.
When I see that smoothing and all that shit, I'm just like, get that the fuck out.
I'm watching the neutron.
I just get, I just get so hard to see all that smoothed out skin.
Half of it.
So hard.
But half of the neutron looks like a goddamn soap opera set.
I'm like, what the fuck?
Why would you do this to your billion dollar show?
I don't love you everybody.