Oh, it's all just great, and everything's taking along just fine. There are no problems anywhere.
Here we go!
Oh, hello there! I am so glad you're here. I would love to thank the ice cream truck
drivers right now. Thank your ice cream truck drivers. Who are the ice cream truck drivers,
you ask? Well, these are the people that deliver that frickin' ice cream straight to your frickin'
face. Right now I'd like to thank Bearded Scoop 3, Blue Line Scoop, Christine Elsesser,
Christie Salinas, Darren Cunningham, Darth Scooper, David Walker, Ted Laszlo, and Dirty
Old Scoop. If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head
over to PreachingFun.com. PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice
cream truck driver, and who knows? The life you saved may be your own.
Yeah, I cut that off a little too early. Sorry, here's the show.
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Oh, I've got a big problem.
What's that?
I have a Sam's Club membership, and that's always been the closest big-box store to my
house, but now a Costco is opening up.
Oh, whatever.
And they're almost equidistant.
Selfie choice.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social. Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt
Donnelly. Sitting in Pittsburgh, PA, that's Paul Mattingly. Sitting in Las Vegas, it's
me, Jacob the Audio Guy. We're PreachingFun.
Speaking of Selfie's choice, I went and saw Fantastic Four.
Right? This is something I want to talk about. Marvel film fatigue is fully setting in.
Is Fantastic Four Marvel? I guess it is. They're original Marvel.
The first family of the Marvel Universe. King Kirby's grand creation. Jiminy jumped up
Christmas. Oh, Lord.
Boy, for somebody that was really upset about the Fantastic Four a minute ago, you are very
defensive of their origins.
I'm not upset about it. I didn't see the movie yet. Although, well, we'll see.
Go ahead, Matt.
I was upset I texted you guys in the middle of the movie.
I know you were really upset. This was hurting your soul.
Paul and I got a text message from Matt in mid-film.
So, you took your kids to go see Fantastic Four.
Yes. I was a group of two other parents and a total of six children went to see Fantastic
Four together. Summer blockbuster. Time to get out in the theaters and enjoy ourselves.
First scene is a pregnancy test. Just her just hanging over a pregnancy test. And I was
like, oh, no, I really don't want this to be about a baby.
Oh, you're in luck, I guess.
And then, it's like straight up with like all of the, like as if they made it for parents,
like as if the kids were maybe secondary to the summer blockbuster thing. They thought
maybe a lot of parents, a lot of moms would come out and want to see scenes about like
losing sleep and like who's going to take care of the baby and all this other stuff.
And is he normal? And let's look at the scans. And I was like, who is this for?
Jesus.
Who is this for? And then, they're like, uh-oh, Galacticus, we got to go talk to that guy.
Let's get the pregnant lady into the spaceship and get her out in outer space. Let's make
sure that she's leaving the planet.
This seems like a good job for the pregnant lady.
To visit a planet eating being and see if he wants to just talk to a pregnant lady.
What? Like why? What are you doing? They're talking about how they struggle to get pregnant.
All the things that like bring back all the, like, you know, as my friend Matt told me
when your first year of pregnancy, your first year of the kids on Earth, it's, he called
it baby-nam. You're in baby-nam.
Right.
So, you want to be reminded of like the time you basically went crazy and lost sight of
everything that was happening in the world for a year. Let's make sure we get that nostalgic
back in here.
Right, good.
And then, and then Galactus wants that baby.
Oh.
That's, that's the deal. He won't eat Earth.
Wait, wait.
He won't eat Earth.
So out of all of the, out of all the babies that could have been shot up into outer space
to talk to Galactus, we happen to shoot up the right one?
Yeah, because he's the child of two superheroes. So he's special.
Wow. That is lucky for us.
Well, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll.
So I assume they just sacrifice the baby and Galactus goes away and everything is fine
from then on.
I'll step in as a...
Because the good of the many outweighs.
As a comic book nerd again, I have not seen the film, but I...
If it's fucking canon, it'll give a shit. If it's fucking from the original author,
if the fucking genius from Marvel's Cradle was like, "No, this is sacred script. I don't
give a fuck. I brought my kids to a summer blockbuster and watched them watch two hours
of whether we should or shouldn't sacrifice a baby."
Yeah. No, I think that's a stupid move.
Now, the only, my only defense, and this is a very weak defense, but in many incarnations...
What do you think, Marvel? Should we sacrifice this baby?
In many incarnations...
I don't know.
Franklin, the baby, they did call him Franklin, right?
Yes. Yeah.
Okay, great. At least they stuck to that. Franklin Richards does become a super genius,
capable of manipulating multiverses. So there is something of the, of a, you know, he's,
he's a keystone character, or you know what I mean?
I understand, but you know what? This is the same argument when fucking, we spent all of
Black Widow setting up the fucking Cannonball family. What are they called?
That's it, Cannonball family.
With Red, Red Tornado or whatever his name is?
No, no, the movie that just came out. Well, the other movie that just came out.
The Thunderbolts.
Thunderbolts. So I went to see, I want to see Scarlett Johansson kick ass as Black Widow,
and they spent half that movie setting up the Thunderbolts movie, a movie that wouldn't
come out for another three years, so thanks for the prequel, and then, great.
Well, I keep in mind too, when they first made the movie, because remember they held
the movie, they held Black Widow for a year, so when they made it, it wouldn't have come
out for four years.
So it's like, well, I don't, I don't need to keep this like encyclopedic, like checklist
of like, oh good, when I'm watching a film, like if it pays off, great, if it has a building
up, great, great.
When the Robert Downey Jr. first Iron Man came out, you didn't sit on your hands during
the movie going like, yes, but what are they going to do with vision?
Okay, here's a, play music or something, Jamie, here's a big spoiler, so play music
or something.
Oh, okay, we got a big spoiler coming up here.
Those in the chat who don't want to be spoiled, avert your ears.
Yeah, yeah, so I'm going to play a little music by the time the music ends, fast forward
until you don't hear the music anymore.
When I go like this again, you can come back on if you don't want spoilers.
There you go, all right, spoilers.
They show her fucking dead for like two minutes, Sue Storm, like dead on the ground.
Oh, the invisible girl?
Fucking dead, like on the ground, fucking Pedro Pascal weeping over her dead fucking
body, like true fucking death scenes, and then finally bring the baby around so that
the baby can start showing his powers for the first time.
That's like punching someone in the face and saying, just kidding, like you can't, like
you made a bunch of children look at a dead woman on the ground for two minutes.
Like, fuck off.
It sounds like the first Pokemon movie, honestly.
Oh, the Pokemon movie had lots of dead women in it, but that is canon.
Do you remember the first Pokemon movie?
Did you ever see the first Pokemon movie?
Oh, yeah, yeah, no, I watched the first Pokemon movie again last night.
I'm not talking to you, Jacob.
I know you never saw the first Pokemon movie.
No, I rewatched it again last night.
It was great.
I loved it.
All of the dead women, it doesn't bother me.
The dead women in the Pokemon movie does not concern me at all.
Matt, you probably missed the first Pokemon movie, too, because that was a little bit
after the boys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We did not get into it.
They collect the cards, but they're not really into any of the ...
So, spoiler for the 20-plus-year-old Pokemon movie.
Yeah.
Ash dies.
What?
He dies.
And then the Pokemon start crying, and their magical tears bring him back to life.
So, it sounds like they just ripped off the Pokemon movie from 20 years ago.
Yes.
Look, I guess we can say thumbs up to rejoin, because we'll talk about it more vaguely or
whatever.
Yeah.
But ...
Oh, scoopernova girl says that he dies in every movie.
Ash knows he doesn't die in every movie.
Does the mate ...
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
No, I mean, there are more dead parents in Disney's canon than there is in every horror
movie franchise.
Disney loves killing fucking moms and dads.
They do.
The canon is how they get rid of the bodies.
They put the bodies in the canon, and then they get rid of the bodies.
And the circus ripped that off, so who's ripping off who?
And the truth is, my kids didn't give a shit.
They just liked watching Fantastic Four.
R-Tax.
Winner scoop, fucking R-Tax.
Yeah.
It is R-Tax.
It is R-Tax time.
My kids didn't give a shit.
They watched the movie.
They were fine.
Yeah.
Or whatever.
Did they like it?
They did like it.
They did not love it.
Okay.
Right.
I will tell you that it was the second movie we saw over the weekend.
Oh.
And the first movie we saw was Naked Gun.
Ah.
How did that go?
I bet they liked Naked Gun.
They loved Naked Gun.
Yeah.
They were just crying out loud laughing.
And this is why it's so funny that we're so cool with violence and so anti-anything that
might whiff of sex, you know?
Yeah.
Right.
I would take my kids to Naked Gun again tomorrow.
They were laughing so hard.
Yeah.
First of all, Pamela Anderson's really good at it, which is something I was not expecting.
Like I expected her to be fine.
Oh, yeah.
I heard she's great.
She's like really funny in it, which I've never seen her be in other things.
I didn't see it.
It certainly seems that as she's getting older, she is accepting more and more, just like,
"I can just be funny.
This is great."
I do think it's a thing about character.
I think as she got older, she's no longer this bombshell, so she's allowed to say things
differently and feel things differently.
Yeah.
Like it's on us, is what I'm saying.
Like she doesn't have to worry about that?
Oh, absolutely.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Oh, I agree with that.
She and Liam Neeson are a item.
They kissed on the red carpet, Paul.
Right.
Scandal.
I mean, not scandal.
It's adorable.
It's a showmance, Matt.
It's a showmance.
It is, but no, it's one of those things like in the movie, his character's a widower and
he falls for her in it, and in real life, it's the same.
But that movie was, I mean, that movie's just a million jokes a mile a minute.
It's what it's supposed to be.
Some people I've heard speak a little snobbly about it, and I'm always like, "What were
you expecting?"
Yeah.
It's a naked gun.
And I mean this like, not to be overly dramatic, but I remember after 9/11, I was in the New
York improv scene, we're all very big comedians out.
Good.
I'm glad we're not going to be too dramatic.
Not to be too dramatic.
But I remember John Bowie saying, "I used to not get the three stooges, and I get the
three stooges now."
Okay.
He was like, we were all at the UCB, we were all trying to do our own version of sophisticated
improv comedy for whatever that's worth, and sketch comedy, and just like these stupid
nang, nang, nang, and weird pratfall stuff.
And after, he said he just found himself watching it right after 9/11, and it was like, "Oh,
this is so soothing."
Right?
I've been told that about the new Naked Gun movie, that it is that old school, because
I haven't seen it yet, but I've been told by multiple people that it's that old school,
like we're just going to get up and we're going to do a bunch of stupid bits and tell
a bunch of jokes, just a joke a second, nothing's ever going to come out of our mouth that isn't
a joke.
And I've been told it's just so irreverent and not trying to deal with issues, and it
is just like an old school checkout.
Like, you just go check out at the movie theater for an hour and a half, two hours, and just
have a nice time.
Yeah.
Is that fair?
Totally.
It's total escapism, just a crazy amount of jokes on every level, from the dumbest jokes
to like really funny, like long bits.
Great.
Really good.
And I just was like, and you're right, Jacob, and that like, I used to like, when Airplane
and Naked Gun were like part of like our regular lives when we were younger, I used to even
talk about it in improv classes, like the idea of like stakes to jokes.
Like, if you want to have the most fun, you have to have high stakes, right?
And then I had to stop saying that because I started teaching people younger and younger
than no one had ever watched those movies at a certain point.
Oh, yeah.
And then there was the Children's Hospital was the only kind of slapsticky thing around
to like illustrate that point.
And then all of a sudden, and now-
Matt doesn't mean the TV show, he means an actual children's hospital that was down the
street from where he taught.
But yeah, the whatever Adult Swim Show.
But yeah, you know, there just wasn't that that slapstick style.
I was like, I remember, I remember even like literally with my children trying to explain
what slapstick was, and like being like, shit, I don't have any concrete examples.
But yeah, they're getting hurt, but it's funny.
It's really sophisticated.
I'm sorry, kids.
So they were just crying, laughing, and they got in the car, and they were debating whether
it was the funniest movie they'd ever seen.
Good.
So I guess-
What were the other contenders?
Ace Ventura.
Great.
That's a that's a good, good entry.
They really liked Ace Ventura.
That's a crazy movie.
It is a joke in the house to do the thing with the sliding door like, oh, yeah, yeah.
Good.
Oh, yeah.
Scoop of Monte Cristo in the chat wants to know, will you show them the original Naked
Gun now?
I think so.
I think now-
I think it'd be good.
I think it's a place where, at first we used to worry about the show and certain things.
Our kids watch The Simpsons all the time, and I guess other kids aren't allowed to watch
that so they come over and they're not allowed to watch it.
And so it was funny because my kids are just, they're not, they know how to negotiate, basically.
They're not, they're sophisticated craftsmen of the deals.
So the next morning they're like, oh, Family Guy's on the channel, dad, can we watch Family
Guy?
And I was like, oh, man.
It's like-
The slippery slope has begun.
It's like you can't put the genie back in the bottle, right?
And I was like, if they watched all the Naked Gun stuff-
Well, can you, you can start them off with Police Squad.
I really, I mean, that's the thing is I think we should just watch that because yeah, there's
like references to Police Squad in it that are direct that you're like, oh, if you know
the reference.
And Police Squad is one of those shows, it was very similar to like Get Smart and those
types of shows where they really did like, it'd be a little bit different each episode,
but each episode was basically the same jokes over and over again, which is kind of delightful
and almost secure.
Yes.
Now like one of the writers on it, it was written and directed by one of the guys from
Lonely Island, but one of the other writers on it is Dan Greger, who is Rachel Bloom's
husband and already a very successful movie writer and filmmaker.
But I still have his number on my phone from when he used to do the Neutrino video projects
in New York.
And I was like, what if he changed his number?
And so I just shot him a text being like, look, I hope you're getting a thousand of
these texts, just left the theater with my kids, all of us just laughing our asses off.
Yeah.
And then for the movie to come out, I'm so happy it came out and everything else.
And so we had a really nice exchange on that.
So it was really fun.
Oh, that's lovely.
Yeah.
I said I was Matt Donnelly.
So I knew I would skip the new phone who dis, get past that part, but it was a super, super
fun thing.
But yeah, very, very happy.
So a lot of cinematic intake for me guys, a lot of cinematic intake.
Yeah.
So I finally got around to seeing Thunderbolts and I did not enjoy that film at all.
Guestimating better or worse than Fantastic Four.
I don't, I can't, I don't know.
That's why it's guesstimating, based on what Matt has said, is it better or worse?
I'm guessing it's worse than Fantastic Four.
Oh, fight.
I don't, I don't know.
I've heard a lot of great stuff about Fantastic Four and I heard middling stuff about Thunderbolts,
but I heard better stuff about Thunderbolts than I thought.
Now problem is you talk about coming in with the comic book baggage, Matt.
Yeah.
So spoilers for Thunderbolts, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, hold on.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Let's get some spoiler music going for Thunderbolts.
When the music ends, the spoiler is over, fast forward until you don't hear the music
anymore.
Thunderbolt spoiler.
So Thunderbolts revolves around the character of the Sentry.
The Sentry is essentially Marvel's answer to Superman.
Okay.
Ah.
Are you familiar with this character?
Not at all.
Superman?
Yes.
Sentry is a relatively new invention and he's only, I don't know, probably not even 20-year-old
character, I don't think.
I have never enjoyed the Sentry at all because, just like Superman, it's hard to make stakes
when you've got an invincible everything thing.
So the only twist on Sentry is that he has a dark side, right?
So he's like Superman, but he's also evil Superman at the same time.
He's like got mental problems.
That's the whole thing.
But it's like if they made Moon Knight Superman, basically.
Gotcha.
So.
Spoiler over.
Yeah.
So it's just kind of bleh, you know, not great with that, because again, the stakes just
don't seem to be there.
Right.
And the characters that I did enjoy, like Yelena, whatever her name, from the Black
Widow series, she just, there's really nothing for her to do.
She's just, it's all, and it feels very, it feels really small.
The movie feels really small.
Everything just feels like it's shot in like five tiny locations.
When they do get it big, it's just to show some buildings falling on each other and nobody
cares.
It's just because nobody cares, because again, nothing, no consequence.
Nothing happens.
And according to Google AI, Fantastic Four is slightly worse than Thunderbolt.
Really?
Oh, well, shit.
I'm in for it.
Yeah.
Like, hey guys, we're kind of losing the handle here on phase four or phase three of the Marvel
universe.
Yeah.
How are we going to write this shit?
You're like, all right, there's a baby.
And you're like, there's a pregnancy test.
All of it.
Yeah, all these ideas.
And the whole thing with, God, David Harbour is just so dumb in this fucking movie as the
Soviet guy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Yelena's dad.
And he comes off like he's trying to hit on her.
It doesn't, there's no parental.
It's just Red Guardian.
Yeah.
Ugh.
Just garbage.
Anyway, I was really disappointed because I really wanted to like it and I did not like
it at all.
How old are the Thunderbolts?
Are they a modern comic book introduction or have they been around for a while?
I'm going to say that was late nineties.
And you know, that was a whole thing where.
So fairly recent, especially for us, fairly recent.
But very different incarnation of who was in it too, sorta.
I think, I think that the former Captain America, what's his name?
Super soldier.
I can't remember his name.
Patriot.
It doesn't matter.
Mr. Patriot, whatever.
I think he was part of it from the jump.
You know who else Mr. Patriot was in?
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Skryte Extra Sugar, the Tooth Loosener.
That's from Cool Yay, I like, I like glass.
I go.
Wait.
Queer a glass.
That's it.
2023.
The product, no problem pronouncing Skryte Extra Sugar, the Tooth Loosener.
Oh yeah, it's me, the ghost of macho man Randy Savage.
I'm here to tell you a little something about Skryte Extra Sugar.
You ever have a tooth that's just not coming loose?
It's just not coming out?
Well, I got the solution for you right here.
You can get this out of your head, no problem.
Cream rises to the top and so does the cane sugar.
Go ahead and get yourself a tall glass of Sprite Extra Sugar and pour it in.
You'll notice the thickening agents are going to work immediately, causing it to drip like
sundae topping right onto your cold ice cubes.
Go ahead and try and drink it.
You won't be able to because it's 99% sugar.
It's granulated for your pleasure.
Go ahead and chew a Sprite Extra Sugar today.
Gargle it down, bitch, yum.
I'm sorry, did you say you're a ghost?
I'm a ghost.
I feel like that is the lead that we are burying here.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, we're talking ghosts.
Talking ghosts.
I'm not the only ghost.
There's a ghost.
Advertisements?
You're not?
No, I mean this has been going on for a long time.
I remember when Gene Kelly was selling vacuum cleaners.
You know, you have an excellent point.
Shoot, Paul Walker's about to start another fast movie franchise.
That's right.
Brought to you by Scryte Extra Sugar, the tooth-loosener.
Anyways, when we got out of the movie, I was like, "Should we go watch Sophie's Choice
now or what should we do?"
And so how did the kids like Sophie's Choice?
They loved all the action.
Good.
Hey, speaking of Sprite Extra Sugar.
Yes?
Have either of you gentlemen heard of the new trend?
Scryte!
Don't get sued by Sprite!
Nope.
We're only talking about Scryte.
Did I say Sprite?
I meant Scryte.
You said Sprite once or twice.
Oh boy.
Well, whatever.
It's all the same.
It's not!
That's the entire point.
It's not.
You're right.
Keeps us free.
Have either of you experienced dirty sodas yet?
Who's that?
I want to experience this person.
I went to Utah.
There's all those soda places.
Yes!
Utah is where it's popping off.
It's a Mormon thing.
Yes.
There are a few here.
It is a Mormon thing.
And it is bananas.
It's super bananas.
It's spread out here now.
So our little local ice cream spot that we go to, they have dirty sodas now and got one
the other day.
I got a regular milkshake and got a dirty soda and I sipped on that motherfucking thing.
I am a fan.
Of course it's crack!
Why wouldn't you?
When we were kids we had Shirley Temples, which was like, "Hey, let's take the sweetest
thing that you could possibly have on earth and then add a sugary syrup to it and mix
it up."
And when you look at the ingredients of these crazy crack sodas, it is just the most caloric.
It is insane.
This one that she got was Dr. Pepper, mixed with raspberry syrup and I believe it's tangerine
cream.
Like, coffee creamer is one of the things that go with these.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Creamer is a big thing.
Yeah, yeah.
So coffee creamer goes into it.
Canadian Scoop Crystal asking about the dirty.
So it's like coffee creamer and then syrups and all kinds of stuff, so it kind of muddies
it up.
And as always, Canadian Scoop Crystal, dirty for Mormons, not dirty for you.
Exactly.
That's right.
And you're absolutely right, Scoop Amante Cristo, the blood does thicken on this stuff.
It is an extreme blood thickener.
You know who hates that soda is your pancreas.
That's who hates that.
Oh, he hasn't had a lot to say around here in a long time.
He really has had no voice in the conversation.
He has been in the non-vocal minority for a while.
Excluded from the conversation for a while.
Pancre-who?
Pancre-hoodis?
Pancre-you, not Pancre-us.
Yeah, here's Winter Scoop's recipe, 44-ounce Dr. Pepper with three creamers, also do it
with root beer, makes the soda into the float drink after the ice cream is eaten up.
Oh, man.
I don't think it was that.
Jesus.
I don't think it was that much.
That's real dirty.
It was a little.
It was a small cup of it.
On the show we talked about, once I put French vanilla creamer into apple cider, because
I did it on Thanksgiving, to be drinking apple pie.
Oh, yeah.
It would come off like a little ala mode.
Yeah.
How'd it go?
So delicious.
But again, my teeth rattle as I recall the story.
I'm not watching a video of somebody make one of these.
Then you're like pouring Diet Coke into a glass, pouring some kind of creamer into it
on top of it, and then just squeezing a lime, and now they're pouring some raspberry-looking
syrups into it.
There you go.
Yep.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's lots of different recipes.
It's alchemy, and I think it's fun that you can come up with all these crazy new things.
Don't get me wrong, I did Mr. Pib Zero with cherry vanilla on the thing, on the soda thing.
Oh, okay.
That was legit good.
I felt like a dirty Mormon at my movie.
Yeah.
Steven Eames asking, "Wouldn't the milk curdle it?"
Well, there's no milk involved in these non-dairy creamers.
They're just flavored liquids.
According to the Googles, some people use dairy creamers, though, and so I would think
those would curdle.
Those people are monsters.
That sounds horrific.
That doesn't sound any better or worse than anything else we're talking about.
What?
Do you want a cottage cheese soda?
That's what that would be.
That sounds as good as everything else you're describing.
I'm fine with ... The dairy is not what's bothering me here.
No, even when you go like AL8 and Big Red, when I travel, you find a novelty soda, and
then you look at them.
One of the reasons why they're thriving as a novelty soda is they have 50 more calories
than Coke.
Right.
Oh, Jesus.
People are just like, "Oh, this is just, that's significant, that's a significant amount of
sugar."
Yeah.
Right.
A Thirsty Scoop had a cherry pie dirty soda, it was sprite, cream, cherry syrup, and vanilla.
Typical dirty soda can contain significantly more calories than a regular soda, potentially
ranging from 250 to 600 additional calories.
For your beverage.
Let's go.
Yeah, that's your beverage.
No, that's your meal.
Now, let's be real.
That's your meal.
I hope so.
I hope so too, but when I have just a bunch of sugar, it doesn't feel like a meal, so
then I still am hungry.
According to this thing that I found that doesn't mean anything at all, some large dirty
sodas are right around 1,100 calories.
There you go.
You need to have a come to Jesus with your pancreas, Matt.
Get them on the straight and narrow.
My doctor already told me to have a come to Jesus moment with my pancreas, actually.
I think he meant the other direction, though.
My metformin prescription tells me I shouldn't be hitting up these dirty soda places, so
maybe...
Yeah, it's a rare treat kind of thing, the dirty soda, rare treat, it's a rare treat.
What was the thing when you guys were doing the potato diet, what was the go-to thing
with him to say you'd rarely feast on something?
Rare and appropriate.
That was it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no appropriate.
I was going to say, appropriate doesn't feel like the right word for dirty soda, no matter
what.
Rare and celebratory.
That's it.
Rare and horrible.
Can't picture...
Rare and annual.
That old text thread with a, "Hey, rare and appropriate, while I'm eating a fucking gummy
worm dipped in..."
Check it out, Ray.
"Cherry cream."
I bit the ends off of this gummy worm and now I'm using it as a straw.
Yeah, dirty soda, latter day scoop says dirty sodas are frequent and excessive and that
is absolutely right.
It's okay though, because while I'm drinking this dirty soda, I'm a little chilly, so that's
probably evening it all out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm outside and it's a bit nippy.
Yeah, next time I sit down with my doctor, we go over some stuff, I'm going to be like,
"That's so strange.
I mean, other than my dirty sodas, I'm keeping it tip-top."
I'm down to two dirty sodas a day.
Oh, God.
I can't...
No, it was a small one and Anne had like, not even a third of it, she's like, "This
is too sweet for me."
Too much, too much.
Was she bouncing off the walls?
Was she a different gal all day?
She was not.
She was just like, "This is just too sweet for me."
She, you know, she doesn't have the candy addiction like I do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She got them itchy teeth.
And I was like, "I'm down.
Let me finish that soda."
So I did and it was good.
We were driving by, children in Las Vegas, I guess children in a lot of places, but...
You say so.
One of the kids, wise asses goes like, "Oh, can we stop by the dispensary on the way home?
We just saw a dispensary."
And I laughed and I said...
Oh, they thought it was like a Soty Pops or something?
Well, I said, I go, "What do you think a dispensary is?"
Yeah.
And he goes, "A place where you dispense of bodies?"
And I was like, "Las Vegas, that seems like a fair guess.
That seems like a fair..."
Like one of those...
They're worse guesses.
Like one of those enzyme pools for horses, but we have one of those at the side of the
road here.
We just asked one of them.
Oh, horse enzyme pools.
Oh.
You know what's in that Planet 13 building?
A horse enzyme pool, that's what.
It's so big because it's Olympic size.
It's an Olympic size horse enzyme pool.
Talk about your fucking Artax, there you go.
That's your sorrow swamp right there.
So how did the kids like the dispensary?
It helped them really enjoy Fantastic Four.
I bet it enhanced their dirty sodas too.
But having drunk that thing, I got to believe that that's going to be the next move for
Starbucks, right?
Like coffee houses got to start serving these things, right?
Because they got all this stuff.
But, Jacob, you make a face, but they got all this stuff except the soda.
I understand.
I mean, I don't think you're wrong from a business standpoint.
I just don't want more of this stuff around.
Well, oh, come on.
I will also say, do you know, I tell you guys last year, it was like a year and a half ago...
Dirty sodas don't really take off when they add ghee.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm so mad at you, thirsty scoop.
Clarified butter soda.
Oh, this is the angriest I have been in a scoop in a very long time.
I'm having an Iron Man soda.
You want to join me for an Iron Man soda?
Oh, what's that?
It's a ghee zero calorie soda chicken.
Chicken?
Just a piece of chicken.
Just a piece of buffalo chicken.
That's right.
Bone-in buffalo chicken wing.
Gummy celery stalk.
Bone-in!
A whole bone-in buffalo chicken wing, diet coke, diet coke, half a cup of ghee.
Bullet dirty soda.
Now with Mero.
You remember that bullet coffee?
Bullet coffee.
Yeah, you put the butter in it.
Bullet proof coffee, put some ghee in it.
That's what I was referencing.
And like, that's like, I'm going to bring that up to ...
Oh, somebody's asking for a dirty soda bar at Scoop Fest.
Yeah, keep asking.
Well, we'll give you a dirty soda bar, but it's not going to be what you're thinking.
It'd be more like the Double Down.
And I was like, butter and coffee is gross.
It was like, what's the difference between that and half and half, like from this fat
content?
Shit.
And I was like, you got me again, cronus.
Did he do butter and coffee regularly?
Was that one of his go-tos?
No, he thought it was stupid.
He just also didn't do the cream or the coffee either.
That's what he was calling it out.
He was like, you're just sacrificing one collection of fat for another collection of fat, and
both serve the same purpose, but just to make your black coffee feel more like a meal.
And that's why everyone says this butter coffee makes me feel like I have energy, and I'm
not crashing, and all this other stuff, and it's only because you turned it into a ...
You put some fat in your system.
You turned it into a calorie machine.
No.
Anyhow.
I've been called worse.
I want to shout out to Jack Recider and Darknet Diaries.
Oh yeah?
The other morning, we're in the middle of talking, my wife gets a call, and she answers
it because it's from a 2-1-2 number, and it's like Old Instincts from New York Actors.
She always answered the 2-1-2 number, says it's the bank, and people are tripping fraud
on her Zelle account.
And so I'm listening to her.
She's concerned, and my wife's very diligent.
She gets out a pen and paper, so I was writing down information, started talking to the guy.
They transferred another phone, and she's going on and on with him for an amount of
time that I start to feel weird.
You thought she was having an affair?
Yeah, I was like, if she's having an affair, let her have her time.
I'll be over here with my ghee and my coffee.
I'll be in my filming chair.
And I'm listening to her go through certain activities, and she's starting to say answers
that are weird to me.
I just was like, what customer service thing would happen?
I'm paranoid, and you know, when you're paranoid, you're like, I don't want to be the dumb idiot
here.
Right.
I don't want to look paranoid.
I don't want to look like I'm the weird paranoid guy, or be dramatic, or whatever my wife is
handling a very serious matter.
But I just find myself on my notes, just typing up, "Do you see fraud in your accounts, and
do you trust the person you're on the phone with, or whatever?"
Right.
Now the person on the phone, they were doing an amazing job of an elaborate con.
When people actually play chess instead of checkers, it is really hard.
First the person said he was from Chase, but since this is a Zelle account, he's going
to transfer them over to a Zelle operative, or whatever.
And the guy says-
Oh, Latter Day Scoop in the chat just said something profound, which is, "With financial
issues over the phone, you are either paranoid or naive."
Yeah.
And I think you're exactly right, Latter Day Scoop.
I don't think you can just be right.
And he was saying, "Don't tell me your account number.
Don't give me any information.
I don't want to know your birthday.
We're just going to handle this as whatever."
And that secondary misdirection of like, "Let's just do this or whatever."
And then I'm listening to her, and so I put that note in front of her.
She's already annoyed that she's trying to handle theft, right?
And she puts it on hold, and she's kind of annoyed, and she gives me all the information
that she has heard.
And I said, "I know it's going to sound dramatic, but all the information you're telling me
is coming from him.
You have no other information from anyone else."
The good move is always like, "Let me hang up on this call now, and I will call the number
on the back of my card."
That's a great move.
Then you just know who you're talking to.
Because if you Googled the number of the call from, it was her bank, but it was just a ...
It was spoofed.
It was a bank.
Yeah.
It was ... You can make numbers pop up the way you want them now with phone apps and
stuff.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
Is that the term?
Spoofed.
Yeah, yeah.
You can just say it, Paul, but just explain it as a term to me.
They call them dirty sodas.
They spoof.
Spoof in them.
It's all the rage with the Mormons.
Mormons love nothing more than a spoofed in diet coke.
They had her typing ... She's like, "Just stay with me on the phone out loud.
I'm asking questions too."
Sounds like a spoof.
They're offering to transfer back and forth to whatever they want to give the number.
I was like, "Do you mind if I spoof while you talk?"
"Spoof and soak," says Sarah Miller-Wall.
I'm just here for a spoof and a soak.
It is 2025.
I can't stop you from spoofing in your own house.
A spoof and a soak and a dirty diet coke.
That's a Mormon Christmas right there.
That's a Mormon Christmas.
That's the song that plays when you're in line with the drive-thru lines down the line.
You can hear that when you get within the border of SLC.
Oh my goodness.
These guys were great actors.
We're like, "Listen.
See, it's a little shady."
The guy was like, "I can understand.
I'm going to give you my number.
I'm going to give you this number, this number.
I can transfer you back to your bank."
I like how much credit you're giving the scammers on the phone here for doing a good job of
a shitty thing.
That's what I'm saying.
I know.
I like it.
Normally, we get just a bullshit text that we can see in two seconds or a spam email.
Yeah.
Usually, just some bullshit nonsense.
Something that we don't have.
Whatever.
This guy had some information to let Sarah know it was her deal.
I said, "We can go to the bank and confirm that."
He said, "Oh, absolutely you can.
No problem.
I can also transfer you back to your bank and you talk to the guy on the phone."
I was like, "Oh, really clever."
Yeah.
That's good.
I was like, "Yeah."
But then he goes, "But he's just going to just get you back on the phone with us because
this is about Zell and not about your bank."
Yeah.
If you're concerned about it, I can easily transfer you back over to the bank and then
you'll be comfortable with them, but honestly, it's just going to be a big waste of your
time.
Now, do you want me to do that?
Do you want me to waste your time?
Because I don't mind.
I don't want to waste your time all day.
But if you're concerned, if you're just a little concerned little fella, I can transfer
you back over to the bank.
No problem."
Then I was like ... So then we let him go on.
So suddenly they're saying, "Your Zell is set to non-transactional, but we're just going
to run this message through to confirm whatever."
And that's when I was like, "Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no."
And that's when I was like, "Get off.
We have to get off the phone."
Yeah, we're done.
We have to get off the phone.
So we go to the phone and I was like, "Let's go to the bank."
And I was like, "You don't have to come."
I was like, "Sarah, someone's trying to shake us down for five grand.
I'll happily come."
Yeah.
Let's go to the bank.
"I'll come to the car.
I'll come in the car and let's figure this out together."
Yeah.
It was a total...credit to the great guys at the bank.
We just were literally like, "Okay, let's just walk through it.
Tell me everything.
It sounds like a scam.
I'm going to confirm this right now."
And just so you know...
Sounds like a what?
Sounds like, "What happened there, Matt?"
He said, "We're going to confirm that nothing has happened right now."
Would you say this is a spoof?
He just actually...he didn't say it was a spoof.
He said, "This is..." and he winked and he took his Diet Coke underneath the table.
Oh shit, that's the move.
That's like the silent alarm.
And he put it right in front of me.
Then he put a second straw in the Diet Coke.
A second straw!
Shall we share?
He said, "This is a race to the bottom."
Spoiler!
Matt won!
I'll tell you who else can win a race to the bottom against anybody, anytime, anywhere.
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by...if you guys want to do a fake commercial for Scoop's
Plumbing and Heating, I'm okay with that.
This is from 2021.
Gas Man Scoop.
Is he still...I don't even...is Scoop's Heating and Plumbing still in business?
I think he's changed it up to...I think it's a Gas Man and Son kind of thing now, isn't
it?
I think so.
I think you're right about the business anyway.
Yeah.
S-L-Y-D-A-T-F-O-W-I-T-F.
Not as catchy as fuck you in the face.
I don't know what that stands for though.
Well, it's something about Scoop's Plumbing, I guess.
I don't know.
All right.
Or maybe it was something that we would have gotten if we had read this a couple of years
ago.
Probably.
That's true.
Could be.
All right.
Scoop's Plumbing and Heating.
Right.
It's time to get yourself some Scoop Plumbing and Heating, isn't it?
Eh?
Yeah.
That's right.
What?
Are you too cold?
You need some firewood, eh?
What?
Were you too hot?
Eh?
We'll bet some ice.
That's what I got.
Got a truck full of it.
Eh?
What?
That would be good.
Yeah.
Right.
All right.
Let's go to Wood's Inn.
Me and you.
Come on.
Come into my van.
Let's go.
And also, my drink is a little warm.
Is there anything you can do for me about that?
Hand it here.
Oh, here you go.
All right.
Give me just a minute here.
There you go.
There.
Spoofed now.
Where?
Where did you get that ice from?
I spoofed it.
Spoofed it.
Wow.
You just spoofed out some ice.
That's what I do.
And you put it in my soda.
Fresh quality spoofed ice right for you.
Enjoy your scoop of spoof.
Just try this.
This is really good.
Damn right.
It's good.
A scoop of your scoop of your spoofin' helps the medicine go down, the medicine go down,
medicine go down.
That's right.
When it comes to your pipes, I'm not Mary fucking Poppins.
And her hay scoops the checkout.
The price is spoofed.
If you heard, Matt's probably seen them around town, but Paul, have you heard about these
electric cars that are the new driverless electric taxis going around Las Vegas?
I have seen some.
John and I, when my brother and I were in town, we actually saw some going around and
we were kind of amazed.
And I remember when I was doing promotional work for Opium back in the day, and I was
walking Fremont, they had them down at the end near Container Park, running practice
loops.
Yeah, they were doing practice loops.
And people could just volunteer and jump in the driverless taxi, which they're crazy looking
things.
They're mostly like open.
Yeah, they don't have a driver's seat at all.
They're not set up like a regular car.
They set up two bench seats facing each other and then the whole side of the automobile
just opens up as big sliding doors that open up and you just walk in and sit down in the
bench seats and it takes you to where you're going.
Winterscoop in the chat says Austin has these and says they're stupid and they cause a lot
of traffic.
They're not Waymo's, but they don't seem to cause a lot of traffic in Vegas.
They really seem pretty good.
I saw one pull up to a Dunkin' Donuts and it said, "I eat businesses" and it just chewed
right through.
Oh!
The car just ate right through the business.
That is tragic.
I eat businesses!
Yeah.
It was like the Galactus of Dunkin' Donuts.
Galactus, the automatic car.
The world eater.
But I saw one driving the other day, I was driving next to one the other day and it didn't
have anyone in it.
And so it was just an empty vehicle driving down the road with no one in it.
They must have sent it on test runs just for advertising purposes, right?
I think it was going to pick someone up based on where I was because I was on one of the
back roads in town.
So I think it was just going like an Uber to go pick somebody up.
Are they affordable?
I think they're a little more expensive than a regular Uber, but I think they're made to
be pretty affordable, yeah.
On the one hand, I don't want to see a crazy amount of jobs go away.
I know specifically there are women who've had a very tough time with specific Uber drivers
and they all have a terrible one storey or two to share.
And so the idea of a robot probably is very comforting from that perspective.
I don't think they're going to go rogue, form a Voltron and destroy the city.
Do you want to see my gear shift?
Work my clutch?
That's the mode.
Can you please make sure it sexually harasses me when it picks me up?
Can I spoof you?
Can I spoof?
I want to spoof, baby spoof.
I'm here to spoof your drink.
Oh, God.
So it was weird seeing it just straight up next to me driving along 50 miles an hour
and just no one in the vehicle at all.
They're just in the lane.
It's a ghost car.
It's a ghost car, you see?
Yeah, because they're wide open windows and shit, so you can just see right inside all
of it and it is really weird.
Yeah.
It was a little freaky.
Kind of looks like a fish tank.
I do kind of like it though.
It does look a little like a fish tank.
I like the idea of it though, especially for cities like this, especially for like the
strip area and everything.
It makes a lot of sense.
I think so too.
I'll be curious how, I mean, it's going to happen in some way or another.
You know?
Yeah.
It's going to catch on, you know, whether it's this year or in five years, it's going
to be...
I sure hope it does.
Until then, I'm so lonely.
Jacob.
Have you been a robot the whole time?
I've been a robot car this entire time.
I've been spoofed by Jacob this whole time.
I've been getting spoof all over your show the whole time.
Oh no.
So caloric.
I'm roughly 1,100 calories per sip.
Oh, I'll take the roughest 1,100 calories you can give me, please.
I'll loosen your teeth right up.
Yum.
There it is.
Scoop of Monte Cristo has got a picture in the chat.
Oh yeah, that's Scoop of Monte Cristo in the chat.
Yeah, that's them.
That's exactly it.
Yeah.
What company is that?
Can somebody tell me what company that is?
I think it's Google.
Oh.
It might be.
I think it's Google.
Zooks.
Z-O-O-X.
Gadzooks.
Oh, owned by Amazon.
Oh, so just a different monolithic corporation, Matt.
You were right about the monolithic corporation.
Just wrong one.
Ah, got me a good Amazon.
Beer Nun is saying we should put my cinema seat head as the driver.
I was talking about that before.
Oh yeah.
I mean, that would be a serious feature.
You'd have to pay extra for a solo ride.
That's definitely happening, by the way, in Vegas.
Oh, people are getting their bone on in those carts.
That's definitely going to happen.
I mean, I'm calling it.
I'm saying it's going to be...
Oh, sure.
Yes.
They're all recorded, though, right?
They clearly got cameras going.
Feature not a bug.
I mean, I guess if it's consensual, then who cares, right?
Oh, someone's going to care.
Yeah.
Someone's going to care.
Scully's like, "It's going to happen?
Yeah."
"It's taking me a second to type that search in.
Has anyone been arrested for sex in a driverless taxi?"
Okay.
"While reports indicate some people are engaging in sexual activity in driverless taxis, there
haven't been arrests specifically for this activity in those vehicles yet."
Mostly just applause and showers of money.
That's it.
Mostly just people screaming, "Oddcore!
Oddcore!"
Get it!
You filth nugget!
All these people dogging in robo-taxis.
Galactic President says, "Challenge accepted."
Someone has to do it.
Yeah.
Oh.
No, baby, this thing on my phone's a signal jammer.
You can't record in here.
Yeah!
No, no problem.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a basic, was it a Fermi cage, what that thing called?
That's a Fermi cage.
What's it called?
No, it's a Fermi cage.
You got it.
It's not a Fermi cage.
A Fermi cage.
Don't worry, baby.
I got this digital cloaking app.
Baby, I'm going to use this Fermi cage.
You won't get pregnant.
It's fine.
Faraday.
Faraday is what people are screaming.
Faraday cage.
That's it.
No, Fermi.
No, it's a Fermi cage.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
My Fermi cage slipped off.
You got to ...
You got to go see the doctor.
It's Fermi Paradox, Faraday cage.
You got to get a Plan B. My Fermi cage slipped off.
A Fermi cage.
What would a Fermi cage be?
The Fermi paradox is the reason why we won't encounter extraterrestrials or an argument
as to why.
What about a Furby cage?
Oh, a Furby cage.
Boy, that's ...
Oh, I had one of those in the '90s.
It was great.
Let's go.
Faraday Paradox.
On Twitch, DoubleOGroovy says Faraday cake.
Been sucking all these cocks, driving around in the Faraday Paradox.
Oh my God.
Go on, Matt.
What's the second line?
Pulled to the robot, "Robot's in my driveway."
Fool.
Yeah, no, that's coming.
Somebody's going to really get busy in one of those.
I think that's going to be the first issue that'll be popping up in the press.
It won't be the elimination of jobs.
It'll be like, "Too many people fucking in those things on Saturday nights."
Right.
But it won't stop it.
No.
Nothing can stop it.
Yeah, I'm not seeing any big reports about people having sex in them yet.
Okay.
But yeah, I think we can fix that.
It's a pioneering activity.
We can really get all the credit.
There's going to be some exploration.
Yeah.
It's going to be great.
Let's see.
You guys want to do a little Scoop Mail?
Yes.
I've got a surprise for you.
Oh shit.
Physical Scoop Mail.
Zippity doo.
We've got mail in a box.
I love it.
That's right.
Message for you, sir.
We've got a Scoop Mail from Yarn and Sticks.
Yay.
Hello, you sexy face fuckers.
I'm not going to read this whole note right now just because we're not all together.
But basically Yarn and Sticks has sent us some decorations for the new churn.
Oh cool.
And they are fantastic.
They are all knit.
Oh, hold on.
I'll turn my screen thing off so you can see on the screen.
But they are all like knit ice cream cock and balls.
And my question is, what else do you want?
That's amazing.
Those look great.
How adorable.
And that's just one of them.
How do you find this?
How do you find this stitching pattern for that?
Wow.
That looks great.
That's just a straight up wiener.
I love it.
Yeah.
There's one more down here too.
But thank you, Yarn and Sticks.
Yeah, Yarn and Sticks.
That's freaking awesome.
Do you have an Etsy shop or something we can promote?
Oh, that'd be nice.
Yeah, those will go up in the new churn.
This actually helps me.
I've been wondering, just to myself, just if we should, for the new churn, actually decorate
it or I'm going to turn this music off, I've been wondering to myself if we should decorate
the new churn when we move into the new churn or if we should do full green screen all the
way around it so that we can just change the decorations anytime we want.
Oh, that's not a bad idea.
The knit ice cream cock and balls makes me want to have them in the new churn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we should definitely have some green screen posters around.
Yeah, maybe we can do something.
Yeah.
So you can just pop up some stuff.
At this point, I think you just want LED screens, so basically TVs.
Oh.
We can do that too.
I was thinking that it might be a little, I was thinking, my thought was it would be,
here, we'll just do that.
Oh my gosh.
Production meeting, when we talk about how the sausage gets baked.
So my thought was, we just have a green screen wrapped around behind us all the time, and
we're just always somewhere different, and it could just be a ridiculous thing, just
a ridiculous bit going on, like a visual bit going on.
If you wanted us in green screen, then anyone could put us anywhere.
That's what I thought you were going with it.
I like your bit.
Oh, we could do that too.
Yeah.
I like your bit, Jacob.
I like the idea.
I would suggest doing it with like a fake window, like maybe even cut out.
That's not a bad idea.
A little square thing.
Yeah, we could do that.
Yeah.
And make it like a fake window, and then we can just put weird stuff going on outside
the window.
Scoop of Monte Cristo.
It's just always going to be the Geekshock house.
That would be pretty funny.
That would be pretty funny indeed.
Yeah.
That would be fun.
But these are so great, and yeah, there's yarn and sticks sent to home.
A screen for bucket picks again.
Should we do that for the show this time, Matt, speaking of we're still in production
meeting mode?
For the Wednesday bucket show?
Yeah.
Should we try a bucket picks thing, or maybe even just for the second show?
We have found it increasingly difficult to broadcast from that theater.
Right.
Yeah.
That's the problem.
There's no Wi-Fi there.
We can think about something.
Maybe we can do like a local bucket picks or something.
Maybe we can do something.
We might figure something out.
Okay.
That'd be fun.
Yeah.
Let's do a little...
We are confirmed for the bucket show the Wednesday before seven and nine o'clock.
Two different shows.
Fantastic.
At the Majestic Rep Theater.
I'm fucking pumped, baby.
That of course is the Wednesday leading up to ScoopFest at the end of September here.
Come join us in Las Vegas for ScoopFest, scoopfest.com.
Head on over there right now.
That reminds me, I have to reply to an email regarding ScoopFest that I completely forgot
about until just now that I shouldn't reply to right now because we're in the middle of
a show.
Here's Jack versus Nerd.
Good narrating, Jacob.
That was very nice.
Very good.
I was also looking for the right button.
Jack versus Nerd action.
Oh, am I?
Fuck, yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Cock and balls.
Nice green cock.
Explosion of spoof.
We got a Scooperty coming at us today from Smart Scoop.
It is the first time Smart Scoop has written us a Scooperty, so thank you very much, Smart
Scoop.
If you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price is Scryte Jack versus Nerd or an Obelisk Jack
versus Nerd, heyscoops.com is where you can go, heyscoops.com.
Make us a Scooperty, just like the one we're about to play right now.
The categories are dead weights, or dead weight, video conferencing, educational TV, and famous
departures.
Matt, you're up first.
I want educational TV, please.
In the '90s, this former engineer from Boeing added the Science Guy to his name and attempted
to educate America.
Bill Cosby.
Bill Cosby, the Science Guy.
Bill...
But you know, it turns out that if you add water to a simple piece of frozen nitrogen,
it'll foam up like that, is what it does, and also you can roofie the ladies' sides.
Thank you, Bill.
That was correct, Matt.
Bill Cosby.
The spoof, the spoof was on fire.
Oh, no.
The spoof was on fire.
We do need some water.
Don't let it burn.
I'll try Famous Departures for $400.
After an incident with a writer, this actor was fired from Criminal Minds.
I have no idea.
I will pass.
Paul.
What's the category?
Departures.
Oh, man.
I don't ever watch Criminal Minds.
I have to pass.
I don't think I've ever seen it.
Matt.
Eric Danson, Ted Danson's cousin.
Eric Danson.
I have no idea.
The Lesser Danson.
Thomas Gibson.
Eric Danson changed his name to Thomas Gibson.
Hold me closer.
Eric Danson.
It was because of the sag issue.
Paul.
I'll try video conferencing.
Bought by Microsoft in 2011 and Sunset in 2025, this video conferencing software was
superseded by Teams.
Hangout.
Oh, hangout or hang out is incorrect.
It's Skype.
Ask my fart.
Poop my turd.
We just got demonetized.
Matt.
Educational TV for $800 please.
Daily Double.
All of it.
I will eat all of the Dunkin Donuts shop.
This television series created and hosted originally by Carl Sagan and later revised
by Neil deGrasse Tyson, attempted to educate America about the universe.
Oh, shit.
I don't remember the name of this.
Let's see.
It's Daily Double.
Daily Double.
It's your Daily Double?
Oh, man.
Let's see.
You remember that?
I can give you a hint.
Secrets of the Space and Time.
I can give you a good hint.
Give me a good hint, Paul.
Kramer.
Non-Dairy Kramer or Regular Dairy Kramer?
Nope.
Regular Dairy Kramer.
Seinfeld Kramer.
Michael, what was his name?
I don't care.
What was his name?
I know that's the hint you're giving me, but I know that I'm experiencing cosmic dissonance
without clouds over my brain right now, so I know I'm not going to charge this.
Wait, cause of what?
Yeah, what did you say?
That was close, buddy.
Cause of what, dissonance?
Cosmic dissonance?
Well, cosmic?
So what was his name?
Oh, Cosmos.
Cosmos?
Cosmos!
Hey!
No problem at all.
Just a couple of very easy, no problem hints given to math there.
His name is Cosmo Kramer is his real name.
Oh, God.
I started to think of his real name.
Yeah, you're trying to think of Michael Richards.
Michael Richards.
Kramer's real name is Cosmos.
Cosmo.
Yeah.
It's me.
Let's keep dragging this out more.
Let's keep talking.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't think people understand what was happening.
Remember how Kramer's name was Cosmo?
Amazing.
Speaking of Cosmo.
Remember that painting they did of him?
How silly.
In shipping and aviation, what is the term for dead weight added to maintain equilibrium?
Paul Mattingly.
Your mom.
What's weird is now like Michael Richards would just be able to tour after what he did
had happened to him.
Oh, yeah.
He'd now just be able to play specific comedy clubs where the audiences would cheer him
as a hero.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
So gross.
He could open for Gutfeld.
In addition to ship and get aviation, oh, right, ballast.
That's ballast.
Yep.
Ballast.
There's like a mine that works in an aquarium and he does this bit where if he sees a woman
carrying a book bag and the guy doing nothing, he stops them and makes the guy wear the book
bag or makes the guy push the stroller.
Have you seen this before?
I have.
I think it's SeaWorld.
And I said, "No one show this to Trump, he'll bam mimes."
All right, where are we?
Paul.
I'll try educational TV.
For $1,200.
This British comedy quiz show hosted by Stephen Fry and Sandy Toksvig.
Toksvig, I never know how to say Sandy, I don't know how to say that name, at different times,
is an abbreviation and favors interesting and obscure facts over the traditional format.
IQ.
IQ is correct, almost correct.
QI.
Oh, it's QI.
Fart on me.
Quite interesting.
Fart on Paul, indeed.
Boy, I'm getting lambasted here.
Matt.
You should get clues like I do, Paul, it really helps.
Matt, the answer is Cosmos.
I don't think anybody else knew this one.
I didn't.
I knew that Penn hosted an American pilot of it, but I forgot the name of it.
Oh, really?
Wow.
Yeah.
It's a funny show.
I've seen it a few times.
I don't remember the name of it.
Since I'm killing on educational TV, let's go for it.
All right, $2,000.
Hosted by Jonathan Ross, Allison Hannigan, and Brooke Burke successfully, this television
program taught me that there are only four magic tricks.
The rest is just stagecraft.
That would also be QI.
QI is correct.
It would be Fool Us.
Fool Us, of course, on the ... I forgot what channel that's on.
CW.
It's easy to forget.
Yeah.
In my show, I say it's the highest rated show on CW, which is like having the best
Italian restaurant in Alabama.
It's not nothing.
It's me.
I'll try.
Let's try Famous Departures again.
The first one went so well.
Successful stints on The Daily Show in The Office made this actor an A-lister.
He left The Office in 2011 at the conclusion of the seventh season.
This is the second question, the one about the show that none of us have seen was the
first question.
To be fair, Criminal Minds is probably a higher rated show.
Steve Carell is the second?
Yeah.
Oh, that's probably true.
Steve Carell, anyway.
Yeah.
I'll try Dead Weight.
I know it's going to be the answer somewhere here.
What is the name of the exercise in which bodybuilders lift large amounts of weight
straight off the floor and hold it for several seconds?
A deadlift.
A deadlift is correct.
Dead Laszlo.
Matt.
Score check real quick.
Matt's in the lead with 3,200.
I'm in second with 1,200.
Paul is in third with negative 800.
He's had a couple of rough stints.
We're about halfway through the game and there's still one daily double left.
Matt Donnelly.
Wow.
Good recap.
Matt Donnelly for 2,800.
Not available.
I will take video conferencing for 800.
This video conferencing software rose to prominence during the COVID-19 pandemic and continues
to be the most commonly used conference tool today.
That would be Zoox, the car, automated car.
Yeah.
It takes you to all of your conferences.
Zoox.
Gad Zoox.
Zoom.
Gad Zoom.
We're on it right now.
We are.
And all of our Patreons are on it with us.
That's right.
It's pretty popular.
It's me.
I'll try Dead Weight for 1,200.
Daily double.
Still for 1,200.
The Rolling Stones have a popular song about a beast of this, a well-known synonym for
dead weight.
Oh, you've got this.
A beast of Mattingly.
Hold on.
Pause.
Wait a minute.
Beast of Mattingly.
Of course it is.
Beast of spoofing.
That's thirsty.
That's a good one.
Of course it's the beast of burden.
Yes.
Blue.
Paul.
I will go with, I'll finish out Dead Weight, please.
All right.
One half of Matt and Mattingly, this comedian and magician has been carried by Paul Mattingly
for so long that Paul's back hurts.
This is different than I thought it was going to go.
Matt Donnelly.
It's a twist.
Matt the Mind Noodler Donnelly, of course.
Holy smokes.
You're not wrong.
He's not wrong.
It could have gone one way or the other.
Right.
Matt, you have videoconferencing or famous departures?
I'll go with videoconferencing, please, for 1,200.
In 2007, Cisco Systems acquired this videoconferencing technology widely used by enterprises prior
to widespread adoption of both Zoom and Teams.
Hmm.
Pass.
Huh.
All right, pass it to me.
I think Cisco was the company that bought TikTok, but that wouldn't be, that's not 2007.
That's too early for that.
Oh, I was about to say it was this Teams, but no Teams is in the thing.
I have no idea.
Pass.
Paul.
Maybe Slack, but I'm going to pass.
Let's try it.
Webex.
God, I'm so glad I didn't pass on that one.
That sounds like spoofing.
Spoofed.
That's what you're left with after you spoof, you get that little bit of web.
Yeah.
Webex.
I'm closing out videoconferencing for 2,000.
My dirty soda's down to the Webex.
You can throw it out.
Upsetting.
For as little as $2 a month, this audience member can get a podcast exclusively for them
over Zoom.
It's $3 a month now, but it's Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Oh, this audience, oh, I was supposed to say the audience member is Scoop, not the podcast
name.
Oh.
Fine.
Paul.
I'll try the famous departures for 1,200 or 2,000.
I'll try the 2,000.
I don't know.
I still can't win.
Try it out.
After sticking it out for over 1,200 episodes, this Scoop has decided to leave the community
after it became apparent that the show is not for him any longer, but for the Scoops
who pay for access.
Oh no.
What?
I don't know.
I have news for that Scoop.
I often put out the Zoomlings for all members, so actually you can get it for free.
We just are asking generally for $3 in support.
That's it.
But if you actually go to our Patreon to become a free member, you'll still get the majority
of the Zoomlings.
There you go.
We're not much of a paywall.
Way to fucking stick it to us as I've been actually giving it to you for free the entire
time.
I think this has got to be a tongue-in-cheek thing, right?
Maybe it's a joke answer.
I don't think so.
Let's see.
We're going to find out in a second.
Paul, do you have an answer?
I don't have a guess.
Let's see what it is.
Smart Scoop.
So apparently it's not a fun answer.
It's just Smart Scoop leaving, I guess.
No.
He wouldn't send in a thing and then be like, "It's for you."
That's why I'm confused.
No.
You've landed on why I'm confused.
Matt, will they, won't they?
One of the most famous examples is Sam Malone and Diane Chambers from Cheers.
Turns out, won't they?
As this actress left the show after the fifth season.
Right.
Smart Scoop.
Smart Scoop is also the answer.
Yeah.
Shelly Long.
Of course it's Shelly Long.
Good old Shelly Long.
She the best.
And that is the game.
I'm sure glad it didn't get awkward at the end.
Matt wins with 5,200, Paul is in second with 1,200, I'm in third with 400.
And that came to us from Smart Scoop.
Thank you so much, Smart Scoop, if you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price is Skryte
jock versus nerd or anything else, head over to HayScoops.com, HayScoops.com right there
on the homepage.
You can send us a Scooperty.
You can send us any kind of jock versus nerd.
You can send us some Scoop mail.
Do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
Thank you, Smart Scoop for sending that in.
I also want to thank the following people who support us on Patreon, the only reason
why I do this show.
Big shout out to WindwalkerScoop23, William MacDonald, Will Kellner, Will Beardydan, HootatScoop,
Who Was Like When Scoop, Wes Culligan, Wendy Bumgardner, Wendy Cooper, WaterEyeScoop, Warren
Bro, Uncle Don's Woodshop, Udo Gerhards, Tyler Scoop McDuck, Tyler Bartlett, Tubascoop, Troy
Anthony Townser, Tristan Guevara, Travis Murray, Travis Uruguay, Tony Scoprano, Tony Cowley,
and Tom Stott.
Big thanks to all of these people who have to decide whether to sacrifice a baby or the
entirety of the planet Earth.
The Going Over Our Friends podcast, the famous ball, Didgeridoo, the Devil's Lettuce Scoop,
the Damsels of Dorkington, the Civic Crew Scoop, the Sensey Scoop, the Bad Humor Man,
the Thing in the Attic, Turn the Page, Temporary.Reality aka Pierce, Technical Scooport, Tamara Hamilton,
Take it Evie Podcast Scoop, Swedish Scoop, Supergeek13579, Sugar Rush Socio, Strap a
Chicken on Scoop, Strange and a Strange Uncle's Podcast.
You good?
I'm good.
Alright, I want to thank the following people for all putting different spoofy flavors in
my diet coke.
Tony Cowley, Tom Stott, Tom Mancreddy, Tom Krieger, TK421 Scoop Please, Timothy Sutton,
Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thomas Beach, the Man, the Myth,
the Scoop, the Dirty Scoop, the Upside Down Underscoop, the Spirit of the Latin Club,
the Scoop Lockian, the Salty Squid, the SCOOP, the Nano Scoop, the Lapis Lagomorf, the Ice
Cream Headache, and the Ice Cream Headache.
Big thanks to all these people who just got spoofed right in the mouth.
Stuart Wilson, Steven Biggs, Steven Landon, Steven Clively, Stephanie Young, Streets Magreets,
Stacy Coleman, Stab and Dash Scoop, Spring Loaded Scoop, Soundman Scoop, Solar Scoop,
Solar Powered Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Smells Funny, Slurpee Kaye Motherfucker, Slightly
Sleddy Scoop, Scully Wall Scoop, Six Foot Scoop, Sir Scoopy, Mick Scooperton III Esquire,
Silverfist Scoop, Silicon Scoop, and Shoeless Scoop.
Thanks guys.
And the following scoops all gather around another scoop and spoof all over them until
they just can't spoof anymore.
That's Sean SF, Sebastian Robbins, Jonathan P, Sean Kelner, Scott Schofield, Scott Muldrig,
Scott Headington, Scott Ashlock, Scott Ashlock again, Scott Andrews, Scott A, Scoopy Scoopy
Jess Jess, Scoopy Bartfast, Scoopy Ramone, Scoopy Dooby Doo, Scoopy and the Beast, Scoop
Trek the Experience, Scoop So Hazard, Scoop-o-Metrics, Scoop Nick, Scoop Neon Black, Scoop Lockeesa,
Scoop Nack Paddywhack, Scoop Kata, Scoop JD, Scoop It Or Ascending, Scoop Pee-a-Loren,
Scooper Nova Girl, Scooper Metroid, Scooper Luga, Scoop It Bids, Scoop Hall's Drag Race,
Scoopa Troopa, Scoopaholic, Scoop T, Scoop Skywalker, Scoop of Saltwater, Scoop Nurse,
Scoop Meefa, and Scoop Lord Tristan.
Thank you all so much.
I love you all.
I just want to put a button on this and just say, we probably haven't, shout out in a while,
you can always reach us over email.
Oh yeah.
Our name @HeyScoops, Matt, Paul and Jacob @HeyScoops.
So if you actually want to talk to us about what we're doing, or maybe want to express
your feelings or something like that, please write us.
We often write back.
And people send me emails on the main line all the time that are just questions that
I don't read on the air.
So if you have a question or a thought on the show or anything, you can send it to us
over there and we'll just reply back to you.
If we don't reply back to you, it's just because the email got buried, send it to us again
or find us on social media, you can DM us on whatever social media we're on and we'll
get back to you.
Yeah.
And in the event, again, if you were serious, we decided to just try to do something fun
and lean in while we were homeless with our churn.
And knowing that we probably weren't going to get another churn all ready to rock before
Scoop Fest, and so we thought this is like a fun way to shake up the format a little
bit after 1,200 episodes.
Oh, Scoli in the chat, though, wants to chat about Israel and Age of Consent laws.
Okay.
So we can just shift.
Let's get that.
We can shift cleanly right over to that.
Let's get that up there.
No problem.
Oh, Winter Scoop says, "I can confirm that they reply to emails."
It's true.
Well, you can reach all of us on the socials in some manner.
Oh, yeah.
We are remarkably easy to get ahold of if you want to get ahold of us to talk to.
Rather accessible.
And we do appreciate the hell out of every one of you guys who contribute to the success
of this podcast, whether it is just listening or participating or actually sending stuff
through Patreon, whatever level you can do, we really appreciate it.
And I'm really loving this Zoom stuff.
I think we're going to keep this up for a while anyway and see where we can go with
it.
Yeah.
I mean, the show, yeah, we're always going to be changing the show up.
But yeah, we've got the Zoom thing going now.
It is fun for us.
So we like seeing all of your pretty faces there in the Zoom chat.
We like seeing everybody interact with us over on Twitch as well.
That is TheBucketShow.com right over there on Twitch.
That's always up and running at the same time that we're on the Zoom, so you can always
check us out over there.
And I hope you do.
I hope you do.
All right.
Yeah, maybe it was a latter day scoop in the chat mentions though.
Hopefully it was just a joke that landed poorly.
Maybe it was.
Who knows?
Yeah.
Maybe it was a scooperty.
I think it was just a joke.
It's true.
And it was a brand new scooperty.
Like they just sent that in too.
I think it was just a joke.
Yes.
Maybe it was.
Maybe it was just a joke that landed a little weird.
I appreciate that a lot.
That scooperty too.
It was a good scoop.
I do too.
I'm already going for a long walk after this, guys.
It's too late.
I'm already crabby.
Matt's crabby.
Look out.
If you see somebody walking down the street with two kitchen tongs held over their head
like crab claws.
That's right.
Going for a long walk.
That's Matt Donnelly.
A long crab walk to think about it.
Yeah.
Scoopfest is right around the corner.
Can't wait to see everybody there.
Really looking forward to playing.
Scoopfest.com.
Come check us out.
Improv with Matt at the show.
So if you're even in just the area and you can make it out to the improv show, if you're
not coming out to Scoopfest, coming out to the bucket show on that Wednesday night, it's
going to be a great time.
Yes.
All right.
Scoopfest.com.
Still tickets available to see us there.
Lots of fun on tap for that.
We're still locking down a lot of fun details, but it's already going to be so exciting.
Oh yeah.
Tickets still available on scoopfest.com.
Still get your discount at the Orleans Hotel Casino.
Just say you're part of Scoopfest.
And thanks for listening everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the Cone.
See you at the Cone with dirty soda.
Dirty Soda Bar at Scoopfest.
Not Guaranteed.
Not doctor recommended either.
Not recommended.
We're making fun.
The doctor just cringes every time they hear about dirty soda.
Oh no.
Oh, you can add an extra 1600 calories a day.
Fantastic.
Just right to you.
See you everybody.
See your nose.
Love you.
Bye.