you want to want to go for it want to go for it twerk off right now
she goes oh i see a twerk off all right
oh hello there i am so glad you're here it's time to thank you the ice cream truck drivers
thank you so much ice cream truck drivers right now i'd like to thank dr scoop little
elk and magic scoop fifi frankie's tiki scoop galactic president scooper star mc scoops a lot
ice blue scoop i want a scoop baby jacob dick licker jake schneider jason klepper and jeff
harris if you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks and help
deliver that fucking ice cream straight to people's fucking ear holes head over to
preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is where you go to sign up and who knows the life you save
may be your own
here's a joke hey johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social
you
in las vegas that's matt donnelly in pittsburgh that's paul mattingly in las vegas it's me jacob
the audio guy
we are preaching fun yes silly oh my god manhole versus car two zero huh uh it was again there's
there's two different rounds of practice laps yesterday and the second round of practice
laps was called off because of a loose manhole cover for the second time in three years same
two out of three years newman didn't pay this time to come to it so at least at least uh
that that part didn't happen that's crazy though that's good at least the money they spend on that
thing and then to just have that happen again that's gotta be according to newman he got a hundred
dollar uh f1 credit which he spent at the store and got five eighths of a hoodie
got nearly all of a hoodie i was you know like i get these uh i'm doing a gig for f1 uh this year
we'll talk about it more in a sec but i i on the break i walked around and saw the store and sure
enough you just see this beautiful merch you know booth and you're like oh maybe i'll get myself a
nice like f1 sweatshirt and they're so expensive and then you're like wait where am i where am i
gonna wear this like right not only where am i gonna wear this but who's gonna respect me in las
vegas for wearing this oh it is so strange okay so like there's so much local anger and hatred
towards f1 oh yeah just a ton uh was the rio put up a billboard we got 99 problems but f1 traffic
ain't one nice uh
you know our pal jonas robertson said a happy f1 everyone it's a picture of him giving two
fingers to the camera um and uh and i and i and jacob you know uh your your commute has been
you know fucked up for weeks right oh yeah oh my god i'm just i'm just losing hours out of my day
every day and so i am feeling guilt paul i'm feeling guilt about like how fun and cool it
is to be in the middle of f1
i
this is the life of the performer right this is how it goes we have lots of our friends who are
doing the stuff with the sphere the sphere is sucking the very life marrow out of entertainment
in las vegas what can you do you gotta ride the devil the day the devil for a while i don't know
yeah i don't know either all maddie lee gotta ride the devil we gotta ride the devil uh and
that's what i tell everyone when i ride in when i go uh all right guys time to ride the devil
when the cab driver says i can't drop you off i'm gonna ride the devil i'm gonna ride the devil
off at the west and the road is closed i say ride the devil ride the devil
all right if we can get a paul mattingly ride the devil uh shirt in time that'll be our black friday
sale great great that'll be a good one yeah black friday so uh speaker world is friday yes is is a
hired partner of mercedes uh and for many years uh not many years for now three years
um they've been doing events here and also sometimes at the miami location as well and
this is where this is always this is jacob you've been in the employee of speaker world for quite
some time we've all been in the employer speaker world for here and there that's um this is my
first time since the pandemic officially in in their in their employ it is both amazing how much
talent they attract in front of and behind the stage ah and how much there's attention of of
always of like
what what are we what are we doing and why are we doing it
that's the whole thing and yet right so what i'm a part of in mercedes is like why you do
hire a spiegel world is because they make strange decisions right so it's spiegel world but they're
like hey you know the circus act thing is pretty cool but can you do something totally different
for us we want our mercedes people to feel special their answer was let's build a ski
line and we're going to build a ski line and we're going to build a ski line and we're going to
build a giant ski launch let's build a giant ski launch let's have a yeti let's have fake snow
going let's just totally transport people to something inappropriate to both miami and las
vegas right right and people fucking love it of course they do it's such a treat to the eye
they eat it up it's it's incredible ski large we are so jaded yeah ski lodge was one of the best
things about super freeko yeah right oh and it's still there and it's still it's still rocking it's
still great yeah there's a hidden there's a hidden ski lodge in super freeko i think there's just a
market to expand on this and just grow it out he just needs to open up ski lodge diners
no ross just needs to make some standout some some ski lodge diners it's the diner part that
he needs a little work on but um why because they don't know how to make food no no the one diner
they open they turn into a steakhouse so they're not their diner oh no no no this needs to be pizza
only it needs to go the chucky cheese route you got already you already got the animatronic
abominable snowman you had some other you had some other animatronics if you add a bunch of
animatronics but half the animatronics are live performers that pop out every now and then and
freak people out holy crap i was i was you know what i gotta just i need a meeting with ross
let me get a meeting with ross i need to sit down and we need to talk about this whole
revitalization you are accelerating like an f1 race car right now and i'm telling you to pump
you know what i'm doing you know what i'm doing what's that i'm riding the devil
that's what i'm doing i was just to say i was worried they might be listening to this but as
soon as you said chucky cheese pizza i'm positive they turned it off bullshit it needs to happen
that guy who did evil pie said he was gonna do it he never did it because he dropped the fucking
ball on a billion dollar idea it needs to happen and it needs to be one of those things where you
don't know is that an animatronic or is that a real person and that's going to be the best thing
when that thing walks off the stage and freaks children out and scares everybody in the restaurant
where are the children coming from it's going to be a family-friendly restaurant
i've lost track as to where you think this is happening where is this going
this is worldwide son okay okay okay franchised this is not for the f1 track i got it yeah yeah
no no no no no no no that was that what you thought i was talking about
yep no i've no i've taken this story all the way behind now this is my whole thing
no no once you ride the devil you go different places very different places
all right all right ride the devil let's bring it back to the enchantment of this
current iteration of the ski lodge which has yet to reach its full animatronic potential
well there's no animatronic so by potential that's what i'm saying yeah
yeah it has not reached its full animatronic potential
all those billionaires hang out and chat together anyway isn't he talking with elon
you know all china's replacing their entire workforce with robots
i don't i don't i don't think that's happening i'll just i i'm i'm doesn't seem like it is very
hopeful and happy that it's not no i don't i know i know for for all the for all the comparisons of
our crazy wily ceos uh there's a gigantic divide when it comes to a gulf a gulf of humanity yes
respect for artists and all that kind of stuff did you see he's such a chode did you see
elon got completely ratioed on uh twitter recently someone i and i was terrible i can't remember the
name of the lady but she called him out and she was like this guy has everything he's got the whole
you know oh god there he is smoking a cigar with all the billionaires um
he quit distracting paul no it's fine uh but he's got all the money in the world
and yet he has no passions he's not interested in literature or film or art he's never even he's
never even complimented a movie he's never even talked about a movie he likes and he got so
butthurt he started listing movies and like this is a good movie this movie's good oh yeah yeah
that's terrible he is
such a loser such a loser oh hold on here hold on here we can we can fix this
let's see here uh yeah let's do this
elon
don't list movies that you like when people say you don't like movies
that's a bad move that's like listing your black friends it works just as well
what are you doing it's exactly if only you had black friends it's exactly the kind of move
it's exactly how it read too it came off so hollow and so ridiculous like he started talking about
movies from like 2003 like titanic was a good movie yeah that's exactly like the stuff it was
like what news news broke obviously he's going to become a trillionaire right right right and he was
like he wrote like i will carry the light of consciousness uh to to other planets into mars
and beyond or something like that right yeah and someone someone just wrote can you just pay taxes
on it like can you just pay your fair amount of taxes on it yep it was weird it's like if you if
you think you take your trillions which no one singular human should ever have um it is a sickness
having a billion dollars seems like the weirdest craziest thing in in
history having a trillion dollars i i don't even know what that means that's just it is the biggest
it is the biggest flaw of americans to not properly fathom the wealth gap and what that's
seen well right oh yeah we should biggest problem we should be i don't understand why we're not in
the streets right now that's that's that's well yeah and it's raining out give me an hour too
give me an hour when it stops raining in an hour i'll go to the streets no problem okay great great
yeah a trillion dollars is meaningless coffee bean scoop it does lose objective reality for
most human beings we can't fathom it i think we're all human beings i don't think anybody can
and it is anti-capitalist because capitalism is uh money re-entering the the the flow of commerce
and so these are weird dragons hoarding wealth that never gets recycled into the environment
it never gets back it'll never trickle down and you can't i don't want to get into it but uh at
oh uh that reminds me uh and also speaking of hoarding wealth we owe an apology uh as a as a
podcast and as a group to jake paul uh last week we called jake paul a douchebag uh today he announced
that he has just purchased a 364 carat diamond necklace uh ahead of his upcoming fight and it
looks like diamond bullets hanging off of his neck so uh sorry jake paul we called you a douche
i think i said it about logan paul they're both awful they're both monsters paul did you not hear
what i just said let me tell you about his necklace wait no no no no no no i think of the
children paul think of the i misheard you gold-plated bullets gold-plated bullets okay
great oh sorry i got so wound up in my anger use that money to save this planet instead of
worrying about putting it on other planets like that actually is enough money
to probably do a lot for this planet when i was a younger man everybody would everybody could just
have food when i was a younger man and fully locked in with star trek and sci-fi and all that
i really was a proponent of space travel and and i still am to a degree there have been great
discoveries that we as a species have made through the advancement of space traveling technology
velcro is just one however
having said that when i became a somewhat older wiser man yeah have you guys uh ever heard uh
gil scott heron's whiteys on the moon yes it's perfect it's perfect uh and that always keeps
resonating in my head whenever i hear these motherfuckers talking about going to space
it's like man it's literally because we got way more shit don't know what to do with their money
like it is too much money because when you have hundreds of millions of dollars
you can afford every single house that you want on the planet you can travel privately to every
single place on the planet you can afford every single meal that anyone could possibly prepare
on the planet you can afford everything every watch every piece of clothing every car i always
say you don't have to consider money you money becomes uh not a consideration in life yeah it's
crazy the only reason to go higher is strictly insane ego bullshit yeah and to want that insane
ego bullshit
and still want to do nothing or barely anything for humans on the planet is just ridiculous
yeah it's grotesque yeah um all right but you can't accumulate you can't there's no great
fortune without uh some great crime right that's what it comes down to and and also just bitching
about these things and not uh acting on them you know that's just a that's just a waste of our time
and your time so uh we here at matt maddenley's ice cream social we want to act on this
so here's what i propose i propose that our patreons give each of us one billion dollars
and we're each going to use that billion dollars as we think a billionaire should do you know how
we're going to see how this works out please go to i would even do this podcast if i had
even a million dollars in my bank account
oh nothing nothing will stop me from wanting to hear the sound of my own voice paul there isn't a
lot of money on the planet you know it's still it would be really fun if i had the if i had like
crazy money i would be setting up uh random live events with us all the time that's okay well that's
the that is what we would do actually yeah that's it's true that actually is we would we would just
that's the problem all the play all over it's like that's why a lot of these celebrity podcasts are
making that loot and catching on because they have the money to go set up live events all over
the world and get get more interest amy pollard did her first live podcast it's pretty great go
check it out i listened to it it was good man of scalco is that is that did i say that right
they said no but i don't have a i don't have a better way to say it man of scalco
men of scalco men of scalco i don't know medicine calca calico medicine calico very
malice calco calico um so anyway preachingfund.com uh we need uh three billion dollars after uh
patreon fees sebastian
man of scalco so actually nailed the last name and blew the first name with the the hard part
versus the easy part there sebastian man of scalco that's that's so funny i only listened to the last
name because that's the part that i just have no idea yeah yeah um yeah or go to we'll show them
dot org oh my god and uh and we can this is how it's done dot org it lemur creamer is a with more
animatronics it would be more animatronics as soon as i had the time to do that i would have
had like crate if i had crazy i would have me a showbiz pizza slash chucky cheese i'd have you
you would have a basically an animatronic museum it would be i've got that showbiz pizza i've got
that chucky cheese i've got that combination showbiz showbiz pizza and chucky cheese it would
be both for sure i would have all of them i'd have chucky and the and the pizza time theater band
with pasquale and all the other dips and i'd have everybody with the rock of fire explosion for
get about it oh man guys be amazing some sense really come up in the chat i mean if you take a
billion we usually get at least you know 200 people to come out to scoop fest if we just
charge five million a ticket it's done a billion done deal all right i'm gonna tell you what for
the five million dollar vip ticket yes you're gonna get a lot of attention from us you would
get away with a lot of personal attention you would get away with a lot speaking of which seems to
be the case with our entire governmental system speaking of uh of five million dollar scoop fests
yes we have a guest here we're gonna have have him pop on here jd would you unmute yourself please
i said jd would you unmute yourself please
so happy to be here good to see you jd how are you i'm gonna leave that in
entire pause in oh jesus everyone's gonna assume like some episode error happened
i'm good very good we're uh we're working on the uh the documentary and uh we're gonna launch a
go fund me to kind of help raise some finishing funds so remind everyone about the documentary
in general what is the documentary the documentary about scoops so we were at scoop fest a lot of you
did interviews with us and and we got some great footage
and we're probably about 75 to 80 there as far as what we need um right now we have a like a four and
a half hour rough cut oh man but we still need to fill in those spots so we need to interview jacob
sj matt sarah and penn we couldn't get penn at scoops because he was sick yeah oh we need to get
that crew back to vegas they were um a volunteer crew friends of friends um and they're all in l.a
back at some point when everybody's schedule lines up and get all these interviews again
um we also need a little bit cash for our art musicians so uh spadoni's doing the music um we
got brogan and ryer doing some logos for us and we want to make sure all those people get a little
trash in their pocket yeah and then at the end we're gonna we're gonna submit uh the festival
or the film to festivals actual festivals so we we want to take it old school
like we used to do about 25 years ago and and hopefully we can travel around and show it or
maybe we'll end up selling it we'll see what oh it's so exciting yeah it's uh super fun so i'll
post the um the gofundme link so i can figure it out well yeah you're gonna post the gofundme
link in the chat here so the people on uh on zoom can see it and we will post that along
with the episode description for this very episode that everybody is listening to
and of course all over the social medias and everything so yeah go uh go check that out
this is the part of the show where we listen to jd figure out how to copy and paste it's pretty
great it's solid it's solid material he actually turned his camera off for a second it's pretty
exciting the coolest thing the coolest thing is that uh you know with with any luck this gets
a little traction somewhere and generates a little buzz and then who knows what could happen
with the podcast maybe we could start doing some live shows around the the country tour with the
with the movie maybe even the goal is for two thousand six hundred dollars that's the start
the way that gofundme it gears it up so the the full goal is ten thousand but you get paid out
before that
got it okay okay it's actually it's way better than like kickstarter or anything especially for
this since we don't have to get randos to find it and be interested in it we can kind of community
hopefully community uh raise some money for that it's a reasonable it's a reasonable amount of
money to fundraise it's not it's not it's not a astronomical yeah and you know i kind of maxed
out my friend for the production right yeah right if you promise to take the light of consciousness
to mars and be able to do that i'm not going to do that i'm not going to do that i'm not going to
beyond. You can ask for a trillion dollars.
Do you know that?
What would we do with the other
$999 billion?
Don't worry
about that. We got that covered.
We have a very interesting experiment
we're going to do. I think a lot of people are going to be very
interested. I have some plans.
You know how you can eat sushi off of people
at fancy restaurants, JD?
Just like a lot of people.
Like a lot of people.
A train track of people with sushi
on them.
I'm going to launch my dream, which is
Spicy Tuna Train to Chicago,
where we just eat our way.
I'm on.
Hey, hey, we're on a spicy tuna
train to Chicago.
The musical rights itself, and those rights
are just ours afterward. We can't stop
making money once we do it.
Can't stop. Won't stop.
But it all starts with this
GoFundMe.
Yeah, and we're going to get it
in front of Netflix, because we have connections
there, and
we know people from
the
De Niro Film Festival
in Tribeca, in New York.
Oh, wow.
Can we ask you, JD, when you go in front of your
friends, because I know you brought investors
to see me at the Magic Castle,
what do you tell them
when you tell them you want to make a movie
about us? What do you say to these people?
That's very funny
they bring up. So, those were our producers
that you met, and they were at
Scoop Dubs with us, and
I told them I wanted to
do this, and he just said, yeah, I'll help you. Whatever you need.
Let's do it. And I said, okay,
Matt's going to be in L.A. Let's go take a
look. And he was hemming and hawing about it.
He wasn't very interested. I, you know,
sent him a podcast. They didn't listen to it.
And then when they saw
you, when they saw you perform,
I saw him get excited.
They're already smart people.
Yeah. Anyway,
oh, now I kind of get what you're doing.
Really?
Yeah, yeah. He got excited,
and, you know, he's one of my
oldest friends in the world, and once I saw him,
he got up on stage with you doing something,
and he saw his eyes light up,
and then I had him.
So, there you go.
Matt pulled out the fish, and the light bulb
turned on. The clown was in that show.
Matt busted out the clown,
jump-scared the clown. I think I had a fish
and a clown in that show. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know me. Production.
Production, baby. Production, production, production.
Yeah, but my pitch
to people about it is, like,
this is a very unique community
that I'm just starting to
find out about, and now
I've just found out about Adopt-A-Scoop and all the
stuff they do during the holidays. It's fucking
amazing. And the amount of
love and acceptance
and
joyfulness that's in this community
just blew me away, and that's why I asked
to do this.
If this doc can get made,
and really get out there, and a lot
of people can see it, it will be
doing Matt and Paul and I
a personal favor on
a different level than I think anybody has really
thought about, and that is when we have
to explain to people who aren't in this
community what this community
is like, we can now just
point at a documentary
and say, watch this,
because I don't know how to explain it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, that was the hardest thing.
People are like, what are you doing? And even the scoops.
When we were at ScoopFest,
and get everybody to sign the releases,
several people were like, I don't know
what you're doing. What is this? What's this about?
And then I had to try to explain it,
that this is about exploring this amazing
community that's grown organically
over the past 10, 12 years.
And they're like, oh, okay, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Myra makes a good point in the chat, which is like a scoop
speeding up outside of ScoopFest, like without
us, they just all get up together and meet up
with each other. We love seeing
players of that, and people
let us know that they got together. It's like the coolest
feeling.
Yeah, we got a couple of those stories in our interviews,
and I was just, like I said,
the whole community just blows me away.
Carl Dribelbus, Carl is welcome
in this community, and he's not welcome in any other community.
He's not welcome
to hang out with anyone.
And there's a tolerance level
in this community that's higher than anyone
he's ever worked with, any
bowling team he's joined,
any poker club.
They've all gotten rid of him.
His family.
He's still just thriving here.
We should say that J.D.'s plug for the GoFundMe
is also sponsored. It's brought to you
by the following sponsor.
That's right. It's brought to you by the following sponsor.
Today's show, no, I'm sorry.
The Hey Scoops documentary
Hey Scoops documentary
GoFundMe is brought to you by
Billy from
Boston's Baked Bean Ice Cream.
Ice Cream. That's right. That's from Florida Man
in 2024. That's Billy from Boston's
Baked Bean Ice Cream.
Hey there. How you doing?
I'm Billy from Boston. I got Baked Beans
Ice Creams. You want
some? Yeah, you would,
chucklehead. Yeah.
Go ahead and sample
a little taste. How's your sister?
Why don't you let her know I'm looking for, huh?
Huh? Trying to talk to her.
I'm trying to talk to your sister. What's going on?
Huh? Huh? I just came in for ice cream.
How did you know I had a sister?
Oh, I can tell by the rings on your neck,
you jabroni.
Alright,
well, yeah.
If I don't have to pay, if I can just get
ice cream, you fuck my sister, I'm in. Oh, you're gonna pay,
pal. Yeah, you're gonna pay big time.
How about them apples?
Whoa.
Hey, bro,
did you get me my ice cream yet? You know what?
Get back in the car.
You know what? Bring her over here.
Hurry up. That's your sister I'm trying to talk
at. Hey, come here.
Come here, cute sister. Come here.
Oh, who are you? Don't worry
about it. I'm the guy.
Come on over here and have some of my
baked blueberries. How mysterious.
I got
some mystery baked bean ice cream in the back.
I can't wait. Oh, you're gonna
wait. That's my favorite kind of ice cream. Yeah.
Yeah. Alright, pal. It's on
the house because I got a date with your sister.
Now. Alright.
Thank you, Billy, from the baked bean ice cream company.
You're welcome.
How about them apples? I'll get my own ride home,
Matt. I'll see you later.
That's right. I'm gonna crack her like the
Liberty Bell. What do you think?
What?
Philly.
I was just gonna say the
Liberty Bell is not a Boston reference.
It's Boston. It's totally Boston.
I'm gonna
get her wedded in the tea
harbor. There we go. How about that?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Boston teapot.
I'm already halfway there. Yeah, I'm gonna turn
her into a freaking teapot. Oh, it's the same color
too. That's right. Get
ready. I don't want to hear about my sister's
tea harbor. Oh,
you don't? No.
I can tell you already have a bunch. Not since last
Christmas.
Well, we all, of course, every Christmas we update
the family on our tea harbors.
That's a given. Nobody's talking
to you anymore, stack of dimes. You need to
hit the arches.
I don't know.
No kidding. No kidding.
My box
is all over the fucking
map.
That was more
drifting than the Tokyo drift
on that accent there.
I do not have a Boston accent.
I mean,
it was like, we're going out to
the barbershop. We're gonna
go get a bar. We're gonna go to the
barbershop. You think you're better than me?
You think you're better than me?
Eh? Eh?
Boston. Tea
party. Boston.
Pack your car. That's
it. There you go. Pack your car in the
harbor. Bring your
sister over here, pencil neck.
Come over here, stack of dimes.
Let's go.
Pack your car.
That last sponsor ran so long, it's
time for the next sponsor. Oh, jeez.
Wow.
Boston represent.
I really brought it home.
Okay, I have a serious...
What you need is your Mayor Quimby. You need a
Mayor Quimby to get through it.
But they're not from Boston, are they?
He's Kennedy. He's Massachusetts.
Does that work? Yeah. Better than what you
did, yeah. I'll accept it. Oh, my God.
Well, if I'd have known that, I would have done
that. All right. All right. Take two.
Hey, there.
I got Boston baked bean
delicious ice cream.
Go ahead and sample some.
How about them apples?
Would you like some? Hey, I'd like
to date your sister. Bring her over
here. Oh, me?
Nobody's talking to you anymore, stack of
dimes. Come over here. I'm gonna
crack you like the Liberty Bell.
Come over here.
Liberty Bell's still out. Liberty Bell's still out.
Come on over here.
I'm gonna go under and through you like
the Great Arch. Like the
Great Arch. No, that's St. Louis.
No, come on. I'm sure that was there.
I'm pretty sure.
I could be wrong.
Park your car.
Spot on. Spot on.
Get me some ice cream with baked beans
in it. Your accent is so authentic.
I'm so desperate to crack you
like the Liberty Bell, you freak.
You little freaky thing, you
weird little sister
girl. Come explore
my Grand Canyon. Yes, just
like our majestic Grand Canyon.
One of the wonders of Boston. On the right
side of the Mississippi. The Grand Canyon.
One of the wonders of
the world. Boston's Grand
Canyon. Oh, look, it's the Mississippi.
Here in Boston.
Turns out, it's
your mom. Your mom is the Grand Canyon
of Boston, you stack of dimes.
Yeah. Planes can
see you when they're flying overhead. They go, hey,
check it to your left. Look out the
window, and you might just see the most
cavernous vajay
that ever walked.
You've actually got grad
students still stuck in you.
Vaginal
cavity. I know you do.
Don't
lie about it. I'm going to crack
you like the Liberty Bell.
Oh, good
news. Twitch just gave us a big upgrade.
Oh, no, never mind. They took it away.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. We're going to crack them like
a stack of dimes.
I love stack
of dimes. I think that's my favorite insult.
I think I'm going to just keep using it.
Production meeting.
Good. Okay. No, I
have a serious question for
JD. Ah, okay.
JD, come on back.
This is good.
Because we were supposed to put it in the last episode,
so now we're putting him twice in this episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unless he left. Did he leave?
Oh, there he is. So, JD,
I am a physical
media snob.
Is there a chance that there is a tier
for production
of a DVD or
Blu-ray? There's no
tiers on a GoFundMe.
Huh? There are tiers on
GoFundMes. Aren't there?
Oh, no. I'm thinking Kickstarter.
Kickstarter. Sorry, I got confused.
Paul, I'm in the same boat with you.
I love physical media. I like buying music
on vinyl. So, I have
two goals with this, and one of them
definitely is to put it to Blu-ray.
The other one is to get
your album printed to vinyl.
Well, that's
good, because we owe
like 25 people that.
We owe people some vinyl copies. We really do.
That could kill two birds with one stone.
I still feel bad about that. That's like one of the
only things we've ever kind of...
Really fucked up. I think it's the only thing that we ever
missed. Yeah. Yeah. Like, ever fully missed.
And people have been very kind about it. The company that we were
going to use to
make the vinyl no longer is a
company. Yeah, that's a
strike against us. Yeah.
It's actually pretty easy to do nowadays.
There's lots of companies that'll do it
for you. It really has changed, even
since we recorded the album.
It's a lot more prevalent, even in just
a couple years here, yeah.
We recorded the album
18 years ago, so yeah.
I did.
Oh, that'd be awesome, J.D.
Sidoni's doing the music for
the documentary as well.
So maybe there's...
Tag that on, make it a soundtrack
collaboration album, whole big thing.
Yeah, we'll figure it out.
Yeah, I would love to do that kind of stuff.
I do love comic books and stuff like that.
Yeah, and well, with you mentioning
there's a four-hour rough cut already,
are we going to be able to get
behind-the-scenes deleted footage
and all that, too? That's what I'd love.
J.D., I think what Paul's asking for his final...
Final cut. Can he have...
Yeah, I do not.
No, last question.
Last question. What's the working title?
Is there a working title?
Working title right now is just Hey, Scoops the Movie.
I haven't come up with anything better,
but I like it, and it kind of...
It is what it is.
Yeah, it says everything,
and it directs people to our website,
so...
J.D., here's Paul,
always thinking about
shuffling people to their own website.
J.D., I don't know
what the fuck to even...
J.D., how far
can Paul
put this cart ahead of the horse
before you can't see the cart anymore?
Paul is talking about the trilogy now.
How much is a booth at Comic-Con,
and what are we giving out?
Hey, that's a great idea, man.
Yeah.
I'm here for it all.
If we did a booth at Comic-Con,
you know what we could do, Matt?
You know what we could do? Seriously?
We could doctor it up like a stage,
and we could put on 15-minute improv shows
every hour, and it would be one of the most
popular booths in all of Comic-Con-dom.
There we go.
A while back, remember, we really were trying to figure out a way to do
improv shows, bucket shows,
at Comic-Con. We did look into that.
It would have been
a good idea.
There's a rumor that Comic-Con is moving to Vegas, too.
Yeah, that's a rumor.
That'll make it easier to do the show,
for sure.
It will make it easier.
I think maybe we even need to look into
PAX or some other
smaller video game
cons.
Smaller cons would be the way to go,
and it would be interesting that we're supplying entertainment
at a con that doesn't have evening
entertainment. That would be a smart move.
That's the way to go.
One other person I wanted to shout out real quick
is Wayne Geo,
who is doing our animation.
Joe Benazzi.
That's my Boston accent.
He's done how many movies?
He's doing an intro to our movie.
Oh, wow. So cool.
Yeah, and it's
fucking hilarious.
He's great. I love his style.
He's so good.
That's so cool.
That makes me kind of jump a little bit.
That makes my heart really happy,
because one of my all-time favorite films
is Christmas Vacation,
and that whole intro is animated.
Yeah, and a lot
of great films started with animated
stuff, so that's
awesome.
One of the greatest artistic casualties
in my life is that
when I stopped wearing overalls
and started wearing a performance tuxedo,
I stopped.
I stopped being a muse to Joe Benazzi.
I stopped appearing in his cartoons.
It's good to know that
at least we can pay him to get back
on the wagon, so that's good.
Yeah, it's pretty epic.
I can't wait to show people.
It's spectacular.
Great. Well, that alone
makes me thrilled, too, that you're
already pleased with the product
and excited about how it's going to go
with the final edit and everything.
Yeah, that's really fun.
I'm crowdsourcing this within the
community.
I'm making sure that they have
input on this and
are along for the whole ride.
It's been an awesome experience.
I can't wait to finish it and show everybody.
Well, there you go, guys. We're almost across the finish line
with the movie, so please help out if you
can. Even a dollar will probably
help us get to that goal quicker.
But not that much. I mean, it won't help that much.
Nah, yeah. I mean, it'll help.
It'll help. It won't be nothing.
It won't help that much.
Kick it up to two dollars.
But you're going to take all the time to fill out the form
for a dollar?
I will. I will fill it out
for a dollar. Do ten bucks.
Yeah. Ten bucks.
It's on GoFundMe. Go check
it out. It's HeyScoopsTheMovie.
The campaign is called Help Finish
HeyScoopsTheMovie.
So if you're searching for it, do that.
Also, the link for it is up on our social media.
It's up on the episode
description for this show. Go over there.
Help it out. It's going to be a really
interesting project, and I think everybody's
going to be super interested
and fascinated.
in how it turns out. I know I'm going to be.
It's like, however
you acquire that dollar, just do that five
more times before you fill out the form
is what I'm saying. There you go.
Just find a way
to make that dollar five dollars, I think.
Maybe like a couple of you go
in, like a couple of you people who are doing
the dollars, like go in together.
Like find four friends,
and all of you go in together on a fiver.
This is starting to sound like a pyramid
scheme, Jacob. No, no, no.
This is a GoFundMe.
It's a whole different thing. Jacob, if those five people
just find five more people each, then that'll
make it much easier. And they find five people, and
they find five people. Oh, when it comes out of your
mouth, Paul, I hear it.
Yep, yep. Especially when he does
that tone of voice. Boy, that's not the first time
I've heard that.
It was usually about the pet bird that we had
as kids.
What the hell are you talking about?
When it comes out of your mouth, Paul, I hear it.
That was the only thing. Otherwise,
you couldn't hear the bird.
Yeah.
Yep.
We had no bird
for long.
No, we had no bird.
What? You were being Sylvester.
Good God, gross.
I would not, no. I mean,
they told me it was a swallow, so.
No, we had no bird.
We had no bird.
Why are you yelling at us?
Because I don't want people thinking I put a bird
in my mouth for prolonged periods of time.
As a child. I didn't.
He did, but he doesn't want you to think that.
Look, it was for a joke.
The more you say it, the more
we think you actually probably had a bird in your mouth
as a kid. I know.
No one else brought this up.
Which is now an even better bit.
Now it's weird, which I love it.
Because now it's like, did he put a bird
in his mouth for a long time? Probably.
I mean, who knows? Also, it was Kentucky.
Right?
Who can say?
It'd be like, I'd be the Roger Whitaker.
Sing, sing, sing
Kentucky songbird.
Wing, wing, wing your love to me.
I spent too much
time traveling on my own.
Kentucky songbird, I'm
coming home.
I put it in my mouth.
You can't hear it anymore.
You know who else is very excited
about that Kentucky songbird?
As well as JD's second appearance on this
episode. And that is the following.
Sponsor. Paul Mattingly's
Illustrated Guide to Feeding a Fed
Horse. That's PETA approved
idiom edition slash
Boston edition.
Anybody
interested in feeding this horse?
I'm about to crack it like the Liberty Bell.
Go ahead and get yourself some birds
and stick it in the horse's mouth.
Two birds in the horse is worth one
in the bush, which I just cracked
like the Liberty Bell. Horse
Bush Crackin'.
Horse Bush Crackin'.
How about them apples, horse?
You can lead a horse to a bird's
nest, but you can't make him put a bird in his mouth.
Enter Hay Scoops at checkout.
Nest. Yes, and that was the PETA approved
version of that. Horse nest.
Horse nest. This is a
horse house.
That was from Frozen Cusser, by the way.
Thanks, Frozen Cusser. Good stuff.
I did not ever put a
bird in my mouth for prolonged periods of
time. No one believes you.
Great. This is what I'm saying. This is my new
bit. This is my new thing about me
maybe or maybe not putting a bird in my
mouth. He definitely did.
I'm not saying one way or the other
now.
We were
backstage for the first
Hillbill shows. Those baby chicks,
they would come out kind of wet.
Oh, yeah.
I think Paul
put them in his mouth.
From my mouth juices.
Um, I
you know, what happens is, you
know, I think we had an episode. I thought we already
had the episode title, but Paul's
mouth juices. The thing
is, you know, the birds don't
realize it because they're in there
and it's warm and it's nice and dark.
But the digestion
process has begun.
That's wave one of the
digestion process, right?
The mouth, the mouth juices.
Yeah, our stone faces aren't because we don't
understand what you're saying.
Okay.
Remember when that one bird
came out and looked all
like it was plucked?
Listen, as someone who is the
owner of Schmiki and Schmuki, all this bird
talk is really kind of just just bring. Oh, my
God. How many more birds has
escape artist Schmiki
gotten away with now? Because they
they're getting out and killing birds at night now, right?
Well,
she was at it again last night. I had to
literally put like a bunch of things in front of the door.
Wait a minute.
I just saw. Hold on.
I want to hear this, but
Nick Newman has just shared
an astounding fact.
He claims horse saliva
does not have digestive properties.
What?
Again, that's why I had to breaking
news this.
So like, how do they
wait? So they chew, chew, chew.
So they're just totally chewing. No, no
additional help from.
I mean,
there's stuff inside their inside their gut,
but it unlike
with humans, where with humans.
The digestive
process begins with the mouth juices.
All right. Where is where is Newman? See here?
It'd
be weird if he wasn't
because he's typed in the chat.
Right, right.
It'd be really weird if he's just typing
rando stuff and just guessed
on that. He wouldn't have guessed on that.
Not in a million years. Could you guess about mouth
juices? He might be at work and not able
to talk, though. Where did he go?
Hey, what's going on?
There he is. Okay.
Well, how the hell does the horse
digestive work if they're if they're saliva
doesn't have any digestive properties?
Yeah, their saliva has had no enzymes.
It is. It is just a
lubricant and
the digestion doesn't start until their guts.
Yeah,
it's just a lubricant.
That's why they're so dismissive of a lubricant.
There's just a lubricant.
That's why they're big old mushy
snout. It's more cushion for the pushing.
So when we give medicine,
we have to be aware of that, that the
medicine will not
start. You can't give sublingual
medication to a horse. It has to get to their
gut before it can.
Podcast.
Okay. Now, now that we
have you here and with your horse facts, okay,
we discussed that a wolf
used someone else's crab trap, right?
My cats have learned to escape from their
own cat. Now, in
Sweden, birds have figured out how to
convert litter
into food. Have you seen this?
No, no. Litter?
In Sweden. Like cat litter?
No, like
refuse. Just regular trash?
Yes. So they have
so they've set up machines
where if you bring
basically garbage to this machine,
the machine will take it in
and then give out bird seed as a
thank you. And so
birds have started cleaning up around
parks in Sweden. Oh, my.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So they're not actually converting.
They're not like, it's not Mr. Fusion type
science. They're not converting.
I thought you were, I thought you were saying like
they're learning how to eat cigarette
butts. No, no, no. That's what I thought.
And then I thought, man, I'm never
going to put one of those nicotine
addicted birds in my mouth again.
No, but the birds collect
trash, put it in a receptacle,
the receptacle
once having obtained the trash
gives out some bird seed
as a reward for the bird doing it.
Crows are going to love this.
It's a startup project in Sweden
by a company called Corvid Cleaning
and they're training wild
crows to pick up litter.
What did I just say?
And I certainly have not put a crow in my mouth
all the way.
All the way? All the way.
So some of the way you have?
I didn't say that.
Okay. Seems like the qualifier implies
that you can't ever know.
You'll never know. Seems like a weird
thing to bring up. You'll never know.
That's between me and author James
O'Barr. Yeah.
Newman, what is the smartest thing
you've ever seen a horse do?
I had a horse. He's a racehorse named
King Sonic.
And if we didn't fill his water
bucket, like if his
water bucket in the stall got too low,
he would shit in it.
Whoa.
And I
believe he would
realize that I was irritated
with the shit I had to clean out of this bucket.
And he'd be like,
if you don't fill your bucket,
you're going to get cleaned.
And he had a full bucket at all times.
But he tried.
Matt, did you ever have any patrons like that
when you were a bartender?
Yes. Holding their empty beer glass,
if I took too long, they just
shat in their beer glass and put it up on the thing
and be like, oh, do you want to get me
a beer?
That's why Matt stopped allowing patrons
with kilts into the restaurant.
I was like, I really got to keep my
keep up my laps around this Tierney's bar
or else it'll be glasses of poop.
I did not get me beer for like
three minutes. So here you go,
Sonny. You got a pint
of Guinness crap.
You got a pint of poop?
A pint of poo. A pint
of the old
hot brown.
Enjoy it.
We did have a woman who would come into the bar
typically on Sunday afternoons
and she
loved the taste of
bass beer.
Bass ale?
Yeah, bass ale.
But if she had
too much beer,
she would blow up the
restroom, like just
destroy it.
Yeah.
Like,
hover and destroy.
Oh, no.
The hovering is the worst.
And just turn the women's bathroom
into a super
fun site. Oh, somebody gave
her her fifth bass ale
and they didn't realize
she's about to crack that bathroom
like the Liberty Bell.
And because she was
a tiny... She cracked it!
She cracked it like the Liberty Bell.
How about them apples, eh?
That is a spot on Boston accent,
Paul.
That's right.
Look out for the Grand Canyon
known as your mama's twat.
What? That's right.
That's a Grand Canyon...
I'm sorry, are you Scottish?
Are you Scottish?
I didn't know.
I don't know.
Scooping over girls'
piff here.
So because
she was a petite woman,
it took us a very long time
to put two and two together
that this was happening.
Because the Sunday Day crowd
didn't attract a lot of women.
So therefore, we weren't going to the women's bathroom
very often in the shift
to check things out, right?
And it took us... It was Pat,
my buddy Pat, who finally was figuring out
that this woman, if she had a second beer,
would like shit herself all over.
The thing...
So now here's my question to you.
To you, Matt. Here's my question to you.
So we all have feverish flashbacks, right?
Because, you know, someone finishes a beer, you go,
you want another one? Whatever.
And I used to always make fun of the fact that she would giggle
and be like, oh, really? Oh, uh...
Oh, shoot.
And she was like, uh, yes, I suppose.
She got really excited about getting that second beer.
Because she was playing
Russian roulette with her asshole?
Yes.
And I was like, oh my god, that explains why she was so fucking weird
every time I offered her a second beer.
That's really funny.
This is my question to you.
Yeah.
Fucking howitzer back there.
In your theorizing. Well, this is what I'm wondering, Jacob.
Is... What do you guys envision?
Are we thinking like
a whoopee cushion type
flapping action?
Or are we talking like
a hole so tight it's like
putting your thumb over the end of a garden hose
thus causing all the crazy...
Was she just really
clenched back there
and that was what caused everything going crazy?
Or was it all flippity-flappity?
No, I think she's too loose.
I think your flippity-flappity is right on.
She's flippity-flappity. All right.
She's flippity-flappity.
All right.
There's no way she's going to make it home, right?
Well, I tell you what.
I'm going to start peeping on the girls
drinking the bass ale at the bars
because I got the flippity-flappity going on.
Because you like that hot brown.
I'm down for the flippity-flappity.
Nobody tell Ann.
What?
She's like, yeah, Paul Mattingly will go to a bar.
I'm going to go to a bar.
Any minute now.
That's really funny, man.
Yeah.
And that really explained her odd behavior.
Yes.
Did she ever cop
to blowing up the bathroom?
Was she subtle enough?
Could you smell it on her when she got out?
You say it went everywhere.
She was still pretty clean?
She did not come out looking like a dirty gal?
I think she didn't come out like a...
A poop scarecrow?
Yeah.
Can you imagine?
She came out covered in shit and hay
and she's just like,
I don't know what happened.
I got attacked by someone dressed up
like the Wizard of Oz.
I believe she would leave after she
fucked the bathroom.
Oh.
So you couldn't get a real good look.
Yeah, was it?
Did anybody see any...
Did she ever, like, trail anything out of the
restaurant?
Was there ever, like, a...
It's not that I don't appreciate your questions, Paul.
It's that...
He signed an NDA.
The answer to all these questions means
we would have figured it out was her sooner
than we did.
It took us a while to decipher.
It doesn't necessarily...
You wouldn't necessarily have been able to follow the trail.
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, if you look at the floor of Tierney's...
If you look at the floor of Tierney's Tavern,
it's on the same floor.
This is 1938.
She might have walked backwards to throw you off.
She might have done some weird, tricky...
And, like, gestured to things on, like,
the shelves and stuff, just pointing.
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
As she's leaving.
And then suddenly you look down and there's just...
She was doing card tricks on her way out
just so you wouldn't look at her feet.
There's this thin stream going on.
She's going all the way from the bathroom.
You're like, what the hell?
No, and then...
I've heard of a snail trail, but this is ridiculous.
So we eventually kept the one-beer rule.
She would come in, we'd have a beer,
and then we would just ignore her until she left.
I bet she was relieved in a lot of ways.
And then not relieved in some other ways.
She was more relieved after a second bath.
Oh.
Yeah.
More like ass ale.
Am I right?
Exactly.
Ass ale.
Ass bale.
Move the B over.
While we've been talking, I've been doing some internet searches
while we've been talking because my Google search history
is not weird enough.
And apparently a lot of people complain about bass
making them shit themselves.
Apparently it's not an uncommon critique of bass ale.
What is the diuretic in bass ale?
Well, all liquor is a bit of a diuretic.
Oh, really, Professor Jacob?
Do tell.
I just did.
That's where you're suspicious of Jacob's science and saying
all liquor is a sense of dung.
I just want to know more.
Apparently someone...
I mean, I didn't have to ask him anything.
He's just like, right off the cuff, he's like,
Oh, yes, well, it turns out that all liquor has certain medications
or properties that...
I did not use my Boston accent.
They often cause the flappity-flappity to go very short and brown.
Yeast and gas.
Alcohol increases your gut moddily.
Things move through you faster.
I don't know.
M-O-T-I-L-I-T-Y.
Modality.
M-O-T-I-L-I-T-Y?
Motility?
Motility.
Yeah, motility.
Yeah, motility, yeah.
I guess, sure.
Motility.
Things move through you faster.
Your body has less time to absorb water,
and that makes looser, quicker bowel movements.
All right.
Well, if you're bound up like a cat in a cage, maybe have a bass.
They should start branding it that way.
Why don't they start branding it?
We can do a whole new Big Mouth Billy Bass.
Why is there not Bass Ale next to the...
Prune juice in the old person's section at the store?
Why isn't there?
Yeah, why isn't there?
Probably because of liquor laws, but it's stupid.
Ah, okay.
Maybe they could put prune juice next to the Bass Ale in the liquor cabinet
so people would get the idea.
I'm also curious.
It was black and tans, right?
Yeah.
That's where people do half bass.
That's no way to speak of her.
Half Guinness, half Bass Ale is called a black and tan.
Oh, is that right?
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought for a second you were turning into an ice agent.
Go ahead.
Oh, my God.
Have you heard that song?
Yeah.
Jesse Elms, is that his name?
Yeah, it's fucking great.
I've been following him on TikTok for a minute.
Really well written.
On a lot of different socials.
He has some really cutting songs.
I guess his first album just came out.
He's blowing up.
Jesse Wells.
Oh, good for him.
He's so good.
Have you heard any of his stuff?
Jacob?
Yeah, I have.
I know him from social media.
Oh, yeah.
Folk singer.
Really, really strong.
No, I didn't know he had an album.
That's really cool.
His Join Ice song is South Park level, scathing and well written.
I did hear, I heard clips of this.
This was, it was amazing.
Yeah, that's interesting.
That's an interesting thing to note, Matt.
I would be surprised if he doesn't get tapped to put together some sort of musical.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
If you say right for South Park, which is not the gift that you think,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Put together his own musical.
You talk to anyone who's ever.
Yeah, yeah.
I just think it's a fun fact for people to know is if you ever listen to anyone who's
ever been tapped by South Park to be a writer, it is a brutal, crazy ass process to be.
Unless you're, unless you're a hater, right?
He had, he's the only one that had fun with it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But he'd already made his bones, so he didn't have to sweat it.
He was already Bill Hader.
Yeah.
But yeah, anyhow, sorry.
I got distracted because I heard it this morning and I was just like,
my jaw was on the floor.
I was like, good Lord, this song.
So a black and tan.
Yes.
Do you think that would be a proper diuretic remedy?
Um, it would, it would slow things down.
Right.
Cause the, uh, I don't think stout has the same effect.
Oh, oh, so it's like, Oh, no, I'm saying, no, I don't even know what mortality means.
So maybe I shouldn't be saying what it's like.
Going to Chili's.
I down a fifth of Pepto-Bismol.
Before I eat my triple dipper.
So it all kind of works out in the wash.
I got you.
That's why he is a motherfucking professional.
I mean, yeah, pre-pepto, I call it my Pepto talk.
I'm giving my system, the Pepto talk, I guess.
Oh, what I was going to get at is that like, I don't go to bars nearly as often, but I don't even think bad.
I don't, I don't think bass is still on tap at tyrannies.
I haven't, what was the last time I've seen bass on tap anywhere is what I was trying to think of.
Is bass still like a bass?
It's around very, very often.
I think, I think it's, I think it's a, I think it's an old, old, I think it's gone the way of the.
Does it have, does it have fish in it?
Fish, fish oil.
That's what really gets it going.
It's the fish oil.
What do they call that?
What do they call it?
Omega three and omega six fats and the, uh, and the bass ale.
Omega three fatties.
That was your nickname for that, that crazy shitter later.
That's the name of this.
Oh, here comes omega three fatty.
If Jacob would put on a few LBs, we could be an omega three fatty.
Sorry.
God damn it.
I'm trying.
Omega three fatty.
I had dinner.
We're the alpha three fatty.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
Who are we kidding?
We're the beta three fatties.
We're the beta three family.
Speaking of betas, let's do a little jock versus nerd.
Yeah, Josie and the beta three fatties.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Beta three fatties.
Time for jock versus nerd.
Explosion.
A very slippery poop.
We got a scooper to come in.
to us today from keister sunday oh keister sunday thank you been a minute yeah this is a uh uh uh
what's that what's the thing the the uh the second movie sequel that's the movie where i can't think
of this is the sequel to keister sunday's last scooperty keister sunday says like most sequels
uh less work was put into it the categories are more 80s comedy more 80s horror more 80s action
and more 80s sci-fi matt you're up first what you want um i will do action please for 200
about that action i'm too old for this shit name that film i guess i thought i'm getting too old
for this shit i saw i'm too old for this right i thought it was i'm getting too old for this
shit but it might be i'm too old for this shit uh it's a uh uh lethal weapon yeah lethal weapon
is correct
paul i will take sci-fi for 800 let's go oh yeah it may be a case of being too ambitious for a
single movie which is why the recent adaptation is multiple films but this 1984 sci-fi epic
is the only movie david lynch regretted making for he is the quitsox it is dune
durex
my dune man i tell you those are becoming my favorite bedtime flicks i throw them on yeah
that'll put your right to bed i mean it no it's great i love playing them in the background but
they're really i love those movies though i got them on the blu-ray i love the new ones or the
old one the new ones are you watching uh alien earth i watched the first like four episodes
okay kind of
it kind of faded for me it started really strong i still like it are you did you are you in yeah
it took me a while to get through the first episode that i really like this uh second or
third episode and that's where i am up up to i still enjoy a lot of the concepts that are going
on with it uh i wasn't watching except i found out the guy behind it's the guy behind all the fargo
uh uh series shows okay i haven't watched any of the fargo shows so oh those are great okay
oh let's see i'll try um uh 80s comedy 200 lloyd bridges picked the wrong week to quit drinking
doing amphetamines and sniffing glue he sure did he did that on airplane yeah nice matt uh i'll go
back to action please back to action donnelly for 400 daily double all of it jacob i want to bet all
of it i feel the need
the need for speed tally day good night
my cokehead vegas bachelor party yeah um that is top top gun that is top gun top gun is correct
i would have messed that up what did you think it was i really thought it was uh days of thunder
oh no there you go there you go paul you're up uh sci-fi please for six for 600 yeah this is
so much better than the one and two disney daydlow classic starring the dude is way more boring than
you remember boo tron tron is correct i love tron that's a nice one to go to sleep to too
that is another good one it's a good but it's such a good movie it's so not i feel like it's
not the praise you think it is the filmmakers don't want to hear that that's for sure i love
tron i know i hear that i hear people say but i but it to me i don't know i don't know i don't know
there's that's a high level of praise that i fall asleep to your movie because it means it's my
it's a comfort movie for me and i've watched it a lot so anyway all right i'm telling you it doesn't
sound good i'm going i realize you're right i know that you're right i could have killed them
all i could have killed you in town you're the law out here it's me don't push it don't push it
or i'll give you a war you won't believe
this that was that a was that a truth social tweet what the
i believe this is uh first blood first blood is my answer oh good it is first blood jake right
yeah don't ask me rambo questions i will answer them matt johnny rambo i do declare uh
80s action 800 please you cold-blooded
bastard i'll tell you what i think of it i live to see you eat that contract but i hope you leave
enough room for my fist because i'm going to ram it in your stomach and break your goddamn spine
it's mommy dearest isn't it this is uh this is just from succession um i actually i actually
know this one am i right that arnold schwarzenegger is saying this you got it you got it that was i
was gonna i was gonna read it in that voice because that's how it goes that's how it's because i hope
you leave enough room for my fist because i'm going to ram it in your stomach and break your
goddamn spine is it break your goddamn spine i remember being such an awkward frame break your
goddamn spine yeah now the thing is i still don't know what movie this is but the contract makes me
think it's running man scooper nova girl is saying twins i think that's a good guess
no i think i think you're dead on uh running man is my guess jacob
running man is i'm sorry matt it's the running man oh damn it running man i'm sorry they're
remaking the running man it's already out and flopped dude it's already it already came out
made no money no no paul i hear they're remaking it man you say so maybe the third time's a charm
they're already making remaking the glenn powell version of running man
uh i'll keep at the the sci-fi
please for 400 all right daily double oh now now comes the big windfall daddy
my name is jacob in this fun 80s romp cardinal blick from dogma guides neo and one of the lost
boys to passing their history exam and creating world peace through the power of rock music
bill and ted's excellent adventure oh i'm sorry it's bogus journey i'm sorry it's bogus journey
no it's the first one bogus journey involves death adventure that's true yeah and he even
raps um i'll do um 80s comedy 400 a year before killing those people in ireland abe froman sausage
king of chicago is guilty of truancy but don't worry all around swell human being uh jeffrey
jones is on the case oh my god
oh my god that question that question i am so confused by that question oh i think i i think i
even get the no i get the references i don't even know what it's talking about before killing those
people in ireland abe froman sausage king of chicago is guilty of truancy but don't worry
all around swell human being jeffrey jones is on the case so do you know who jeffrey jones is
that's the that's the part that i'm missing i think i gotta pass
matt oh uh so the it's this is all matthew broderick uh the movie is ferris bueller's
day off and uh year before killing all those people in ireland is matthew broderick when he
was an actor uh killed a bunch of people in ireland and they basically paid off and covered
up the case uh he plays he said he lies and says he's abe froman sausage of chicago oh that's his
alias in that that's right and jeffrey technically i think uh cameron is the one that provides the
voice for abe froman oh i think you're right
is the guy got kicked out of the he plays the principal he's the one that's kicked out of the
beatles movie because he's a oh that guy bit of a diddler yes yeah yeah there you go there you go
ferris bueller's day off that's correct matt and uh matt it's your turn uh 80s comedy 600 please
the director of the smash hit dark shadows also made this little known film in the 80s starring
batman thelma and stephen baldwin's less talented brother
uh so that's michael keaton uh-huh uh michael keaton alec baldwin and uh
who plays i didn't get ferris bueller but i got this one well i mean you just talked about it man
the movie yeah essentially well there's an you talked about yeah you talked about it
okay uh
oh this is beetlejuice there you go
it's beetlejuice
now i get it paul i'll do horror for 800
and the sequels to this entirely unproblematic 80s slasher movie the boss's sister plays a
mentally deranged slash abused camp counselor obsessed with spreading summer camp spirit
with murder for some reason james earl jones's dad was in the first one
oh uh
huh uh
the sequels oh uh i think this is uh sleepaway camp all right it's sleepaway camp wow
got there
oh it's me i'll try i'll close out comedy 800 woody princess leia and rock and roll megastar
cory feldman suspect their new neighbor's brother theodore and his family of killing mr moody
that's the fucking burbs y'all yeah it is that was a weird one the weird one how dare you i never
like the burbs i'm sorry oh i like the burbs tom hanks fine enjoy the movie i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm
fine enjoy the burbs i thank you paul
also you're up i never put the burbs in my mouth
not all the way i would you would bring it up i would need to get all of the leftover questions
to beat paul uh oh yeah paul has 3600 matt has 2400 i have 1600 and there are no more daily
doubles left there are four questions left just try it and then have a grand total of 1400 points
to win the game and then you're done you're done you're done you're done you're done you're done
total yeah and i'm down by 1200 to paul so um i will do i will do 600 horror
rodney dangerfield's son in back to school plays a bullied teen who falls in actual love with his
58 plymouth fury in this carpenter classic this is a good flick good flick um god uh christine
christine that's it i'm sitting i'm over here in my head going like nadine charlene i was
please don't put unleaded in my tank what's what's the what's the i kept being like carrie's not
carrie carrie's not carrie carrie's not carrie that's what my brain was doing that's that's a
good loop it's still not carrie it's definitely not carrie it's definitely not carrie but you
are on it there's a lady with a c name that's right uh
what'd you say about my mom i said she's like the grand canyon i'd crack her like the liberty bell
uh 80s horror for 400 all right in this film directed by the author of the novella it's
adapting a fun uh melanin challenged fella just wants to share the joy of playing with his rubik's
cube oh geez
in this film directed by the author of the novella it's adapting a fun melanin challenged
fella just wants to share the joy of playing with his rubik's cube i i kind of want wait this is
horror uh yes that is the question that you ah yes yes yes this would be uh hellraiser hellraiser
of course
i was wondering what was taking you so long on that one because i thought for a minute it was
talking about soul man because he was melanin challenged oh i was like powder
powder's closer powder and pinhead are probably cousins
probably i never saw powder powder's supposed to be awful oh powder yeah no one did no one saw
that movie no i saw that movie in theaters and um yeah did you guys see
kevin spacey's homeless now i saw i saw that kevin spacey says that he's homeless yeah yes oh
poor old k-packs
i guess that k-packs uh residual money isn't coming in like it used to that idiot here's
the thing like why should why why get into this at all um uh we love walking on the tightrope baby
uh let's move on i'll say sci-fi for 200 that's where i'm going
i mean we all hate him that's all i'm saying for lloyd how to pronounce gigawatt
just that's the whole question is who the hell taught christopher lloyd how to pronounce gigawatt
did he not pronounce it correctly in back to the future which is the answer to this question
gigawatt did he say gigawatt or gigawatt he says gigawatts 1.21 gigawatts well there you go
i guess that's how you mispronounce it yeah and matt closing out the category and the game 80s
for 200
1984 classic a festively dressed burned victim tickles johnny depp in his sleep
until he's turned into a gravity defying blood typhoon it's true that is true all happened
for real it wasn't a nightmare it's all happening for real for real on this road
never meant to kill you in your dreams
i'm sorry for your terrible screams
uh matt that's your question oh it's me oh nightmare on elm street sorry there you go
sorry miss kruger it is a nightmare on elm street i thought it was yours i'm so sorry
oh no worries no it was the last one that is the game paul wins with 4 000 matt is in second with
3200 i'm in third with 1800 and that's from keister sunday thank you sunday thank you if
you want to send us in a scoop or your price of strike jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus
nerd or some scoop mail you can do all those things right over there at hey scoops.com go
over there it's on the home page make us uh jock versus nerd send us some scoop mail we love to
hear from you we need to hear from you it's part of the whole show it is um i was basically lost
in like trying to find how i was going to say the kevin spacey thing and not leave a curiosity and
worse things happening going to a future episode so um uh uh
on the one hand he was acquitted of everything he was never convicted uh he had one conviction
in a foreign court that was overturned and on the other hand you're not entitled to be a movie star
like uh like uh being a working actor is one thing being a star involves affection and you
can lose affection right and there are many people who've had their career take a downturn
for less controversial reasons who simply can't be actors anymore
right so the idea that kevin smith kevin smith kevin spacey let's not mix those two up
dr freud the idea that kevin spacey is homeless to me just simply says he's not willing to work
at any other job like you can do other things besides act he's and make money like you're not
like do something else yeah he's getting what he deserves what a show um yeah yeah
yeah i'm just i i don't i don't believe that he is destitute or anything like that yeah so i so i'm
just i just don't care about the the story at all it also means it also means like did you do
nothing with your money while you were like making all that money like what are you including just
putting it in a mattress or something yeah nothing like shack owns like 400 annie ann pretzels like
right get yourself a franchise buddy he has a pizza named after him get some buffalo wild
wings going yeah shakaroni we could be eating space or running pizza right now wondering what
it's named for we don't remember uh why aren't we taking those streets yet there's a trillionaire
oh all right i'm still waiting it is it is still raining that is that is a fine point
a very slick investment opportunity he could have invested in storage units called it kevin spacey's
um he did miss that one i want uh to thank uh jd for coming in the podcast go check out the fun me
and for putting together the documentary yeah the link is in the episode notes um and uh i want to
thank all the people supporters over on patreon in fact i have a list of them right now um and all
these people could do something else besides try to revive house of cards on netflix uh that's gross
is he even trying that really gross
dull whip scoop dipping dots jack dirty old scoop distiller scoop doc scoop don dotty don't say scoop
name doug lay dr science scoop dr scoop little dr tobias scoop a duck flamb duck scoop duane webb
uh ed short arms marcus ed ondrick ed wagner and ed less scoop the following people go off like
those dog fireworks that you lighten their ass poops out a thing as soon as you get them that
fourth bass ale gene zinc genetic scoop george kaskov gerardo garcia gizmo scoop greater sunday
scoop gravel scoop green wolf scoop grill sergeant scoops guy wade guar thock hatchet scoop heather
divine hansen holly marshmallow lightly house dad scoop hillian scoop i don't have a scoop name
ian a chapman ian soto ice cream manwich ice blue scoop i want a scoop baby
jacob dink laker and jake snyder uh the following people uh all can't wait to go to the lincoln
memorial in boston um edward bender eliza walzak elkton magic scoop uh eric nielsen erotic scrape
scoop evil monkey fade out scoop fifi finn stephenson flat kidney frankie's tiki scoop
freehold scoop freeze dried scoop frozen 49th scoop frozen cusser fudgy the whale uh galoo
lucia scoop galactic president star mc scoops a lot galen diggs garrett godfrey gas man scoop
gazpacho scoop gelato problems gelato steve and of course bossy the portuguese scoop because he's
here in chat and probably didn't get thanked another time there you go you well well done
well good good catch on that one these individuals are about to get cracked like the limity bell
james dawson james fox james hubbell james and fisher janine lankard jason klepper jason
horcostas jason speckland jason street jason vasquez jason victor jason yanowitz jay shapiro
jed taxon jeff bezair uh jeff faust jeff harris and jeff libby and the following scoops looked a
little too closely into my sister's tea harbor that's jeff loomis jimmy ebarb jeremy hudson
jesse rain jill short jimmy slonina john carter john glore john holshin gla john jacob scoopenheimer
schmidt johnny parker jonathan jordan campbell joseph foster joseph polaro josh katona josh rich
roberts joshua tar joshua wilson jay rock scoop juan galvez judy schneider justin robert young
kate mathis keister sunday keith uh robert corning scoop kelsey kundari ken fargi ken the soto kevin
chamberlain kevin dory kimchi douche scoop king scoop kiwi fruit scoop uh colin townie kristin
claddock kurt egner kurt henderson
la j lance amon larry goodale and latter day scoop thank you all so much we sure do appreciate you
thank you all so much if you want to hear your name read on air or receive a bunch of other
kinds of prizes and rewards head on over to preachingfund.com and select a tier that works
for you come visit preachingfund.com it's better than hanging with your mom
or if you too are looking forward to a hey scoops documentary just to help you explain
what all this is to other people head over to farts in a bag dot biz
that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preachingfund.com it takes you over to our
patreon page where for as little as three dollars you can help keep this show on the air this show
is dependent on our patreon supporters so if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars
preachingfund.com farts in a bag dot biz those are the places to go also of course you can also you
can always help us out by going to our shop that's over there at hey scoops.com slash shop how do you
get there door jingle door a big door it's on we got a store and that's part of our billionaire plan
because the percentage we get from our billionaires is a lot of money and that's part of our billionaires
from our shop we just need to sell a billion t-shirts and we'll become a billionaire hey you
know i've been getting inundated with t fury discount stuff they're having sales they're
having sales constantly so now is the time during this holiday yeah jump on there get go through
please go through our shop storefront and even if you don't buy any of our merch we get to wet
our beak a little bit and we really appreciate that hey scoops.com slash shop or store jingle
jingled.com also uh uh the patreon has now made it easier to give uh subscriptions as gifts um so
if you don't know what to ask for for christmas people like what do you want for christmas and
you're like i don't know you can give a patreon subscription to our show as an idea for one of
your gifts that you'd like there you go oh nice yeah and if you're at the ten dollar a month level
or more you get to come and hang out with us on an unrecorded zoom hang the next one
this month's one is happening next wednesday the day before thanksgiving believe it or don't
it happening my time 7 p.m eve yes the the time when the the line between the worlds is at its
thinnest so because because on thanksgiving you get fat thin goes out the window you know who can
join you in that chat now uh sarah fowler wolf who just upped her patreon pledge to
the ten dollar tier oh fantastic to that person so uh the invite has already gone out for those
of you who subscribe uh to the patreon look check your emails check your papers for openings check
your openings for papers it is in there you can grab onto that link and jump in on uh wednesday
at 7 p.m my time 4 p.m vegas time and come on by it's going to be a hoot nanny we're going to just
chill and talk nanny well
out i'll probably i'll probably bust out some toys we'll see what's going on
i think that's my plan is maybe just build some uh some lego or something i don't know nothing
too nothing too heavy we're just gonna talk we're just gonna hang out and chat and you know
we're gonna chat no no big whoop no big whoop just very heavy it'll be very heavy but it's
gonna be a lot of fun it's gonna be a lot of fun uh yeah yeah yeah yeah fun not guaranteed
all right well thanks for this everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
the movie
won't find me
let's make some magic y'all
what are you doing
see ya
bye