Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Oh man, it is Scoopfest here in Las Vegas!
Woooo!
Let me hear you, Scoops!
Of course we'd have a great night here with us.
Ohhhh!
It's time for Matt Madley's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting to my left is Paul Mattingly!
Left cross for me, that's Mr. Matt Donnelly!
On the knobs and tiles is Jacob the Audio Guy!
Oh I love that guy!
We're preaching fun!
Wooo!
How we doing, Scoopfest?
We've had a long Scoopfest.
Yeah, it's been a good one.
It's been a real good one.
You guys having a good Scoopfest so far?
Oh thank God, I'm glad it's not just me.
Yeah, it's been a blast.
It's been such a cool deal.
Of course, we've just always got to cap it off as our last kind of live event before we do the big jock versus nerd ball.
That's right!
So, got to bring back our boys.
Our brothers from another podcast.
The OO boys!
The OO boys, if you will.
Gentlemen, thanks for being here.
Oh man, it's the best.
It does not get better than hanging out at the Orleans at Scoopfest.
Is it just us?
I mean, just Las Vegas is the Orleans to me?
Everyone else is trying too hard, the Orleans?
Oh, in terms of like, if you really try to boil down Las Vegas.
I feel like every other building in this town is trying to be something they're not, except for the one that we're sitting in right now.
It's the most honest building in Las Vegas.
Yeah, right down to the three alligators playing jazz.
The iconography of authenticity, anthropomorphized alligators.
And also, just the sheer size.
When you walk in the Orleans, they're like 20 foot alligators.
Who turned in the drawings, they're like, "That's how much space you should take up when you walk into this place."
Yeah.
So, a long running joke that Brian and I have had whenever we've been at the Orleans is that nobody knows when the Bailey Wick is open.
Yes, always true.
And they've posted hours.
I've never seen, as far as I knew, it opened when somebody phased into existence inside of it.
There's no rhyme or reason.
You have properly summoned Bailey Wick.
Want a beer?
And they're even more fucked up.
It's only open from like 3 p.m. to 10.
In Las Vegas, at 10.
No, your premium bar.
Fuck you, get out.
It's like, "Oh, the place for live music and food and booze?"
Nope, after 10 o'clock, you are not allowed in here.
Just psychotic, just sociopathic behavior by the Bailey Wick.
Somebody do a Netflix series on the Bailey Wick.
Find out what skeletons are in that attic.
Bailey Wick Doc Series, TM, that is ours.
So, Brian, you have kept up your bit of asshole blackjack?
Oh, Jesus.
Now I know why he's homeless.
Alright.
Now I am homeless.
Okay, first of all, I was gambling with somebody who didn't like the idea of asshole blackjack.
Because he's somebody who feels like, "Hey man, gambling is supposed to be fun."
And you're like actively...
Does anybody not know? I don't know why I'm phrasing it this way.
We don't know it. What's asshole blackjack?
How do you explain asshole blackjack?
So, blackjack, game where cards come out.
People at tables get very mad if you are not playing correctly.
Quote, unquote, "by the book."
By the book, because they believe that the cards that you got by playing incorrectly or didn't get by playing incorrectly is affecting them.
And they want everyone, no matter who's sitting at the table, they want the table to play as a team as a whole against the dealer, not against each other.
That's how it's supposed to go, right?
So, what Brian does is the opposite.
Yes. Well, every so often, I'll play something a little bit off book or do something silly just because it's delightful when doing something wrong yields amazing results.
And then I hear to my left, "That was my ace," or whatever.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's like, okay, well then now we're no longer playing blackjack, we're playing asshole blackjack, which usually lasts about five minutes, and then the game is over and all my money is gone.
Right? Every so often, an epic run ends up happening, and Justin and I laugh and shout and make a lot of noise, chase everyone off, and then as we leave the table they say, "Excuse me, you dropped your Percocet."
Yes.
A true thing that happened, one of the first times we played asshole blackjack is we just infuriated a family from Alabama that were just like spitting fucking mad, and we could not stop laughing.
And then at the end, my Percocets fell out of my pocket.
Now, just collapsing this fucking caricature of a human into startling relief, "Oh, this just got real."
Now, as I was trying to explain the beauty of asshole blackjack is a piece of performance art, and I like to think of myself as a patron of the arts by spending all my money on asshole blackjack.
Good, good.
Jesse, our friend, had the mistaken impression that the point was to piss people off.
No, that is a side effect.
Ah, yes. That is righteous and good, but it is not the point.
That's right. The point is to bend reality just a little bit, and maybe, just maybe, you'll get lucky, and doing the wrong thing will yield something magical, right?
So, Jesse and I were playing blackjack, and eventually got down to just the two of us. Jesse did not believe in asshole blackjack. He didn't believe it would work, and he didn't much care for the idea of it.
And then I got dealt a five, and the dealer had a three face-up, and then I got dealt another five, and then a face-down card, right?
So we all know what you're supposed to do in this situation, right?
Split.
Okay, so I take my chip, and I push it forward, and they say, "Double?" I said, "Uh-uh."
The move is, the rules say you are supposed to double there.
That's right. But in this case, I split my fingers, and I said, "No, split." And they're like, "Are you sure?"
Do I look like a man who is sure?
Pit Boss kind of glances over. First card, an ace, and then push that second chip forward.
To double down.
To double down on a soft 16.
All right.
Next one, five. Three goes down. It's an eight.
Yeah.
Chip goes forward.
Let's go.
Keep it going.
Oh, wait. I'm sorry. I left out the most important part.
When I split them fives, the first card that was dealt was a five, at which point that got split.
So there are three fives. I forgot that part of the story.
And it was upon the third five that another five was dealt.
Chip goes forward.
Four fives. Four fives on the table.
Another card. It's like some bullshit in the teens.
Finally, last one. I think it was another eight, and I doubled down on it again.
At which point, it ended up they threw down a bunch of cards, and then they said the word's 21.
I was like, "Well, dang it. That would have been a neat story."
But then there was like a weird vibe, and then she smiled and was like, "Eh?"
I'm like, "I don't get it. You took all the money."
And they were like, "No, it's 21. It's 22. We busted. You won."
And then they gave me a $500 chip.
Hey!
Believe in magic, people.
Yeah.
Assholes win.
Exactly. Show your hole.
On the tables.
At the Orleans.
The home of asshole blackjack.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Spread 'em.
Justin?
Yeah.
You're running the Politics, Politics, Politics podcast.
Yes. Yes. Quiet, quiet, couple weeks.
Nothing to see.
Just real tumbleweeds, you know, bunch of action.
As a podcast, you consider it like a great time to be a political podcaster?
How does it feel when things are so divulgent?
It feels great that I don't have to think about what I'm going to talk about.
Because you have to do it at a certain point beyond all of the subject matter is obviously as emotionally charged as you can make it.
But I have to kind of make the donuts every day.
Right.
It's a lot easier when it's like, "Okay, well, here's what we're talking about.
Now we're going to have somebody on and we're going to talk about the very obvious thing that everybody wants to hear about."
But yeah, no, it's fucking insane. It's crazy.
Do you ever wake up and be like, "I just want to do a football podcast."
I often fantasize about doing another podcast.
And then I realize that that's what's gotten me into this mess.
Doing too many fucking podcasts.
But usually, yeah, it's usually like that.
It's like, "Oh my God, I would love to just have shitty hot takes on sports."
But then I'm like, "Yeah, but then I would have to actually think about them and I wouldn't want them to be embarrassing."
Right.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But also, yeah, I don't know.
Most sports podcasts are bad.
That's the sound of you ask too real a question.
Yeah.
You poked them right in the id.
Sorry.
Apologize.
Give me a sports hot take right now.
No, no, no, no.
I will be up at 630 in the morning.
Hopefully, I'll go to McMillan's across the way.
What is this thing?
What is happening?
Well, the Steelers are playing the Minnesota Vikings in Ireland.
Right.
In Ireland.
Yeah.
So I'll be over there.
Several of you just asked why.
Why?
Who knows?
No one knows.
If you want to improve relationships with Ireland, you send Aaron Rodgers.
Yes.
That's right.
You send...
Our best and brightest, Carson Wentz and Aaron Rodgers.
We send our cave-dwelling ayahuasca-drinking weirdo conspiracy theorist to Ireland.
Look, if the red zone offense stays in the 80%, then I will also take ivermectin.
Seems like a needless wager on your part, but okay.
Yeah.
That's fine.
I mean, I don't know how it happens, but we're scoring a lot inside the twin.
Mattingly.
Yes.
You woke up super...
Not super.
You woke up early.
You took scoops on an outing.
Some scoops on an outing.
I did.
We had a little nerd out.
Went out to Alternate Reality Comics out here in Las Vegas.
Yes.
Big shout out to Alternate Reality.
It's my boy Ralph.
Ralph has been holding it down for damn near 30 years out here.
It's the best little comic shop in Vegas.
I just love it.
Love it.
And yeah, some scoops were kind enough to join me in the morning.
It was Vegas early, but we went out there and had a great time.
I really...
It was awesome because I've just gotten really back into comics in the last year and a half
or so, so I was able to give heartfelt, earnest recommendations on what is on the shelves
right now.
So that was kind of fun.
And people bought books I recommended, which was great.
That was really cool.
And then we went...
A lot of tits.
A lot of boobies.
A lot of circles.
More circles.
Circles.
They're just circles and squirrels.
You don't know.
You mean like in the comic shop or in the comics?
In the comics.
So this is the thing.
Paul handed my son a comic with tits in it.
Nice.
When he took...
But your son is 28 years old, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a bargain bin.
Wait.
He said tits only to Paul.
So that was...
I found a...
Give me that book with them titties.
An old 50 Cent issue of Powers, and it's one of my favorite series ever, and I was like,
"Here you go."
And Michael Avon Owings' artwork is very stylistic.
Sure.
And it's really just circles and circles when you're looking at the boob, but whatever.
Paul's staying at my house this time around, though.
He actually says that in real life to his wife as well.
It's just circles and circles, baby.
Yeah.
They're just circles and circles up there, baby.
Thank you.
My boobies don't look like that.
Circles and circles is my favorite.
Yeah.
Boobs is a flat circle.
No, that was awesome.
And then right next door to the comic shop is a new card shop, which is under new management.
I had never been.
Card?
Card.
Collectible cards, Pokemon, Magic, all that kind of shit.
It was incredible.
Well, really well kept, nice, run well.
Are there sports cards in these types of shops, too?
No, sir.
No, no.
So this is all just like Magic cards?
This is all Magic the Gathering and Pokemon.
And maybe a little dash of Lor-Kana.
Don't know what that is.
Disney trading card game.
Good.
Yeah.
So yeah.
And they really were holding it down.
They run tournaments there, so clearly they had their stuff on.
It was just clean.
Shop was clean.
Prices were right.
Oh, nice.
Which is a huge thing.
I don't know.
You guys keep up.
I mean, some dirty Magic the Gathering shops, right?
Oh, god.
Filth Fest.
No, seriously.
No.
Do we have any Magic fans out here?
Any Magic players?
You know what?
That was a no.
I gave up Magic the Gathering in 1993, and I gave away my Black Lotus.
Damn.
Before you did that, Mr. Brian Brushwood.
Oh, shit.
That's valuable.
What does that mean?
That is an extremely valuable card.
Okay.
Before you did that, Mr. Brian Brushwood, would you say that the average conglomerate
of Magic the Gathering players have the highest standards of hygiene about them?
There are signs on many Magic the Gathering convention doors that say, "Wash your ass
before you come in here."
Like, seriously, there are rules in tournaments that are like, "Stinkies go home."
It's a problem.
I'm almost certain that for a while there was a Twitter account that was nothing but
asscracks at Magic.
Oh, yeah.
There was a Twitter account.
No, there was a dude who would always take pictures with his hands in prayer emoji form
like by just heinous asscracks at Magic.
If you can look it up.
Yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
That's right.
He did his little meme of praying to the asscracks, and many were strewn with stuff.
Just bad.
It was a fucking ...
Look it up.
Strewn with stuff?
I'm telling you.
I will not look it up.
By the way, and here's how fucked that community is, they yelled at the guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They banned the guy from coming to Magic tournaments when it's like he is a Pulitzer Prize winning
journalist who has just broken loose a horrifying scandal.
You should be thanking him.
He should be the commissioner.
You leave our dirty butts be.
Exactly, but no, big ass told him to fucking pass out.
That's right.
All that to say, when you find a really clean Magic the Gathering shop, you're like, "Holy
shit.
I might be able to breathe in here."
Yeah.
So, it was really well kept and really nice.
And then of course, just down the way from there ...
Much easier to tap two mana than to wipe twice.
Good Lord.
It's a fucking fact, man.
Their asses are their graveyards.
It's just ...
What is with ...
What is that expression?
Bones are their money.
Yeah, because this is the thing with pro wrestling, too, where especially for big shows, you'll
have these things on the reddits that are like, "Guys, just shower for the love of God.
Why are you going to show up and just stink out everybody?"
Now, like WrestleMania here in Vegas, the cheapest seat that you can get is $800.
And imagine that you're standing next to somebody who's a fucking biohazard and just stinks
to high heaven the entire time.
That's going to be bad.
Paul was just telling me about this the other day, about the WrestleMania thing here, just
being so fucking expensive.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Luckily, I have just purchased a black Lotus card.
Oh, really?
What deal did you get?
I got it for $400,000.
There you go.
Yeah.
I'm just going to use that.
Is it really worth $400,000?
According to this, it is.
Yeah.
Look, when you need three mana ...
It depends on the addition.
It depends on the condition.
In the early days, they didn't have the play balancing quite right.
In tournaments where you're playing for keepsies, then all of a sudden, it became profitable
and made sense.
The value went up, and then the legend grew long and all that stuff.
But I quit because I was finally making friends in college, and that was ruining my friendship.
So away it went.
That was exactly a conversation that was had at the Magic Place, because he was talking
about he plays commander, and he's got a couple of different decks.
He has to decide on the day, do I want to keep my friends, or do I want to play a fun
game of Magic?
Yeah.
Well, because if you're playing mathematically, then some pretty unfun, brutal strategies
start to make sense.
Exactly.
There are mechanics that you can lose forever friends from, just by taking all this shit.
You could play a high-risk thing, and so it's not fun for the other player.
There was a land killer deck that I played where it's just like, you need land for energy.
So imagine if you never got to take a single step forward in the contest, and then meanwhile,
the moment you put down one land, like, "Fuck you, fire, dead, you're not doing anything."
How did you acquire the Black Lotus card?
This is so early, nobody had even heard of the game.
There were what they called black-bordered alphas, and so we would congregate.
I heard they make the rockin' world go round.
They did, yeah.
We would wait for them to show up with a Tuesday mail, and then we would just like, vultures
just have everything.
Okay.
So it's like an unboxing.
Yeah, yeah.
You just found one in a pack.
Yeah.
That's the one, that's that black rim.
Oh, there it goes.
Did you ever play it?
Oh, sure.
It was just a card to me, and then I gave them all away.
I think my brother gave me 70 bucks for all my cards, and he later, I think, sold it for
500.
Yeah.
Did you even have them sleeved back then?
No.
Goodness, no.
They were sleeves, though?
They were sleeves, though.
They were no sleeves, though.
Yeah.
They used to, in the very early on, they claimed-
They were sleeves, though.
They claimed that you had to ante every single game, so you would shuffle your deck, and
then blind, you'd have to set out a card, and then you'd play, and then the other person
got it.
That didn't last.
Well, that was the whole thing with Pokemon, too.
It was all six prizes.
They would go.
Yeah.
Now, what time period is this?
Fall 1993.
Two fistfuls of cookie dough.
Yep.
I remember those days.
No, because I'm trying to say, what's weird now is that, as someone who, they're teens
and 20s and the 90s, any niche culture was actually kind of shit on.
You just kind of-
Yes.
Right.
You always had to alth to alth.
No matter what was going on, as soon as it became popular, it was like, "Go left."
This is before the great flattening of the geek empires, thanks to the internet.
This is at a time that I was excited about Magic the Gathering, because it was a more
approachable bridge to Dungeons and Dragons at the time.
I'm like, "Well, they're just playing the game."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because what I'm trying to say is you chose friends over this game, right?
This time.
This is before the dark times, before Mikey.
Yes.
But now, I feel like you don't, right?
I feel like the internet makes these communities a thing, that people are losing friends.
There's just no king media.
There's no king thing.
There's no mainstream anymore.
Everything is just its own niche.
And so, it's like, "All right, is there a one weird thing that people are all obsessed
about?"
Yeah.
You want to know the problem with the internet?
Nobody's lonely.
When you're lonely, you have to do a little thing called compromise and meet other people
at the square dance, dipshits.
Instead, everyone's all making hierarchies.
This fall on Fox News, Brian Brushwood shares the real truths.
Why aren't the kids at square dances?
I had to tell you, Brushwood, as someone who's just been dipping my toe, by dipping my toe,
I mean paying two 20-year-olds to edit clips for me.
Oh, is that what you're paying them for?
It's part of it.
We have different hobbies.
Yeah.
Believe me, take the reels.
It's so much simpler.
Trust me, you'll be happier with the reels.
Okay, so which means I've experimented with putting things on Instagram, Facebook, YouTube.
Everyone loves them.
Super supportive.
YouTube is a hellscape.
Luckily, it's not one of our jobs to fucking stare at the raw feet of God's butthole the
whole day long.
Actually, it was really funny.
Even one of the clips, I looked also, I was like, "What 40 comments?
What the fuck's going on here?"
Simply, it was a thing of doing a trick I bought from you.
Oh, that's right.
I think my wife saw this.
She was like, "Hey, I think you take tricks pretty good."
Yup.
I'll let it stand.
I'm doing your trick, and I simply say, "What's your favorite book?"
She goes, "I don't have one," and I go, "Correct."
That's the whole hoping to go viral moment.
And then a debate breaks out about whether or not books are stupid.
In the comments.
Yeah.
Nothing to do with me at all.
Yup.
Just people going at it, like, "Why don't you fucking read?"
And defenders go like, "No, reading's dumb."
And it just goes on and on and on.
So yeah, I had this conversation in the car back from the fucking ...
That reading's bad?
This is why ... He's from Kentucky.
This is why we need to support comic book stores and libraries and all this kind of
shit.
We need to read.
Fucking read.
I love the fact that comics went from being the scourge of literacy to, "Guys, at least
there's words in them."
Whoa.
Honestly, if we put words next to the titties, they might read.
They might notice them.
That was my hope.
I'm trying to get Matt's kids literate.
What's this hidden word around this areola?
Constitutional democracy.
What the hell?
No, but even at just a base level, I've always, in my head, thought, "What better way to
get people of any type to learn how to read, but by having visual representation of what's
happening accompanied with dialogue and explanation?"
Eventually, they move on to chapter books.
Right.
What the fuck?
Some people do.
Paul hadn't moved on yet.
No.
Props to Chuck Windy.
Who won in the comments, from your opinion?
Books or no books?
Books crushed it.
Books did.
Good for books.
You know what?
I would say I'd be okay with those random arguments if YouTube would bake into the system
the ability for you to be the judge.
Man, this is your room.
There's no fight.
You get to call the winner.
That's it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll write them.
Dear YouTube.
You should post that.
It was John Waters.
Right?
I believe it was John Waters.
John Waters' quote.
He was like, "Please, if you go to someone's house and you see that they don't have any
books, don't fuck them."
Right?
I think I'm attributing that properly.
Yes.
I think it was Houdini.
Oh, you're right.
It was Houdini.
Shit.
The Virgin Islands.
That was not an option.
No.
Yeah.
You walked in.
You're like, "Here's a gift of a book."
No reason.
I had so ... Do you have a shelf?
Put this on.
Matt bought three girls the entire Encyclopedia Britannica before he left the Virgin Islands.
I'm back with G.
Yeah.
That hit the spot.
One, I was thinking it would be really funny if you just said, "Worked in a big way."
If everyone was like, "He's right."
Then we all rushed to comic book stores and created a wave of everybody to do it.
I get lost in these conversations because we're getting older, right?
Yes.
Speak for yourself.
Slow decay.
Slow.
As someone who started a magic career late, I went on tour as a guy, and now I'm touring
as an old guy.
I definitely noticed that, where people talk to me to start, and then they're like, "Okay,
we're done talking to the old man.
Now let's go back to talk to each other."
I'm like, "Oh, okay."
So when we get on our high horses ... On the slow road to total burdened-dom.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can see the light in people's eyes slowly start fading, as you drone on and on about
the Gulf War, some shit.
I used to be guile, now I'm dulcine.
The slow road to total burdened-dom.
Yeah.
You're just like, "So Norman Schwarzkopf was popular."
What?
No.
Nobody here saw Good Will Hunting?
Yeah.
They're like, "I don't know, fucking their brains are just rotted with a million TikTok
trends."
Well, that's it.
The internet is everything, right?
Right.
No.
What I mean to say is, we talked about this off air, but on the episode where we did something
kind of serious.
Yes.
I basically said it's hard because there's so many forces that profit from the destruction
of hope.
Yes.
Basically, by making it feel like a hellscape all the time, it makes money and it also tells
me to go for self.
I don't have to worry about the future, I don't have to worry about future generations
because they're never going to change.
They're going to fuck it all up and they is whoever, I'm talking about any issue, they,
they're going to fuck it all up and then, so therefore, I don't have to worry about
shit anymore.
You know what I feel like the solution is?
In-person events like what's happening right now at ScootFest.
Agree.
I agree.
We talked about it years ago.
We talked about the, you have to identify the they.
You can't just-
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can't just say they.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's important.
It's super important.
Thank you very much.
People are just bringing me booze.
It's great.
I love ScootFest.
Name them, Jacob.
Who's bringing you booze?
By the way, I'll sign up for that as well.
Dos Equis, please.
Or whiskey.
Cheers.
Cheers, mate.
That whiskey break is brought to you by our sponsor?
Yes, that whiskey break is brought to you by our following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Maddie's Ice Cream and Social, still haven't moved the commercial
tab to the front page of my phone.
Why do that?
That's too much.
Time swipes to the right before I get to that square in the middle.
It's fine.
Who's getting older?
Not us?
Jesus, that font.
So bright.
Matt, just-
Just hold your phone up so the background can read it.
I think you can read that from space.
What the fuck?
I'll just have the bartender tell us who's sponsoring this today.
Oh my God, did you hear the wave of horror?
Matt just showed his phone to the room and there were legitimate woes.
No bullshit.
Hold that up and if you can read it, stand up.
There we go.
How far back can people read that?
I think it is rivaled only by the Hollywood sign.
I actually can't see the Hollywood sign right now, but I can see that.
I legit was surprised by the reaction from the audience.
This has been a startling mirror onto self.
No, only because I know that I'm actually holding out at this font size.
I've gone up one and if I go up two, I'm going to feel really old, so I'm trying to
hold it down.
I say bull the fucking ripples.
Let it go, baby.
All you're doing is fooling yourself.
I'm going to tell you right now, my font size on my phone is the standard size.
I can't read it, but I will not change it.
Jacob has not read a text message in three years.
That's right.
He blindly responds, "Ha!" to everything.
I give a lot of thumbs up.
100%.
100% emoji.
Oh, sure.
100%.
Very nice.
Oh, sure.
100%.
Oh, great.
Pass my whiskey back over then.
It's keeping tabs over here, Jacob.
Anyways, today's show is brought to you by Beef in a Box, now with Extra Box.
That's from Belgian Tripple Scoop in 2023.
Some people tell you no beef, bullshit.
You want beef, and you want beef in a box, and you want extra box, so come on, get this
beef in a box with the extra box.
Boom.
Uh.
Box.
Beef.
Beef in a box.
Boom.
Boom that beef in a box.
Yeah, you hear it mooing?
That's your beef.
Sorry.
I'm distracted by this commercial.
Someone threw up a package of Aldi hot dogs, and Brian is squeezing it like a stress toy.
I will warn you of this, Brian.
Should the contents of that in any way touch your skin, you will be unable to remove that
scent for at least two nights.
You will not be allowed into-
That's great, because I have a Magic the Gathering tournament scheduled for tomorrow.
And I'm not joking when I say, yeah, you're right.
That's what, that's kind of the vibe.
It gives off the scent of a gathering of Aldi hot dogs sweating, sweating too close together
and letting their ass cracks out.
That is unfair to disgusting people.
No, it's not.
Do you think that that shit happens because people can't smell?
Or have they become immune to smelling themselves?
When you are saving up money to buy $500 pieces of cardboard, other things slip through the
cracks.
Like lava.
Like loose toilet paper.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think really it is a combination of that kind, but I think it is just living really
stretching stuff out and not even thinking about that.
That's a cry for help.
Right?
Yeah.
Being that smelly.
I don't know.
I think it's a sign of depression.
Yeah.
But also there's a bunch of creators that I see on TikTok and whatnot that are like,
don't wash your hair.
I know.
Right?
I'm like, ew.
They're like, don't wash your hair.
I'm like, what?
I legit had an LA friend tell me to stop washing my hair.
See?
That's what I'm saying, man.
And they probably don't miss, I don't know, I don't want to get into a hygiene debate,
but I will.
But nobody's saying don't wash your ass.
Yes.
I'm spoiling for a hygiene debate.
I'm just waiting for the right YouTube short magic trick to bring it out.
I will finish the trick and be like, whoa, pull that one out of my ass.
And they'll be like, you shouldn't store stuff in your ass.
Yes, you should.
You should use pockets.
We are evolved to store things in our ass.
Asses are dumb.
That's why we beat the monkeys.
It's nature's pocket.
Nature's pocket.
Excuse my ass.
Today's show is brought to you by nature's pocket.
Oh, God.
Interhase Group's a checkout.
I just got done writing my 200-word comment about South American tariff rates on bandana
banana.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Interhase Group's a checkout.
Nailed that one.
Extra long commercial.
If folks brought stuff, we're going to do like a physical Scoop Mail thing during the
concert tonight.
Yes.
We want to do a physical Scoop Mail thing now just because narrating GIFs is...
Not exciting.
...burdensome to the listener.
Not the greatest of podcasts.
But...
We do have a microphone for people who want to do any kind of in-person...
Narration of the gift that they brought.
Scoop Mail.
No.
And...
Who?
In-person Scoop Mail.
So we won't narrate it, but if you want to narrate it...
Or argue about whether or not reading is dumb.
Yeah.
You can also do that.
Those are the two things that are mostly what we want.
But I guess you could also do anything else.
So if anybody has an in-person Scoop Mail you'd like to do, come on up, get lined up
at the microphone up here, and we will get to that in just a moment.
That doesn't include an item.
Is it just me, or is the energy weird?
The energy's weird today.
The energy is weird.
No, the energy's weird.
I don't think it's bad, but it is weird.
No.
I think we're at day three.
Yeah, that's it.
And I think also, I am pacing myself for tonight, right?
Yeah.
That's what's going on.
These guys are just taking it to zero, and then at eight o'clock, it's ass cracks out.
Yeah.
I can answer your question about what happened to the mood in the room.
Okay.
Oh.
You got all the international scoops arrested, so that's what happened to all the good scoops
left.
That's true.
That is true.
Okay.
Now that you bring it up, I apologize.
Okay, good.
That joke is from Penn Sunday School, so good.
This is good.
It's like a comic book series.
You have to listen to them all together to figure it out.
That's right.
Yeah.
It's good.
Very nice.
Yeah.
Well, a lot of these people have had two nights at McMullin's.
It's a lot.
Oh, yeah.
No, we're running on empty here.
Fucking redlining.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Oh, we have someone coming up here.
Oh, hey.
Even if I'm an international scoop, shame on you.
It was so real.
I don't know why it was so real.
I've never had any kind of a police job, or I don't know why anybody would believe you
had an earpiece.
Yeah.
I don't know why it thundered forth so big.
I do have one question, because I asked Scoop if they know the answer for it, and I don't
remember it ever coming up.
Who is Annie?
So the person we're getting our emails from, from Patreon.
Oh, Annie.
I never, ever heard anything about the person behind that.
Is there an answer?
Is she okay?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask her?
Annie, are you okay?
She honestly, and this is the timely, because she was recently hit by a smooth criminal.
Damn.
She was actually struck by a smooth criminal.
She was hit by, and struck by, yeah.
Oh, by the way, hilarious.
Great question, because 1200 episodes in, Annie was an, or was a listener, was a listener?
We don't know.
And she definitely was a listener.
Yeah.
We think she still listens.
And we first busted out the Patreon.
We were overwhelmed.
Yeah.
As happens.
And we offered a lot of stuff.
And so we basically said, like, none of us have office skills, does any scoop out there
have office skills?
And Annie stepped up, and we created an email address for her.
And also, we just thought it was a good idea to have a barrier, not, not, not from like
a don't bother Jacob Paul and I with stuff, but we actually just thought our listeners
will talk more honestly and frankly with someone whose job it was to talk to scoops.
Like if there's an issue.
Yeah.
Like some scoops might not want to come to us with it with an issue might be easier to
go to any with an issue.
Yeah.
And so we have to interact with Annie all the time.
She emails us before episodes, that kind of stuff.
And so she does all of our kind of like Patreon relationship housekeeping and has done it
now for fucking as long as we've had Patreon nine years.
It's been crazy.
She's great.
No, he's amazing.
I have met her.
I believe the other two have not.
Nope.
I have not met any.
I follow her on the socials.
She, uh, she and her kids, uh, do Disney world occasionally and yeah.
Uh, nice.
Good.
People were doubting Paul, but he came over the top of that Disney world thing.
The guy wants to know and he's can't fabricate that detail.
She's in the magic kingdom.
I occasionally email.
By the way, it's mostly like, I love this question.
Like, do we have like weird, small ice cream, social minutiae questions?
Like, oh, yeah, this is great.
Line up.
Come on.
But I met her and her husband.
Uh, they came and saw me open for the magic dragon in Connecticut.
Uh, at Foxwoods and Annie is lovely and has been extremely, extremely helpful.
How has she not been to a scoop fest?
Oh, we don't let her.
Oh, she doesn't like now.
Uh, give us a scoop name, a scooper Nova girl, scooper Nova girl.
There she is.
Yeah.
So scoops have a lot of call and responses and greetings.
Do we have a toast?
A toast.
Well, the answer is we don't.
I don't think so.
Well, well, well, I mean, we have my toast, which is Kapla and good journey, which combines
my love of Star Trek and you guys can pick up on one of our favorites, which is, uh,
jizz.
Yeah.
You never noticed that, all right, if you do that, that's rude, crass, ugly.
Oh, if you, if you add the word mate, they assume you're British.
Just mate.
Oh, I got you.
Okay.
So I like that.
And actually we started doing that on a podcast where the head of the network was on it.
It was a, uh, it was just a cheap way to just say jizz on a polite society live stream.
And at some point we just keep, uh, cause it was a new year's Eve thing.
So it happened a lot.
And so we were cheersing a lot.
And so we're just like, jizz, mate, jizz.
And at one point he just looks at me and he's just like, yeah, that was it.
How long did it take him to realize?
We got seven, eight jizzes before he even, you got so much jizzes.
Oh, we were firing ropes, dude.
Like, it was, I mean, it was Peter North all the way down.
Yeah.
So we don't, we don't have an official, uh, thing, but I think we could all do like a
salt pork.
I need help.
Do you have a, a suggestion?
No, it's the top of your head.
No.
Fair.
All right.
Yeah.
Right.
What you got?
Doc, Doc Scoop.
Doc Scoop.
There he is.
We, we, uh, fall in love with characters over time and people that come and go, I haven't
heard from Brit Mukai in a while and any updates on how he's doing, what's going on with him?
I've, again, he's another one that I follow on the old, uh, socials.
Takes his kids to Disney world every now and then.
Kids going to Disney world.
Kids now.
Um, no, his VO career has continued to be successful.
Uh, recently he's had some health and dietary struggles.
Um, not trying to put you on blast, Brett, uh, but he's sharing all that.
He's doing it publicly.
Yeah.
He's sharing all that.
And, um, but he's doing really well.
I'd like you, if you follow Brit Mukai, he's not hard to find on socials.
Yeah.
He's doing lots of convention work and signing autographs, uh, because he is the voice of
many anime characters.
Oh, fantastic.
That people know and love right now.
He's working.
He's doing well.
Yeah.
Brett is working.
No, Brett, that's why he's not hanging out with us.
He's in LA making that dollar.
That's right.
You think we can get him to do a phoner?
He?
Check in with us.
He bought property in California.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Right.
Like, yeah.
Damn.
But, but you bring up a good point.
Tell me about this home.
It is.
It has been a long time and we should probably reach out to Brett for a touch base, uh, maybe
a Zoom.
You should probably call him right now.
No.
I feel like I've got at least another year in me before I need to talk to Brett.
Are you going to try it?
Just give him a try.
Alright.
He's going to try it.
I mean, it's ScoopFest after all.
You're right.
He's going to try it.
When all miracles take place.
Alright.
They say that if you rub your two fingers together, then Brett McKay will send us the
voicemail.
It is a pretty miraculous time.
Well, I mean, it's, what is it?
It's a Saturday afternoon.
It's as good a time as any to reach him.
I guess so.
Yeah.
He might be at a con.
Uh, that's quite possible.
Oh my God.
God.
Signing him things.
It's my only Star Trek joke.
Brett's doing great, man.
Brett's doing great.
Uh, what do you got?
Scoop name?
Technical Scoop.
We're checking in again.
Oh, hold on.
Wait, wait.
Sorry.
Technical Scoop.
We got Brett McKay.
Brett McKay.
Do you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
What's up, brother?
You are live at ScoopFest in front of hundreds of Scoops right now.
How's it going, Scoops?
Oh my God.
Brett, uh, literally, uh, someone came up and just said, how is Brent?
Why haven't we heard from a while?
Where is he?
So how are you, Brent?
What's going on?
Dude, I'm fucking rad, man.
And in fact, I was gonna hit, it's so crazy.
I was gonna hit you guys up.
I'm actually gonna be in Vegas, um, next weekend.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I'm one weekend too late.
Can he come on the Friday episode?
Uh, yeah.
I mean, we're on Zoom.
He can come on the Friday episode.
But, uh, yeah, come on, come on by, uh, I'll be in Canada, but don't, don't let that stop
you.
Uh, uh, uh, what, what are you, what are you up to?
Tell the, tell the Scoops something they can like dive their teeth into.
What's up, Scoops?
I'm, I'm at a convention in Florida, in Tampa Bay and, uh, yeah, I'm just eating dinner
with like, uh, Pokemon voice actors and people like that.
And, uh, yeah, I'm just chilling, having a good time and ate a great burger just now.
Oh, there you go.
Well, Brent, thank you so much for answering my call.
Uh, if you didn't, I was gonna be so furious.
Uh, so I appreciate you, you doing it.
That's the only reason I answered it, man.
I was like, if I don't answer this, I'm going to miss out on something awesome.
All right.
Give it up for Brent, everybody.
Take it easy.
We love you, Brent.
We'll talk soon.
Bye, pal.
Technical Scoop board.
You got a question.
I do.
Uh, it's been quite a while since I've heard the, the haiku from the Patreon requests.
Is that still a thing?
We are changing the Patreon right now.
Yeah.
So this has been really tricky because, uh, Patreon changeups happened right around the
time.
Scoop Fest preparations really kicked into high gear.
So we're hoping to have things remedied and squared by the middle of October.
You're the second person who's asked this.
Yep.
Um, so I propose, and this is just Paul, and I might just do it by myself if I have to,
I propose we try and do kind of a, uh, make good on what suggestions we still have in
the kitty and maybe a few that keep that come in now and do maybe a special hour long bonus
episode of just the, the haikus and the, and the, what do you call it?
And the triple threats and all that.
You guys would like that maybe?
Yeah.
And then, and then they are going to go away, um, until, except for, except for special
occasions.
Yeah.
Except for when we want them to come back.
And then we'll do them.
And by we, I mean, we, all of us, we.
But it's not going to be an essential part of the, uh, Patreon moving forward.
Right.
So I'm actually going to speak a little, a little, a little deeper to that question.
Oh, please.
Uh, get deep.
No, no.
Cause, uh, like in truth, like, uh, uh, comedy has changed a lot since we started doing this
podcast.
Yeah.
12 years and sensibilities have changed a lot and an awareness of being like three white
dudes doing a podcast has like been a thing on our minds.
And on some level, like in the room, like when we do the bucket show, we do other things
like that.
Like when we're in a room with people who like us, who trust us and just like any other
group of people where you're in a room where people trust each other, you can tow the line.
You can push the envelope.
You can, uh, basically get left for saying something a little, a little.
You have some latitude.
Uh, knowing that the person thinks you're a good guy.
Right.
And as comedy changes, as we got older, like the idea of leaving constant physical evidence
of us doing haikus and saying your mom, a difference in your mom and blank and that
kind of stuff just started getting a little like, uh-oh, maybe this might be a bad idea
in the longterm.
And so we got a little, uh, gunshot about doing it.
You didn't want to turn on the printing press of liability receipts.
Yeah, exactly.
And, and it's a shame because like, I know that like, uh, we've always joked from the
beginning, like we are dumb jokes for smart people.
Like it's like always like kind of like what I like to think of us.
Uh, and, uh, and so like, I know we get the benefit of the doubt from the people that
do it.
And there is something like there's guilty pleasure about being childish in humor, sometimes
stuff like that.
So we do enjoy doing it like we would still do it at the bucket shows and things like
that.
Uh, but it just became something that got a little, uh, uh, it got a little dicey for
me, uh, for doing on air.
I think it's also something that is going to be better received as it's rarer.
Like if you, if you do a thing every once in a while, um, you know, that's a very involved
bit.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's, it's hard, it takes away some of the magic when you see it so often
that it becomes, I mean, our first patron was a nightmare and, uh, it was so funny and
that's what we loved.
Like we made a very funny.
Right.
You go, you guys had the most convoluted reward system.
It was one time we would eat weird things on camera was one reward.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Oh, no hands.
We would no hands.
No hands eating.
We did that.
Yeah.
We did that at a pepper mill.
We recorded people eating things without using our hands.
I forgot about that.
We, uh, we used to try to do individual made up credits for each person we thanked at the
end of episodes.
Yep.
Every single person.
And then it mostly was just got to be too many people.
Yeah.
So we'd literally be like technical school board, technical school board.
He graduated from this university and he did all this and allegedly he did this.
Yeah.
We would do like five minutes was a blast.
And then it became like really unfunny.
And then we just finished the episode, like, I don't want to end episodes doing our most
unfunny shit.
Where we run this fucking momentum into the cliff face of mandatory fun.
Yeah.
So like, uh, and you know, it's like Paul and I are improv guys.
And so like so much about like being improv, like we can always make it up on the spot.
We can always generate gold.
We can do this.
Uh, and then putting it to the test, you know, for three hours a week for 12 years, it's
just, you know, maybe, maybe gold is a high standard.
Um, you know, and so I think we tried to kind of, we also, yeah, we would kind of pump breaks
on weird shit like that.
Yeah.
But as I said, it's just not going to be part of the patron going forward in a large capacity,
but we will do a make good episode from some of the old stuff.
If you got one specifically, you really want to hear, uh, send it to Jacob.
And we're, and we're going to do them.
Like we're, we're still going to, we're still going to do all of our stuff, you know, as,
as time goes by.
Uh, but yeah, maybe just not quite as often.
Yeah.
Is that fair?
Very fair.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Come on up.
Scoop name.
It's, uh, Belgian Triple Scoop.
Belgian Triple Scoop.
Love it.
Actually, I'm very grateful technical scoop port, cause you kind of started the question
that I have, which is, you know, um, I bought tickets for Scoop Fest before I, I'm now in
a serious relationship.
We're about to be a year, but she doesn't share the same kind of sense of humor though.
I think we, everybody in this room really loves.
Come on guys.
Yeah.
Jump jokes for smart people.
Woo.
So you're asking us if you should leave her?
This is so awkward and unexpected, but yes, you should leave her.
I feel bad that you said that because now four people just said, you know what?
I'm over it too.
And they just left.
But that's, but it's, it's, how do you marry that idea of, this is something that you love,
right?
Like it's, you know, you, you talked about, you know, obviously you're very thoughtful
response to how you do the different jokes and oh, this is great comedy gold.
It's comedy gold everybody, but explaining the Captain Morgan podcast and why that's
funny is sometimes difficult.
I don't think I can explain why, if the Captain Morgan podcast is funny, super cerebral, but
it's exactly, it's a high watermark.
But that's the idea.
How do you, Captain Morgan, did you want her in this?
I just wanted to let you know that the podcast is funny because my name is Captain Morgan.
What do you want to do?
What are you doing?
Captain Morgan, you seem like, you seem like you're on the precipice, you're, you're on
the precipice.
Well, okay.
Hold on.
Get out of my precipice.
What?
Don't know.
I'm perspiring on the precipice.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm just here for you, Brian.
Well, I know you seem very upset though, Captain Morgan.
Why do you have hot dogs?
Well, it's, I invented hot dogs, by the way.
I didn't know this about you.
Well, funny, funny, you should ask.
I didn't.
But you have a hot dog that I invented.
Okay.
That one.
Yes.
Not the rest.
Well, tell me about it.
I put it together in a spindle that I carried in a bindle.
Oh, are you homeless as well?
Nope.
No, you're not.
No, I have a boat.
I take my boat around to the high seas and if I ever see a hot dog I don't like I kick
it off.
I say get the fuck out of here, hot dog.
Okay.
Well, why?
It's a real problem.
Now, wait a minute.
These days.
When would you encounter?
Hot dogs everywhere.
Running, hither and yon.
Can't trust them.
Can't look a hot dog in the eye anymore and say, "Hey, we're going to make a square deal.
Now, these hot dogs be doing, hot dogs be trifling."
Did a hot dog disappoint you?
Fuck yeah.
Oh, tell me about it.
One hot dog crashed the stock market and high interest loans and next thing you know Obama
was president.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, Captain Morgan.
But that's exactly what I mean.
I'm doubled over laughing and you guys, I mean all five of you have-
75% of the audience wasn't.
But that's the point.
You guys all have partners, you have children, you have people in your life who may not share
that.
How do you find the kind of balance in you guys making your living off of jokes that
I find amazing, but I have a hard time sharing?
How do you find that balance?
Oh, none of our spouses think we're funny.
My wife does.
None of our spouses think we're funny.
No, my wife thinks I'm funny.
No, no, she calls me all the time and tells me.
Wow.
She thinks I'm funny.
She just thinks I push it too gross sometimes.
Should there be a statute of limitations on lore, like at some point they expire and you
have to let them go?
What?
Should there be a statute of limitations on lore, like at some point, because it's impenetrable
at some point.
It's like-
Dude, you haven't heard from Mothra's Secret Agent in a while for a reason.
So yes.
Because the last time I started to hear from them, Matt and I just yelled-
Yeah, no.
"Now!"
It doesn't happen.
Yeah, so I mean that's-
I mean, you look at The Simpsons, right?
They didn't think they were going to go 30 years and so all of a sudden they're being
held accountable for decisions they made 20 years ago, like that's fucking bananas.
Yeah.
Because it implies that you're looking back as like the powerhouse of that you knew what
you were the whole time, and not that you were desperately trying to get anyone to pay
attention to you doing anything that came into your brain and just hoping it flew in
the moment.
Yeah, I mean-
But no, I mean, I think any time you try to make any kind of living being creative at
all, something that really comes from your heart and your mind, it's fucking ballsy.
And any time you get any kind of audience of support, it's really something special.
Comedy is also very, very specific.
There's not a lot of objective elements to comedy that you can say like, "Well, clearly
this is funny," because it's all dependent on where people come from, their expectations.
I think I've quoted this one before, but this is my go-to right now.
Zach Anner, the comedian, multiple sclerosis guy, he's amazing.
He's fantastic.
He's on social media.
Zach Anner, this is his whole thing.
Comedy isn't meant to be timeless.
Great comedy is in service of its time.
It helps start the conversations that will eventually deem it irrelevant, outdated, or
offensive.
You laugh, you think, you grow, and you move on.
That said, farts are always hilarious.
But it's so true.
I went back and listened, like last week, two weeks ago, I listened to a Bill Cosby comedy
album.
Boy, I didn't know there'd be edgy humor on this show.
But I mean, it was the edgiest, not even edgiest, but it was hilarious.
It was a huge seller of its time.
I went back and listened to it.
Forget about all the Bill Cosby stuff, or try to, just go to sleep and forget about
it.
It's fine.
He'll make you forget.
Yeah.
I mean, all of that aside, it's just not poignant.
It's simply not relevant to this day and time anymore.
And it's so hard.
Jacob's like, "When you guys are done bitching about the other stuff about Bill Cosby, I'd
like to take the content of a special for Dad."
Can we get to the real issue here?
I'm going to really focus in on the minutia of Bill Cosby.
The drain-bamage bit.
But it really is.
You go back and listen to it now, and it's just a, it's a relic of the past now, is all
it is.
And you're listening to that and you're listening to it for the nostalgia.
It's pure nostalgia at this point.
It's not comedy anymore.
It's a history.
It's a time capsule.
I don't think you guys are time capsules.
Eggs.
Eggs are in the cake.
No.
The kids won't pull up their pants.
So to be kind of, just to wrap everything up, it's figuring out that way to share that
part of your personality and your comedy, but not push the envelope too far, but like,
you know, understand that it's of time, but you know, I don't know, drawing the line.
Look, look, look.
I mean.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to make this more serious.
No, you always, you always want to say like, hey, you know, whatever I do is not for everyone.
But as soon as you find out it's not for everyone, it's devastating.
Really hurts your feelings.
You do.
You always say this is like, I, I, I, my comedy heroes never cared about mass popularity.
My comedy, yeah, just made the funniest thing possible.
And then it's like realizing like you hope you're wrong.
Yeah.
Hope it's like, like, no, I'll be as funny as my heroes that didn't get the recognition
that they deserved.
And then you're like, oh no, but I'm not getting the recognition that I deserve.
No, like when I like, you know, go do a cruise ship or the audience, just the energy, just
fucking zip.
Right.
I absolutely go to sleep hating myself going, I guess I'm not for everyone.
And then I have to walk around the ship with them the next day and then like go up and
hide on deck 19 and look out and hope I don't get harpooned.
But like, you know, it's, it's, you know, it's not for everybody.
But the bottom line is, is that like, I don't looking at us over time or any kind of stuff
like the body of work, all that feels cool, like to create something that like we want
to come to feels cool in the moment.
The smartest thing that we decided we were was that we are a service and that service
is a weekly service and we are there to help people in that moment.
And we hope that the podcast helps people in that day or that drive or that walking
of their dog.
Yeah.
Everything else after that.
Sure.
But that's the primary.
That's the primary deal.
That's why we keep doing it.
I'll tell you what, when, when scoops come up to me and this, and this happens, this
has happened multiple times this weekend, it happens all the time.
When scoops come up to me and say, Hey, I listened to the whole back catalog.
My blood runs cold every single time, but good God, what did we say a decade ago?
Yes.
I agreed.
Oh, I'm terrified all the time.
I start laughing.
Exactly.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Scoop name.
Give it to us.
Gelato problems.
Love it.
So my question's about commitment.
I don't know if it's.
What the fuck?
You wrote commitment?
Go ahead.
Explain it to him.
Commitment to a bit.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, commitment to a bit.
To the point of.
To the point of endangerment.
You know, it just felt like this was like a love line segment from like 2001.
So I don't know if my husband's Max the ginger scoop and I don't know if he was always going
to be a commitment guy and you just named the thing that he does or if he's just following
you to be a commitment guy, but he is that guy and he will kill something until it is
dead and buried.
And I'm like, please stop and he won't.
And so my question, this is a crowd that will show up at the party tonight in commitment
outfits.
Yes.
You guys love commitment, but is there any commitment that in your lives, maybe bad jokes
like there are some bad jokes that I'm like, kill it and it won't die.
And bad jokes, commitments, bits at home or bits in your lives that you're like, I'm going
to keep doing it no matter how upset it makes everyone at work or at home.
Anything like that, Paul?
Your moment has come, sir.
The audience said it first.
The people that I love the most get nicknames and those nicknames stay forever.
So Matt and I don't have nicknames.
That's true.
So far I see no complications.
Everything's good.
It's legit.
But you're the audio guy.
Move on.
Don't.
It's fine.
It's worse if you try to make it now.
It's worse.
Yeah.
Just go ahead.
But I will.
I will.
I keep at it.
I started calling Ann.
It's so great if you just shoehorned Madinator in like he had always done it.
I started calling Ann Snakey, you know, when we were dating early on and she was like, what
the fuck are you talking about?
And she didn't like it, but I kept it up.
And I have called her Snakey for damn near 20 years now.
And now it's cool that she knows that's I'm Snakey, you know, and it's all good.
The honk.
My beloved brother that came up.
We were what?
Twelve?
Ten?
Less?
Yeah.
Younger is the word you're looking for.
He's also from Kentucky.
Yeah.
Not with the math.
Stop fucking with the math on us.
We were lesser people.
But that's what it is.
It's yeah.
I mean, it started with that.
It started with those kind of things.
And there will be moments when I am in a real goofball mood and some days Ann is like enough,
enough.
And she will say she was sometimes just to say, you got to stop here and make me cry.
And I'll be like, OK, because I don't mean to because I think it's and then but then
sometimes really hard because that's when I know, oh, God, this is really funny.
She hates this.
This is amazing.
And so that's when you know that the shields are down.
That's what it's a combination of things.
So I have to be very careful.
I understand that I wield a certain power and I need to respect it.
But for the most part, I will.
There are few things funnier than the true flash of rage in the eyes of somebody that
you love.
Oh, my God.
I will say that this is one I'm going to I'm going to give out a posthumous shout out.
Many of you guys listen to Geek Shock.
Yeah.
Shout out to the Geek Shock boys and big ups to 80s Jeff, who is no longer with us anymore.
We lost 80s Jeff last year.
Broke my heart.
That's real commitment.
80s Jeff was the butt of a lot of my shit.
If you listen to those, even just those episodes, one of the worst was he came over.
He came over to the we would gather up after Trek almost every I don't know, every three
nights or so.
And we'd all be playing video games and watching anime and just acting a fool.
And this is after you all watch Star Trek together.
All that kind of stuff.
Just doing very nerdy things in somebody's house.
And there's like, okay, cookie, eight or 10.
Very nerdy.
Eight or 10 people playing cookie cookie.
Oh, my God.
80s Jeff had a habit whenever.
That is a case of pink eye waiting to happen.
Whenever he walked into a room, whenever he walked into a room, it didn't matter what
was going on.
If something was playing on the TV, he'd be like, what the hell is this?
That was his go to thing.
He just, what the hell is this?
Just didn't matter.
He could have been something he kind of knew.
Could have been something he hadn't.
Just, what the hell is this?
And we all made it, he always says, what the hell is this?
And so, finally, there was this, I can't remember exactly what the anime was, but it was this
moment of these samurai looking guys and gals and very traditional kimono garb and all these
things.
And these sakura flower petals are falling all down the ground.
And he's like, what the hell is this?
And I go, it's your wedding.
And he goes, what?
And I go, this is footage from your wedding.
And he says, what the hell are you talking about?
And some of my friends start laughing.
And I go, yeah, man, this is your wedding.
This is your upcoming nuptials.
And he says, what do you mean?
And then people really start laughing.
And I go, yeah, this is Jeff's wedding.
We got this on tape already.
He's like, what are you talking about?
That's not funny.
What are you talking about?
I'm not married.
What are you, that's not, and then everybody's like--
Because Jeff was not married.
And then everybody starts to really lose their shit because he gets that angry.
He gets angry.
He's like, what do you mean?
My wedding.
And we're like, no, it's your wedding, dude.
This is your wedding.
What are you, that's not funny.
And then everybody is just fucking losing their minds.
There's nothing better than when somebody starts shouting, it's not funny.
Yeah, what's funny about it?
And this goes for an hour of bullshit back and forth until he's just like, fuck you guys.
Fuck you guys.
I'm not getting married.
This is not my wedding.
Fuck you.
And then to this day, to this day, you go up to one of the geek shop crew.
You want to get them going.
You say, hey, Jeff's wedding.
And we all just fucking fall out, just Jeff's wedding.
We all fucking lose our shit.
But there came a time when we could not say it anymore.
That's great.
Around him.
Magic the Gathering.
I lost casual friends to a bit.
Oh, oh.
Yeah.
So I was in my comedy group, Possible Side Effects.
We loved doing bits.
I loved doing bits.
Part of why I wanted to do a podcast with Paul in the first place was that I was like,
I want to keep doing bits all the time.
And I loved, and I hated when improv theaters, when they police bits, like, oh, you guys
are doing a bunch of bits.
I'm like, shut up.
This is my love language.
And let me do bits.
Yeah.
And I was walking, we were visiting friends in Boston, and I was walking on the sidewalk.
It was like, it was definitely like a not, it was not a jovial mood.
Just calmly walking.
Yeah.
And I go, oh, man, this is getting hard.
And the guy was like, what?
I was like, I'm Dr. Sam Beckett.
And I leapt into Matt's body.
And I am trying left and right to figure out, like, what wrong to right to, like, leap out
of this fucking body.
And my comedy group was like, like, yes.
And they just would grill me about being Sam Beckett.
And I would have to start answering questions like, oh, shit, and I started answering questions
of Sam Beckett, who leapt into Matt Donnelly's body to right wrongs in his life.
And so whenever my comedy friends were bored at a party, and I'd said anything, one of
them would just go like, whatever, you're not even Matt, and I'd be like, all right,
let's not.
And I would commit to being Sam Beckett immediately.
And I'd answer questions of Sam Beckett, who leapt into Matt's body for years, for years.
If it came up, I would never not be Dr. Sam Beckett if they brought it up.
And it ruined people I was hitting on.
It ruined, like, just casual friendships.
Wait, you'd be hitting on somebody and one of your friends would go over there and ask
Sam Beckett a question.
I'd be like, we're going fucking Sam Beckett, I'm cockblocking Matt.
And I would just be like, oh, I'm sorry, I don't want to get the wrong foot with you,
but I am.
I should confess that I am Sam Beckett.
I am Sam Beckett and I love to act.
And I, I mean, we did the bit for like a decade.
I don't, I never stopped, like, I never, I don't know when we stopped doing it, but I
would never not do it.
What a checkmate move when somebody's just trying to, like, lay some game and then just
be like, oh, wow, I guess my only options are, do I explain quantum leap to them?
Like, I remember my buddy Steve Buck on Neutrino, he would do a thing called Bitbot, give me
a quarter and I'll do a bit.
And this drove improvisers crazy.
And then I would just get out an invisible quarter every time, like, no, I was like,
you guys are watching the best bit in the world.
He'll do a bit on anything, I would sell Bitbot and I just fucking loved it.
I would say as I got older, I guess I'm not as super major bit crazy, but when I get in
the groove, I love it.
And my wife and I met doing improv, so we do fucking really filthy, disgusting bits
all the time and, and like really say like really next level, like offensive things to
each other.
And it's so fun because it's like almost like a game of chicken with each other sometimes
and it is a love language and I do love it.
Yeah.
I will, my wife might not like me personally, like, like because I will just run fucking
bits that aren't funny, like I could repeat them to you, like they're not even clever
or interesting, but they make her mad and that makes me happy.
Does your, does your wife think you are a funny person?
I suspect that she does, but she's very fucking loathe to give me any hint that like she will
suppress laughter.
She will turn her face away.
She will give it to you.
You won't give me that point.
Oh no, that's SJ.
SJ will not laugh at me at home.
Really?
Don't give me that point.
SJ is like, go fuck yourself.
No, cause she knows that if she laughs, she's going to hear that fucking joke for the rest
of her life, like she knows the ones that are sticky and she's like, like I can't tell
you that's clever.
I can't tell you that's interesting or else it will just be repeated right before we go
to sleep for the rest of her fucking natural days and, and she is right.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
She's absolutely correct.
She is dead right.
100%.
I mean, Brian, I know, I know Bonnie likes you because you're thin, but does she like
you?
Oh, Matt.
Good news.
Bonnie just texted me and she said, I don't know why, but I like Matt a little more right
now.
Yeah.
Trim it up a little bit.
All right.
No, I actually have good news from the future.
Cause your kids are how old?
10 and 12.
Yeah.
Cause there are families that do music and they'll just naturally the kids grow up and
they just learn to harmonize instantly.
It is a fucking blast when, when you have teenagers who have grown up where just naturally
bits are ongoing and you understand the importance of setting up a runner and all that stuff.
And it's those to be honest, I was really hoping that Josie didn't want to go to college
and instead would sneak out to be the surprise guest at scoop fest.
But it's like, she is objectively the coolest of all her friends and I am certain it's because
of all the ongoing bits and her natural understanding.
So yes.
I highly recommend.
Oh, you tell Josie anytime she wants to come to scoop fest, call me.
Yeah.
And she can just come to scoop fest.
Tell dad to stay home.
Yeah.
No.
Doing bits with kids.
My kids is awesome.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
If you hear Max, this is the one that I want people to boo him.
If you hear Max say that he kicks children for a living because he's a martial arts instructor,
it's a stupid joke.
And I've heard it for eight years.
Boo him.
Max, you keep kicking those kids for a living.
I know we have a lot of bit people in our audience and I do.
I love it.
I love seeing.
I love seeing the bit game over our audience.
I love Max.
Max actually hopped in one of my shows in New York and like I literally was like, Hey,
I need a punch line for this magic trick.
Let's do this at this point of the show.
And it was so awkward and doesn't help.
It was so random.
And he just did it.
And then he crushed.
It was awesome.
Thank you, Max for helping in my show.
Oh, we got two more here.
We've got to wrap it up.
We got Bobo Bobo the flound.
Talk about commitment.
Yeah.
I don't know what you're talking about.
All right.
Oh, wait, you guys not see this person dressed up in front of the microphone.
What is objective reality?
No, no.
Back to that one.
Is it just a microphone?
Just a microphone.
Jesus Christ.
I don't know why no one would take a microphone.
This is a microphone right there.
I actually have Gilbert Godfrey doing the voice for me in the background right now.
I'm actually just doing it silently.
All right.
So my question on to you is, where do you draw the line in the sand for a comedian to
clown?
Because you'll have like prop comic, you'll have physical comics, but they're not necessarily
a clown.
So where do you draw that line in the sand?
Oh, interesting.
Because I definitely have a line in my mind, but I don't know where it is.
So maybe I have a weird perspective on this, but if you have a physical skill, I put clowning
above comedian.
Oh, I do too.
It's ancient.
Yeah.
Not that old.
Clowning is just ancient.
You are.
Okay.
The questioner is ancient.
Oh, I mean, the truth is off the bat, I don't have an answer.
This is not something I've contemplated before.
I definitely do, as you bring it up, I do see a difference in it.
It is a blend of intellectualism and physical comedy, but yeah, I don't know where that
line is.
And there is, it's weird because I definitely have a real line in my head between people
in my life that are comedians and people who are clowns and I don't know exactly what that
line is.
It might be self-identifying, I'm really not sure.
I will say, I don't know artistically, but just in the difference between clowns and
comedians that I have met in my life, they are very different people.
Yes.
Oh, always.
In general.
Like a comedian, once you've been around people who've done comedy, there's an archetype,
kind of brooding, there's little buttons and love languages that you can understand.
Clowns are far more like carnies and renaissance fair people where there's a fucking tough
as nails element to clowns.
There is a, you can't phase them.
Yeah, but also it's like, maybe there's a dark secret.
I don't know.
There's an element, usually comedians' dark secret is that they didn't get along with
their mom.
Right.
I'm shooting off a hip here, but I think comedians, you tend to like their perspective
on things.
You kind of like want to know a comedian's perspective before you kind of laugh at their
jokes and clowns seem to like want to make what's ever happening an event that's happening
like right now.
Well, even presentationally, like presentationally, clowns kind of remove your ability as an audience
to look into the performer, right?
Like the performance is its own thing.
It is very loud.
It is big.
It is in your face.
It's not like somebody telling a story about, you know, breaking up with somebody and people
in the audience are like, wow, that makes me think of that experience that I went through.
It's very performance focused, which almost makes it harder because now you don't have
a little bit of the emotional buy-in that can make art kind of like special and magical
if it hits.
But if it's, you know, a cloud act, then you are looking at physical reaction.
You're looking at, you know, athleticism, timing, like all the the basic building blocks.
This got fucking deep into comedy, but it's important for our it's important for our legacy.
That's true.
I wanted to hit an eject button for me.
Thank you.
That was actually very insightful.
Can I tell you a joke?
Yes.
Go ahead.
All right.
Why do Catholic priests touch little boys?
Why?
Because they can't get none.
Ah, okay.
All right.
There it is.
Mystery solved.
I'm now regretting following that.
I don't know why.
You guys and the conversation I have, oh, sorry, Shula scoop, there is this fucking
liar.
This popped into my brain after something you said in the conversation I was having
back there.
When I was in college, one of my friends in theater, I was in theater at the time, whenever
he would go to his room to masturbate, he would tell everybody he was going to get ice
cream.
So, like I said, short, but that was all I had to say.
That's great.
That's a good bit.
I loved it.
10 out of 10.
No question.
Yeah.
It was great.
That's fantastic.
That's it.
On that note, I think it's time for me to go get some ice cream.
Yeah.
I'm going to go get some ice cream.
Hey, Justin, you want to go get some ice cream together?
I'd love it.
Let's go.
Two scoops.
Two.
Okay.
All right.
Give it up for Brian Breschwood.
Hey, guys.
Give it up for Justin Robert Young.
Give it up for all y'all for coming out to ScoopFest.
We appreciate it so much.
Yeah.
Thank you all for being here.
Thanks so much.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the Cone.
As always, check out Great Leather.
Check out PX3.
Check out all the things that these fellas do.
We appreciate it.
See ya.
Yeah.
Yeehaw.