Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to. Great, let's go!
It's a bonus episode! Thank you to the Patreons! We didn't play the theme, but this is the Sporty McBall Things Considered. Oh yeah, it's time for the Sporty McBall Things Considered ice cream social bonus episode with Justin and Mitzi! It's all of us, we're all here at Justin River Young, it's Mitzi, Paul, Matt, and Jacob! It's gonna be crazy!
Oh hell yeah! It's our Super Bowl special!
It's our Super Bowl special! Jacob, you really just summed it all up, I don't know how we could possibly do a better intro than that, but um...
I mean honestly, I think we just have to go home now, I think we're kind of done. Yeah.
But just summing up a little more, with a little more length. We of course are beneficially, we benefit from being friends with our famous Vegas odds maker. So Mitzi is here in the studio, he handles all the things.
Joining us of course is politics, politics, politics host, Justin Robert Young. And that's because...
If people don't hate sports enough, let's add politics into the fold, because that'll definitely keep it going.
That's my day job, but mostly I spend my time bullshitting about sports in a group chat with everybody in this show, except for Paul.
Paul for whatever reason has not rated an invite to the group chat, how does that make you feel Paul?
It makes me feel good, because I purposely boycotted all NFL stuff this season, because of the Aaron Rodgers going on to the Steelers thing, I was just like, well, there's nothing keeping me watching the local games, so I'm not gonna watch any of it.
And I think I've been proven right, as more and more it becomes crystal clear that everything's a fucking setup, and it's all scripted from the beginning.
So yeah, that's it. They definitely wanted a backup quarterback in the finals of the NHL season instead of Josh Allen.
That is the correct answer, because it is the greatest act of love that the four of us can have for you, that we don't bother you with the inane bullshit that we put in there about the minutiae of day-to-day sports, it would only pollute your life and we keep it with pride.
I can't imagine Paul being on the thread where we were debating Notre Dame's inclusion in the college football playoffs.
See, this is what's funny, the breakdown of NBA trade analysis right now.
I'm all for nerdy minutiae breaking point of how many games I can take the under on in college football, like that's mostly what we talk about.
Yeah, you've got a longer under streak than the Taker had WrestleMania victories.
So, dude, it did me well this season, though, until the playoffs, that was a good thing to note.
It's just my nerd nerddoms don't flare up as constantly as sport does.
Sport is just a constant festering wound of bullshit with my thing.
It's like, oh, once every 10 years, a He-Man movie happens.
Once every once every six months, a new toy line comes out.
That's it. Yep. And there's still plenty of vitriol and hate with that.
Believe you, trust me. Yeah, but no, it's just talk about himself.
No, I don't get it. I don't get it. I'm all love right now.
I it is more good. It is we he fans be eaten good right now.
More importantly, though, is that we are gathered here because our scoops who don't like sports are still invited to Super Bowl parties.
So we like to write them up to date with things they can keep track of and stuff.
It's a Mitzi in the past. We've had you save the crazier bets to the end.
I actually think I want to front load this and then so we can get more nerdier as we go on.
All right. We can do that. We'll do let's just do the game prediction first and then we'll go into the fun stuff.
We'll go back to the normal kind of game. So I didn't do a lot of crazy player prop stuff or anything this year that not that might not be great with everybody.
Most of the stuff is pretty general. Should be acceptable for most parties.
So just a great job prepping for this episode and we appreciate it.
Yes. All right, gentlemen, let's just start it off.
We're going to go straight up. First of all, we need to pick the Seattle Seahawks or the New England Patriots.
The Patriots are technically the home team, but the Seahawks are four and a half point favorites.
The game is being played in San Francisco, so it is a neutral site.
OK, are we picking against the spread or just picking straight up picking against the spread?
We always pick against the spread. Great. We're adults.
I am definitely go with Seattle and the spread.
No problem. You had to land four and a half for Matt.
I think Seattle is going to believe in Sam Darnold.
Oh, more than anything, I think his name and he appears.
I think even Sam Darnold, I believe I was brought up right.
My dad always said fifth time's a charm and I was on his football team.
And so I figured this is the one five is my lucky number for folks who do not know.
This is something that you can take into your Super Bowl parties that will get a laugh
or you will learn people something and you can get credit for it.
But Sam Darnold was once most famous as a highly drafted
quarterback for a graphic that was shown during an ESPN broadcast,
which said that he was out for mono.
That's right. You can look that up.
And they said out and they had him for whatever reason, doing like the motion
graphics that they have all the players record at the beginning of the season
where they're doing like kind of badass shit.
And so it was like a slow motion of him pointing like at you.
This is out for mono.
That was what he was most famous for, because his career on the field was disastrous.
He bounces around the league, has a great season with Mitzis, Minnesota Vikings.
But because Mitzul is not allowed to be happy, they trade him away
and they let him go out indefinitely for mono-nucleosis.
And the barrel down the gun is just pointing straight down the lens.
He's sick looking. Only you can prevent mono-nucleosis.
I mean, that's what he used to be the most known for.
Right. All right. And now he's in the Super Bowl and he's been favored by five points.
Honestly, it was a more fun time when that's what he was known for.
It was a better time, I think, in America. Hilarious.
Between that and seeing ghosts, he was all sorts of good.
I'm with you though, Matt. As a failure.
Wait, he saw ghosts? Seahawks and four and a half, I'll take it.
Was this another thing, Mitzi? Was he also a ghost inventor?
This is what did his career with the Jets.
What sealed his fate as a Jets quarterback was the Patriots destroyed him so much
in the game that he goes, "Oh my God, I'm seeing ghosts out there."
And it was caught by NFL Films. It was put out as a clip.
On a live mic, yeah. And then they just cut to late-night footage of Gettysburg.
With the Minutemen traipsing across the field eerily on their last march.
They just intercut it with bedknots and broomsticks.
That was scary back in the day. That was scary. That was some good shit.
Angela Lansbury was a scary biatch.
Angela Lansbury put the fear of the Lord in you. Is she still alive?
No. Are you sure?
She died. I'm pretty sure she died.
I'm just getting word. There is still some good fucking left in her.
Put her on the microwave. She'll be fine.
So Matt and Jacob are both on Seattle.
Murdersheets, grope.
Cabot Cove, Maine, if it were a real place, would officially be the most murderous city in the country.
That's what they called her, hoo-hah.
And part of New England.
All right. So I hesitate to be chalk here with you guys because I do also like the Seahawks giving four and a half, mostly because I don't believe in the Patriots.
I think they have looked like dog shit for two straight weeks and it has only been blizzards that have saved their ass.
And CJ Stroud, who decided to have a Richie Tannenbaum style fucking panic attack and melt his career down.
That's no, that blizzard game was incredible.
That blizzard game. I mean, like the second one, the AFC championship or when it was crystal clear in the third quarter.
And then the fourth quarter looked like the ninth circle of hell.
But here's my problem. And here's what I don't know.
I don't know if the New England defense, which has also been very good, is just going to turn the ball over four times with Sam Darnold.
And Sam Darnold is going to his carriage is going to turn into a pumpkin.
And we're all going to be like, what the fuck? Why did the entire world bet on Sam Darnold?
And it's only going to be Mitzi's employer laughing their way to the back.
This is the correct Monday morning quarterbacking breakdown of this game.
Yes. Yeah. And yeah.
And so so I don't I have made several bets on this game already.
But I have not bet on the game outright because I don't know whether or not the New England money line is the thing to sprinkle.
If you think that they can win outright, which I think any game, anybody, any two teams that are in the Super Bowl, you could you can make the argument that they can win the game.
The nine out of the last ten underdogs have four and a half points or more have covered.
OK. Yeah.
So I don't know. Maybe it's maybe it's a field goal.
Something like that. Four and a half is a lot. It's a lot. I like a lot more of the props than I like the game itself.
OK. But just move forward. You're at you're at you're at Seattle. You're you're you're fuck. Fuck. OK, fine. I'll I'll take New England in the points.
I hate myself. I hate my life. I hate everything because I hate there's not a team other than the Cleveland Browns and the Baltimore Ravens that I hate more than the New England Patriots.
Like and mostly because the the Ravens fans, I can sit down and I can drink with a Ravens fan and we can we can talk about games for years and we can share times where it went good for me.
It went good for them. The Browns fans, I just have pity for.
Like I there's only so much. Yeah. Like the slash the tires on the short bus and feel good about yourself.
But like the New England Patriots, I want to move on with that metaphor.
How many times is it for you when it comes to the Browns?
I'll let you know when I find it less fun. But when it comes to the New England Patriots, the there are a few people on Earth that deserve pain more than Boston.
OK, OK. They are arrogant, angry, low born people that deserve nothing but misery and pain.
In fact, there are times where I've thought about the city of Boston and I'm like, would it be worth it to cancel the American experiment just so they would be sad?
And it takes me longer than I would like to admit to come to eventually saying that, yes, the United States of America should exist if it means the pleasure of Boston, even though Boston is happy about it.
Hey, Jacob, put a time mark on this right now. I forgot to put on my microphone until this moment.
Oh, great. Were you recording the Twitter, the zoom? Yeah, yeah, you know, I've got it. Good.
Anyway, do you have a do you have a lean on this one? I'll just go with the Seahawks because that's a she was boyfriend.
I'm going to go with the Pats because I am in every Super Bowl world as an oddsmaker, you will be rooting for the favorite to win, but not cover because the public either takes the favorite laying the points or the underdog on the money line.
So we would like to take it to lose by like a field goal. Right. So that was already world.
We have our total for the game over under a forty five and a half.
Could be this is right about a little higher than most Super Bowl or a little lower than most Super Bowls, but still a decent total.
So forty five and a half is the number. Well, let's start with Paul this time.
Paul, you got to lean on this. I'll go over because that's what America wants right now. They want blood in the in the water.
They want to see big numbers, big gains, big losses, no way big, no way.
Stop. And they'd probably be really happy if one team is is that like 60 and the other teams like to.
But yeah, I'm going for it.
Jacob, you got one on this. I think it's going to be over.
I have not been impressed by by either defense, really. I think we're going to see some points.
Justin, you know where I'm going.
I'm going to get the fucking under both these defenses are really, really good.
I know it's more pleasure for betting for less points than you like nobody.
Inept football team, a football game than you.
There is nothing as pleasurable as watching a college football game where a bunch of 18 year olds fuck up and being happy about it.
It feels so good just to watch 20 year old kids drop the ball when they really want to try to catch it and just being delighted.
And they're so sad. Oh, they're so sad.
I am. I'm also going to go with under.
I think I think Seattle knows how to play D against the Patriots.
And I believe Seattle will also turn the ball over.
So I imagine a muddy, muddy game is what I'm predicting under 20, 27 points.
That's what the L.A. Rams hung on Seattle two weeks ago.
Yeah, yeah. The Seattle Rams.
Do you want to go over the Rams receivers versus the Patriots receivers?
Oh, no doubt, no doubt, no doubt.
I'm just saying they're going to score a little bit.
Have receivers. I didn't know that.
I'm also on the under train. I think it's going to be a tight game.
I think both defenses will show up to probably be a couple of turnovers.
And I think it's going to be like a 17 to 20 ish kind of a below 40 game.
So I might even take an alternate under if I'm feeling super, super flying about it.
Speaking of speaking of of the Patriots receivers,
I don't know whether or not the schedule is going to allow for Steph Curry of the Golden State Warriors to be at the game in Santa Clara.
But if Chef Curry is in the building, I expect Stephon Diggs,
as he is with many chefs, to get probably too aggressive.
Yeah, they are in there in L.A. on Saturday and home on Monday.
So they will probably be probably be able to make the game.
I don't know if they'll be in attendance, but he would be able to make it.
All right. Something to keep in mind.
I haven't seen that on the list of crazy ass who will be attendance props.
He hasn't been listed. So all right.
And then we will go with a national anthem length.
It is Charlie Perr or Pew.
I don't know how to pronounce his last name.
Yeah, yeah, Charlie. OK.
OK, I must have that misspelled then.
But the over under is at one hundred and twenty four and a half seconds.
So here's the thing.
Most of the time you have a national anthem prop.
It's because the person has some national anthem at another event.
This person has not.
They only played it on piano once for an event.
We have no bearings.
This guy likes to hold notes out or not hold notes out that that.
That there's no historical legacy which makes handicapping this an adventure.
And it seems high. That number seems high to me.
That's a long anthem.
Do we know what the what the length was last year?
No, I think it was right at one.
Nineteen and a half or one twenty somewhere in there.
I can't remember on top of my head, but it was right around that one.
It's right around that two minute mark is usually where it lands.
So right.
I tend to always bet over on this.
And so I'm going to pump my own breaks and I'm going to go under on the anthem.
I'm also going to go under Putes or pews singing style.
I've always thought is a little bit more clipped.
Like he's not a like Ed Sheeran like, you know, like being big voice guy.
I'm sorry, Justin.
He's not like a what?
I'm sorry, Justin. My headphones are cutting out.
What are you saying?
Ray Romano took over here.
You know, Ed Sheeran, big, tall, full of hair.
You know, definitely graying.
Yeah.
So I'm going to go under.
I think he's going to sing a kind of hipster for the Superbowl.
A little bit of a hipster version of the national anthem.
What's the what's the time on this one?
Over under one twenty one twenty four and a half.
I think I'm going to go over.
Last year, John Baptiste did a minute fifty nine.
Yeah.
Oh, but you know, Baptiste.
I felt like he did a pretty clipped version of it, though.
I didn't think he did a terribly long version.
I don't remember him doing a long version of it.
Let's stop pretending.
Let's stop pretending like we can remember in detail, Baptiste's anthem.
Yeah, exactly.
What are we doing?
It's been a week or two since I've watched it.
So I'm not exactly sure.
I'm going to be on the over as well.
I think we're do a very embellished national anthem.
We haven't had him in a while, so I think we're good for a few extra.
Not lying.
By the way, he's a huge tick tock guy.
So so there is the chance that he is going to do a thing so he can be a meme
on the tick tock on the tick tock.
I say what's the next shout out to the amount of scoops that have stuck around
for this recording.
This is pretty impressive to have this gallery that we have.
Paul, do you have a lean on that?
No, no.
So I'm just objecting.
Will not bet on the length of the national anthem, a bridge too far.
I respect it.
And I respect it.
Well, Paul is taking Paul is taking an Ian of standing from this one.
What I'm thinking is maybe they want it when it comes to betting the length of the national anthem.
Paul is out indefinitely.
I think they might find a way to stop it.
Well, then that would be over.
If Paul, we're going to put if anthem is interrupted, Paul gets an extra point.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm calling for.
Does not finish.
Paul is DNF.
The most skilled prediction of the entire super bowl, coin toss, head or tails, tails, baby.
It never fails.
Now we've discovered there's like many ways to bet on the coin toss, right?
It's like, will they call heads?
Will they call tails?
Will there be heads with details?
There's what the coin toss will be.
There's what the coin toss is called.
There's a team that wins the coin toss.
There's will the team that wins the coin toss opt to take or receive or defer bets off of
the coin.
Then there's also, there's, there's, there could also be a couple of the variants at
the current point toss as well, depending upon how crazy you want to get into it.
Has it ever landed sideways?
Nobody.
Hey, no one gets the ball.
Totally do.
It's been 60 super bowls.
It hasn't happened.
So it's totally do.
And with that, we are adjourned.
I crown the two teams, coach champions.
Wouldn't that be the best if they stopped the game right there?
No, but by law at that point, both team captains have to go into a stalled burpee and start
blowing to see which way it falls to the, they actually revert to the XFL rule.
But instead of players, it's both coaches have to scrum for the ball on the 50 yard
line.
Oh, you're all wrong.
You're all wrong.
They go back to the locker room and on their way in, they play death in the doorway.
Well, gentlemen, you're all wrong.
It's a thumb war between Cardi B and Sam Darnold's old case of mononuclear.
Oh, we've just gotten word.
Cardi B is out indefinitely.
Damn that kissing game.
We got Jacob on tails.
I mean, that's one of their guesses.
Boys.
Matt, what do you got?
I want to go through all of them.
I want to say it's going to be called tails.
It's going to be.
And Seattle will like to receive.
And then what's the other thing?
Oh, Seattle.
When?
Yeah.
Pages will lose the coin toss.
Seattle, when the coin doesn't, Seattle electors.
Holy shit.
Can you please box that up as a parlay?
Can you do the same?
Do you parlay on?
I don't think it's parlayable in Nevada with those options, but I'll take a look around
and see if I can.
That's amazing.
If you could box up a three, a three-point parlay only on the coin toss, you could lose.
You could lose a grand before the court.
Before the whole Superbowl starts, you're like, I fucking blew my big bet.
Let's take a 50, 50 bet and make it even more.
But if, but if, but if you bet a thousand dollars and you won your coin toss parlay,
you can buy the Washington Post.
Bro, I think it's, I think it's pretty cheap to get right now on the market.
Paul, heads or tails?
I will go heads.
And Justin, heads or tails?
And Sacajawea coin, please, down to Sacajawea coin.
It's always a, it's always a limited edition collectible coin, sir.
Yeah.
And this year they're going Sacajawea catching a ball.
Oh, my sports betting app will not let me bundle even two of those things.
Oh, that's so funny.
Usually you can't parlay the coin toss by itself because it's got short odds, but maybe
the, maybe the probable ones, but even then they're usually not parlayable.
It's weird that I can't parlay it with like winner of coin toss.
Because one side of the coin is chief interception and the other side is Sacajawea.
They're recognizing the indigenous peoples of the, of the area and the Santa Clara Valley.
I'm going to say tails never fails.
I'm going to say that it's called tails and I'm going to say that the Patriots defer.
Oh yeah, I'll say, I'll say that it's Seattle is Seattle will be calling the toss because
they are the real team.
Then Seattle will defer.
Seattle will defer.
Tails is called Seattle wins.
And it's a, I'm not, I'll just go back to the video because I'm not going to be able
to write this all down.
And I will be going on team tails never fails as well, because even though it is a head
in the longterm, I believe it is, it has been three of the last five have been heads or
three, three and two in the last five years have been heads.
So tails is due to wash it out.
All right.
I'll say, I'll say New England wins the coin toss and New England takes the ball.
And I would say that it's going to be going to say it's going to be tails.
I think the, I've got tails, New England, New England takes the ball tails is called
Seattle wins.
Seattle, the first, that's my guess.
So we'll jot all the extra ones down later, but we'll get that one.
All right.
I'm going to dump down to the fun stuff.
Let's get some crazy things going on.
Well, let's get the first one out of the way.
Will there be an octopus Matt's favorite prop at the super bowl, an octopus is well a player
that scores the touchdown also score the following two point conversion.
So like, for example, Stephon digs catches a pass for the touchdown.
And then on the next play catches the pass for the two point conversion.
He has to score all eight points by himself.
So not the quarterback throwing the ball.
That doesn't count.
You have to be physically carrying the ball into the end zone for both the touchdown and
the two point conversion.
Yeah.
It has happened.
It happened like one of the first years.
So it's always been interesting to bring that up.
And I was like the first year I brought it on here happened.
So I still remember getting a giant text of all caps from that.
That just was octopus with 28 exclamation points after it.
It was the best thing.
It was the most interesting thing that happened to zipper ball.
Yeah.
And you, and Andy called it out.
So he looked like a God in his party.
It was always really good.
So, all right, will there be an octopus?
This one, the S will be a two pointer because it is a plus money.
It is plus 15 to one right now for again, if you were at a Superbowl party, you're not
a sports fan.
They score a touchdown.
You hear they're going to go for two, right?
You may even know it.
You might even not know all the focus to be here.
Go for two.
Yell octopus.
That's it.
Just go octopus and you'll be the hit of the party.
It'll be the hit of the party because someone could potentially score eight points.
Yeah.
And then when somebody else asks what's an octopus, pull this episode up and go to the
bathroom and watch back to this moment so you can have it explained to you because you've
definitely forgotten.
Or just ping me on discord and I'll see if I can set it here real quick as much as I
love it.
This Justin's going.
Yes.
Yeah.
You want to know what I'll say, um, well actually no, cause new England's run defense is really
good.
So normally it would either be running quarterbacks or running backs.
And if you have a really, really good running game, I don't think new England trusts the
running game.
I think that the C is Seattle does, but new England's run defense is really good.
So if you're going to go for two, you would probably want to try to get at least JSN involved.
Although you want to know what I'm going to say?
Yes.
And here's what it is.
It's going to be, uh, it's, uh, uh, you're calling the specific octopus Jackson Smith
and Jigba on the score.
And then he has like run, no running plays.
He's running like five running plays all year.
That's when you do the jet sweep, that's going to be the end around JSN and he, and he makes
he outruns whoever he needs to outrun the corner.
I like it.
I like, I'm, I'm going with yes as well.
And I like JSN for the, uh, for the octopus as well, uh, Matt, oh, uh, no, I'm not greedy.
I've had one octopus in my lifetime in the super bowl.
That's in moderation, everything in my, I'll be telling my grandkids about, I choose to
live in a world where fun things happen.
Yeah.
Uh, Paul, do you, will you be partaking in the calamari or do you think it will be not,
not happening?
I think it's going to happen.
Whoa.
All right.
And I will be on the not happening as well side because good God, we lose too much money.
If that does happen, can I tell you guys?
All right.
This is inside sauce.
Okay.
Um, but, uh, there's a new episode of world's greatest con coming out in the next 48 hours.
And, uh, somebody sends, uh, somebody involved Brian send somebody preview episodes because
they really like it.
It's a member of Penn and Teller.
I'm not going to tell you which one, but he doesn't have a podcast with Matt and may or
may not be Brian's adopted father.
Yeah.
I'm not going to tell you which, which member of Penn and Teller, but, uh, in the new episode,
the phrase proposition bet is explained.
And this member of Penn and Teller mystery said that he has never been clear on what
a proposition bet was until he listened to this episode.
Oh, okay.
I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, if you're not a sports person, you wouldn't really know that you wouldn't really
know it.
Even though they've lived in Vegas for 30 years.
There's probably been actively involved, something with them as a bet at one point in time.
It is amazing to me when Vegas people ask me like, wait, what does the plus and minus
mean on the, on the sports betting, but you, you live here, you should have picked that
up at least.
Although I think when it comes to football, the last time I know two times ago at scoop
fest, when we were on Penn Sunday school and Penn was complaining about how he doesn't
know what the NFL draft is and I reminded him that he was explaining the NFL draft on
television.
You're literally on it explaining it right there.
All right.
We'll go.
We're going to take this one is this one is for Paul, put on your tin foil hats, ladies
and gentlemen, bring it.
Until they mentioned the electrical substation by the stadium during the broadcast.
Oh, I'm not sure you're familiar with this, but he's much more loquacious than I am.
What is the significance of the electrical substation?
Yes.
We get to explain the substation.
Justin time.
Oh, I'll refer to you, sir.
So the 49ers practice at a facility in Santa Clara.
Yeah.
So that practice facility is an electrical substation.
The 49ers have been especially injury plagued over the last few years, but never more so
than they were this year when it seemed like every other week, one of their star players
was going out with season ending injuries, ACL tears.
And so there became a rumor that maybe the electromagnetic field from that substation
that was weakening the ACLs of the 49ers players, this led to both of the teams not practicing
for super bowl week at that 49ers facility instead opting to go to other colleges in
the, in the area to practice all week and also being two and a half mile hours of a
drive away from both hotels that are being hosted.
It doesn't help either.
Talk about the journal.
Oh, there was a journalist that went in there and was measuring to take readings of, of
the electromagnetic fields.
So there's been, there's been a lot of conversation about it.
It's probably bullshit, but I care to ignore that and believe that this is an actual issue
that just being torn from the bone by electromagnetic pulses is this field.
What is this field, John Lynch, the 49ers general manager said that it was conjecture
worth looking into.
Oh boy.
That was the thing is that when the Niners said, we'll take a look at it, I was like,
that's not the answer you want to give, but okay.
No, right.
What is, so yeah, there's been a whole bunch of hype around this.
It's Levi's, Levi's stadium.
All right.
I got you.
So it's, it's an electrical substation.
No, no, no.
It emits.
Oh, no, I got that.
I'm telling you, not that I'm asking about the stadium.
What kind of, it's Levi's stadium open air.
What kind of events are played there in San Francisco, like it's just like full on regular
season games.
It's mainly big concerts using the Niners play there.
It's not, the substation is not getting mentioned substation is not getting mentioned in the
broadcast.
Wow.
Conspiracy theory taking the no or Paul, you taking the no here because I don't think the
yes.
Man, no, if, because if they, if even ingest the NFL, if the NFL broadcasters mention the
fact that there is speculation even that electromagnetic fields are affecting players and therefore
they practiced offsite.
What do you think that does to the general populace who goes to see games in that stadium?
The lawsuit fetishes of this country will be all the fuck over it.
Paul, I think you're undercutting this.
I think you are not going big enough.
It is not what will people who go see games in the stadium say.
It's what will people who live near electrical substations across the country say?
You're right.
Well that too.
Well, but dude, I mean, no, cause this is just electrical substation.
Look, this is not like a big special thing.
I'm a Kentucky boy.
This ain't new to me.
This was, this was one of the things that dairy farmers always talk shit about.
They're like, I can't get my cows to milk, right?
Because of all these goddamn electrical lines.
So this is the thing.
This has been a fall.
You are wrong for the right reasons.
Great.
This is my life.
Here's why.
So go ahead.
Tell me you are.
You are correct in that the NFL is a punitive old boys network that would crack down on
anything that could be a bad for any one of the owners.
Here's where you're missing it.
Okay.
It is an old boys network that is essentially just a very exclusive golf club for 32 very
rich men who hate each other.
So there's never really any one thing that's sacred except for we should not offer players
guaranteed contracts.
That's the one thing.
Okay.
That's the one thing they all agree on every day.
Like, so if somebody says, yeah, the substation is just tearing ACLs off the bone in San Francisco.
Wow.
Then Jerry Jones, who has his own cadre is going to be like, ah, what a great line.
Oh, that's amazing.
He's going to be texting whoever the announcer is.
Great job.
Keep doing it.
Okay.
That's possible.
All right.
So yeah.
So Justin's going to the yes side on that one.
No, I also think they're going to say no, but I don't think they're not going to say
anything about it.
Yeah.
I don't think that that's going to be where they, they, well, who, hold on, who are the
announcers?
It's a Collins worth crew.
So it's ended CNBC.
Oh my, you know, that's substation has just been a killer for all these players.
Yeah.
A hand to the Niners making it through the season with Collins worth and Melissa Stark
will be the main three.
No.
See, they're not like, wink, wink guys, they're not saying it, they're not saying it.
If it were Tom Brady and KB, I would vote yes.
But it's Collins worth and Stark.
I'm going to say no.
All right.
So I am the only person who would do it is Al Michaels.
If Al Michaels was doing it, then he'd be like, according to the substation, they're
not doing their thing.
They're all dying.
You don't think Terry McCauley, you don't think rules analyst, Terry McCauley is going
to mention it.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Maybe gene's territory.
All right.
So while we're on the announcing team, we'll go with the next one.
I am the only yes on that one, by the way, will Chris Collins worth somehow find a way
to mention Patrick Mahomes?
Yes.
Okay.
Can you really bet on this?
Sure.
There are all, there are offshores that out for it.
So yes.
Oh God.
Bet my mortgage.
I would also like to bet just as mortgage, anyone who throws on the fucking run, it's
like, Oh my, you know, Drake, man, I haven't seen a quarterback.
Patrick Mahomes.
I mean, my God, he's going to bring up the fact that the last five Superbowls have had
a minute until this one.
Yeah.
This is the last one.
And I was just dreaming about Patrick Mahomes last night and I was just thinking about his
sweet baby face and his round derriere and Mike, I was just in hog heaven.
I was thinking about it.
My wife is fully turgid.
My wife has never loved me.
Like Collins worth loves Patrick Mahomes.
I don't think anybody has loved anybody in humanity.
Like Patrick Collins worth loves Patrick Mahomes.
Yeah.
Paul, are you joining us on team?
Yes.
Are you going to be our contrarian here?
I say, I say, no, it's not going to, it's not going to happen.
No.
All right.
Paul will be our contrarian.
Will bad.
We'll go to the halftime show here for a little bit.
Will bad bunny mention ice during his performance?
Will bad bunny mention ice?
A yes is the betting favorite at minus one 50 right now.
It actually might be up to 200 cents.
The Grammys.
I haven't checked.
Let me, let me ask you a question.
Clarifying question.
Does he have to mention ice by name?
Does he have to say the word ice?
Will he mention it in Spanish?
Yes.
He has to say ice.
Oh, but if he says it in Spanish, El Frigio Agua, everyone knows.
Yes, El Frigio Agua.
So we've got, I think he will do something because he did it on the last thing he did
at the Grammys.
So I can't see him not saying something at some point.
All right.
So we got Jacob on the no, no, I guess me, Oh, Jacob's on the yes.
I guess everybody's out.
Is everybody on the yes?
No, I'm going no.
Cause I think they're going to do like some symbol that's supposed to be interpreted as
anti ice, but they're not going to say specific.
So you guys are going to come across zero percent chance, zero percent chance that this
happens.
Look, there's a lot of talk about that 32 old boys network, right?
Here's one thing that they all agree on.
They don't want Kaepernick.
They don't want anything like when Kendrick Lamar came out, Kendrick Lamar had to do things
that were kind of, it was like Sam Jackson yelling in an uncle Sam outfit is like, okay,
that's vaguely, you know, it seems like a Spike Lee movie.
Those are racial.
Like it wasn't anything direct.
Like I don't think that there's anything close to a specific mentioned eyes.
I think there might not be a moment where he rips out his shirt and his titty says,
fuck ice on it.
So there could be background signs and stuff, but I'm saying he has some civically say fuck
ice or get ice out.
You might get a fuck ice titty.
Is there now in the, in the parallel kid rock conscious happening in the like whitey McWhitey
network, whatever it's called the TP USA, the real halftime show in my house.
Oh no.
Will he mention ice?
You know, will he, will he, will he hand medals to ice?
Those agents that killed people in Minnesota.
He's gonna, he's gonna kiss one live on stage, him and the two guys that shot pretty are
going to triple kiss.
He's going to baptize.
I'm really surprised.
I'm not surprised.
They haven't had a damn.
I just totally lost my train of thought.
Nevermind.
Sorry about that.
Justin, could you name any of the other three headliners that are going to be part of that
halftime show with kid rock?
No, the other random creative players, the music creative players, the other country.
One of them's like an American idol person.
I think Rhett Rhett chamber, chamberless, um, Gary Busey, Dirty McBurks fan, Doug McFiddleston
and uh, uh, uh, Bill guitar, guitar.
You said you didn't know any of them.
Dude, I saw Bill guitar open a Cachella.
He was actually really good.
Yeah, no.
Yeah.
I am in the entertainment industry and I have no idea who these other three people are.
Where is the, where is the tapu so halftime show happening?
I don't even know how to tune in.
Uh, I would assume somewhere in the South, other than that, I'm not sure.
I just assumed it was happening at the Arizona Cardinal stadium.
I think it's on like Newsmax and a couple other channels being simulcasted on a bunch
of different, um, cable networks and like online streaming services.
Weamer screamer creamer with the brutal one in the chat over, under our odds that Christie
Noam appears at the puppy bowl only at the end, only at the end.
I'll tell you that just to lose the new wrinkle this year, the winning team gets adopted.
The losing team gets to hang out with Christie Noam.
Oh, she's going to bring you out to the gravel pit.
Like we take what headwear will bad bunny be wearing at the start of the halftime show?
Your options are a straw hat, a baseball cap, no headwear, a beanie or any other.
Oh, I had where I'll take any other, yeah.
Isn't he known for wearing a salad shooter in his concerts?
Isn't that part of his stick?
He comes out and he's like, you know, sometimes people tell me I'm a bad bunny and I just
tell him, honey, it's like a carrot filled salad.
And then he starts turning his hat and he crunches a carrot through it and he's like,
Paul, Paul, I shoot some salad challenge.
I think you're thinking Gallagher.
Right.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
It's Gallagher.
I was thinking Gallagher.
Yeah.
Gallagher.
That's Gallagher and bad bunny.
I think it was Gallagher too.
Not Gallagher.
You're right.
It was Gallagher too.
Cause he's from Puerto Rico.
I'm going to go.
No head.
No headwear.
All right.
Justin and Matt on none me on province straw hat and Jacob and Paul on any other.
Cause Paul's strictly moonshotting a salad.
Hey, can I ask you guys a real, a real question?
Oh, now here we go.
They're going to do subtitles.
Yes.
I hope they do.
I hope they do the because they did that.
I saw the video where they did that for one of his recent songs and it was great.
So yeah, I think, I think they will cause he doesn't sing in England.
I don't think people really understand that like there's no English words in any of his
music at all, but he sings, he does not.
If there is a word that is in English, it's by fucking accident.
Cause it's the same word in Spanish.
Do you think that they might not have the Spanish word is no.
Do you think that they might put subtitles on inside of the arena itself?
I would think you, you gotta do it for the audience at home.
Cause that's the, I think they're going to have a team of really aggressive people with
a scroll and one person writing really fast with a marker and they're just going to run
it really fast across the, across the stage.
Oh, I mean, they do have the ribbon, the ribbon boards in stadiums that show the closed captioning
already.
So they probably will have it for his thing as well.
Or also ASL.
There's probably that.
Ooh.
Would that be ASL or that is there Spanish?
How do you sign Spanish in American sign?
That mean ESL for Espanol.
I thought you meant English, second language.
No.
All right.
Well, let's get to some, let's do some ads here while we're at it.
Which animal will be shown first in the super bowl ad starting after the kickoff.
So this doesn't count anything before the pregame show.
After the game is kicked, we go to commercials, will a cat be shown first or a dog be shown
first?
Ooh.
Straight up normal man.
Dog.
I am on dog.
Yeah.
Dog.
Nasty dog.
Dirty dog.
Unless the cat is, is torturing the dog or tormenting the dog.
So that, that, that, that just wanted, I can't go horse cause I would go horse.
No, no horses allowed.
This isn't, this isn't Taylor.
Sheridan is going to be furious.
No horses.
I know Taylor.
So pissed.
He's like, what the fuck?
I'm going to Netflix.
Matt, you go on Contrarian on this one.
Of course I am fucking team cats surrounded by two sleeping ones right now.
All right.
Continuing on the ad form, which ad is shown first, the liquid death ad or the, he gets
us ad.
What's he get?
Both have been.
He gets us.
Is the church Jesus, the churchy one that is going to be very early.
It's going to be the churchy one is the, they're, they're like the youth pastor.
Yeah.
Like the, it's the commercial that sits down on a chair backwards.
Turns attack guys.
You want to know who else you want to know who else kicked off and wound up finding glory?
Our Lord Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
You know, I was led 11 men to the victory.
Now when you're talking about the liquid death, what's been the resolution on the fact that
it's been proven that they're not giving any of their funds to charity.
Like they claim Paul, you want to know which business magnets not being held accountable
for the horrific crimes against humanity they're committing on a regular basis.
Yeah.
And that's the climate where, where our government is cracking down on, on fraud.
I'd like to know how,
they're getting to it now from the public.
That's fine.
They're not taking government.
I guess you're right.
Good.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
What?
Look, they're fucking charging $4 for a can of water.
They won.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
They can operate above the law happened on Epstein Epstein's Island in 4k and nobody
gives a shit.
They've hoodwinked the public already.
So I'm going to take liquid death history, the contrarian apparently on that one.
Then
I'll take a diamond J.
Will Cardi B be wearing a Stefan Diggs?
I went liquid death.
Oh, by the way.
Oh, Matt, when we left, okay, Matt and I are both looking at death.
Some of us need liquid death to stay in business in order to keep doing their most requested
magic trick.
So I guess we need them to keep doing well.
Good call.
Will Cardi B be, will Cardi B be wearing a Stefan Diggs or will she be wearing something
else?
Nothing else.
She is connected to Jersey.
Doesn't show the girls off.
You know what I mean?
Not at all.
We need Cardi.
We're in a hole that way.
We are.
Are we counting a custom?
Like, if it's a, if it's a, if it's a Christian Juzic, as long as the Jersey is the base
of it, it still counts.
Yes.
I think yes.
I would say yes.
Yeah.
She has been in the past wearing those.
I'm on the yes as well because I think she'll get that Niners tight end dude, Juzic or whatever
his name is, wife to make her something.
Cause she did all the puffer jackets for Taylor and all this stuff for Brittany Holmes.
I think she'll do something for them as well.
For Cardi.
I think she's going to be in the craft box too.
So they're going to, they're going to see her a lot.
And also there's the rumor that she is going to be part of the halftime show because she
has that song with Bad Bunny.
And she also, unlike Bad Bunny, raps in English.
Oh yeah.
Oh, well she's out.
Yeah.
Sorry.
So Paul, you got a stance on that one.
Yeah.
I agree.
I think yes.
However, also like Bad Bunny.
I also need subtitles to know what she's talking about.
Never experienced that.
Take a look at this.
Will the final score of the game be a Scoragami?
For those of you that don't know at home, a Scoragami is a unique score that has never
happened in NFL history.
There is a website that tracks all this.
It's been around for quite a while.
It's a pretty fun factor.
So will the team, will the final score of the game be a unique score that hasn't happened
in NFL history?
Those aren't that hard to come by.
Are they Mitzi?
Yes.
It's about, yes.
It's 25 to one that this will be a Scoragami.
It's not very likely to happen.
Okay.
So it is more, okay.
So most scores have happened at this point.
The chance for a Scoragami is higher in that weird shit does happen more often than you
would think in the Superbowl.
Like there's a, there's a fair, there's a lot of safety.
There's more safeties than you would think of in the Superbowl for random reasons.
But I will say no, I'll take chalk on that.
I'll say, Paul's on the yes on that one is going to be a weird score.
Final score.
Be a Scoragami.
Oh, I wanted it in my heart.
Let's say yes.
Yeah.
I wanted in my heart.
I already took the octopus.
I'm not taking Scoragami too.
You want to parlay them, Jacob?
I will parlay.
I would love to parlay them.
All right.
Will a scoring drive take less time than the singing of the national Anthem?
So will a draft scoring drive in the game take less than the right now at two minutes
that it's set to be the Anthem.
Yes.
The yes is the heavy favorite.
I will be taking a yes as well because it could be one play or yeah, and it's got to
be a, it's got to be a scoring drive any time in the game.
So not a kickoff return doesn't count.
Okay.
So I have an established play and then go from there.
So it could be a first play touchdown.
It could be a couple of plays.
I'm taking the yes because there's usually, right, especially now with the modified kickoff,
the opening kicks aren't getting, they're getting closer.
So it only takes one or two plays for them to get that last second field goal.
But wait, hold on, hold on.
Are we talking about game time or real time?
Clock time, not actual time.
So two minutes of clock time, not two minutes of actual time.
I'm going to say no.
Do you think it's going to be a lot of long drawn out slogs?
I just think that both teams are going to need to rely on running the ball or they're
going to be relying on short passes inside.
And so just, you're going to see a lot of clock even for drives that are moving fast.
I was going to say, this is, this is me saying yes, because I also took the over.
I think there's going to be some scoring drives.
Yeah.
Paul, you got a stance on this one?
I said, I think, I think, I think there will be one that goes quicker.
All right.
And Matt?
I just, just no, cause I want to go against Jacob and Paul.
You're racking them points up.
All right.
First play of the game will be a run or a pass.
I will, I will be taking a run because it is currently the favorite.
Justin was on the favorite as well.
Yeah.
I'll take that run.
Oh, in the sky, it's captain contrarian.
It's going to be a pass.
I'll take pass Matt and Paul on the pass.
All right.
A Jersey number of the first player to score a touchdown.
The overrun is the overrunner set at 10 and a half players with the number under 10 that
you need to worry about our Stefan digs, Drake may a Walker and I believe he is Sam, right?
I got to find his one second here.
Yeah.
Where are you?
JSN under over for me, Jen or Jason's 11.
So he's over.
Oh, that over.
So over.
I'll stay on Jacob.
So Jacob and I are on the under.
Everybody else is on the over X P N captain contrarian.
Captain contrarian.
All right.
Let's get the another fun one.
Will an offensive lineman score a touchdown?
Will a player that is listed as an offensive lineman score a touchdown with tackle eligible
has happened a bit with these teams, but I don't think anybody has scored a touchdown.
Yes is the massive underdog in this one.
Here's the reason why you roll the dice.
One of the people that famously did this was Bill Belichick with his offensive lineman,
Mike Frabel, who is now the head coach of the new England Patriots.
Is he going to pass down the lineage and have a big man touchdown?
That's the argument and I'm going to, I'm going to buy the hype.
I'm going to say, yeah, I live in a world where things like this can happen.
So I'm saying yes.
If it's in the playbook, it would be brought out on Sunday.
There ain't no more games.
You can't exchange unused trick plays for sizzler gift certificates.
It's baby.
Yes, Matt and you lean on this one.
Yes.
Only cause I liked the term gadget and Paulie.
Paul.
Nope.
I will, I will be the contrarian on that one that all right, will a field goal or PAT hit
the upright or crossbar?
Will there be a kick that clanks?
What's the normal thing on that?
How many, how often does that happen?
Is there, it's happening a little bit more now that they moved the PAT back, but also
now they're just missing more.
So it hasn't been as much, but when it opened, it was like doing this prop first started
being dealt.
So eight or 10 to one, now it's about five to one on the yes.
So it is drifting down and just happening a little more regular.
But here's, here's the other thing, Paul, is that the field goal kicks have gotten ridiculous
lately where it used to be like a shocking thing that would break in live if somebody
was kicking from past 30 yards and now people kick from 70 yards and nobody blink blinks
an eye.
And the only reason why people were missing is because that same strategy was being applied
when the weather got shitty and outdoor stadiums.
It's going to be in the Bay.
It's going to be the exact same fucking weather that it always is in the Bay.
It's going to be gorgeous.
No one's going to give a fuck about a shooting their shot from as far out as they want.
And I don't think that the wind is going to be a factor.
Okay.
That being said, I'm taking it just so it goes from a shot of Cardi B to a shot of a,
a hitting it off the post.
It's the donk doink.
I like it.
Don't get doink.
But don't get doink.
I don't think I can get donk donk clearance cleared through gaming, donk donk partly cleared
through gaming.
But that would be a fun one to often.
That would be.
Yeah.
I'll take it.
I say, what the hell?
It's not that rare.
I just need to remember it happening a lot in, in Super Bowls.
So Jacob and I are saying no, no, I'm going to, I'm going to take the yes just because
if it happens, we get our asses kicked and it usually ends up happening.
All right.
Will the game go to overtime?
Usually the no is a lock.
Last year didn't happen.
Last year it actually went to overtime.
So what do you think?
Nah, no way.
Nah, no, no, I don't think so.
No.
All right.
That is the first one.
We are full team one side.
When will the first player go into the medical tent before or after halftime?
So this is either concussion protocol or an on-field injury getting checked also has to
be shown on the broadcast.
So that's the other thing is either so shown or have the side and correspondents say, blah,
blah, blah was in the tent.
So it's got to be shown or mentioned.
If an ACL rips clean, like a slow cooked baby back rib because of EMF rays, do they go to
the tent or they just go right to the, no, that's carted off.
That's different.
It's got to go into the blue tent protocol, ankles, knees, stuff, stuff, stuff, stuff like
that.
Justin, here's my feeling on it.
It's going to be second half because adrenaline so high in the first, even if that does happen,
they're still walking it off from a little dirt in it.
Well, but the problem is now they've got the independent people that are watching the game.
So if you, if you get hit in the head, the air on the side of a fencing position, because
that's the universal sign that your brain turned off against its will, normally you
would just be allowed to play another down a football and then they would shoot you up
with Torah doll on the sidelines.
Now they have somebody like a pussy who makes you go to the back and, you know, concerned
about your health.
Yeah, no, that's good.
I, I, I'm going to go with the second half still.
I'll say first half because also this, this is the time where they're going to be extra
fucking concerned about shit like that because they, they do want to make it seem like they
give a fuck.
So I'll bet on first, they want to make it look like they care about concussions.
I think it's going to happen before, even though Paul's hecking have, we know it's also
a good lead because the start of the second half, there's a slightly more prone to injury
because it's a longer half time than normal.
So they're a little more rested as they cool, they get iced, tighten up, bad buddy has his
way.
Hey, second half, please.
No medical, Tim, that would be second half or never been, baby.
I'm saying never know the MVP bank first in their victory speech.
Your options are God teammate, family, city or fans and the super long shot at 6,660 420
to one Staten and or Snoop Dogg teammates teammates.
So my pick of golden palace.com off the board.
Yeah.
Yes.
So Paul, Paul's going teammates.
I'm going to God.
God.
Yeah.
Big man.
First of all, give all the glory to God.
Number two, I just love my teammates, man.
And my family, I'm going to go previously unacknowledged child previously unacknowledged
child.
Oh, she has a secret family.
He's going to thank his secret family.
Stefan Diggs says the right over the longest time ever, because yes, I think all 97 of
his children.
I know Stefan between Stefan Diggs, Elon Musk and future.
I think that they might be able to populate a small town with, and that's just the kids
that they don't know their first names right now.
That's the entire, that's the entire, that's one section of the stadium.
It's just that it's just their kids right now.
That's just, that's just sons from the three of them that they only referred to as big
man because they can't remember what the first name is chief right now, Robert Sala and Philip
rivers are like, damn, yeah.
It's like, fuck man.
We were just trying to populate a basketball team.
Like you guys are going for the full Genghis con.
All right, just laying Maxwell for keeping my name out of her fucking mouth.
We're going to call that family cause she's like family to some of them.
Yeah.
Hey, position of the player that gets the MVP quarterback running back, wide receiver
tight end defensive player or any other, Oh, I am going to go wide receiver.
I'm going to go quarterback.
I think it's been, I think quarterback and I think it'll be if they, if they're, if they're
0.0% chance that it is going to be anything other than quarterback.
And I'll explain to you why this has driven me nuts and listening to everybody talk about
this shit.
The only way that a wide receiver wins is if they throw a touchdown, neither of these
teams have plays where they throw it.
Antoine Randall won it when the Steelers won and why, not because he caught a touchdown.
It's because he threw a touchdown.
If if JSN catches three touchdowns, Sam Darnold will get the MVP because he threw the three
touchdowns.
What if the other reason what, what if though, what if JSN catches three touchdowns and gets
an octopus with an end around run still Sam, here's why, because the narratives on both
sides with the quarterback matter.
It's either never stop dreaming.
Never stop hustling.
Sam Darnold is every sports movie.
What a great guy or welcome to the next 20 years of your life.
The Patriots are going to break back.
Drake may has now replaced Tom Brady in either way.
It's going to be them in Jacob's defense.
No one has scored an octopus and not won the MVP.
True.
Every true one person was a quarter.
Matt, do you have a, I'm so I'm saying Justin, you're taking quarterback.
Yes.
That all being said, tight end.
You have to take a specific position.
I think it should be just non QB as its own prop, but it has to be a specific position.
There are, there are quarterback versus other, any other position props, but I wanted to,
this is one of those multi-spotters.
So I wanted to have a few options.
If the same person intercepts Sam Darnold three times, that person might be the MVP.
Ooh, that would be DB.
Yeah.
So you're going, yeah.
Christian Gonzalez.
Are you trying to force it to JSN?
Yeah.
You're going to go to defense on that.
All right.
I like that.
That being said, their wide receivers are so athletic.
I almost feel like that would be hard to do, but it would require Sam Darnold shitting
the bed.
Like, hold on.
Oh, he's done repeatedly.
Nevermind.
Oh, no, come on.
Sam Darnold's got a flawless record in nationally televised games that are broadcast to millions.
He sure does.
Paul, who do you think is going to be the MVP?
I think it'll be a quarterback.
All right.
Paul on quarterback as well.
First scoring play of the game.
Will it be a Seattle field goal, a Seattle touchdown, a New England field goal, a New
England touchdown, or a safety slash anything else that might happen, which I don't think
safety is the only other thing, but we put other on there just in case something crazy
happens.
The referees award a point.
Maybe they enact the rouge on the last minute and we're just not aware of it, so.
I will be taking a New England field goal, is my guess, because I think Seattle wins
the first, Patriots drive it down the field and get an early field goal.
I'll say Seattle field goal.
I think that the New England offense sputters.
I agree with your opening, but I think the New England offense sputters and you get one
early, you know, squirt out, kind of run, but then still go position.
This is first score.
First score of the game.
Yep.
I say, yeah, I'm darn old Mike.
I mean, you'd look at that pass and people thought he had mono and he was out indefinitely.
Well, he's back, not since Patrick Mahomes, not, you know, they call it the kissing disease,
Mike, but I'll tell you what, the amount of smooches that I would give to Patrick Mahomes,
I'd risk it for the biscuit.
I say Seattle touchdown.
All right, Matt, we go to Seattle touchdown as well.
And Jacob, Seattle defensive touchdown.
Whoa.
Holy.
That is not, there are, there are other spots that have that as a breakdown using that,
that is one of my, that is one of my very real bets on this game as a defense or special
teams touchdown.
Oh, it should be.
I think it is live for both teams.
I like both teams secondaries and I am Dicey on both teams quarterbacks.
Number of players to attempt a pass.
The over-under is two and a half.
So well, a non-quarterback throw a pass over.
Yes.
Over.
Yeah.
Jacob and Justin on the over.
I am on the over as, oh, actually I'm going to take the under and be contrarian I think
this year.
Oh, I was just saying I'm going over as well.
And Paul.
Good for able to take it to the next level.
And instead of having the live offensive lineman catch a pass, maybe the, the live offensive
lineman throws the pass.
To my right.
You run a counter, you run a counter, you hand it off to the left tackle who then throws
it to the right tackle.
Right.
Yup.
It'd be the most beautiful double tackle eligible play.
That sounds like something that Ben Johnson would think of after like his fifth line of
coke in the off season.
That's a bit too deep in a K hole.
Yeah.
Oh, do you think we're getting a non-quarterback?
Actually this could also also impact if one of the quarterbacks gets hurt and somebody comes
in for a player too.
Oh shit.
Oh, that's true.
Medical Ted medical Ted, let's say Drake may gets his bell rung.
And the next thing you know, you have whoever fucking comes up for, for them.
Who is their backup quarterback?
I don't know.
Either.
It's also Drake.
Damn it.
Yeah.
The Patriots I believe is a car, one of the cars, beep, beep, beep, beep someone related
to Derek or whatever.
It's Josh jobs.
And then it's, and then it's Tommy cutlets after that.
He's their Tommy DeVito is their third stringer.
Oh snap Jersey pride on the line.
All I need is two quarterback entries and he's in the game.
If Tommy DeVito comes in, we all become Pat's fans immediately.
Oh my God.
I mean, he was the accused guy too, so big Paul, you think in the over or the under on
that one over.
All right.
So I will be the Katrina on that.
I think the over is the good play, but I'm just taking the under for good measure.
Which quarterback will have the most passing yards in the game?
Sam Darnold is the favorite over Drake may for this proposition.
Oh, downtown Sam Darnold.
Come on super bowl MVP, Sam Darnold.
Let's go.
Take a dig up yards on interceptions.
Don't count for a passing really not in your book, maybe it's Sam Darnold.
Number one.
He is the number one.
I'm going to take Drake may just because I'd like to be on the underdogs in stuff.
It runs an oil.
Matt and Paul.
Do we have any liens?
Well, you know what they say?
The nucleosis is the powerhouse of the cell.
So I'll go Donald.
Yeah, I'm on Darnold because he's my pick indefinitely.
All right.
Will the final score be odd or even odd is the slight favor in this one.
The combined total score combined total score.
Yep.
So final scores.
Will it be odd or even?
All right.
These also, these are beds for which it's like it should come with a wellness check.
Like your employer, Mitzi should actually be dispatching people like you should be.
This is the one you're going to point out.
Not the coin prop partly that we built this is on the same level.
This is on exactly the same level as the coin should be a Trump executive order, everything
they're betting combined, they're betting up, up and down and over and under and when
army and Navy are playing even never Stevens.
So I'm going to go with even even never come to my attention that there's a combined RFK
jr.
Yeah.
You should not be batting these things unhealthy.
It's unhealthy.
Well, it's raw milk, raw, raw betting.
Prop betting has been linked to autism.
So we got to watch a good, more real than you would like to admit.
Even or odd odd Paul, even or odd odd.
I am on odd as well.
And like the ledge, I would jump off of if I were actually putting money on this.
All right, let's take a look here.
Which team will Drake bet on?
Drake is notoriously known to curse no singer, Drake from Toronto, the Canadian rapper, singer.
Now look, there is an argument that Drake might be feeling himself famously before he
got humiliated at the Superbowl by Kendrick Lamar being called a pedophile.
He was humiliated by a rapper by the name of Pusha T who turns out appeared in the Epstein
files last week.
Things are going well for Drake.
I think that he is going to bet on his friend's team, Robert Kraft.
I think he's going to bet on the Patriots.
I think he's going to be a pats money line guy.
I'm sold.
I'm riding with Justin.
Yeah.
That sounds right.
Wait, this is about Drake.
Who?
Drake will bet.
Who's in God's plan?
Yeah.
I should actually play.
Say I should put that in quotations because it'll be on stake and who knows if that's
actually his money or not.
So I'm going to go with the Seahawks because I think that Drake also missed time when he
was an actor because he had mono and so he has a brotherhood.
So he feels.
Yeah, their brothers and brothers, their brothers and mono.
I will be taking the Seahawks as well on that one because I think he likes chalk more than
anything.
So yeah.
All right.
Is that cocaine?
Is that what you're saying?
Chalk?
Yes.
Chalk.
Yeah.
Will the team that scores first win the game?
Yes.
Jacob is on yes.
I'm going to take no.
I think maybe we can trade on this one.
No.
I mean, I bet on the Seahawks to do it.
And even though I bet the Patriots, that was an emotional lie because I'm hedging my bets.
I believe that the Seahawks are going to win.
And so I will say that Seahawks will score first and they will win.
That is also a bet you can make.
Yep.
Wait, is this better?
Do we do scores first?
I'm so confused.
No, this is, will the team that scores first win the game?
So not, so they have to score first and win the game.
Yes.
All right, Paul, you got to lean on this one.
Yeah.
I'll say yes.
All right.
I will be the only no on that equation.
Team to offer the team to have the first coach's challenge Seattle or New England to pick
them if it doesn't happen points out didn't bet never happened.
Patriots, Frabel, Frabel's got his, he's got an itchy challenge finger.
Frabel likes the challenge.
I'm going, I'm going to England as well.
I'll go Seattle just because I don't have strong feelings for it.
And I want to steal points from Jacob, Mike McDonald, right?
I wonder if he's got those changeables, I'll go Seattle.
I'm going to go to new England with Justin and color of Gatorade this on the coach at
the end yellow or we have orange, yellow or green, blue, clear or no bath and red or purple,
yellow or green.
That is Paul on yellow.
I want red or purple.
Jacob is on red or purple orange, just daring.
There's no green, right?
You showing through yellow is yellow, yellow, green, yellow, green are connected in the
same one.
Cause there's they're kind of close.
They are, but it's going to look like piss.
I don't think they want it to look like piss.
So I'm going to go unless Mike McDonald's like a fucking golden shower fetishist, right?
Is the players who are picking the Gatorade are really funny.
It's so yellow.
Oh no.
I'm embarrassed.
Yeah.
Boys, it's 98.6 degrees.
Exactly.
If, if, if, if R Kelly was the halftime show, I definitely mean yellow.
I'm going to go purple, red, purple will be there and I'm going to take blue.
I don't know why.
I just think blue could be fun.
Okay.
Smurf fetish.
All right.
Will.
Yeah.
Now this one's going to be a funnel.
Let's throw back to the last Superbowl.
Will Seattle throw a pass from the Patriots or inside of the Patriots to yard line?
Will they tempt fate?
I will say yes.
They will redeem themselves.
So anyone who's not a, anyone who's not a sports person, stop listening to this podcast.
But this is a few years ago, last time I'm having to listen to it.
No, it was.
Yeah.
They, they opted to throw instead of head off to Marshawn Lynch, who was getting six
yards for tiny.
What's the difference?
Yeah.
Like I remember it.
I remember that ball.
Now it would make a lot more fucking sense than it did in that Superbowl because the,
the Patriots run defense wasn't what it is now, which is fucking excellent.
And the Seahawks said Marshawn Lynch, one of the greatest short yardage backs of all
fucking time.
So it was too clever by half for them to throw now throwing would be their best option.
Their best playmakers are a quarterback that can read really well.
And JSN, which they can throw a short pass that could be a safe one and let him try to
run it in with his, with his legs.
So I'm going to say, yes, I also, I think that's probably their best play within short
yardage.
Even note the time that jury said something nice about Sam Darnold.
I will.
I think they'll, I think they'll do it for the redemption arc.
I just think there's a chance that it won't happen at all.
So I'm going to go, no, oh yeah, I'm going to take the note because I don't know if they
ever get inside of the five yard.
I think they're going to skip a score.
It's going to be from a distance.
I think this is going to be more of a kick to point conversions count or is it only a
touchdown inside the two, two yard line.
No, that would not count because then two point conversion start at the two yard line.
So it has to be a play inside the two.
Yeah.
What is the illegal forward pass?
What if they throw an illegal forward pass on a two point conversion?
That would be, the play would be overturned.
So the play never happened.
So that passed.
No, it had to be, it had to be a, a penalty on the Patriots, right?
It would be like pass interference in the end zone.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
You could do it.
If it's a pass interference, put it on that.
But no, cause then the ball is put on the two.
Have we already, have we already passed the point?
So it's the one.
It's the one.
I've already passed the point Mitzi because variable was famous for catching touchdowns
as a linebacker in super bowls.
We already did that.
Yeah.
We talked about that already.
Okay.
Thanks for paying attention though.
I was not D line, but we can modify it to just alignment if you want to do that.
So that way it's either side of the mall.
Did you go, did you go over the coin toss?
Who's playing in the game?
We're going to talk about the super bowl.
Oh, this is all hindsight betting.
All right.
Let's do one more.
And I think we'll be good for the good for the punk position player of the player to
score the first touchdown.
That's what I'm talking about.
Linebacker.
Ooh, wait, I already said, I already said CB.
So that is Matt and Jacob on defensive player.
Yeah.
I'll go with quarterback.
Sneak.
He'll still, he'll zip it in.
Drake may would be, that would be bad.
That would be legit.
And then pushing, I'm going to say wide receiver and I will go running back just to take the
full field there.
All right.
I think we've got most, um, um, will there be a safety?
I'm on the no.
Oh, nah.
Yes.
This is to be such a go-to.
Yeah.
I love that.
Yes.
For a long time.
I'm off of it now.
So Justin's are you asking anybody else on the yes on that one?
I'll do yes.
This is the first time to see Seahawks were in the Superbowl that started with a safety.
So let's, let's go with this.
Let's go with yes.
All right.
And uh, total number, uh, let's see here.
I think that should be everything from the sheet.
I don't think we need anything else.
I was going to do songs in the halftime show, but I have no clue what song is and isn't
a bad bunny song.
So I wouldn't know if he was singing the same song with the transition or if he's doing
different songs.
All right.
One more.
We're good.
Will an offensive play be scored on a fourth down?
Will the offensive team score a touchdown on a fourth down play?
So when they have to go down and score a touchdown on that, no, no is the heaviest favorite.
No, no, no, no.
I'm going to take the yes.
Cause I think there could be like a fourth and they've been doing some fourth down in
the red zone stuff.
That's been kind of creepy.
Four downs, I'm with you mids these days and there used to be so that's because I used
to always, I used to always bet on prime time games.
First score of the game will be a field goal.
It's always plus money happens more often than you think has happened less this year
because now they're going for it on fourth down inside the 30.
So they're, you know, it's, it's happening less.
Even though the kickers are getting better, the coaches are getting more aggressive.
So I actually had to stop betting that one going forward because I just kept losing my
ass on it.
Is there a bet on whether or not, uh, Bill Belichick and Robert Kraft will have been
inducted into the NFL hall of fame by the time the super bowl starts?
Uh, they both have not accepted enough votes.
I do believe I know that right now.
That's why I'm asking, do we know the hall of fame can overturn it any day?
The hall of fame is too busy to building a should do or Sanders statue outside because
he got a passing touchdown in the flag football exhibition at the all-star game.
So there's a prop bet for whether or not Belichick and craft will be in a love triangle with
an unnamed 23 year old girl yet.
Yeah.
Or if a craft is going to change it up and not take his private jet down to West Palm
beach first to get some handy J's before going to the, which you did last time.
It's a long, it's a long detour to go from the, on that flight from New England to make
a pit stop in Florida, if you've got a jet, the super bowl, he did that for, was not in
Florida.
There is a lot, there is a lot of crazy props that you can and can't bet.
Um, if you're in a state with legal sports betting, have fun if you're to stay without
it.
I don't acknowledge that you're doing it.
Exactly.
Good luck.
Talking to St. Lucia, have fun, have fun in the Caribbean and or the isle of man.
There we go.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Thank you guys.
Thank you Mitzi as always.
And where can they go to print out this form, uh, to take to their parties?
I will, I will clean this up and get the sheet done and I will throw it on the discord and
I will tweet it out at clean it and put it on threads under @mitzula on both MIT ZULA
on all platforms.
There you go.
If you're not big on the sport thing, or even if you are and you want some real fun bets
to play around with at your super bowl party, grab Mitzi's scorecard.
Yeah.
What I'll usually do is I'll make it so it's one or two page so you can put them together
and then you can just circle your, which ones you like that up, who has the most picks at
the end.
You've you're good to go.
And it's nice because it's got sports things.
It's got non-sports things.
It's got a little bit of everything for everybody.
So cool.
Uh, by the way, I'm Justin our young everywhere that you find, uh, Justin our young is on
social media.
And when it comes to my availability for this podcast until next time I'm out indefinite.
Oh no, thank you to all those Patreons out there that made this bonus episode possible.
Justin Robert young get well soon, get well soon, buddy.
Thanks everyone.
I mean the person who did that graphic knew what they were doing.
Oh yeah.
It's really funny.
I mean, it was, there's no question that they were like, this is hilarious.
Put it on TV.
This is a celebration.
Oh yeah.
It just points right into the camera.
Oh, chef's kiss.
Motherfucker chef's kiss.