Hey, before you enjoy today's podcast, I just want to quickly shout out all the people following
me year-round on my Torco. That's right. They're part of my exclusive WhatsApp thread. You could
be too, but I want to thank them right now. Steve Neruda, Bob Baker, Galactic President
Star McScoopsalot, Sebastian Robbins, B.B. Hermit, Colton Satmary, Sax Guy Jimmy D,
Joe Bethar Bowers, Adam Mancini, Michael Elsroth, Brandon Allen, Mike Mayhem, Jesse Miller,
Jason Yager, Robert Sherman, Matt Glowacki, Russ Matkin, Nate Walk, Jeff Loomis, Smitty Scoop,
Lee Popsicle, Greg and Felicity's Behind the Scenes Podcast, Ben Sherman, and Wendy
Bumgardner. Thank you so much. Enjoy the pod. Hey, I'm Matt. This is Abracababble.
And with me today is Mike Mills.
Hello.
Mike, thank you for joining us, but me. Well, you're joining us, our listeners, and me,
the person talking to you. Producer of numerous shows, including The Jokers of Magic, star
of The Jokers of Magic, host of The Jokers of Magic.
Oh, let's say host, please.
You Winston star. There's only four of us.
I'm deeply uncomfortable. If there's stars in that show, I'm not one of them. But I am
the host.
I am the host. I am your humble host.
Like, if there's credits, it's just like three names go by, and then you wait until
the scroll, and you're the only name in the scroll. Like, that's how it would go?
Maybe. Have you noticed that some of these shows now, they'll roll the credits, and it'll
be like, starring so-and-so-and-so, and then it's with, it's like tied on the end. And
I don't know what that means.
I don't know either. And then, like, in movies, like, if you, you go lower and lower and lower
unless it goes to and, you know.
Right.
Like, and then there's a last one.
The last star that says, and this person. Like, it's very, very crazy. We are about
to hit the road. We're about to hit nine cities.
Nine cities in ten days.
How, on a scale of one to ten, how much do you regret doing this as a whole?
What is a number? I can say, I can say eight and a half. But I, you know, it's a lot of
work, but it's, it's so much fun. It's all.
All the work is front-loaded. You know, the booking, the contracting, the insurance, the
travel planning, the technical advances. That's all, those are all the moments I wish I didn't
have to deal with.
I think it's interesting because, like, you have a, you know, it's like, it's like you
were, for our listeners who maybe don't know you, you were a magician, a magic enthusiast
and working magician, just like all the other nerds who still work today, besides me.
And Rob Zabrecki. And then you, you literally figured out how to start touring, how to start,
like, getting, booking shows. Like, where does it start? When do you start producing
shows at your college? Where, where does it go?
No, I, I was, I was a magician. I was paying for, I was working on my bachelor's at the
University of Albany and, but paying for my tuition by doing shows. And long story short,
I also had a magic shop in, here in Albany, New York, that I sort of,
fell into owning this magic shop. And then...
How old are you when you owned the magic shop? Are you 18?
Like, 20.
20.
19, 20. Yeah.
Is that the start of you being entrepreneurial? Or were you entrepreneurial before that?
No, no. That, yeah. I had, you know, as a teenager, I'd always been hustling, trying
to figure out how to make a buck, sort of by necessity.
Right. But what did you do?
What did I do as a teenager?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What did I not do? Selling hot dogs, selling, you know, milkshake stands, you know, starting
at age, you know, 8, 10.
All the stuff that kid entrepreneurs do.
Right. But you say that, like, it's common. It's not common to be a kid entrepreneur.
There are not, like, the majority of kids are not, like, go-getters and, like, want
to get into commerce right away.
I feel like, well, it's one of these things, I feel like there's less of it than there
used to be.
Right.
But I feel like back in the day, more kids were out, you know, trying to make a buck.
You know, here it was shoveling driveways or mowing lawns more often. But I got lucky
that I found magic pretty early. And not only did I love it, but you're like, oh my God,
$30 to go do a show at their kid's park. I'm 12. I'm 12 years old.
Yeah.
And there's a six-year-old that's having a birthday, and I can get $30 to go for a half
hour. And then if I do balloon animals, I can get another 10. Like, these are insane
amounts of money. And so...
So you were on top of incentive, you know, experience and that kind of stuff on top of
that as well. VIP experience, balloon animals on the side.
I'd stay and take photos with the kids, and I'd do a talk.
Yeah.
And I'd walk back.
Aren't you served Q&A?
No, I never thought of that, actually.
But, you know, so that was... But I think that's a story of a lot of young magicians
who are, you know, find out that there's some commerce to be had. And then what happened
in college, I was at a magic convention in Vegas, and I met this guy who ran a theater
in Pennsylvania, and I was picking his brain. He's like, oh, yeah, you know, we just had
Penn and Teller come through, and we did the Pendragon.
I was like, oh, how would that work if I wanted to promote a show in a theater? And he told
me. And so, actually, 1998, the first show I ever promoted in a theater was Penn and
Teller.
That's getting smart.
Yeah. I mean, it was a good choice. It was a dream for me. I can't... I had no business
promoting that show.
How did you... Because Glenn's not their manager then, is he? Or is he...
No, Glenn was around, but he... Glenn was 20 at the time, too.
Right, right. So were you doing Crasher?
Crasher was their manager.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But by way of William Morris. There was this agent at William Morris who this guy I met
in Pennsylvania introduced me to. Old-time William Morris agent, Marshall Resnick. And
he took my call, and I think he was confused, because when I told him that I owned Planet
Magic, the magic shop in Colony, New York, he thought I owned a nightclub called Planet
Magic. So he thought I had experience, which I did not.
So you were bluffing, or did you... You were accidentally bluffing.
No, I was just...
No, I just, you know, was the benefit of, I think, him misunderstanding what I did. I was not
bullshitting at all.
Right.
You know, so I...
Just a quick... I want to hear the rest of the story, but I'm just writing a side note that
we can still open a nightclub called Planet Magic, so...
Yeah.
Good, good. All right, good.
That's nice. Thank you.
That probably would have been... That would be a whole different path. That's one of those
sliding doors moments.
Very sliding doors moments.
A much more profitable path, but...
But you wouldn't be alive anymore.
I don't know where I'd be. But actually, this Penn & Teller show is one of those moments,
too, of like, if this hadn't gone... It went well. Long story short, like, somehow the theater
was willing to rent the space to me. The people who ran the theater, they were so sweet. It was,
you know, this beautiful old vaudeville theater.
How big was the theater?
It could be here. 2,700 seats. It was, you know, like, a legit situation. But they knew me
because I was...
Was this the first show you produced?
Yeah. It was crazy.
The first show you produced was a 2,700-seat theater for Penn & Teller.
When Marshall... When the...
Agent's assistant was on the phone with me, and she said, I'm going to need to get a rider.
I thought she meant I needed to rent a rider truck to get Penn & Teller's stuff to the theater.
She meant a contract rider, a technical rider.
She...
Irene Pisani, she's still in the business today, and she's the best. She really helped me a lot.
But then what happened is, they're like, okay, yeah, your date's good. We just need a $10,000 deposit.
It's like, a $10,000 deposit?
Well, that's... So that's where... That's why all of us don't start off with a 2,700-seat theater as our first show.
Right. Because who hasn't? I didn't have $10,000. But you know what I did have?
I had good credit on my credit card because I had been doing the magic shop for a couple years.
Yeah.
And every month, I'd buy my inventory from D. Robinson Company, the magic distributor.
So all those whoopee cushions and ball vases and cement galley decks went on my credit card, and I paid off every month.
So I took my credit card, and I swiped it at my own terminal in the store for $10,000.
$10,000.
That's incredible.
It's incredibly stupid, and I feel like if my kids did that, I would tell them they're crazy.
But thank God that show worked. That show worked. It made some money.
But this... I mean, this is the whole thing.
There is no perfectly smart way to go about any kind of business.
At some point, it takes some kind of risk, and that risk, if it backfires, yes.
Anyone would point the big, what a moment of idiocy.
I took my college money and tried to produce a television pilot, and that pilot failed.
So therefore, it is my thing to talk about.
I blew my college money.
But if my show took off, then it's that bold risk, right?
So you were taking much less of a risk than I was.
I was relying on television.
You were relying on 2,700 people in New York wanting to see Penn & Teller.
That's different.
There's just all kinds of risks.
But you're right.
In this industry specifically, there's no path.
If somebody said, I want to be a promoter, or I want to be a producer, or I want to...
Maybe if you were going to be an agent, you'd still try to do the mailroom route.
Like, that's sort of a proven...
Yes, that's still...
...development path.
Yeah, yeah.
But for anything else, it's sort of like, well,
what could you do today and tomorrow?
What's the next thing you can do to move this forward
without losing your shirt or crashing and burning?
Right.
So anyway, I only share that story because the Penn & Teller of it
is still one of the things that just brings me great joy.
And the show sold well.
The show did well.
It sold enough tickets where I made a few thousand dollars,
which, same thing, not to talk about money.
I was like, oh my god, I could do one of these and make a few thousand dollars.
How do I do 50 next year?
And of course, the next year I do two, and they both lose money.
And the next year I do four, and two of them work and two of them don't.
It's very, very tough.
Oh, it's almost like winning your first blackjack bet, right?
You're like, oh, I'm good at this.
And then you find out...
Reality strikes.
Reality hits hard at some point.
But you were able to pay off your credit card, though.
You paid that back, yeah?
Indeed.
So you start producing three shows, four shows.
Are you still finishing?
Are you still finishing on college?
Yeah, I did.
I got a degree, a business degree.
I felt like...
You sound so defeated when you say that.
No, I debated at the time.
I was so tired of it.
I wanted to just get out in the world and do stuff.
Right.
My sister convinced me to stick with it.
She's like, you're close enough.
Just get the degree.
And it was.
It's good to have an education.
I don't know that I never...
The degree actually has served me, but the education did.
Shots fired.
I'll take it.
That's fine.
I'm pretty sure that I'm better for my one year of acting education.
at Montclair State.
So I'm pretty sure that that's what set me on my way.
Is it true that you studied Shakespeare?
I have indeed studied.
But weren't you a Shakespearean actor?
I have done Shakespearean shows, yes.
Why is that?
Have you talked on this podcast about the thing you did on Thanksgiving?
Oh, no.
I think I did, actually.
Yeah, yeah.
But that's fine.
Exactly, yeah.
And that's it.
When I was younger, I did an improv show every Friday and Saturday.
And obviously, we did improv shows.
And we did genres and stuff like that.
And so my high school drama teacher, I went to a former arts high school,
was one of the renowned Shakespeare training people in the state.
And so I was improvising Shakespeare all the time.
So when he cast me as the lead in the Shakespeare show my senior year,
he would laugh and be frustrated at the same time about my ability to
improvise lines where I was lost in scenes.
I played Falstaff in The Merry Wives of Windsor,
just an epic amount of Shakespearean scenes to memorize.
And so I did a lot of improv.
And so he was laughing that I would just improvise my way through some of the smaller scenes
that I just couldn't crack.
Incredible.
Oh.
So yes, yeah.
So I was excited to improvise with Brad Sherwood.
We did Shakespearean Presented of Magic at Matt King's house, the musical.
It went so well that we pitched it at a local French festival here.
I pitched, sure, we've heard of Shakespeare's plays, but why does no one perform Shakespeare's
musicals?
And so that's the pitch for us to do it.
So good.
I can't wait to see it.
It's so fun.
But Brad Sherwood is the one who did it.
It was just still tip top with improvising Shakespeare.
I put it to bed for a very long time.
So trying to dust it back off was really tough, really tough.
I mean, he's a genius.
And the fact that that's just one of all the genres that he can instantly access and immerse
himself in and just bring to life.
When he had the idea, he called me on the phone.
He just started improvising on the phone with me.
I was like, he's being hilarious just to me on the spot at like 10 o'clock in the morning.
Also, it's also kind of weird if we're being honest.
It's like, what are we doing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Like, it's fascinating how many layers, like how much time before we're, yes, we're using
the same words, but not speaking the same language, right?
Like my kids studying like the Gettysburg Address right now.
And I'm translating the Gettysburg Address to him because like it makes absolutely no
sense to him whatsoever.
And you're like, it's like, and that's what, that's 100 years, 100 change, right?
So you're like, yeah.
Yeah.
Shakespeare, it's like you're, you're, you're just translating English to English, which
is the weirdest thing, but you are doing that.
But it's a, it's a weird thing.
Anyhow.
All right.
Back on topic.
Yeah.
The Jokers of Magic.
You know, we've, we've talked obviously a lot off air.
We've, we've toured.
So, you know, when I look back at like, you loved magic, you started producing shows.
At, at any moment, are you hoping to produce your own show or do you, did you see this
two-part?
Or how did you, how did you?
No, I stopped doing magic because the, the producing thing started to work out and I
found a career there and, and then I had a, you know, got married and had kids.
And so you just do the responsible thing.
And it was also very exciting.
I was loving producing, but for most of the last 20 years, I just did that.
And, and, you know, did the responsible thing.
I'm like, oh, I, who has time to perform?
Also, I was very self-conscious because I was like, no, who's going to take, especially
when I was younger, who's going to take me seriously as a producer?
If I'm off, like promoting myself as a magician, I just.
Or you were just trying to do magic tricks in front of them, right?
Like, I'm going to bring you into this huge theater, but like, here, do you want to see,
pick a card?
Yeah, no, it's just all felt like.
I don't know about that, Mike Mills.
Yeah, it just felt like, you know, be a professional, do your thing.
And, and, you know, and I did some, some shows here and there, but for the most part, I gave
it up.
But then what happened is you get to a certain point in your life and you're like, oh my
gosh, I, you know, being a producer is, is a lot of fun.
But it's mostly spreadsheets and meetings and email.
It's, it's, it's business for the most part.
And it's not.
I mean, like, I remember meeting you, I believe Matt King's Roast is the first time I remember
having a conversation.
And you definitely were not like, even talking about producing a magic show, you weren't
like, you know, I also love magic or, you know, I also did magic.
Like, there was not a part of you that came off as a, as a guy who liked magic, you know,
as a, as a, as a performer.
Do you know what I mean?
Like you.
That's too bad.
I've always loved it.
But it is, but it's also a tough thing to produce commercially, meaning it's really
tough.
You know, it's, it's, it's.
Well, you've said famously, I know we, you have a board with your company, your company
produces how many shows?
How many, how many shows does Mills Entertainment send out?
You know, we did a little under 300 dates last year.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
Across like what, 12, 15 shows?
Yeah.
Exactly.
Yep.
Yeah.
And you said your board would like to have how many dates of those booked as magic shows?
Oh, it would be zero.
I still haven't found, you know, I have such great respect for, say, Alex Jarrett, who
champions of magic and has made such a great business and career out of it.
And it's, the show's great.
He's figured out the formula for selling tickets.
You know, there's, there's a handful of those people that, that we know that have done it.
Um, and, you know, also the other thing is most of the theaters that my company does
business in are 1,500 seats or 2,000 seats or 2,500 seats.
It's a lot of seats to sell.
Yes.
Right, right, right.
So you need some amount of celebrity, uh, or, or, um, you know, or intellectual property.
That's.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Like, now you see me, you know.
That kind of stuff.
Great example.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, so you never, so you basically put it away.
Now, as your children get older and you're a secret magician, you're still like a closet
magician at this point.
Do you still show this?
Do you start showing them magic tricks?
Do you bust it out at the Christmas party?
Oh, yeah.
And I did have this one place I performed every summer that was like a really wonderful
creative outlet for me.
So I would do like four or six shows there every summer.
And, and so the kids always came and, uh, if they still, by the way, if they hear like
Mr. Brightside or some of the songs that I use in my pre-show, they still go, Daddy Magic
Show music.
Because those songs are etched.
So they liked what you did.
You did magic tricks for them.
They loved it.
I mean, they loved it.
It was such a, they had so much fun coming to see those shows.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
So that was very rewarding as a father.
Um, but then, yeah, basically it's, it's one of those COVID moments.
It's like, oh, you know what?
I miss it.
Let's do it.
Let's do some more performing.
So I started performing again.
And then this tour sort of came a little bit out of the Foolers tour.
Yeah.
And that we're like, oh gosh, there's no perfect formula.
But I felt like the one thing that hadn't been done, and we talked about this, like
you were the first person I talked to about this.
Right.
Was like, I don't think there's been a touring comedy magic package.
Like, I think that's novel, especially adult leaning.
Now that's not totally true because the Naked Magicians were out a few years ago and that
was, you know, comedy magic.
I never saw it and I don't know it, but I, you know, that, that sort of.
But it's still not putting comedy first.
It's putting nudity first.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess I'm putting jokes in their mouths.
I don't know how, maybe they're playing it straight.
Maybe it's, is that a sexy show?
You just put, you know, in sports metaphors, it's bulletin board material, right?
Where if the other coach talks to the press and says something derogatory about the team,
you put it up on the bulletin board so all the whole team reads it and wants to like
tear the doors off, right?
Man, sports metaphors are 100% lost on me.
I was, that's a, I really tried to explain it.
I, did you, did you just listen to the story?
I did magic as a kid.
How am I supposed to understand a sports metaphor?
Just so you know, that right now the Naked Magicians are huddling up being like, that
guy said they're laughing at our dicks.
And then they're going to, they're going to huddle up and they're going to go out there
and give the best show they've ever done.
That's what, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
So, uh, so yeah, we have, we have some things in common with the Naked Magicians, but maybe
not so much the commerce of it.
But, uh, yeah, so, so, so it actually, I think, I think it's working.
What we're doing is working.
It's just one of those things where we haven't, you know, what did we do?
Three, we did like five cities the first time.
Yeah.
Nine now.
And we're in that phase of like, it is hit or miss at the box office.
Like some of these are working and some of them are working really well and then some
are just a little soft and you're like, Oh, I wish I knew exactly why, which ones, I think
I'm starting to get a hunch, which I won't comment on here, but I think I'm starting
to see what's working.
Oh yeah.
See, this is what's exciting.
Like, I know, like, uh, I laugh because like, I love this show.
I love the idea of doing the Joker's magic.
I love a comedy forward thing.
I had this conversation with Harrison Greenbaum where I was like, you know, we have the term
like alt rock, but we don't have a term for like alt magic.
But like, you know, when I talked to him and I was like, you and I are all.
We're not traditional magic.
Like if you want like the most, like, you know, traditional magicians show up at this
party, that's not, you don't want us to show up at this party, you know, you want something
like, I love doing shows where people are like, I don't normally go see magic shows
or I was skeptical when I walked in.
I was like, yes, that's, that's exactly who I want sitting down in front of me.
Uh, uh, is like, cause like, yeah, I, we were going to win you over tremendously.
Um, sorry, I just did a show last night where someone goes, I didn't think you need to do
the tricks.
I just liked your joke.
And I was like, that's the, that's all I'm looking for.
Sometimes I thought if I were funny enough, I, if I could do, I would just wean myself
off the tricks and just go out and do the jokes.
That would be fun.
But, but I will say like, there's magic comedy is different than comedy in that we're not,
we're not providing commentary about life.
We're creating ridiculous and hilarious situations.
It's situational comedy, which, which I really enjoy and people do too.
The social experiment of it of like, oh, this is, this is a weird conceit.
It's a super playful thing that can take you to some great places with people.
Um, but yeah, I think like to go from producing other shows and they fall in love with magic,
but now we've, we've cornered you into producing your own magic show where you don't necessarily
get to, it's not the break from your routine that it normally is.
Right.
Like, you know, like when you go off on cruise ships, you get to, it's a total break from
producing tours.
This show relies on you to wear both hats, you know, producer hat and magic hat.
Is that something that you surprisingly enjoy or are you, is it, is it as, as annoying as
anticipated?
How would you describe wearing both hats?
Um, I love, I love, well, you know, there's some ambivalence there.
There's like some, you know, there's some things I love, but it is tough to do it all.
So just to be clear, like the only, you know, I have to do all the steps of the process
as the producer of the show, because.
This piece of business, the Jokers of Magic is a relatively small piece of business.
So the company, the team has said to me, Mike, we support you, but we can't really put a
lot of time into this.
So it becomes a magic project and that's okay.
Like that's, that's okay.
But what's great about it is I do love talking to, like, I don't handle the booking of our
tours anymore.
Uh, you know, I, I did that in the beginning of the company, but I don't do it anymore.
But for this show I do.
So I get to talk to the theater operators and it's really nice because, uh, I haven't
done as much of that.
Oh, so it's like a, it's like an old school that you're dusting off.
Yeah.
I literally like, yeah, it's like, Hey, I got a pitch for you.
I want to hear a pitch, you know, like, Hey, we should do this show together.
Let's make the deal, which is super.
I love, I love.
Yeah.
And then, you know, but I will say the hardest part, and this is the thing that we talk about,
you and I talk about a lot, which is like the marketing is tough.
How do you, how do you get people to pay attention?
We know that they'll have a great time if they come out, but there's so much noise in
the market and there's so much competition for our marketing for live entertainment.
It's harder than ever.
Right.
And across the board, like not just for magic, right?
Like marketing.
Yeah.
Um, I would say it's harder than ever, partially because it's changed so much in the rate of
change is so rapid that, um, you know, none of the traditional media really works.
There's no ROI there, you know?
And, and then, um, you know, we do, we spend most of our money on paid digital.
We can get in front of people, but it's just hard.
People are busy.
They have limited dollars to spend.
They have the best entertainment options at home, historically speaking.
Right.
Like why the hell even leave the house?
Yeah.
Get a babysitter.
You got to drive downtown, you got to pay for parking and then, you know, you got to
buy the ticket.
So it's, it's a big ask, but, um, that was always my comparison.
People talk about like living in Las Vegas versus New York.
I moved here, I moved here from New York and I was like, you know, uh, I just remember
doing some interview for something and they're like, is it, is it, it's gotta be easy to
do a show here in Vegas and New York.
I go like, no way.
And they're like, what do you mean?
I go, New York, no one's home.
No one goes home.
So like everyone's out and about.
So you're, all you're trying to say is like, Hey, if you're already out and about, come
by.
Come by here at this time, you know, this night, go for it.
You know, I was like here in Vegas is like, you're, you're home.
You're sitting in your couch.
You can, you can make dinner.
Now you want to get up and get out of your house and then go to this show downtown.
Like, Oh, that's such a harder ask than, than asking New Yorkers to do stuff.
New Yorkers is a lot of noise, but everyone's doing stuff there.
You don't, you don't live in New York cause you want to like sit at home, you know?
So it's like, it's easy.
It's a culture thing.
Yeah.
But it's, it's, I mean, but when people talk about doing shows in Vegas,
they're mostly talking about selling tickets to the, the visitors, the tourists.
Right.
So, and then which they also assume is sort of easier, but it's so much harder than it
looks.
Oh, it's so much harder than it looks.
And now especially, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, cause we've, we've, we've, we've, we've turned basically Las Vegas into one hotel.
Right.
Cause the, the sphere and the Raider stadium have turned.
So everyone coming to town for blank, can they, do they also want to do this other thing?
And now everyone's competing for this other thing.
No.
No one's competing for the primary thing.
It's a, it's a really weird thing.
Is this late stage capitalism?
Is that what they call this?
We're seeing, as we sit here and complain about how tough these markets are and how
saturated and how dominated they are by, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, Vegas has always changed, changing significantly.
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's a phase thing for sure.
For sure.
But you know, we'll see.
We'll see.
Let's see.
We're going to Lexington, Kentucky.
Yes.
Bloomington, Indiana.
Uh, Wabash.
Cincinnati, Ohio.
Ohio.
We're doing a few shows in Cincinnati.
Yeah.
A couple, two shows, uh, uh, in Cincinnati, um, Milwaukee, Madison, Green Bay.
All right.
And Chicago.
Yeah.
We're playing a comedy club.
I'm very curious how our show will feel in the Chicago comedy club.
I'm very excited that we're doing a comedy club.
I just.
It's going to be a little bit of a different show.
Yeah.
In a, in a way that I think I'm going to love, but I'm curious if the others are going
to love it as well.
And the others being the audience.
Um, no, it's going to be great.
It's just like you have to, we can't pretend it's a theater and pretend that, that, that
the kinds of things we, you know, just, uh, it'll be a little bit different and we'll
just do a club show in a club and it's, um, yeah, I'm really excited about that too.
We'll see what we'll see.
But, but for instance, no intermission, right.
In the theater show, we usually take it.
Intermission.
We don't need intermission.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
That's what I'm curious about.
All that.
Because we're doing it without intermission, still doing the bits without like a lot of
tech, uh, feeling how much magic is an add on in a comedy club environment, uh, versus
a comedy being an add on in a theatrical environment.
Uh, yeah.
I'm curious about all of it, but you already, you know, this, you seem skeptical about this
show.
Um, no, I actually really thought about it that much other than knowing we should do
something a little different and figuring.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, it's halfway through this little run.
So we'll have a number of days in, in, you know, our van to talk about the approach.
Um, so if anyone wants to join us for that one, Tuesday, January 27th, that'll be a fun
experimental situation.
Yeah.
But it's gonna be great.
I mean, you're very comfortable in a club.
Uh, Eric Dittleman is, he does clubs all the time, you know?
I was going to say, and it's a Tuesday, so I'm also comfortable with smaller audiences.
So then you'll be very comfortable.
I mean, I don't know.
It's one of those, it's like, it sells late.
Like that's one that, that, you know, we don't know if we're going to have, you know, if
it's going to be, the whole capacity is only 150.
So it's going to, it'll be fine.
It'll be great.
Yeah.
It'll be fine.
Oh, which, which, which venue are you looking forward to the most?
Uh, those like Cincinnati is selling great.
We have two shows and they'll both be packed.
You know, that, that's great.
And I love to show days.
I love settling in.
And getting to sort of two at-bats in the same venue.
Yes.
Yeah.
Um, um, but all of them really, it's a, it's a really great set of venues.
So if you look, you know, I hope if you're listening and you live in any of these towns,
uh, I think you'll be really thrilled with the show.
And these are all the, you know, the, the best local venues.
Yeah.
And if you don't live in those towns, but you know, someone who does tell those people
to go to our show.
Yeah.
And they're all listed at jokersonmagic.com with direct links to the official sites.
Um, well, I'm so excited.
One is, you know, of all the things we've talked about, it's like, I actually love the
show that we've put together.
Like, I like that it's not just a lineup show and that we've put together like a really
cool way for all of us to interact and share the stage and stuff.
And, uh, I'm really looking forward to, to the longer run, meaning we can find more bits
and other things to add to the show.
Yeah.
I think we will have some, I feel like now this is the second round.
We should try something new every night.
Yeah.
It could be small, it can be big, it could be, you know, whatever.
Just, we should, uh, we should not.
We should not settle in too quickly here.
This will be a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Well, Mike, thanks for taking time to do, uh, to do this.
I know you're a very busy guy, so I appreciate it.
My pleasure.
This is, I'm so excited.
Thank you.
I have to say, none of this would be happening without you.
Like from day one, you were so supportive of this idea and.
I'm so supportive of me having a job.
Was that, oh, wow.
Yeah.
But in a way, I think everybody who gets these gigs is grateful, right?
You, you, you, you, how many times have you called and said, uh,
Hey, there's this, there's this place that invited me to perform and it might fit in between here and here.
And we should, we should talk to them and, and, you know, so many of those.
So, so thank you.
Well, you know, we, we, we all like doing the shows.
That's, that's the, so we can add more to it, but I appreciate it.
I'm looking forward to it.
And, uh, uh, we'll, I'll see you in Lexington.
See you there.
All right.
Thank you.
Thanks for listening to today's podcast.
Time to thank a few more people.
Support me over on Patreon.
Uh, that'd be David Smith, Zelda.
Ray Skywalker, Kirby Beeler, M hers, David, Lucy, Steve, the Ruta, Ross crater, Bob Baker, Stacey Donahue, Ryan coach, rat bastard, Kevin Suarez, all Michael Mills, galactic president, scooper star, McScoops, a lot.
Michael Moore, no relation, Sebastian Robbins, Chad Rabinowitz.
My tummy hurts, but I'm really, really brave about it, but I'm being really brave about it.
Yeah.
Benny Kirschner.
Peter S Izzo, scoop Brady, BB Hermit, Ed Wagner, Colton Satmary, what to sex guy, Jimmy D, Sasha Haberling, Jason Klepper, Casey, Stephen Marston, Jobeth R Bowers, Michelle Yizer, Bob Bakker.
Nope.
That's Bob Baker.
James Dawson, Ron Bowes, tour Raven gel, Frisbee, Juan Galavis, Ian Soto, Phil Spector, freak the clown, Richard, Matthew.
Hunt, Chris Angel has, uh, I'm married.
All right.
Trent Lloyd, Adam Mancini, Fiona skilling, Brian Christ, Jonathan Stigman, and Ken DePonte.
Thank you all so much.
Thank you.