Oh hello there I am so glad you are here this is the part of the show where we
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers it's a new month I don't have a new list yet but we will thank each and
every ice cream truck driver at this part of the show before this month is
over if you want to be in a say big now during Menard's super savings sale
brighten your home with a three-panel LED light bulb now just $1.99 stay warm
with a hardwood firewood bundle only $3.99 stock up with Clorox all-purpose
cleaner just $2.99 a 16 pack of zest bar soap is only $7.99 hurry these great
deals won't last long sign up for Menard's emails to get the weekly flyer
plus exclusive daily flash sales right here in box
ice cream truck driver and I sure hope you do preachingfun.com is where you can
go to hang out sign up to be an ice cream truck driver right there and who
knows the life you save may be your own and now a show hey Johnny do you want to
go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go Jacob I want to know
that the jokers of magic we're making fun of this microphone on my face for
the life part because you look like Britney Spears yeah I didn't stop the
microphone man you just look like Britney Spears
it's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social sitting over there in Las Vegas it's Matt Donnelly sitting over at
Pittsburgh BA it's Paul Mattingly also in Vegas it's me Jacob the audio guy
I love the microphone on your face Matt I think it's dapper backstreets back
alright yeah it is it's kind of cool I mean it did it improved our the audio
quality of our show dramatically when I was traveling so yes there you go I'll
take I'll take the jokes can't fight that oh yeah yeah no I I want to be very
clear I'm very willing to in exchange for improving the quality of this show I
am willing for you to be made fun of by your peers I said fine with that trade
off I packed it with my regular microphone road runs road rig microphones
you know handheld microphones for right Africa Babel and I said I packed this
one because that way I thought if I could drive and do that we could do the
podcast while actually driving and like Mike Mills our producer/host said what a
terrible idea well once we ended up driving through not one but two
blizzards well that would have been distracting so trying to podcast would
have been really really difficult we honestly I'm sad that we don't have just
recordings of you guys trying to podcast through a blizzard yeah we we hit a
second blizzard and we were all upset because the first blizzard was very much
talked about in the news as is coming towards us and then we hit a second
blizzard in India and I was like what no we had no idea we had no idea we're
gonna hit a blizzard and then we we hit this gas station at like like midnight
trying to fuel up and get some food and we're just surrounded by snow coming
down it was I guess the tip of the lake they kept saying so like the flakes are
really big chunky flakes tip of the lake I was like I'm not not to borrow from my
clown name but chunky flakes a lot of chunky flakes coming down and then the
clown the guy in the gas he was like oh my god no we're getting at least ten
inches and I just heard from Valparaiso they're getting you know 15 inches and
the other reports I mean everywhere I go it's like he was like don't go anywhere
and one oh we were at a gas station in the middle of some town that they have
hotels so terrible advice we were a gas station intended to give anyone we were
going somewhere yes and then we were like kind of starting to panic about
like what do we do and looking at the nearest hotels and then I remembered hey
guys the all the information we just got was from a cashier at midnight in a gas
station so like all of the reports are coming from you know one point even the
cashier he's working with she was like can you chill out and he's like I'm just
telling them
great and then she was like that guy's a soft guy over there you can ask him and
I was like well this is the kind of town we're in where we're actually at the
coffee shop you know the coffee stop where the guy who's salt in the roads is
there yeah I said oh you know the salt guys because he's my dad and I was like
we are in a tiny tiny town oh boy but you made it out we made it out we lost
an hour driving from Milwaukee to Wabash Indiana and then we got in end up
getting in with the snow at like five o'clock in the morning with a 9 a.m.
lobby call so it's pretty great it's pretty great so we had two shows Wabash
and then they put the man a two o'clock instead of four but we did two shows in
Wabash we were a little delirious but they were super fun great crowds came
out and including the else Roth's yeah and Michael else Roth always being a
gentleman brought me a dr. pepper cream zero for me to delicious he knows is my
favorite he goes brings him to scoop fest he knows he knows his stuff but I
got to sneak out and have a little bite to eat with with the else Roth the hard
part is always finding a hooker that's named dr. pepper cream zero I think he
just tells how Matt happens to be in I think he just pays extra for whoever to
just say it I don't think he can to do the legal name change does anyone who's
in the commitment it's Michael else wrong that is true that is true so are
you still in snowed in areas now or you're back no I'm back go back in Vegas
yeah yeah yeah but you've been driving through crazy snowpack everywhere well
yeah and the good the good news for me I seem like I was making the big
sacrifice everyone else was flying out of Fort Wayne I drove the Sprinter van
back to Cincinnati to drop off where we rented it from and flew out of
Cincinnati and everyone's flights were messed up and delayed out of Fort Wayne
and everything everything in Cincinnati is going off without a hitch so I was
like if you look yeah would you drive three hours just to make sure your
flights were totally normal you would say yes fine yeah yeah yeah there's some
driving who decides to introduce letters to exit numbers you know this has been
at the top of my list to talk about four years I'm glad we're finally getting to
as a secondary component of the exit right so you go 42 B right so you go by
exit 41 then 42 a 42 B 42 C and you're there come driving out here in fucking
Pittsburgh you will it is everything is just blabbered a blabbered a blaze oh
Pittsburgh is no I mean like it has so confused riding with the uber drivers in
Pittsburgh it's the worst I just had I had to stop paying attention but it has
to be a meeting right and that means some of the meeting goes whoa whoa whoa
those exits are too close together to have their own numbers well I guess
that's it I guess that's it numbers are mile markers yeah essentially mm-hmm I
mean on the right on the interstates growing up you'd have the mile markers
and then you would have an exit and the exit would serve as a mile they're
supposed to correspond pretty closely yes right all right I guess the letters are
just between the mile markers but yeah it seems like they've they've raged out
of control Jacob Jacob just said something that makes a lot of sense and
I feel dumb for bringing it up but no I think that's how it's supposed to be I
don't think that's how it is out here well it's definitely because they're
just too close exits like we have like on the freeway here we have you know the
flamingo eggs and the tropical eggs that are not a mile apart from each other
right the designs of all of it are just so it's just so bad I drove I had to
drive in for class last night and just two or three times I was like god damn
it where did you learn the driving in Pittsburgh just isn't designed at all no
it's not and it's it's it's terrible roads stacked on each other over the
years and I just you know we keep discovering everything in our society is
built as a massive Psyop to confuse and upset us and control our brains and I
feel like the driving shit is a big component of that too like they make
these things now we're talking Jacob's making sense Paul saying it's because of
a Psyop we're back in business I'm telling you it's all just like I mean of
course the interstates were built for interstate trucking primarily but now we
always have to use them to just get to our third and fourth jobs I don't know
it just seems fucking insane to me how much we have with the interstates
initially built primarily for trucking yes yes oh I didn't know that yeah
Eisenhower was the president who did a lot of interstate stuff right yeah yeah
yeah I like when you could point at a president and just casually list the
thing that they did here's just something that happened under this
administration that was just I don't know I guess a net positive I guess I
don't know sure at the very least it's something that got accomplished also the
crazy fucking thing with my commute now I've got into where I'm really leaving
very early because I know how insane the commute can be but it's
approximately I think as the crow flies as you'd say about 12 miles from my
house good shape and I couldn't fly 12 miles if you paid and it takes me no
less than 45 minutes yeah ever that's the that's the quickest ever that's just
the amount of time that that trip takes because you got and I and I'm so I got
so spoiled in Vegas too because it's all on a grid out here it's yeah be a horsey
trail this guy owns a part of this this is where you cannot be this is a
demilitarized zone it's just fucking bananas the loopy doop floop driving shit
on the horse 150 years ago does that how you were gonna get to work today yeah
oh well there's the easiest way for the nag to get through without breaking its
leg my wife I keep asking you not to call her that that'll work that'll work
for a Porsche in about a hundred years that's perfect no problem yeah I'll be
perfect for a German engineered piece of machinery horse rhymes with horse I'm
sure it'll be fine anyway uh yeah so I've been busy with improv this week I
had a free class on Saturday that I co-taught with my friend Sarah we had a
couple of ladies come out we're gonna be working with them on a project too which
is cool they got to see it big shout out to Malia for coming out to the class too
and it was awesome to have her there and a couple other scoops Alex and Anna
showed up which is awesome just great to see scoops coming through at my little
events I don't know the algorithm is not promoting the stuff I'm promoting I
thank every scoop for retweeting and putting out as much info on that class
we could we still had nine people I promoted the shit I mean I got promoted
I didn't pay for anything you're having a crazy winter aren't you that's part of
it too yeah yes yeah ultimately it was we had nine people show up in two degree
weather so that's pretty good right possible that everybody knew about it
it's also possible that the algorithm just did its job and everybody in
Pittsburgh knew about that class and just nine people were in it's possible
it's quite possible it's cold as fuck it's cold as fuck out here and just
insane and every time and like and then I was going to teach my new level one
which had to get postponed I was teaching they're doing that yesterday so
last night again I'm heading out early my class starts at 630 I'm in the car
around 5 I open up the garage door and it's fucking snowing again it just
doesn't stop but we've got a solid you know almost ten to twelve-inch he's got
a solid twelve inches it's just not moving it's not going anywhere it's just
there I've already had to dig out my mailbox I had to dig out a place for my
fucking take out your mailbox I had to dig out the mailbox because the mail
people were like please dig a path so we can get to your mailbox so I had to dig
dig a big old path to get him yeah that big high of seven on Saturday scooping
over girl yeah it's cold as fuck out here and then I dug a place to put my
trash can so that it wouldn't be out on the street exactly you know and the
plowing is is crazy so it's where I'm digging out is like 14 inches no I mean
my buddy my oldest friends Pat said picture him and his kids standing on the
Navis Inc River in Red Bank New Jersey oh that river never froze over the
entire time that I lived in like my entire lifetime I've never heard of that
river being frozen it was it was nuts this is when Matt goes into his no such
thing as global warming because the river froze spiel now that's right
exactly it the people just don't understand like it's guys it goes both
ways it's real cold we've been asked to have an emergency Vegas parking and
weather from Ryan is it me or is there a recent increase in people who insist on
backing into parking spaces why is this what does it mean for our society as a
whole I need an emergency Vegas parking and weather this is a great point I have
noticed this too and I asked but I just like Jacob had a very logical answer for
my exit thing there is a logical answer as to why there's an increase in this
happening great because I've noticed this too I want to know the same thing
quality of reverse cameras you're right yeah all these cars put much better ways
where they show you the lane that you're turning in and everybody would rather
park pulling out of their spot that way then backing up it's annoying ready rich
has the best take on this is that you shouldn't be mad that people do it you
should be mad that people are bad at it that's right because that's it it's like
what happens is that it takes so much longer if you're waiting to park and
you're behind someone and they have to do this giant production to get the car
back into just pulling in a goddamn space I I'd like to I'm a backer inner
I've been a backer inner for for decades unapologetically especially with the with
the truck you know if I'm driving a pickup truck it's just so much easier to
back in and then pull out nose first I am but yeah when people are bad at it
it's terrible and if there are a line of cars behind me in the parking lot then I
do the gentlemanly thing and I go nose in just just to do it a little faster so
I don't have to pull forward and then back in yeah I'm a consummate pull
through guy so I go all the way to the other side that's backing in but I'm
going through and then then I'm ready to go that's only dangerous for like two
split seconds yeah what do you mean dangerous if someone else is someone
else wants to pull into the regular spot that you're pulling forward you don't
understand how I do my pull throughs I park in BFE there is not another car
around me my friend this is the thing that drives seriously and goes fucking
crazy over my parking she's like you always zig when I think you're gonna
sag manically I go I go so far away she's like the other night it was it was
balls cold again the wind was blowing we had to go to Lowe's this was right
before the fucking crazy storm hit and we went to go find a terracotta pot just
in case we needed an emergency heater type thing we could pack because we had
plenty of candles and we just needed a terracotta pot to use as an emergency
heater if we absolutely lost power and everything went to shit hey man it works
it fucking works so we went to go pot it was freezing cold backstage at Madison
Wisconsin and and Mike noticed that the dressing rooms had old light bulbs not
LEDs but old style light bulbs there's a yeah close the doors leave the lights on
and we went and did a sound check and we came back took the toastiest dressing
rooms we basically easy we easy baked ovened our dressing rooms and they are
they are hot yeah this is how you fucking do it and yeah so these are the
hacks but yeah I parked over by the garden section and pretty close to the
front but there was nobody else there and we had to walk all the way and she's
like what the fuck you doing Mattingly you're killing me this is crazy she's
like just shivering and shaking the whole way and I'm cold too it's cold as fuck but
then we got the thing and we're heading out the door and I'm like can we go back
over to the door we came in on she's like no we have to go out this exit which
is even farther away from where you fucking parked and I'm I didn't know I
thought we could go out the front again she's like no we can't why did you do
this this is insane that's really she she does not like my parking but I don't
sound like this she does but my parking could not be could not be safer in so
much as there's no one there no I don't like people combat park when it when the
spaces are diagonal you don't back into spots when they're dying what that's
right even no you don't you do not back into that's that's how they're designed
and so you don't have to back yet yeah that's of the douches and still do it
buddies literally doing that right now listen to me douches stop it here you
hear you douches that's like almost doing a donut to get into that shit that's
making a you what a load of people do that in the Caesars parking garage all
the time sure has the angled parking spots but they will get into the the
wrong lane you know they'll be they'll be going up the down lane and now they
have to back into the spot just because they they can't get into it that's a
double douche it's not to two negative don't make a positive that's a double
douche that stays double douche it's two squared it doesn't make a positive I
don't know when I see them doing it I give them the stink eye they know what
they did they know what they did we've got snow lined up on the streets
everywhere still and the small as the roads already are it makes some lanes
like even more super tight so it's a little dodgeball out there we should
note that it's a it's a patreon bonus month so thank you for everybody thanks
everyone we're preaching fun calm we broke our bonus level and for that we
are going we owe you a bonus episode now we were gonna give you a bonus episode
anyway because it's the Super Bowl and we always do our Super Bowl prep for
people who don't love football where we have Mitzi our odds bigger come on and
we give it starts with our outlandish bets we break down ways for you to
survive your Super Bowl party when you're when you're when so you have a
couple things to talk about some people don't love sports stuff no matter what
and so I'm offering I'd on my other podcast abracadabra I did three behind
the scenes on the roads podcast with when we were touring backstage with them
and they're all funnier than the average nerdy or magic podcast and we don't talk
magic secrets or anything on that those ones so I'm offering that to go into the
feed as well for as a thing fantastic look at that more bonuses for signing up
as a patreon you can't go wrong you do get a lot of good bonuses we had a real
fun game night hangout just recently and sticker images and artwork and candid
photos went out for everybody you got to see my om cheeseburger in action glued
to the plate a patreon you did not get pictures of my om cheeseburger no I did
not get a picture of Jacob's om cheeseburger a picture of Jacob a picture
of Jacob with the construction of the giant guitar a lot of cool behind the
scenes picture the new hard rock guitar I was walking under that the other day
and snap the pic of it to to send out to the scoops yeah yeah they're the the
cross pieces on it they're starting to test the the lights oh cool Wow so it's
still I think like a year out from being open but they're starting to test like
individual those these giant LED lights that cross the entire tower they're
started to test those out and yeah it's pretty fucking cool it's it seems like
it's curving back up so like the shape of the guitar is kind of completing if
you want to see something that kind of looks like it if you're curious about it
though there's one in Miami that is similar to the one the one that they're
building here but the one they're building here is just right on the Las
Vegas strip and I mean right on it like yeah all the other casinos are set back
from the road this tower is like next to the sidewalk that's crazy that that's
wild and it's gonna yeah it's gonna stick out like a sore thumb but that's
it's the landscape of it dramatic yeah the strip is definitely gonna be but
that's what you got to do and then we've also got photos from Matt on the road so
if you are an abracadabra listener you get to put some of those pictures into
your mind as to locales and places he's been but these are pictures that we
don't share on our normal socials so it's exclusive to you guys to get a
little glimpse into what our day-to-days are being like yeah yeah I'll tell you
who else will give you a little glimpse into what their day-to-days are like if
you just hang out with them a little bit though they'll let you know what's
going on and that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you
by Spock rings not intended for your penis that's Spock rings from ML
Kennedy in 2024 sex the final skin tear these are the
adventures of Spock rings guaranteed not to puncture wieners or rip labia in fact
they're not even designed for sex at least not in the way you experience it
human come close and feel my hand upon your face your mind to my mind my
thoughts to your thoughts now we are linked and can have brain wiener games
thanks to Spock ring yes I'm wearing one right now you'll see how flashy it is
right here on my ring finger it is nice here let me see I'm gonna put that on
my penis no notoriously razor-sharp on penises but strangely enough I know I
know it's weird oh no well hey scoops of checkout
congratulations Starfleet SJ had some weird travel this week oh yeah she's
been it she's been in Canada for the last I don't know week and a half or so
doing shows with the the Spice wannabe show back up and cooking huh a lot of
road gigs SJ just stay there you're better off well that's just hang out
that's just it that's just it Matt on Monday she had a gig back here in Las
Vegas oh and so she flew down did her gig here was in town for about 15 hours
yeah and then 430 this morning back at back to the airport back to Canada to do
a show tonight holy shit and she's back in Canada until I think Saturday how's
she doing this it's insane oh air travel Paul those things those things that pass
over you would the sky no boy I'm talking about the physical toll my god
that's got she's hurting she is hurting uh yeah we did that show together with
Saris Arash she was talking about this travel uh schedule and I said you know
these are the kind of things like in our 20s like we've been loved we did it in
our 20s I got to do this gig here and they got a fly yeah you can fly right
back here and finish out this gig yeah and when you're older you're like now
that SJ is in her late 20s she hates it it is different in your late 20s it's
true yeah it's very different in your late 20s it's because Saris Ross I guess
I don't know do you trigger warn for the only curse would we really have in the
English language the only one that's left yeah she has go for it she's a song
cunt trigger warning she called serving cunt and if you look closely you can see
me dancing as an Elvis impersonator on Fremont Street with her there it is it's
very fun is directed by my wife my very talented wife who may or may not be in
the room with me right now and she did she did an amazing job that was super
fun and gave me my backup plan for if anything goes south as I got stopped
multiple times for pictures just walk to my car dressed like Elvis on Fremont
Street I now know what's gonna happen you know when when my me too scandal hits
so right we'll be right there you got a solid thirty dollars a day coming to you
there remember remember when people listen to the will of people wasn't that
fun back in the day I don't know anymore I don't even know if ever the will the
people ever listen to I don't know what the fuck's going on at the time it
didn't seem like it was but now it seems like it really was oh god damn shit is
fucking crazy right now it's crazy oh somebody wrote us the other day on pod
therapy actually as this comes out of that show might not even be released yet
so I might be crossing timelines here but they were saying because you know we
commented on pod therapy when the most recent presidential election happened and
just said you know basically let's all let's all stay calm and react to things
as they happen and you know a lot of things have happened since then and
continued to and so they wrote in and they said you know hey you guys you know
you said react things as they're happening and now a lot of things are
happening and now what and we were like yeah you whatever you want ever you
think about that that's that's what we think too we agree that's yep I am that's
that's just it I have a lot of friends in Minneapolis from the improv community
back in the day many apps sure I'm so grateful that we got to go out there
that you brought me along for that festival just recently because I got to
get a taste of that place and the people who were working a huge at the time got
to take me on a quick little tour we went around they showed me the George
Floyd Floyd Memorial and everything so I was in that whole zone right like it was
chill no Minneapolis is a great city and there's a lot of pride in it and so like
what I'm seeing in my timeline is like I am actually like really proud of my
Minneapolis friends I feel like I feel like I feel like oh yeah I feel like
they chose the wrong city to mess with in a lot of ways yeah it really seems
like that I proud is a good word it's they're doing a really good job I feel
bad this is just arbitrarily heaped on them because someone was mad they didn't
win the state in an election oh no I'm not mad about that at all I have I am
thoroughly not bothered by the arbitrariness to heaping on Minneapolis
the shit that just that seems fine blows my mind the stuff that just making me so
I don't know not hopeless but I'm very curious as to where we go from here in a
lot of ways because it seems to me that no one is exempt from this shit no
matter what side of the aisle it's getting you know where we're going from
this we're going we're going to full-on anarchy colonies Mad Max style I think
you might be right Jacob because here we go it's just gonna be city-states it's
gonna be old-school city-states there's no one each other Athens and Sparta
there is no no for me there is no one at the federal level I would trust in any
respect so how do you take directions like there's no one to give us a voice
there's no one to unify and say hey maybe this is our next move or maybe we
should try and improve this next you know there's no there's no steps that
are being lined out there's no actionable plan to be taken as I simply
do not trust anyone and I mean nominate you Paul Paul you should take us to take
us to the promised land no no ah all right no Jacob will you I'm just gonna
go around the horn here no I don't I don't know that I don't I'll go to the
rest of the zoom technical school port will you take us to the promise it's not
supposed to be any one person it's not supposed to be any one person that's why
we have a group of government oh you know you're right Paul you're right Matt
I think we're doing wrong zoom chat zoom chat this group of people will you take
us to the promised you know one person it's a group of people I would love to
have scoop community lead us into whatever's next for a fee for a fee
there's a patreon level for that chaotic clumsy who the fuck knows what's going
on anyway I'm just SJ just texted me she is at the hotel in Canada oh good she
made it back they didn't she made it back her passport well we were a little
leaving Canada because she's there on like a work visa thing you know it's all
legit and everything and she was like leaving and then coming back in less
than a day later during the during my work visa that was the only thing that
she was a little itchy about going back yet of course but I like it all she has
the paperwork for everything and it was all just legit Paul it is nice that is
the nice thing about doing this in your late 20s versus your early 20s is you're
you're prepared and you're just doing it all legit this time we did it in our
early 20s we were just doing like tourist visas be like what we're not
working while we're here I still remember bring a suitcase of mr.
Piffles customs of being like it's just for friends gonna show it off to some
pals right if we had our merch confiscated multiple times by Canadian
officials sell t-shirts and mr. Piffles dolls what what do you do they hold it
for you to come back is that how that yeah yeah pick it back up on your way
out yeah that's not so bad if they sell it at the duty-free shops I was gonna
say I doubt they just doubt they just hold on to it for you now anymore yeah I
don't think anybody's doing us any favors at the borders these days I think
our goodwill ship has sailed back through and everybody's wearing the dog
who knows shirt yeah Paul just say I was I did Penn Sunday school yesterday and
again yes this will probably come out before that so we're jumping on podcasts
in multiple directions here okay but Penn always brings up it's a quote
attributed Gandhi but people are suspicious whether it is but that it is
first they ignore you then they laugh at you then they fight you and then you win
and the the quote is about fight you stage yes yeah I mean there is reason to
be hopeful Donald talks about all time protests always work protests always
work yeah and I know I brought up on presented school the counter example you
know that I don't like is there was anti-abortion protests my whole life and
I thought there's no way they're gonna take away freedom of choice from from
women that's that's a right it's it's it's really bigoted towards one gender
that's the way laws supposed to work but it did it worked so January's you're
absolutely right j6 definitely kind of worked it worked so you know we were at
that we were at the fight and jail phase of of the protest movement so yeah I'm
just my hope is that we can survive the fighting the fighting stage yeah I agree
with you I think the I think the the the old way is is dying and this and these
are the death throes yes there is some of that too I just hope we can we can
survive it I hope we're good at the end of it and a lot of people who are staying
on the sidelines are no longer staying on this like it is it is it is galvanizing
what is happening that is true yeah well I've certainly I've certainly seen you
know plenty within the podosphere coming forth and letting our voices be heard
and I don't want us to be out of that conversation anyway I want everybody to
know which side we're on at least what side I'm on for sure and I want
everybody to know they're not alone out there we see it we feel it we hear it
it's fucking horrible and I like guess like Matt said we're coming together
we're getting out there we're getting our voices heard and we're gonna get
through it somehow I think so we don't have any choice we don't have any choice
but to get through it I mean I don't think we'll ever do things that are
better for the environment there's certain things I've think the ship is
sailed on but I think for protecting our own freedom and stuff I think we're
gonna we're gonna get better at it hopefully hopefully yeah the river will
freeze over a few more times and somebody will go hey wait a minute well
I mean it's all fucking connected right like I truly believe we're gonna have to
dismantle these goddamn data centers and holding cells we're gonna have to
dismantle all that we're gonna actually physically have to get in there and
break apart some structures I'm following there's a new giant data
center being built in rural Louisiana not too terribly far away from my mom's
house mm-hmm and so I've been following this and it's it's a you know huge it's
I I don't even know how many multiple acres yeah yeah acres and acres of
warehouse being built and it's the new meta like AI Center and it's being built
in a town of like I don't know a few thousand people and everybody there is
just like scared and yeah weirdly in the dark about everything that's happening
cuz it's gonna it's gonna take all their water supply it's gonna fuck that's it
it's water electricity is gonna be a thing and yeah the fact that they can
just arbitrarily decide well now electricity cost five times what it used
to because we need more of it for this I guess so Will Smith can eat spaghetti in
a more convincing way what the fuck man you know what I was off of it and
so you said that now I'm kind of back out you're back on you like being more
convincing will buy spaghetti if I watch unbelievable spaghetti eating it ruins
my day noodles yeah oh we got to do something to get through this uncanny
valley I'll tell you what else we're gonna do to get through it and that's
listen to the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by Bob Evans
flavored toothpaste that's from Florida man scoop in 2024 Bob Evans flavored
toothpaste well how do y'all and welcome on in to my barn shaped restaurant Bob
Evans you know me for my delicious biscuits and gravy my fresh country
raised eggs and my oh so succulent bacon well now the flavor of Bob Evans is
delivered right to your mouth on a toothpaste holding device hopefully a
brush but here's the thing we've decided to forego our classic country cuisine
and you're getting the direct flavor of Bob Evans that's right me this
toothpaste tastes like me my scientists have worked day and night to make this
toothpaste tastes like me like you're eating a piece of me Bob Evans the real
man behind the restaurant it doesn't taste like your delicious breakfast
items it tastes like my direct delicious breakfast breakfast items if you like
huevos el Bob Evans what's what's huevos no Bob Evans tastes like well open that
mouth let me dip them in you can be the judge when you actually slide see how
close we came speaking of close we came didn't say dip them in anything for my
teeth so let's do it oh here's the thing about Bob Evans paste it's good for any
cavity if you know what I'm saying our scientists didn't stop with just flavor
they've also worked on lubrication it's the slickest fucking press you've ever
had in your life that's like it agrees now shit yeah that's low and chat soylent
gravy soylent gravy is Bob Evans that's right
it'll drip right off you like come on a gold tooth sling I don't think that's a
metaphor I think you just put like essentially what's gonna happen yeah hey
I'm just a plain old barn right barn restaurant tour difference what's the
tenth that is doing he's right here doing the dip I want to do a Matt was
right segment beast games continues to be the craziest fucking bat shit thing on
television anywhere I'm on episode up to episode 3 with my kids are watching that
oh my god I see that survivor also can't watch it it scares me to see it okay so
last year this is a spoiler never mind I'll wait it's crazy though like last
year we talked we talked about beast games because Matt started what Matt
started watching beast games with his kids that's right came out yeah because
Matt Matt's kids like every other child on the planet watches mr. beast on
YouTube uh-huh and so watch that I watched it because I love really bizarre
reality TV game shows like the the competition reality TV thing is like a
weird spot that I like to dig into in these things games is truly like the
weirdest one it is this year is much more competition based and less
psychological torture based so far yes that I've been watching so that part I
like it is still so funny where he sets up things to have like this twist and
when people don't become absolute assholes it's so clear he's so
disappointed like he's so upset people I am on episode 4 yeah I'm one episode
ahead of you yeah and I'm gonna tell you that he has noticed that too and
changes some of his tactics going forward to get them to do it so the
niceness might not continue as it is in the earlier episodes it doesn't go it
does not go to psychological torture though I mean it definitely doesn't do
that laugh about it the first season there was so much crying yes and so much
like it was just awful yeah I can't I can't do it it makes me upset to see in
the clips like I said I'll just get something else come up in a scroll I'm
like oh this looks awful yeah I know it's tough but it is it is really like
super we I watched this one this other reality show competition game out of
Korea because they make some fucking weird ones over there and this is the
idea of it and the execution of it both are so much bigger and stranger because
of it because they're doing these things on such a large scale I mean when they
when they filmed it in Vegas they were in Allegiant Stadium they go out to
these places out just in the open areas and build these giant scale things and
it is weird the amount of effort that goes into something that is so stupid
yeah yeah yeah I say that as a podcaster but we have it on the effort and we're
we're right we're in check we're in check we got it we got it I don't know I
keep watching it and I'm like every time I go every time it says TV PG at the
beginning of it I notice that and I think of your kids and I go like yeah
cuz kids are cuz kids are watching this and I've been trying to watch it through
the lens of a young person watching it which is impossible for me to do it is
it bothers me on it doesn't bother me but it like it it it makes me
uncomfortable on a different level yes well on a more positive media note new
show new show note I will shout out mystery science theater and rift tracks
are combining again or should I say rift tracks is basically re taking up the
mantle of mystery science theater 3000 and they are going to produce four new
episodes utilizing Kevin and Mike and oh my god Bill from the OG rift tracks crew
as you know reprising their roles Tom Sarvone Crowe and him and yeah it's
gonna be really cool to see them back in the saddle instead of the whole new crew
which nothing against the new crew for the most part there were one or two
times that whoever was voicing Crowe on a couple of this last season I was like
shut up they were just screaming like that is not the fucking voice but yeah
it's already up to 1.6 million on Kickstarter that's amazing brand new
thing and they've still got 45 days to go something like that wow but it's a
wonderful thing to see them back at it and this is the rift tracks fans coming
through big time for them because I've backed several of their kickstarters to
a back the mystery science theater crew too but I am far more in the camp of
what rift tracks has been doing than the last because laughing and more than the
than the MS the last MSC 3k failed because people were just kind of like
that like because that last season was just not great and it's because they
really jacking around with who they had voicing Crowe they had a couple people
really knew how to do it but then if you're watching a movie and someone's in
there shut fucking up I can't I love the things that bother you about about
movies Paul it's I watched that mystery science theater 3,000 season and there
was a single time that the robots voices even occurred the most recent one the
most recent season I don't know if you saw this most recent season I didn't see
the most recent one you'd because you would go oh shit I can't unhear this
it's awful it's awful it's just a screeching banshee and and it just ruins
any of it so they had good performers that first reboot they were fine I was
like this is great you know let's go but now I'm really excited because it's the
old bots with the old voices it's you know you don't want weird sounding
Muppets it's the same shit people are all on the Kermit thing too you know
there's something to it there's really something to it and you know Kermit the
Frog always said it's not easy being blue hey invent some new robots they
invented some new robots throw them in there that's fine but also just don't be
screechy screechy ain't gonna just goddamn screechy ain't funny it's not
not Dustin Diamond is he's no longer with us yeah he's no longer and so I
mean just just bringing it up and it's truly in bad taste so everybody who is
doing screech impressions on mystery science theater 3,000 episodes just
stop it exactly well they've they've stopped it because they didn't get fun
in our last one but anyway Mary Jo Peel is gonna be back as Miss Forrester and
that's gonna be funny Pearl Forrester so that's gonna be funny too they got the
proper antagonist with them I think it's gonna be quite good I'm looking forward
to the new four episode mini season thing I went ahead and backed it on the
Kickstarter and of course got to get my physical media on so I ordered the four
DVDs and VHS tape yeah the VHS tapes are going up dude the money on those it's
crazy it's true I don't doubt it they're really expensive now comparatively
especially like horror I think it's dumb but I don't doubt it I know it's done
but there is a huge market for it but anyway just want to say shout out to the
rift tracks guys I listen to them every night pretty much Matt have you dipped a
toe yet on the old to be did you take in any of the rift tracks films yet to try
and use them as sort of your lullabies I have not used them as lullabies or check
them out I should I should really should you really should they had some really
great stuff in there right now yeah I'm about to do another two-week stint on
the old Sun Princess so maybe I can crack it then well and I'll just put this out
there's my number one recommendation for anyone who wants to see if they like
this kind of shit go on to be look up rift tracks and then watch samurai cop
the samurai cop episode of riff tracks is one of the funniest things I've seen
it so many times still laugh my ass off even just thinking about it it is a
super cheese-o B movie action thing it's crazy I it's great you know if you if
you grew up like us when that was the thing like you know aping commando and
all those kind of things but samurai cop god damn it's the movie is so crazy on
its own so check it out if you get a chance it's also amazing like how many
movies have they covered they are I think they they're cracking around 500
maybe more it's amazing like how many like because it's not like there's a
certain aesthetic because there's a lot of like just bad bad yes yes and it's
it's it's it's a very fine needle of thread you wouldn't think but it really
is and there's some of them that are better than others by far basically it
feels like what their show basically is is it seems like if Penn's old movie
night had morphed into a podcast I mean yeah that's what you know mystery
science theater was always that but there there has to be a certain level of
watchability to the movie that's right it can't just be absolute trash
unwatchable and again has to have decent audio and all that kind of thing
because otherwise it just you know you can't sit there for two hours and
watch it and there's been a couple of of them that are really pushing the line
because they are digging pretty deep in the catalog but yeah man oh god this
samurai cop will fucking well I mean we we learned that lesson too with some of
the episodes of what was the the Michael Landon angel show oh yes I would have a
highway to heaven I would have it not all gems not all some of those were just
so bad you can't make fun of them right oh this thing's like I love the movie
night at Penn's house it was like one of my favorite things and then when I was
younger and I had a house full of guys that's what we do we would just flip to
find the worst movies on HBO and make fun of them it was an activity I loved
it I miss it I was like I'm basically hoping like my kids are now getting funny
enough that like if I can get them on board I have to figure out a way to like
get them into the idea of making fun of a movie while we watch it out loud to
make use of the lap but I feel like I can recreate it with my with my boys
right now show them some mystery science theater riff tracks has some some
question like samurai cop would not be suitable for your young ins it's it's
violent and there's boobies and shit circles and circles you wanted me to show
them terrifier three I mean I do still want you to show them terrifier three on
Christmas I would give you I might I would I might actually give you money for
that it's the first 15 minutes it lose their fucking minds all right tell you
what if Matt loses jock vs. nerd today he's showing his kids terrifier 3 on Christmas
the hunt for balls we have a winter Olympics themed scooperty from freehold
scoop today the categories are curling biathlon luge and bobsled I'm up first
oh let's see I'll try curling for 400 this is how much the stones that the
players slide down the ice way in pounds within five this is the first one this
is the first how much does the Rockwell is the first question but Jacob they're
called stones and you know in Europe when you say oh I lost 30 stone or more
oh you know or I lost five stone over the summer vacation because I stopped
eating gummy bears or whatever so maybe I believe that's 20 pounds you think you
think one stone is 20 pounds I was about to say I don't know I think that's what
it is uh fine Paul 20 pounds that's my logic all right let's try it 42 oh the
answer 42 that's much heavier than that's heavier than 20 that's two
not within five at all I think it's well I don't know what it's I thought is one
I was gonna ask you is one stone 20 pounds that's what I thought I say
somebody weighs how many stones oh it's 14 pounds oh one stone is 14 pounds yes
sorry Paul you're up okay um biathlon let's go for 14 for 400 biathlon
combines cross-country skiing and this other sport target shooting target
shooting I'm sorry it's rifle shooting Paul you're not shooting targets you're
shooting rifles Matt you're up um curling for 800 curlers use these
household devices to melt the ice causing the stones to go further and
curl less rooms brooms and rushes chimney chimchimmy chimchim surey Jeff Loomis not
in my house it's me I'll try bobsled 400 mmm an Olympic bobsled team consists of
either two athletes or this many I believe it's four I believe of two or
four yeah don't they have single-person bobsleds or are they called something
that's skeleton oh that's right skeletons over you lie down yes feet
first skeleton what's the one what's the one where you go headfirst is that the
last skeleton head first and skeleton feet first is luge oh maybe that's the
first question on luge Paul you're up I will take biathlon for 8 by athlete
shoot it targets from two positions standing and this lower position fucking
that's why they're biathletes they have to show that they're biathletes yeah
fucking a lady and the other is fucking a dude
band kick kneeling one leg up kneeling prone prone like the like the oh so we
were talking about sexual positions like the shrimp dog go prone trim is prone
kneeling okay elbows but up elbows out I'll show you gotcha I'll teach you some
pronin yeah I'll do curling for 1200 all right oh shit oh my god the target
scoring area of the ring is called this the same thing you might call your
residents buck house domicile to the tickle house
this is the house or the I think it's home base like in tag oh I think it's
just home I think it's just home
they send it home I think that's what that's from I'll go I'll go with home
all right the house we were close nobody listens to Jacob I would have been
closer to the fuck house yeah it's me I'll try but curling well I'll try
biathlon for 1200 to both in Vegas you should know the house always wins
athletes must hit targets at this distance in meters during Olympic
competition within five meters 14 pounds Jacob 14 pounds final answer it's
English money I feel like it's I want to say it's like 25 but it might be 50 I
don't I got a pass Paul I'll go 50 all right it is 50 yeah I'm a biathlete sure
Paul you're up I'll do it for 2000 let's go daily double look at this here we go
Norway's all inner yours run holds the record for most olympic biathlon medals
with this many within three or John for every in our board Boria Dean borderland
borderland for every person offended by Paul's accent earlier think about how
the norwegians feel okay only in our borderland Bjorn Bjorn Dylan that's it
so those things only come around so often four years four years I think no
no Matt every so often can you win multiple medals like swimming yeah in
biathlon I mean I think I just win for the biathlon that I'll go here right I'll
go with five okay let's see 13 Jesus fuck me what you were doing the right
math you just did not get close to what Norway shit early in your version so
well you just had he had multiple events to place in I didn't realize it was a
multiple event I mean you're assuming he I'm not assuming anything only I only
don't know only is a dude's name sure I think all right great double down same
points is only a man Matt you're up I got a curling for 2000 the main two types of
shots are curler throws are draws and this other type designed to remove the
opponent stones dickhead ministration boppers boppers great answer if it's not
called Bob should be boppers I'm gonna go with knockouts oh good guess good
guess I'm getting Chinese food later tonight I can't fucking wait I'll go
bobsled for 800 the athlete who steers the bobsled from the front position is
called this captain suicide Edward his name is Edward it's something about the
hell they have like a leash right it's like it's a couple of little strings
pull things yeah a little pulley string so it's probably something like the
leashman or the the stringman the leashman I saw those I saw those guys
they played prim the quartet I saw it with Chuck Connors was still on it
deletion but he says they saw Chuck Connors in the leachman nobody saw Chuck
Connors in the leachman ah it's like the the steerer or the wheel man there you
go wheel man he's the wheel man he's using ropes he's like the rope stir or
something no they call him the wheel man ironically Paul oh because he drives to
the event well uses his feet probably - oh I don't know I don't think I don't
think they use their feet yeah it's on a thing uh yeah I don't I don't know I
passed Paul okay here we go they use their feet final answer ropesman show me
ropesman pilot or driver well well well well well aren't we creative mr. Bob
sled or should I call you Robert sled Paul you're up fuck I'll do luge for
2000 oh let's do it I gotta get back on Germany has dominated Olympic luge
winning approximately this fraction of all gold medals in the sports history
within ten percent 73 percent Jacob that is dominant for sure let's see I'm sorry
it's 60% you're off by three percent
oh no now that I've leapt into second place by the way we got five questions
left quick score check I am currently winning with zero you're not uncatchable
donnelly Matt has negative 2400 anybody negative 4000 anybody just say at this
point in the show that the three of us really know our winter Olympic sports oh
got that winter Olympic fever that's right man I think it's the flu Matt
you're up let's go I'll go lose for 1200 okay luge runs are time to this tiny
fraction of a second where races are often decided my penis oh it does come
in second I would guess thousands oh good get a thousandth of a second I mean
that's a that is a tiny fraction of a second on thousand yeah I'm sorry it's
100 ah mr. by mr. by one order of magnitude a bridge too far a bridge too
far gift of the Magi last place is within my grasp mattingly mine too this is the
maximum weight limit in pounds for a four-person bobsled including crew
within 100 pounds well each of the people weigh a hundred and twenty pounds yes so
that's another five hundred and and twenty pounds right plus some of them
been snacking so that's okay 550 just for the people about 550 550 maybe let's
let's be generous their athletes they're hefty muscle weighs more than fat let's
say 600 just for the four individuals okay the thing itself is very lightweight
I think the sled the sled I would imagine the sled the chassis is all
fiberglass II right sure it's something yeah so I don't know 30 pounds for the
chassis okay then you've got to have the structure and the thing to hold it
together that's where the real weight comes in but I would see isn't the
thing holding it together no I'd say the the the legs and the thing would be the
that's that's another 200 so probably get 250 for the whole kitten caboodle so
250 plus 600 so 850 that would be my guess okay I pass Paul you're up all
right so the so 850 I think would be a safe bet maximum weight I'm gonna guess
is a thousand let's try a thousand I'm sorry 1389 pounds I underestimated you
underestimated Paul you're up yet Luz and Bob sled left Bob sled down on the farm
for 2000 Jamaican famously competed in this year's Winter Olympics inspiring
the film cool runnings Oh cool runnings happened when I was still in high school
which had to be 92 or 93 okay John Candy was alive right but when was that winter
Olympics okay now I got to count it down so 6 2 18 10 6 to 98
94 90 had to be in 1990 I guess 1990 and it wasn't that's not even I was off by
two years somewhere we're gonna lose two years or gain two man I suck a man Matt
yet lose for 400 or 800 no matter what you do it doesn't matter I'll do one
bomb sled question right but then I clearly lost that money somewhere lose
sleds have no break so athletes slow down using these parts of their body
what parts of their body they use to slow the sleds down I think it's grow
them whoa Bob Evans it's like a beaver tail just like dragging it down
oh if you're if you're scrotum as beaver tail oh I mean it's gotta answer feet
right it has to be one of the I'm done guessing at this at this fucking game is
it is it their knees the back of their own heads now the luge are they on
there on there are they on their stomach or on the on their back no they're on
their backs they're sitting skeleton his head first okay so the sitting loses
feet first okay chaotic either hand they use their opponent's stones oh they
throw up parachutes I'll say hands let's try hands their feet
damn it I've been really gonna marry it down to 50/50 on this one the wrong way
every time you have been really good at least saying the correct answer
somewhere in your discussion I'm closing out the category and the game lose for
400 if I get this question right one of us will be in positive points well I'm
not counting a day unlike Bob's letters who sit upright yes lose up right news
athletes race in this body position they're on their backs yeah wait a
minute Jacob that puts you in positive points
400 points I will just happened is I won the game with 400 points Matt is in
second place though with negative 4400 points and Paul is in third place with
negative 7200 points Winter Olympics catch the fever everybody the fever get
pumped JJ just popped in the chat I'm trying to get JJ on earlier but she had
a very important doctor's appointment oh that's good JJ good to see you though
can you unmute yourself JJ no she can't know the answer is absolutely not no oh
well no the answer is genuinely she can't unmute yourself hey did I do it yeah you
did it you guys I just had my Botox and filler redone you can't do it revenge
med spa revenge revenge med spa I mean you sound so happy about this but you
look so apathetic it worked it worked I it weirdly feels good I feel like it's
some sort of weird face massage for weird people like me I was like do the
needles but yeah JJ is someone who's open about their cosmetic work can you
tell the story about happen to you at the Las Vegas Airport please rock man
this is such bullshit I was so mad plane right and I'm like I have 20 bucks I'm
just gonna put in a machine and see what happens sorry the Botox doesn't work yet
so my face is all over the lot I sit down with my backpack and I've got my
magic castle hat on put my 20 bucks in and it goes to 60 and I'm like whoot and
the lady comes around the corner she puts her hands on her hips and goes
hello little one and I was like are you talking to me and she's like yes she
goes so you're trying to gamble I was like yes and I was like I'm 36 years old
we're gonna have to see some ID passport she opens it and she goes oh
god yeah so that means that this shit works I guess the hands on hips little
one is so degrading do you think this is an affectation of you dealing on Disney
so long that you are just de-aging because the Disney the Disney magic is
just continually de-aging you I'll tell you what I I've gone places where people
are like she's a vampire Matt was at the crazy castle in Savannah Illinois where
people that tour it try to get me to stand in front of a mirror and then they
go she does have a reflection but no Disney I literally asked him I was like
listen I don't want a lot of shit I was like Disney cheeks I need Disney cheeks
okay there she is on point we're at the end of the
episodes we have to save your topic for you have to come back on next week and
do the other thing we want to do Oh deal because if people want to hear about some
porch pirate shit and Jesse going full Nancy Drew I got you yeah of course you
like of course you fucking track down a porch pirate I did the police's job for
them and that is a story for another time you're on a ship next week yeah I
get on the ship I got on the ship the fifth but I have really good Wi-Fi on
Disney okay so I'll let you know because I'm doing it from the ship too so we'll
both check it from our ships and and we can we can do your porch pirate story
yes I've got photos and video too I documented the whole thing where your
life preservers congratulations and make sure you have an adult hold your hand
when you go on on the ship okay careful there little one oh you trying to get on
the ship oh look at you trying to get on the ship it is a big ship I work here
cunt I am the oldest person in the entertainment department on the ship
like by ten years holy crap oh yeah the kids are on the ships oh yeah the kids
take the ship jobs that's true some of them are like 18 like I saw Maleficent
came out of the elevator and they have to stay in character even in the crew
areas so I was backstage and she's like move out of my way peasant and they were
like she's 18 years old I was like well fuck they stay backstage in character
what no no oh yeah oh yeah this is why my god my Loki Maleficent Cruella shit
this is why we can't have you pop out of the end of episodes JJ you're a powder
keg of craziness we need you to give you proper episode slot Disney characters on
the cruise ships have to stay in characters backstage that's incredible
yes until they get to the wig room yeah the wig room what happens with the wig
room the leg room stays in the way this breakdown is like I was mean to so many
people I was such a jerk handbag on the deck in the moment the Cruella - the
amazing thing on destiny is the people that are Loki Cruella and Maleficent
there's not multiple cast it's just them so they know everything that's been said
they are awesome oh man wow oh yeah there's actually a Cruella improv show
and it's awesome it took me until just now to realize that you were saying Loki
loki and not Loki l-o-w-k-e-y low-key giving Mickey a mini I'll send you I'll
send you the Disney life I'll send you the zoom links next week JJ yes yes my
face won't be nearly as mobile all right we'll see you then bye all right I want
amazing thanks many scoop for his scoop pretty I want to thank Pinch up for
creating this podcast it wasn't Smitty who was it it was oh it was freehold
scoop I always think freehold scoop and speedy scoop are the same person no
they're not oh no I don't think they are they have two different names because
Smith is they both of their their pot their their questionnaires fuck us both
the same same way but yeah well I apologize I don't know what you're
talking about I had positive 400 points I apologize I apologize to freehold scoop
but I kind of don't because that was that really buried me that really hurt
me that was my worst group in a very long time that was our worst collective
scooperty in a very long time hard just got swing for the fences I know fucking
go for it you just gotta say fuck it here good money after bad yeah just say
there we go here we go let's see you want to send us one of those if you want
to send us a scooper to your any kind of jock versus nerd hey scoops calm go over
there you can send us a scooper to any kind of jock versus nerd also send us
some scoop mail do all those things over there at hey scoops calm all right it's
a new month so we haven't organized our patreon thank yous yet correct but we
will get everybody thanked throughout the month here and we want to thank you
thank you to all of you for getting us over the hump on to our bonus episode
spot let's see if we can make absolutely wary right we appreciate all the new
scoops coming in and contributing please keep it up we want to keep
bringing you bonus episodes every month if we can yeah absolutely all right well
thanks for thanks for putting us in your ear holes week after week and if you
want to support us as a patron get access to some of those bonus episodes
and other other cool rewards head on over to preaching fun.com
or if you're also excited about scoop fest norway head over to farts in a bag
dot biz that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun.com it
takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month
you can help keep this show on the air we are dependent on our patreon
supporters so please if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars
preaching fun.com farts in a bag dot biz those are two of the ways you can
support us they're kind of the main ways you can support us another way you can
support us as you can tell people about us spread the word be part of the obelisk
scheme we need more listeners we want more listeners we demand more listeners
but we will not stoop to doing a pyramid scheme no that is unethical and
we will not do gross that's where you that's where one person tells two
friends and then they each tell two friends and all that stuff that's a
pyramid scheme we are an obelisk scheme one person you find one person that's
gonna really dig this show vertical growth all the way to the top build the
obelisk tell that one person who you think is gonna really dig this weird
shit that we're doing over here and they will then be part of it as well then
they'll tell a friend and they will build the obelisk if everyone listening
right now would simply tell one person and get one new person listening we
could nearly double our listenership almost almost
everyone Paul's doing Kentucky man again hey is there a store where people can go
to buy our merch Jacob oh no no we've gotten rid of that store store we used
to have a store it was it was a whole thing it had a jingle and everything oh
yeah it's a door jingle door a big door it's on we got a story that's store
jingle of course hey scoops calm slash shop go there now do it all right
thanks for everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
that's a fine way to do this as long as it's not here talk about the time here
man on top of both sides I have a wife and she's in Canada for a reason one you're gonna go joy boy