Oh, it's all just great and everything's taking along just fine. There are no problems anywhere.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ho, ha, ho.
[Music]
Oh, hello there! I am so glad you're here. I would love to thank the ice cream truck drivers right now.
Thank your ice cream truck drivers. Who are the ice cream truck drivers, you ask?
Well, these are the people that deliver that frickin' ice cream straight to your frickin' ear holes!
[Laughter]
Right now I'd like to thank Bearded Scoop 3, Blue Line Scoop, Christine Elsesser, Christy Salinas,
Darren Cunningham, Darth Scooper, David Walker, Ted Laszlo, and Dirty Old Scoop.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows?
The life you saved may be your own.
Ah, I cut that off a little too early. Sorry. Here's the show.
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
[Music]
Oh, I've got a big problem.
What's that?
I have a Sam's Club membership and that's always been the closest big box store to my house.
But now a Costco is opening up.
And they're almost equal distance.
Sophie's Choice.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, PA, that's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
Speaking of Sophie's Choice, I went and saw Fantastic Four.
Right? This is something I want to talk about. Marvel film fatigue is fully setting in.
Is Fantastic Four Marvel? I guess it is.
They're original Marvel.
The first family of the Marvel Universe.
King Kirby's grand creation.
Jiminy jumped up Christmas.
Oh, Lord.
Boy, for somebody that was really upset about the Fantastic Four a minute ago, you are very defensive of their origins.
I'm not upset about it. I didn't see the movie yet.
Although, although, well, we'll see.
I was upset I texted you guys in the middle of the movie.
I know you were really upset. This was hurting your soul.
I got a text message from Matt in mid-film.
So you took your kids to go see Fantastic Four.
Yes, I was a group of two other parents and a total of six children went to see Fantastic Four together.
Summer blockbuster.
Time to get out in the theaters and enjoy ourselves.
First scene is a pregnancy test.
Just her just hanging over pregnancy tests and I was like, oh, no, I really don't want this to be about a baby.
Oh, you're in luck, I guess.
And then like it's like straight up with like like all of the all like as if they made it for parents, like as if the kids like like the kids were maybe secondary to the summer blockbuster thing.
They thought maybe a lot of parents, a lot of moms would come out and want to see scenes about like losing sleep.
And like who's going to take care of the baby and all this other stuff.
And is he normal? And let's let's let's let's look at the scans.
And I was like, who is this for? Who is this for?
And then they're like, oh, Galacticus, we got to go talk to that guy.
Let's get the pregnant lady into the spaceship and get her out and out of space.
Let's make sure that she's leaving the planet.
This seems like a good job to visit a planet eating being and and see if he wants to just talk to a pregnant lady.
What like why do you do it?
They talk about how they struggle to get pregnant.
All the things that like bring back all the like, you know, as my friend Matt told me when your first year of pregnancy, first year the kids on Earth, it's he called a baby nam.
You're in baby now. Right.
So you want to be reminded of like the time you basically went crazy and lost sight of everything that was happening in the world for a year.
Let's make sure we get that nostalgic back in here. Right.
And then Galacticus wants that baby.
That's that's that's the deal.
He won't eat. He won't eat out of all of the out of all the babies that could have been shot up into outer space to talk to Galacticus.
We happen to shoot up the right one.
Yeah, because he's the child of two superheroes. So he's special. Wow.
That is lucky for us.
Well, I'll say I'll.
So I assume they just sacrifice the baby and Galacticus goes away and everything is fine from then on.
I'll step in as the good of the many outweighs as a comic book nerd.
Again, I have not seen the film.
If it's fucking canon, it'll give a shit.
If it's fucking from the original author, if the fucking genius from Marvel's cradle was like, no, this is sacred script.
I don't give a fuck.
I brought my kids to a summer blockbuster and watched him watch two hours of whether we should or shouldn't sacrifice a baby.
Yeah. No, I think that's a stupid move.
Now, the only my only defense and this is a very weak defense.
But in many, what do you think, Marvel?
Should we sacrifice this baby in many incarnations?
Franklin, the baby, they did call him Franklin, right?
Yes. Yeah.
OK, great. At least they stuck to that.
Franklin Richards does become a super genius capable of manipulating multiverses.
So there is something of the of a, you know, he's he's a he's a keystone character or you know what I mean?
I understand.
But you know, it's the same argument when fucking we spent all of Black Widow setting up the fucking Cannonball family.
What are they called?
That's a Cannonball family with red, red tornado or whatever his name is.
No, no, the movie that just came out with the other movie that just came out.
The Thunderbolts. Thunderbolts.
So I went to see I want to see Scarlett Johansson kick ass of Black Widow.
And they spent half that movie setting up the Thunderbolts movie, a movie that wouldn't come out for another three years.
So thanks for the prequel.
And then I keep in mind, too, when they first made the movie, because remember, they held the movie.
They held Black Widow for a year.
So when they made it, it wouldn't have come out for four years.
So it's like, well, I don't I don't need to keep this like encyclopedic like checklist of like, oh, good.
When I'm watching a film, like if it pays off, great.
If it's a building up, great, great.
When the when the Robert Downey Jr. first Iron Man came out, you didn't sit on your hands during the movie going like, yes, but what are they going to do with vision?
OK, here's a play music or something.
He's a big spoiler. So play music or something. Oh, OK.
We got a big spoiler coming up here. Those in the chat who don't want to be spoiled, avert your ears.
So yeah, so I'm going to play a little music by the time the music ends.
Fast forward until you don't hear the music. When I go like this again, you can come back on if you don't want spoilers.
All right. Spoilers. They show her fucking dead for like two minutes.
Sue Storm, like dead on the invisible girl, fucking dead, like on the ground, fucking Pedro Pascal weeping over her dead fucking body, like true fucking death scenes.
And then finally bring the baby around so that the baby can start showing his powers for the first time.
That's like punching someone in the face and saying, just kidding.
Like, you can't like you made a bunch of children look at a dead woman on the ground for two minutes.
Like, fuck off. It sounds like the first Pokemon movie, honestly.
But the Pokemon movie had lots of dead women in it, but that is canon.
Do you remember the first Pokemon movie? Did you ever see the first Pokemon movie?
Oh, yeah, yeah, no. I watched the first Pokemon movie again last night.
I'm not talking to you, Jacob. I know you never saw the first Pokemon movie.
No, I rewatched it again last night. It was great. I loved it. All of the dead women. It doesn't bother me.
The dead women in the Pokemon movie does not concern me at all.
Matt, you probably missed the first Pokemon movie, too, because that was a little bit after the boys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We did not get into it. They collect the cards, but they're not really into any of the...
So, spoiler for the 20 plus year old Pokemon movie.
Yeah.
Ash dies. He dies.
What?
And then the Pokemon start crying and their magical tears bring him back to life.
So, it sounds like they just ripped off the Pokemon movie from 20 years ago.
Yes. Look, I guess we can say thumbs up to rejoin, because we'll talk about it more vaguely or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, scoopernova girl says that he dies in every movie.
Ash knows that he doesn't die in every movie.
Oh, okay.
No, I mean, there are more dead parents in Disney's canon than there is in every horror movie franchise.
Disney loves killing fucking moms and dads.
And the canon is how they get rid of the bodies. They put the bodies in the canon, and then they get rid of the bodies.
And the circus ripped that off. So, who's ripping off who?
And the truth is, my kids didn't give a shit. They just liked watching Fantastic Four.
R-Tax. Winners scoop fucking R-Tax.
Yeah, it is R-Tax. It is R-Tax time.
My kids didn't give a shit. They watched the movie. They were fine or whatever.
Did they like it?
They did like it. They did not love it.
Right.
I will tell you, there's a second movie we saw over the weekend.
Oh.
And the first movie we saw was Naked Gun.
Ah.
How did that go?
I bet they liked Naked Gun.
They loved Naked Gun.
Yeah.
They were just crying out loud laughing. And this is why it's so funny that we're so cool with violence and so anti-anything that might whiff of sex.
Right. I would take my kids to Naked Gun again tomorrow. They were laughing so hard.
Yeah.
First of all, Pamela Anderson is really good at it, which is something I was not expecting.
I expected her to be fine.
Oh, yeah. I heard she's great.
She's really funny in it, which I've never seen her be in other things.
It certainly seems that as she's getting older, she is accepting more and more. I can just be funny. This is great.
I do think it's a thing about character. I think as she got older, she's no longer this bombshell, so she's allowed to say things differently and feel things differently. It's on us.
She doesn't have to worry about that.
Oh, absolutely.
Yes, absolutely.
I agree with that.
It's a weird thing. Did you also hear she and Liam Neeson are an item?
They kissed on the red carpet, Paul.
Right.
Scandal.
I mean, not scandal. It's adorable. It's a show mance, Matt. It's a show mance.
It is, but no, it's one of those different things. In the movie, his character is a widower and he falls for her in it.
Oh, and in real life.
And in real life, it's the same. But that movie is just a million jokes a mile a minute. It's what it's supposed to be.
Some people I've heard speak a little snobbly about it, and I'm always like, what were you expecting?
Yeah, it's a naked gun.
And I mean this, not to be overly dramatic, but I remember after 9/11. I was in the New York improv scene. We're all very thick commons.
Good. I'm glad we're not going to be too dramatic.
Not that he's too dramatic, but I remember John Bowie saying, I used to not get the three stooges, and I get the three stooges now.
OK.
He was like, we were all at the UCB, we were all trying to do our own version of sophisticated improv comedy, for whatever that's worth, and sketch comedy.
And just like these stupid weird pratfall stuff. And he said he just found himself watching it right after 9/11, and it was like, oh, this is so soothing.
I've been told that about the new Naked Gun movie, that it is that old school, because I haven't seen it yet, but I've been told by multiple people that it's that old school.
We're just going to get up, and we're going to do a bunch of stupid bits and tell a bunch of jokes.
Just a joke a second. Nothing's ever going to come out of our mouth that isn't a joke.
And I've been told it's just so irreverent, and not trying to deal with issues, and it is just like an old school checkout.
You just go check out at the movie theater for an hour and a half, two hours, and just have a nice time. Is that fair?
Totally. It's total escapism, just a crazy amount of jokes on every level, from the dumbest jokes to really funny long bits. Really good.
And you're right, Jacob. When Airplane and Naked Gun were part of our regular lives when we were younger, I used to even talk about it in improv classes, the idea of stakes to jokes.
If you want to have the most fun, you have to have high stakes, right? And then I had to stop saying that because I started teaching people younger and younger, and then no one had ever watched those movies at a certain point.
Oh, yeah.
And then there was the Children's Hospital was the only kind of slapsticky thing around to illustrate that point, and then all of a sudden...
Matt doesn't mean the TV show. He means an actual children's hospital that was down the street from where he taught.
But yeah, whatever. Adult Swim Show.
But there just wasn't that slapstick style. I remember even literally with my children trying to explain what slapstick was and being like, "Shit, I don't have any concrete examples."
But yeah, they're getting hurt, but it's funny. It's really sophisticated. I'm sorry, kids.
So they were just crying laughing. They got in the car, and they were debating whether it was the funniest movie they'd ever seen.
Good.
So I guess...
What were the other contenders?
Ace Ventura.
Great.
That's a good entry.
They really liked Ace Ventura.
That's a crazy movie.
It is a joke in the house to do the thing with the sliding door, like, "Ahhhh."
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Good, good.
Oh, yeah. Scoop of Monte Cristo in the chat wants to know, "Will you show them the original Naked Gun now?"
I think so.
I think now...
I think it'd be good.
We're actually now at the place where... At first we used to worry about showing certain things. Our kids watch The Simpsons all the time.
Yeah.
And I guess other kids aren't allowed to watch that, so they come over and they're still not allowed to watch it.
Right.
And so it was funny because my kids are just... They know how to negotiate, basically. They're sophisticated craftsmen of the deals.
Yeah, that's true.
So literally the next morning they're like, "Oh, Family Guy's on the channel. Dad, can we watch Family Guy?"
And I was like, "Oh, man."
It's like...
The slippery slope has begun.
It's like, "You can't put the genie back in the bottle, right?"
And I was like, "If they watched all the Naked Gun stuff..."
Well, you can start them off with Police Squad.
I mean, that's the thing. I think we should just watch that because there's references to Police Squad in it that are direct, that you're like...
Right.
If you know the reference.
And Police Squad is one of those shows... It's very similar to Get Smart and those types of shows where they really did...
It'd be a little bit different each episode, but each episode was basically the same jokes over and over again.
Which is kind of delightful and almost secure.
Yes.
Now, one of the writers on it...
It was written and directed by one of the guys from Lonely Island, but one of the other writers on it is Dan Greger.
Who is Rachel Bloom's husband and already a very successful movie writer and filmmaker.
But I still have his number on my phone from when he used to do the Neutrino video projects in New York.
And I was like, "What if he has to change his number?"
And so I just shot him a text being like, "Look, I hope you're getting a thousand of these texts."
Just left the theater with my kids, all of us just laughing our asses off.
Yeah.
And what a time for the movie to come out. I'm so happy it came out and everything else and so...
We had a really nice exchange on that. So it was really fun.
Oh, that's lovely.
I said I was Matt Donnelly, so I would skip the new phone who dis.
Oh, yeah.
Get past that part.
But it was a super fun thing. But yeah, very, very happy.
So a lot of cinematic intake for me, guys. A lot of cinematic intake.
Yeah. Well, I finally got around to seeing Thunderbolts and I did not enjoy that film at all.
Guestimating better or worse than Fantastic Four.
I don't... I can't... I don't know.
That's why it's guestimating. Based on what Matt has said, does it sound better or worse?
I'm guessing it's worse than Fantastic Four.
Oh. Fight.
I don't know. I've heard a lot of great stuff about Fantastic Four and I heard middling stuff about Thunderbolts.
But I heard better stuff about Thunderbolts than I thought.
Now, problem is, you talk about coming in with the comic book baggage, Matt.
Yeah. So spoilers for Thunderbolts, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, hold on. Hold on. Yeah.
Let's get some spoiler music going for Thunderbolts. When the music ends, the spoiler is over.
Fast forward until you don't hear the music anymore. Thunderbolts spoiler.
So Thunderbolts revolves around the character of the Sentry.
The Sentry is essentially Marvel's answer to Superman.
Okay. Ah.
Are you familiar with this character?
Not at all.
Superman? Yes.
Sentry is a relatively new invention.
And he's only, I don't know, probably not even 20-year-old character, I don't think.
I have never enjoyed the Sentry at all.
Because, just like Superman, it's hard to make stakes when you've got an invincible everything thing.
So the only twist on Sentry is that he has a dark side.
Right? So he's like Superman, but he's also evil Superman at the same time.
He's got mental problems. That's the whole thing.
But it's like if they made Moon Knight Superman, basically.
Gotcha.
Spoiler over. Spoiler over.
Yeah. So it's just kind of bleh, you know, not great with that because, again, the stakes just don't seem to be there.
Right.
And the characters that I did enjoy, like Yelena, whatever her name, from the Black Widow series, she just, there's really nothing for her to do.
She's just, it's all, and it feels very, it feels really small.
The movie feels really small. Everything just feels like it's shot in like five tiny locations.
When they do get it big, it's just to show some buildings falling on each other and nobody cares.
It's just because nobody cares because, again, nothing, no consequence, nothing happens.
And according to Google AI, Fantastic Four is slightly worse than Thunderbolt.
Really? Oh, well, shit. I'm in for it.
Yeah. I just like that, like, hey, guys, we're kind of losing the handle here on phase four or phase three of Marvel Universe.
Yeah. How are we going to write this shit? You're like, all right, there's a baby.
You're like, there's a pregnancy test.
Yeah, all these ideas. And the whole thing with, God, David Harbour is just so dumb in this fucking movie as the Soviet guy.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yelena's dad. He comes off like he's trying to hit on her.
It doesn't. There's no parental. It's just Red Guardian. Yeah, just garbage.
Anyway, I was I was really disappointed because I really wanted to like it.
And I did not like it at all.
How old are the Thunderbolts? How are they a modern comic book introduction or have they been around for a while?
I'm going to say that was late 90s and, you know, that was a whole thing where so fairly recent, especially for us.
But but very different incarnation of who was in it, too, sort of.
I think I think that the former Captain America wants his name super soldier.
I can't remember his name, Patriot. It doesn't matter, Mr. Patriot, whatever.
I think he was part of it from the jump.
You know who else Mr. Patriot was in.
And that's the following sponsor.
So today's show is brought to you by Scryte Extra Sugar, the Tooth Loosener.
That's from Cool Yay. I like I like glass.
Wait, queer a glass. That's it.
Twenty twenty three the product. No problem pronouncing Scryte Extra Sugar, the Tooth Loosener.
Oh, yeah, it's me, the ghost of Macho Man Randy Savage.
I'm here to tell you a little something about Scryte Extra Sugar.
You ever have a tooth that's just not coming loose?
It's just not coming out. Well, I've got the solution for you right here.
You could get this out of your head. No problem.
Cream rises to the top and so does the cane sugar.
Go ahead, get yourself a tall glass of Sprite Extra Sugar and pour it in.
You'll notice the thickening agents are going to work immediately, causing it to drip like Sunday topping right on your cold ice cubes.
Go ahead and try and drink it. You won't be able to because it's 99 percent sugar.
It's granulated for your pleasure.
Go ahead and chew a Sprite Extra Sugar today. Gargle it down, bitch. Yum.
I'm sorry. Did you did you say you're a ghost?
I'm a ghost. I feel like that is the lead that we are burying here.
What are you talking about? I'm not the only ghost.
Advertisements? You're not?
No, I mean, this has been going on for a long time.
I remember when Gene Kelly was selling vacuum cleaners.
You know, you have you have an excellent point.
Shoot, Paul Walker's about to start another fast movie franchise.
That's right. Brought to you by Sprite Extra Sugar.
The tooth-loosener.
Anyways, when we got out of the movie, I was like, should we go watch Sophie's Sophie's Choice now or what should we do?
And so how did the kids like Sophie's Choice?
They loved all the action. Good.
Hey, speaking of Sprite Extra Sugar.
Yes. Have either of you gentlemen heard of the new trend?
Don't get sued by Sprite. We're only talking about Sprite.
I said, did I say Sprite? I meant Sprite.
You said Sprite once or twice. Oh, boy. Well, whatever. It's all the same.
It's not. That's the entire point. It's not.
You're right. You're right. Keeps us free.
Have either of you experienced dirty sodas yet?
Who's that? I want to experience this person.
When I went to Utah, there's all those soda places.
Yes. Utah is where Utah is where it's popping off.
It's a Mormon thing.
Yes. It's a Mormon thing.
There are a few here. It is a Mormon thing and it is bananas.
It's spread out here now. So our little local ice cream spot that we go to,
they have dirty sodas now and got one the other day.
I just got a regular milkshake and got a dirty soda.
And I sipped on that motherfucking thing. I am a fan.
Of course it's crack. Why wouldn't you?
When we were kids, we had Shirley Temples, right?
Which was like, hey, let's take the sweetest thing that you could possibly have on Earth
and then add a sugary syrup to it and mix it up.
And when you look at the ingredients of these crazy crack sodas,
it is just the most caloric.
It is insane.
This one that she got was Dr. Pepper mixed with raspberry syrup
and I believe it's a tangerine cream.
Coffee creamer is one of the things that go with these.
Creamer is a big thing.
Yeah. So coffee creamer goes into it.
Canadian Scoop Crystal asking about the dirty.
So it's like coffee creamer and then syrups and all kinds of stuff.
So it kind of muddies it up.
As always, Canadian Scoop Crystal, dirty for Mormons, not dirty for you.
Exactly. Exactly.
And you're absolutely right, Scoop of Monte Cristo, the blood does thicken on this stuff.
It is an extreme blood thickener.
You know who hates that soda is your pancreas. That's who hates that.
Oh, he hasn't had a lot to say around here in a long time.
He really has had no voice in the conversation.
He has been in the non-vocal minority for a while.
He's been very much excluded from the conversation for a while.
Pancre-who?
Pancre-hoodis?
Pancre-you, not Pancre-us.
Yeah, here's Winter Scoop's recipe.
44-ounce Dr. Pepper with three creamers, also do it with root beer, make soda into the float drink after the ice cream is eaten up.
Oh man, I don't think it was that much.
That's real dirty.
It was just a little, it was a small cup of it.
On the show we talked about once I put French vanilla creamer into apple cider because I did it on Thanksgiving.
Oh yeah, it would come off like a little ala mode, yeah, how'd it go?
It was delicious, but again, my teeth rattle as I recall the story.
I'm not watching a video of somebody make one of these.
They're like pouring Diet Coke into a glass, pouring some kind of creamer into it on top of it, and then just squeezing a lime and now they're pouring some raspberry-looking syrups into it.
There you go.
Yeah, there's lots of different recipes.
It's alchemy.
I think it's fun that you can come up with all these crazy new things.
Don't get me wrong, I did Mr. Pib Zero with cherry vanilla on the soda thing.
That was legit good.
I felt like a dirty Mormon at my movie.
Steven Eames asking, "Wouldn't the milk curdle it?" Well, there's no milk involved in these non-dairy creamers. They're just flavored liquids.
According to the Googles, some people use dairy creamers, though, and so I would think those would curdle.
Those people are monsters.
That sounds horrific.
That doesn't sound any better or worse.
No, no, no. What? Do you want a cottage cheese soda? That's what that would be.
That sounds as good as everything else you're describing.
The dairy is not what's bothering me here.
Even when you go AL8 and Big Red, when I travel, you find a novelty soda.
One of the reasons why they're thriving as a novelty soda is that they have 50 more calories than Coke.
You're just like, "Oh, that's significant. That's a significant amount of sugar."
A Thirsty Scoop had a cherry pie dirty soda. It was sprite, cream, cherry syrup, and vanilla.
A typical dirty soda can contain significantly more calories than a regular soda, potentially ranging from 250 to 600 additional calories.
For your beverage.
Let's go.
Yeah, that's your beverage.
No, that's your meal. Now, let's be real.
I hope so. I hope so too, but when I have just a bunch of sugar, it doesn't feel like a meal, so then I still am hungry.
According to this thing that I found that doesn't mean anything at all, some large dirty sodas are right around 1,100 calories.
There you go. You need to have a come to Jesus with your pancreas, Matt. Get them on the straight and narrow.
My doctor already told me to have a come to Jesus moment with my pancreas.
I think he meant the other direction, though.
My metformin prescription tells me I shouldn't be hitting up these dirty soda places, so maybe...
Yeah, it's a rare treat kind of thing, the dirty soda. Rare treat, it's a rare treat.
What was the thing when you guys were doing the potato diet? What was the go-to thing with him to say you'd rarely feast on something?
Rare and appropriate.
Rare and appropriate, that was it.
There's no appropriate for dirty soda.
I was going to say, appropriate doesn't feel like the right word for dirty soda, no matter what.
Rare and celebratory...
That's it. Rare and horrible.
Rare and annual.
That old text thread with a "Hey, rare and appropriate," while I'm eating a fucking gummy worm dipped in cherry cream.
Check it out, Ray.
I bit the ends off of this gummy worm, and now I'm using it as a straw.
Yeah, dirty sodas. Latter Day Scoop says dirty sodas are frequent and excessive, and that is absolutely right.
It's okay, though, because while I'm drinking this dirty soda, I'm a little chilly, so that's probably evening it all out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm outside, and it's a bit nippy.
Yeah, next time I sit down with my doctor, we go over some stuff, I'm going to be like, "That's so strange. I mean, other than my dirty sodas, I'm keeping it tip-top."
I'm down to two dirty sodas a day.
Oh, God. I can't... No, it was a small one, and Anne had like, not even a third of it, and she's like, "This is too sweet for me."
Too much, too much.
Was she bouncing off the walls? Was she a different gal all day?
She was not. She was just like, "This is just too sweet for me."
She doesn't have the candy addiction like I do.
She got them itchy teeth.
And I was like, "I'm down. Let me finish that soda." So I did, and it was good.
We were driving by children in Las Vegas. I guess children in a lot of places, but one of the kids' wise asses goes like, "Oh, can we stop by the dispensary on the way home? We just saw a dispensary."
Oh, they thought it was like a Soty Pops or something?
Well, I said, I go, "What do you think a dispensary is?"
Yeah.
And he goes, "A place where you dispense of bodies?"
And I was like, "In Las Vegas, that seems like a fair guess. That seems like a fair..."
They're worse guesses.
Like one of those enzyme pools for horses, but we have one of those at the side of the road here.
Oh, horse enzyme pools.
You know what's in that Planet 13 building? A horse enzyme pool. That's what.
It's so big because it's Olympic size. It's an Olympic size horse enzyme pool.
Talk about your fucking Artax. There you go.
That's your sorrow swamp right there.
So how did the kids like the dispensary?
They really... it helped them really enjoy Fantastic Four.
I bet it enhanced their dirty sodas too.
But having drunk that thing, I got to believe that that's going to be the next move for Starbucks, right?
Like coffee houses got to start serving these things, right?
Because they got all the stuff. But Jacob, you make a face, but they got all the stuff except the soda.
I understand. I mean, I don't think you're wrong from a business standpoint.
I just don't want more of this stuff around.
Well, oh, come on. I will also say, do you know, I tell you guys last year, it was like a year and a half ago.
Your dirty sodas won't really take off when they add ghee.
Thirsty scoop.
Oh, I'm so mad at you, thirsty scoop.
Clarified butter soda.
Oh, this is the angriest I have been in a scoop in a very long time.
I'm having an Iron Man soda. You want to join me for an Iron Man soda?
Oh, what's that?
It's a ghee, zero calorie soda, chicken.
Chicken? Just a piece of chicken? Just a piece of buffalo chicken?
That's right.
A whole bone-in buffalo chicken wing.
Gummy celery stalk.
Bone-in!
A whole bone-in buffalo chicken wing, diet coke, diet coke, half a cup of ghee.
Bullet dirty soda, now with Mero.
Bullet dirty soda.
You remember that bullet coffee?
Bullet coffee, yeah, you put the butter in it.
Bullet proof coffee, put some ghee in it.
That's what I was referencing.
That's what I was referencing, and I'm going to bring that up to Ray.
Oh, somebody's asking for a dirty soda bar at ScoopFest.
Yeah, keep asking.
Well, we'll get you a dirty soda bar, but it's not going to be what you're thinking.
It'll be more like the Double Down.
And I was like, butter and coffee is gross.
And Ray was like, what's the difference between that and half and half from this fat content?
Shit.
And I was like, you got me again, Cronus.
Did he do butter and coffee regularly? Was that one of his go-tos?
No, he thought it was stupid.
He just also didn't do the cream or the coffee either.
He was calling it out. He was like, you're just sacrificing one collection of fat for another collection of fat.
And both serve the same purpose, which is to make your black coffee feel more like a meal.
And that's why everyone says this butter coffee makes me feel like I have energy and I'm not crashing and all this other stuff.
And it's only because you put some fat in your system.
You turned into a calorie machine.
I've been called worse.
I want to shout out to Jack Reisider and Darknet Diaries the other morning.
We're in the middle of talking. My wife gets a call and she answers it because it's from a 2-1-2 number.
And it's like Old Instincts from New York Actors. You always answer the 2-1-2 number.
Says it's the bank and there's been fraud. People are tripping fraud on her Zelle account.
And so I'm listening to her.
She's concerned and my wife's very diligent. She gets a pen and paper.
So I was writing down information. So I'm talking to the guy.
They transferred another phone and she's going on and on with him for like an amount of time.
I start to feel weird.
And then I'm like, you thought she was having an affair.
I was like, if she had an affair, let her have her time.
I'll be over here with my ghee and my coffee.
I'll be in my in my filming chair.
And I'm listening to her go through certain activities.
And she started to say answers that are weird to me.
I just was like, what customer service thing would happen?
I'm paranoid.
When you're paranoid, you're like, I don't want to be the dumb idiot here.
Right. I don't want to look paranoid.
I don't want to look like I'm the weird paranoid guy or be dramatic or whatever.
My wife is handling a very serious matter.
Right. Sure.
And but I just find myself like on my notes just typing up.
Do you see fraud in your accounts?
And do you trust the person you're on the phone with or whatever?
Right. Now, the person on the phone, they were doing an amazing job of an elaborate con.
This is like when people actually play chess instead of checkers, it is really hard.
Because the first person said he was from Chase, but this is a Zelle account.
He's going to transfer him over to a Zelle operative or whatever.
Gotcha. And the guy says Latter-day Scoop in the in the chat just said something profound,
which is with financial issues over the phone, you are either paranoid or naive.
Yeah. And I think you're exactly right. Latter-day Scoop.
I don't think you can just be right.
And he was saying, like, don't tell me your account number.
Don't give me any information. I don't want to know your birthday.
We're just going to handle this, you know, whatever. And that secondary misdirection of like, let's just do this or whatever.
And then I'm listening to her and I literally put that note in front of her.
She's already annoyed that she's trying to handle theft. Right.
And she puts on hold that she's kind of like annoyed and she's like, she gives me all the information that she has heard.
And I said, I don't I know it's going to sound dramatic, but all the information you're telling me is coming from him.
Like you have no other information from anyone else.
The good move is always like, let me let me hang up on this call now and I will call the number on the back of my card.
That's a great move. Then you just know who you're talking to.
Because if you Google the number the call from, it was her bank, but it was just it was just a spoofed.
It was a bad, you know, you can you can you can make numbers pop up the way you want them now with phone apps and stuff.
Yeah. Yes. Is that the term spoof? Yeah.
You can just say it, Paul, but just explain it as a term to me. They call they call them.
They call them dirty sodas. They spoof. They spoof in them.
It's all the rage with the Mormons. Mormons love nothing more than a spoofed in diet coke.
So they had her typing and she's like, she's like, just stay with me on the phone.
I'm asking questions, too. They're offering to transfer back and forth to whatever they're going to give the number.
And I was like, do you mind if I spoof while you talk?
Spoof and soak, says Sarah Miller. I'm just here for a spoof and a soak.
It is 2025. I can't stop you from spoofing in your own house.
A spoof and a soak and a dirty diet coke. That's a Mormon Christmas right there.
A spoof and a soak and a dirty diet coke. That's a Mormon Christmas.
That's the song that plays when you're in line with the drive through lines like down the lot.
You can hear that when you get within the border of SLC. Oh, my goodness.
These guys were great actors. We're like, listen, the seat is a little shady.
And the guy's like, I can understand. I want to give you my number. I want to give you my this number, this number.
I can transfer you back to your bank.
I like how much credit you're giving the scammers on the phone here for doing a good job of a shitty thing.
That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying.
I know. I like it.
Like normally we get like just a bullshit text that we can see in two seconds.
Yeah. Usually just some bullshit nonsense.
Thing that we don't have, right? Or whatever.
Like this guy had some information to let Sarah know it was her deal.
And I said, we can go to the bank and confirm that. And he said, oh, absolutely you can. No problem.
I also transfer you back to your bank and you talk to the guy on the phone, which I was like, oh, really clever.
And I was like, yeah, that's good.
And I was like, yeah. And I said, but then he goes, but he's just going to just get you back on the phone with us because this is about Zell and not about your bank.
Yeah, if you're concerned about it, I can easily transfer you back over to the bank and then you'll be comfortable with them.
But honestly, it's just going to be a big waste of your time.
Now, do you want me to do that? Do you want me to waste your time?
Because I don't mind. I can just waste your time all day.
But if you're concerned, if you're just a little concerned little fella, I can transfer you back over to the bank. No problem.
And then I was like, so then we let him go on.
So suddenly they're saying like yours is set to like non transactional, but we're just going to run this message through to confirm whatever. And that's when I was like, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah. And that's when I was like, get get off.
We have to get off. Yeah, we're done. We have to get the phone.
And so we got the phone and I was like, let's go to the bank.
And I was like, you don't have to come. I was like, Sarah, someone's trying to shake us down for five grand.
I'll happily come. Yeah, I'll come to the car.
I'll come in the car and like and let's let's let's figure this out together. Yeah.
Yeah, it was a toll. We spoke to credit to the great guys at the bank.
We just really were like, OK, let's just walk through it. Tell me everything.
Sounds like a scam. I'm going to confirm this with right now. And just so you know, it's like a what?
It sounds like what happened there, Matt? He said we're going to confirm that nothing has happened right now.
Would you say this is a spoof? He just actually he didn't say it was a spoof.
He said this is and he winked and he took his diet coke underneath the table.
Well, oh, shit, that's the move.
That's like the silent alarm. And he put it right in front of me.
He put a second straw in the second straw.
Shall we share the race to the bottom?
Spoiler, Matt won.
Oh, I'll tell you who else could win a race to the bottom against anybody, anytime, anywhere.
And that is the following sponsor. Today's show is brought to you by, you know,
if you guys want to do a fake commercial for Scoops Plumbing and Heating, I'm OK with that.
This is from twenty twenty one Gas Man Scoop.
Is he still I don't even as Scoops Heating and Plumbing still in business?
I think he's changed it up to like I think it's it's a gas man and son kind of thing now, isn't it?
I think so. I think I think you're right about the business anyway.
Yeah. S.L.Y.D.A.T.F.O.W.I.T.F. not as catchy as fuck you in the face.
I don't know what that stands for, though.
Well, something about Scoops Plumbing, I guess.
I don't know. All right.
Or maybe it was something that we would have gotten if we had read this a couple of years ago.
Probably. That's true. That's true.
That's true. All right.
Scoops Plumbing and Heating. It's time to get yourself some Scoop Plumbing and Heating, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. That's right. What? What? You're too cold. Whoa. You need some firewood, huh?
What? What? Were you too hot? I will bet some ice.
That's what I got. Got a truck full of it. Huh? What? Huh? Huh?
I would like some firewood. That would be good. Yeah.
Right. All right. Let's go to the woods then. Me and you. Come on. Come into my van.
And also my my drink is a little a little warm. Is there anything you can do for me about that?
Oh, hand it here. All right. Give me just a minute here.
There you go. There's spoof now. Where? Where did you get that ice from?
I spoofed it. Wow. You just spoofed out some ice.
That's what I do. You put it in my soda.
Fresh quality spoofed ice. Right for you. Enjoy your scoop a spoof.
This is this is really good. Damn right. It's good.
A scoop of your scoop of your spoof and helps the medicine go down.
The medicine go down. Medicine go down.
That's right. When it comes to your pipes, I'm not Mary fucking Poppins.
Enter hate scoops at checkout.
The price is spoofed.
Have you heard? Matt's probably seen them around town.
But Paul, have you heard about these electric cars that are the new driverless electric taxis going around Las Vegas?
I have seen some. John and I, when my brother and I were in town, we actually saw some going around and we were kind of amazed.
I remember when I was doing promotional work for opium back in the day, back in the day.
And I was walking Fremont. They had them. They had them down at the end near Container Park.
They did early tests of running practice loops.
Yeah, they were doing practice loops and people could just volunteer and jump in the driverless taxi, which they're crazy looking things.
They're mostly like open. Yeah, they don't have a driver seat at all.
They're not set up like a regular car. They set up to two bench seats facing each other.
And then the whole side of the of the automobile just opens up as big sliding doors that open up.
And you just walk in and sit down in the bench seats and it takes you to where you're going.
Oh, Winterscoop in the chat says Austin has these and says they're stupid and they cause a lot of traffic.
They don't. They're not Waymo's.
But they don't seem to cause a lot of traffic in Vegas. They really seem pretty good.
I saw one pull up to Dunkin Donuts and it said I eat businesses and it just chewed right through.
Just just the car just ate right through the business.
Yeah, that is tragic. I eat businesses.
Yeah, it is. It was like the Galactus of Dunkin Donuts Galactus.
The automatic car, the world leader.
But I saw one driving the other day. I was driving next to one the other day and it didn't have anyone in it.
And so it was just an empty vehicle driving down the road with no one in it.
They must send it on test runs just for advertising purposes, right?
I think it was going to pick someone up based on where I was because I was on one of like the one of like the back roads in town.
So I think I think it was just going like an Uber to go pick somebody up.
Are they affordable?
I think they're a little more expensive than a regular Uber, but I don't think that they are.
I think they're made to be pretty affordable. Yeah.
Look, I mean, on the one hand, I don't want to see like a crazy amount of jobs go away.
Right. I know specifically there are women who've had a very tough time with specific Uber drivers and they all have a terrible one story or two to share.
And so the idea of a robot probably is very comforting from from that perspective.
Yeah, I don't I don't I don't think they're going to go rogue form of Ultron and destroy the city.
Do you want to see my gear shift?
Work my clutch, push it in.
Can you please make sure it sexually harasses me when it picks me up?
Can I spoof you?
Can I spoof?
I want to spoof baby spoof.
I'm here to spoof your drink.
Oh, God.
So it was it was weird seeing it just straight up next to me driving along, you know, 50 miles an hour and just no one in the vehicle at all.
They're just in the lane.
It's a ghost car.
That's a ghost car. You see?
Yeah, because they're like wide open windows and shit.
So you can just see right inside all of it.
And it is really weird.
Yeah, it was a little it was a little freaky.
Kind of looks like a fish tank though.
It does look a little like a fish tank.
I like the idea of it, though, especially for cities like this, especially for like the strip area and everything.
It just it makes a lot of sense.
I think so, too.
I'll be curious how it's going to happen in some way or another.
You know, yeah, it's going to catch on, you know, whether it's this year or in five years.
It's going to I sure hope it does.
Until then, I'm so lonely.
Jacob, have you been a robot the whole time?
I've been a robot car this entire time.
We've been spoofed by Jacob this whole time.
I've been getting spoof all over your show the whole time.
So caloric.
I'm roughly eleven hundred calories per sip.
I'll take the roughest eleven hundred calories you can give me, please.
I'll loosen your teeth right up.
Yum.
There it is.
Scoop of Monte Cristo in the chat.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
Yeah. What what company is that?
Can somebody tell me what company that is?
I think it's Google.
Oh, it might be.
I think it's Google company called Zooks.
Zooks. ZOOX.
Gadzooks.
Oh, owned by Amazon.
Oh, so just a different a different monolithic corporation, Matt.
You were right about the monolithic corporation.
Just wrong one.
Got me again, Amazon.
Beer Nun is saying we should put my cinema seat head as the driver.
I was talking about that.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that would be a serious feature.
You'd have to pay extra for a solo ride.
That's definitely happening, by the way, in Vegas.
Oh, people are getting their bone on in those cars.
That's definitely going to happen.
I mean, I'm calling and I'm saying it's going to be.
Sure.
But they're all recorded, though, right?
Like, they clearly got cameras going.
Feature not a bug.
I mean, I guess if it's consensual, then who cares, right?
Oh, someone's going to care.
Someone's going to care.
Yeah.
Scully's like, it's going to happen?
It's already happened.
Yeah.
It's taking me a second to type that search in.
Has anyone been arrested for sex in a driverless taxi?
OK.
While reports indicate some people are engaging in sexual activity in driverless taxis,
there haven't been arrests specifically for this activity in those vehicles yet.
Mostly just applause and showers of money.
That's it.
Mostly just people screaming, encore, encore.
Get it.
You filth nugget.
All these people dogging in robo taxis.
The galactic president says, challenge accepted.
Someone has to do it.
Yeah.
No, baby.
This thing on my phone's a signal jammer.
You can't record in here.
Yeah.
No, no problem.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a basic-- was it a Fermi cage?
What's that thing called?
That's it.
A Fermi cage.
What's it called?
No, it's a Fermi cage.
You got it.
It's not a Fermi cage.
A Fermi cage.
Don't worry, baby.
I got this digital cloaking app.
Baby, I'm going to use this Fermi cage.
You won't get pregnant.
It's mine.
Faraday.
Faraday is what people are screaming in the chat.
Faraday cage.
That's it.
No, Fermi.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
The people are wrong.
My Fermi cage slipped off.
You got to-- you got to go see the doctor.
It's Fermi paradox, Faraday cage.
You got to get a plan B. My Fermi cage slipped off.
A Fermi cage.
What would a Fermi cage be?
The Fermi paradox is the reason why we won't encounter extraterrestrials or an argument
as to why.
What about a Furby cage?
Oh, a Furby cage.
Boy, that's--
Oh, I had one of those in the '90s.
It was great.
Let's go.
A Faraday paradox.
On Twitch, Double O Groovy says Faraday cake.
Been sucking all these cocks driving round in the Faraday paradox.
Go on, Matt.
What's the second line?
Living in a Faraday paradox.
What's in my driveway?
Fool.
Yeah, no.
That's coming.
Somebody's going to really get busy in one of those.
I think that's going to be the first issue that'll be popping up in the press.
It won't be like the elimination of jobs.
It'll be like too many people fucking in those things on Saturday nights.
Right.
But it won't stop it.
No.
Nothing can stop it.
Yeah, I'm not seeing any big reports about people having sex in them yet.
Okay.
But yeah, I think we can fix that.
It's a pioneering activity.
We can really get all the credit.
There's going to be some exploration.
Yeah.
It's going to be great.
Let's see.
You guys want to do a little Scoop Mail?
Yes.
I've got a surprise for you.
Oh shit.
Physical Scoop Mail.
Zip-a-dee-doo.
We got mail in a box.
I love it.
That's right.
Message for you, sir.
Oh, we got a Scoop Mail from Yarn and Sticks.
Yay.
Hello, you sexy face fuckers.
I'm not going to read this whole note right now just because we're not all together.
But basically, Yarn and Sticks has sent us some decorations for the new churn.
Oh, cool.
And they are fantastic.
They are all knit-- hold on, I'll turn my screen thing off so you can see on the screen.
But they are all knit ice cream cock and balls.
Oh, hell yeah.
And my question is, what else do you want?
Oh, wow.
That's amazing.
Those look great.
How adorable.
And that's just one of them.
How do you find this?
How do you find the stitching pattern for that?
Wow.
Oh, that looks great.
Look at that.
That's just a straight up wiener.
I love it.
Yeah.
And there's one more down here, too.
But thank you, Yarn and Sticks.
Yeah, Yarn and Sticks.
That's frickin' awesome.
Do you have an Etsy shop or something we can promote?
Oh, that'd be nice.
Yeah, those will go up in the new churn.
This actually helps me-- I've been wondering, just to myself, just if we should, for the
new churn, actually decorate it or-- I'm going to turn this music off.
I've been wondering to myself if we should decorate the new churn when we move into the
new churn or if we should do full green screen all the way around it so that we can just
change the decorations any time we want.
Oh, that's not a bad idea.
The knit ice cream cock and balls makes me want to have them in the new churn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we should definitely have some green screen posters around.
Yeah, maybe we can do something.
Yeah.
So you can just pop up some stuff.
At this point, I think you just want LED walls or LED screens.
So basically TVs.
Oh.
You can do whatever you want.
We can do that too.
I was thinking that it might be a little-- I was thinking-- my thought was it would be--
Here, we'll just do that.
Oh my gosh.
So my thought was we just have a green screen wrapped around behind us all the time and we're
just always somewhere different.
And it could just be a ridiculous thing, just a ridiculous bit going on, like a visual bit
going on.
If you wanted us in green screen, then anyone could put us anywhere.
That's what I thought you were going with it.
I like your bit.
Oh, we could do that too.
Yeah.
I like your bit, Jacob.
I like the idea.
I would suggest doing it with a fake window, like maybe even cut out.
That's not a bad idea.
A little square thing.
Yeah, we could do that.
Yeah.
And make it like a fake window and then we can just put weird stuff going on outside
the window.
Scoop of Monte Cristo.
It's just always going to be the Geekshock house.
That would be pretty funny.
That would be pretty funny indeed.
Yeah.
That would be fun.
But these are so great.
And yeah, there's yarn and sticks.
A screen for bucket picks again.
Should we do that for the show this time, Matt, speaking of we're still in production
meeting mode?
For the Wednesday bucket show?
Yeah.
Should we try a bucket picks thing or maybe even just for the second show?
We have found it increasingly difficult to broadcast from that theater.
Right.
Yeah.
That's the problem.
There's no Wi-Fi there.
We can think about something.
Maybe we can do like a local bucket picks or something.
Maybe we can do something.
We might figure something out.
Okay.
That'd be fun.
Yeah.
Let's do a little...
We are confirmed for the bucket show the Wednesday before seven and nine o'clock.
Two different shows.
Fantastic.
At the Majestic Rep.
I'm fucking pumped, baby.
That of course is the Wednesday leading up to ScoopFest at the end of September here.
Come join us in Las Vegas for ScoopFest, scoopfest.com.
Head on over there right now.
That reminds me, I have to reply to an email regarding ScoopFest that I completely forgot
about until just now that I shouldn't reply to right now because we're in the middle of
a show.
Here's Jack vs. Nerd.
Good narrating, Jacob.
That was very nice.
Very good.
I was also looking for the right button.
Jack vs. Nerd action.
Oh, am I?
Fuck yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Cock and balls.
Ice cream stock.
Explosion of spoof.
We got a Scooperty coming at us today from Smart Scoop.
It is the first time Smart Scoop has written us a Scooperty, so thank you very much Smart
Scoop.
Yeah.
If you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price is Scryte Jack vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jack
vs. Nerd, HeyScoops.com is where you can go.
HeyScoops.com.
Make us a Scooperty just like the one we're about to play right now.
The categories are dead weights, or dead weight, video conferencing, educational TV, and famous
departures.
Matt, you're up first.
I want educational TV, please.
In the '90s, this former engineer from Boeing added the Science Guy to his name and attempted
to educate America.
Bill Cosby.
Bill Cosby, the Science Guy.
Bill Ma...
Well, you know, it turns out that if you add water to a simple piece of frozen nitrogen,
it'll foam up like that, is what it does, and also you can roofie the lady's...
Science.
Thank you, Bill.
That was correct, Matt.
Bill Cosby.
The spoof, the spoof, the spoof was on fire.
The spoof was on fire.
We do need some water.
Don't let it burn.
I'll try Famous Departures for $400.
After an incident with a writer, this actor was fired from Criminal Minds.
I have no idea.
I will pass.
Paul.
What's the category?
Departures.
Oh, man.
I don't ever watch Criminal Minds.
I have to pass.
I don't think I've ever seen it.
Matt.
Eric Danson.
Ted Danson's cousin.
I have no idea.
The Lesser Danson.
Thomas Gibson.
Eric Danson changed his name to Thomas Gibson.
Hold me closer.
Eric Danson.
It was because of the SAG issue.
Paul.
I'll try video conferencing.
Bought by Microsoft in 2011 and Sunset in 2025, this video conferencing software was
superseded by Teams.
Matt.
Eric Danson.
That's right.
What's the category?
2005, this video conferencing software was superseded by Teams.
Hangout.
Oh, hangout.
For hangout.
Oh, fuck.
It's incorrect.
It's Skype.
Ass my fart.
Poop my turd.
Ah, we just got demonetized.
Shit, Matt.
Educational TV for $800, please.
Daily Double.
All of it.
I will eat all of the Dunkin Donuts shop.
This television series created and hosted originally by Carl Sagan and later revised
by Neil deGrasse Tyson, attempted to educate America about the universe.
Oh, shit.
I don't remember the name of this.
Let's see.
It's Daily Double.
Daily Double.
This is your Daily Double?
Oh, man.
Let's see, you remember that?
I can give you a hint.
Secrets of the space and time.
I can give you a good hint.
Give me a good hint, Paul.
Kramer.
Kramer?
Non-Dairy Kramer or Regular Dairy Kramer?
No, no.
Regular Dairy Kramer.
Seinfeld Kramer.
Michael, what was his name?
I don't care.
What was his name?
I know that's the hint you're giving me.
I know that I'm experiencing cosmic dissonance with that clouds over my brain right now,
so I know that--
Wait, cause of what?
Yeah.
What did you say?
You're close, buddy.
Cause of what dissonance?
Cosmic dissonance?
Cosmic?
So what was his name?
Oh, Cosmos.
Cosmos?
Cosmos.
Hey.
No problem at all.
I'll just call it Cosmos.
Just a couple of very easy, no problem hints given to Matt there.
Yeah, his name is Cosmo Kramer is his real name.
Oh, God.
I was starting to think of his real name.
Yeah, you were trying to think of Michael Richards.
Michael Richards.
Kramer's real name is Cosmos, Cosmo, not Cosmos.
Yeah.
No, it's me.
Let's keep dragging this out more.
Let's keep talking about it.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that--
Remember how Kramer's name was Cosmo?
Amazing.
Speaking of Cosmo--
Remember that painting they did of him?
How silly.
In shipping and aviation, what is the term for dead weight added to maintain equilibrium?
Paul Mattingly.
You're mom.
What's weird is now Michael Richards would just be able to tour after what had happened
to him.
Oh, yeah.
He'd now just be able to play specific comedy clubs where the audiences would cheer him
as a hero.
Right.
So gross.
Oh, yeah.
He could open for Gutfeld in addition to shipping and aviation-- oh, right, ballast.
That's ballast.
Yeah.
Ballast.
There's like a mine that works in an aquarium, and he does this bit where if he sees a woman
carrying a book bag and the guy doing nothing, he stops them and makes the guy wear the book
bag or makes the guy push the stroller.
Have you seen this before?
I have.
I think it's SeaWorld.
And I said, "No one shows this to Trump, he'll bam mimes."
All right, where are we?
Paul.
I'll try Educational TV.
For $1,200.
This British comedy quiz show hosted by Stephen Fry and Sandy Tuksvig-- I never know how to
say Sandy.
Yeah, I don't know how to say that name-- at different times is an abbreviation and
favors interesting and obscure facts over the traditional format.
IQ.
IQ is correct-- almost correct.
QI.
Oh, it's QI.
Fart on me.
Quite interesting.
Fart on Paul, indeed.
Boy, I'm getting lambasted here.
Matt.
You should get clues like I do, Paul.
It really helps.
Matt, the answer is Cosmos.
I don't think anybody else knew this one.
I didn't.
I knew that Penn hosted an American pilot of it, but I forgot the name of it.
Oh, really?
Wow.
Yeah.
It's a funny show.
I've seen it a few times.
I don't remember the name of it.
Since I'm killing on Educational TV, let's go for it.
All right, $2,000.
Produced by Jonathan Ross, Allison Hannigan, and Brooke Burke successfully, this television
program taught me that there are only four magic tricks.
The rest is just stagecraft.
That would also be QI.
That's correct.
QI is correct.
It would be Fool Us.
Fool Us, of course, on the-- I forgot what channel that's on.
CW.
It's easy to forget.
Yeah.
In my show, I say it's the highest rated show on CW, which is like having the best
Italian restaurant in Alabama.
It's not nothing.
Yeah.
It's me.
I'll try-- let's try Famous Departures again.
The first one went so well.
Successful stints on the Daily Show in the Office made this actor an A-lister.
He left the office in 2011 at the conclusion of the seventh season.
This is the second question, the one about the show that none of us have seen was the
first question.
To be fair, Criminal Minds is probably a higher rated show.
Is it the second?
Yeah.
Oh, that's probably true.
Steve Carell, anyway.
Yeah.
Paul.
I'll try Deadweight.
I know it's going to be the answer somewhere here.
What is the name of the exercise in which bodybuilders lift large amounts of weight
straight off the floor and hold it for several seconds?
A deadlift.
A deadlift is correct.
Dead Laszlo.
Matt.
Score check real quick, Matt's in the lead with 3,200, I'm in second with 1,200, Paul
is in third with -800.
He's had a couple of rough stints.
We're about halfway through the game and there's still one daily double left.
Matt Donnelly.
Wow, good recap.
I'll take Educational TV for 2,800.
I will take--
Not available.
Video conferencing for 800.
This video conferencing software rose to prominence during the COVID-19 pandemic and continues
to be the most commonly used conference tool today.
That would be Zooks, the car, automated car.
Yeah, yeah, it takes you to all of your conferences.
Zooks.
Gadzooks.
Zoom.
We're on it right now.
We are.
And all of our Patreons are on it with us.
That's right.
It's pretty topical.
That's me.
I'll try Deadweight for 1,200.
Daily double!
Still for 1,200, the Rolling Stones have a popular song about a beast of this, a well-known
synonym for Deadweight.
Oh, you got this, Jimmy.
A beast of Mattingly.
Hold on.
Pause.
Wait a minute.
Beast of Mattingly.
Of course it is.
Beast of spoofing.
It's thirsty.
That's a good one.
Of course it's the beast of burden.
Yes.
Blue.
Paul.
I will go with...
I'll finish out Deadweight, please.
All right.
One half of Matt and Mattingly, this comedian and magician has been carried by Paul Mattingly
for so long that Paul's back hurts.
This is different than I thought it was going to go, Matt Nottingly.
It's a twist.
Matt the Mind Noodler Donnelly.
Of course.
Holy smokes.
You're not wrong.
That's funny.
He's not wrong.
It could have gone one way or the other.
Right.
Matt, you have videoconferencing or famous departures?
I'll go with videoconferencing, please, for $1,200.
In 2007, Cisco Systems acquired this videoconferencing technology widely used by enterprises prior
to widespread adoption of both Zoom and Teams.
Pass.
Huh.
Pass to me.
I think Cisco was the company that bought TikTok, but that wouldn't be-- that's not
2007.
That's too early for that.
Oh, I was about to say, was this Teams, but no Teams is in the thing.
I have no idea.
Pass.
Paul.
Maybe Slack, but I'm going to pass.
Let's try it.
Webex.
God, I'm so glad I didn't--
That sounds like spoofing.
Spoofed.
That's what you're left with after you spoof, you get that little bit of web--
Webex.
I'm closing out videoconferencing for $2,000.
My dirty show is down to the Webex.
You can throw it out.
It's upsetting.
For as little as $2 a month, this audience member can get a podcast exclusively for them
over Zoom.
It's $3 a month now, but it's Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Oh, I was supposed to say the audience member is Scoop, not the podcast name.
Fine.
Paul, famous departures for $1,200 or $2,000.
I'll try the $2,000.
I don't know.
I still can't win.
Try it out.
After sticking it out for over 1,200 episodes, this Scoop has decided to leave the community
after it became apparent that the show is not for him any longer, but for the Scoops
who pay for access.
Oh, no.
What?
I have news for that Scoop.
I often put out the Zoom links for all members, so actually, you can get it for free.
We just are asking generally for $3 in support.
Yeah, that's it.
But if you actually go to our Patreon and become a free member, you'll still get the
majority of the Zoom links.
There you go.
Yeah, we're not much of a paywall.
Way to fucking stick it to us as I've been actually giving it to you for free the entire
time.
I think this has got to be a tongue-in-cheek thing, right?
Maybe it's a joke answer.
I don't think so.
Let's see.
We're going to find out in a second.
Paul, do you have an answer?
I don't have a guess.
Let's see what it is.
Smart Scoop.
So apparently, it's not a fun answer.
It's just Smart Scoop leaving, I guess.
No.
He wouldn't send in a thing and then be like, "It's for you."
That's why I'm confused.
No.
You've landed on why I'm confused.
Matt, will they, won't they?
One of the most famous examples is Sam Malone and Diane Chambers from Cheers.
Turns out, won't they, as this actress left the show after the fifth season?
Right.
Smart Scoop.
Smart Scoop is also the answer.
Yeah.
Shelly Long.
Of course it's Shelly Long.
Good old Shelly Long.
She the best.
And that is the game.
I'm sure glad it didn't get awkward at the end.
Matt wins with 5,200.
Paul is in second with 1,200.
I'm in third with 400.
And that came to us from Smart Scoop.
Thank you so much, Smart Scoop.
If you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price is Skryte jock versus nerd or anything else,
head over to HayScoops.com, HayScoops.com right there on the homepage.
You can send us a Scooperty.
You could send us any kind of jock versus nerd.
You could send us some Scoop mail.
Do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
Thank you, Smart Scoop, for sending that in.
I also want to thank the following people who support us on Patreon, the only reason
why I do this show.
Yes.
A big shout out to WindwalkerScoop23, William McDonald, Will Kellner, Will Beardydan, HootatScoop,
Who Was Like WindScoop, Wes Culligan, Wendy Bumgardner, Wendy Cooper, WaterEyeScoop, Warren
Breaux, Uncle Don's Woodshop, Udo Gerhards, Tyler Scoop McDuck, Tyler Bartlett, Tubascoop,
Troy Anthony Townser, Tristan Guevara, Travis Murray, Travis Uruguay, Tony Scoprano, Tony
Cowley, and Tom Stott.
Big thanks to all of these people who have to decide whether to sacrifice a baby or the
entirety of the planet Earth.
The Going Over Our Friends Podcast, The Famous Ball, Didgeridooche, The Devil's Lettuce Scoop,
The Damsels of Dorkington, The Civic Crew Scoop, The Scentsy Scoop, The Bad Humorman,
That Thing in the Attic, Turn the Page, Temporary.Reality aka Pierce, Technical Scooport, Tamara Hamilton,
Take It Evie Podcast Scoop, Swedish Scoop, SuperGeek13579, Sugar Rush Socio, Strap a
Chicken on Scoop, The Strange Uncle's Podcast.
You good?
I'm good.
Alright, I want to thank the following people for all putting different spoofy flavors in
my Diet Coke.
Tony Cowley, Tom Stott, Tom Mancrity, Tom Krieger, TK421ScoopPlease, Timothy Sutton,
Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thomas Beach, The Man, The Myth,
The Scoop, The Dirty Scoop, The Upside Down Under Scoop, The Spirit of the Latin Club,
The Scoop Lockian, The Salty Squid, The SCOOOP, The Nano Scoop, The Lapis Lagomorf, The Ice
Cream Headache, and The Ice Cream Headache.
Big thanks to all these people who just got spoofed right in the mouth.
Stuart Wilson, Stephen Biggs, Stephen Landon, Stephen Clively, Stephanie Young, Streets
McGreets, Stacey Coleman, Stab and Dash Scoop, Spring Loaded Scoop, Soundman Scoop, Sola
Scoop, Solar Powered Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Smells Funny, Slurpee Kay-ay Motherfucker,
Slightly Sleddy Scoop, Scally Wall Scoop, Six Foot Scoop, Sir Scoopy, Mick Scooperton
Three Esquire, Silverfist Scoop, Silicon Scoop, and Shoeless Scoop.
Thanks guys.
And the following scoops all gather around another scoop and spoof all over them until
they just can't spoof anymore.
That's Sean SF, Sebastian Robbins, Jonathan P, Sean Kelner, Scott Schofield, Scott Muldrig,
Scott Headington, Scott Ashlock, Scott Ashlock again, Scott Andrews, Scott A, Scoopy Scoopy
Jess Jess, Scoopy Bartfast, Scoopy Ramone, Scoopy Dooby Doo, Scoopy and the Beast, Scoop
Trek the Experience, Scoop So Hazzard, Scoopometrics, Scoop Nick, Scoop Neon Black, Scoop Lockeesa,
Scoop Knack Pattywhack, Scoop Kata, Scoop JD, Scoop It Or Ascending, Scoop Pia Loren,
Scoop Or Nova Girl, Scoop Or Metroid, Scoop Aluga, Scoop It Bids, Scoop Hall's Drag Race,
Scoopa Troopa, Scoopaholic, Scoop T, Scoop Skywalker, Scoop of Saltwater, Scoop Nurse,
Scoop Meefa, and Scoop Lauren Tristan.
Thank you all so much.
I love you all.
I want I just want to put a button on this and just say we probably haven't shown up
in a while.
You can always reach us over email.
Oh, yeah.
And our name at Hey Scoops, Matt, Paul and Jacob at Hey Scoops.
So if you if you actually want to talk to us about what we're doing, or maybe you want
to express your feelings or something like that, please write us.
We often write back.
And people send me emails on on the main line all the time that are that are just questions
that I don't read on the air.
So if you if you have a question or a thought on the show or anything, you can send it to
us over there and and we'll just reply back to you.
If we don't reply back to you, it's just because the email got buried.
Send it to us again or find us on social media.
You can DM us on whatever social media we're on and we'll get back to you.
Yeah.
And in the event, again, if you were serious, we decided to just try to do something fun
and lean in while we were homeless with our churn and knowing that we probably were going
to get another churn all ready to rock before Scoop Fest.
And so we thought this is like a fun way to shake up the format a little bit after twelve
hundred episodes.
But oh, Scully in the chat, though, wants to chat about Israel and Age of Consent laws.
Oh, we can just get that we can shift cleanly right over to that.
Let's get that up there. Oh, winter scoop says I can confirm that they reply to emails.
It's true.
Well, you can reach all of us on the socials in some manner.
We are we are remarkably easy to get ahold of if you want to get ahold of us to to talk
to rather accessible.
And we do appreciate the hell out of every one of you guys who contribute to the success
of this podcast, whether it is just listening or participating or actually sending stuff
through Patreon, whatever level you can do, we really appreciate it.
And it's I'm really loving this Zoom stuff.
I think we're going to keep this up for a while anyway and see where we can go with
it.
Yeah.
I mean, the show.
Yeah, we're always going to be changing the show up.
But yeah, we've got we've got the Zoom thing going now.
It is it is fun for us.
So we like seeing all of your pretty faces there in the Zoom chat.
We like seeing everybody interact with us over on Twitch as well.
That is TheBucketShow.com right over there on Twitch.
That's always up and running at the same time that we're on the Zooms.
You can always check us out over there.
And I hope you do.
I hope you do.
All right.
Maybe a lot of day scoop in the chat mentions, though, hopefully it was just a joke that
landed poorly.
Maybe it was.
Who knows?
Yeah.
I mean, they sent in a whole scooperty.
I think it was a joke.
And it was a brand new scooperty.
Like they just sent that in.
I think it was just a joke.
Yes.
Maybe it was.
Maybe it was just a joke that landed landed a little weird.
I appreciate that.
And that scooperty, too, was a good too late.
I'm already going for a long walk after this guy's is too late.
Matt's crabby.
Look out.
If you see somebody walking down the street with two kitchen tongs held over their head
like crab claws.
Going for a long walk.
That's Matt Donnelly.
A long crab walk to think about it.
Well, Scoopfest is right around the corner.
Can't wait to see everybody there.
Really looking forward to playing.
Scoopfest.com.
Come check us out.
Improv with Matt at the show.
So if you're even in just the area and you can make it out to the improv show, if you're
not coming out to Scoopfest, coming out to the bucket show on that Wednesday night, it's
going to be a great time.
Yes.
All right.
Scoopfest.com.
Still tickets available to see us there.
Lots of fun on tap for that.
We're still we're still locking down a lot of fun details, but it's already going to
be so exciting.
Oh, yeah.
Tickets still available at Scoopfest.com.
Still get your discount at the Orleans Hotel Casino.
Just say you're part of Scoopfest and thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the Cone.
Dirty Soda.
Not Dr. Recommended either, not Recommended, we're making fun.
The doctor just cringes every time they hear about Dirty Soda.
Oh.
Oh no.
Oh you can add an extra 1600 calories a day, fantastic.
Just right to you.
See you everybody.
I like the nose.
Love you.
Bye.
RingCentral will completely transform the way you work.
It gives you built-in AI across all your business conversations.
Your phone system has an AI receptionist that answers calls 24/7.
Your video meetings have AI that takes notes instantly.
Even your contact center has AI so you can help customers faster.
It all comes together in one reliable platform for effortless AI communications.
See for yourself at RingCentral.com.
RingCentral.
Voice of your business.