Oh hello there I am so happy you're here because I want to thank the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers it's a new month we don't have a new list yet happy here come the Hawks get your tickets today and get in on the excitement that is filling the United Center visit Blackhawks.com/tickets before it's too late
December by the way but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver at this part of a future show I met the lost ice cream truck driver last night she came to the show and introduced herself to me personally I was so happy to meet an ice cream truck driver if you want to meet an ice cream truck driver if you want to be an ice cream truck driver if you want to meet one it's easier but if you want to be one preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save may be your own.
Look out it's a show hey Johnny you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go.
Mike Jones is here the jazz demon I am.
The star for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social sitting in Pittsburgh PA that's Paul Mattingly sitting at sea it's Matt Donnelly in Las Vegas it's me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun.
Greetings from the ocean. Yes.
Mike do people still call you the jazz demon and when did first people start calling you that.
As a as a small child no it was on my second birthday it was a rainy evening it was after the second conviction for arson.
No I of course that was I believe that was Zeke Zabrosky from the Penn and Teller show back when he was a young child.
He started calling me the jazz demon very early on in in my career with Penn and Teller and Penn latched on to it and still use it every night in the show.
And I have a jazz demon license plate so I can't get rid of it now oh yeah you're stuck with it now although it's more it's more horrific than that because you can only use how many whatever seven letters so I decided to use Jay ZZ DMN because I thought
Jay ZZ DMN might be a different connotation on a B. So I went with jazz demon but then I get these people say jazz demand what does that mean and you know and so I just I just ignore people.
Do people stop you and talk to you about your license plate all the time I feel like this is something that happens in Las Vegas as people discuss other people's license plates.
Yeah, it's happened more than once, which is one time too many. No, it's no it's it's fine. It bothers me when I come up behind people and I can't figure out what their plate supposed to mean.
But it always means just on my penis that's that's what it means.
Yeah, exactly. Um, a, but it's it's been oh yeah it's been 25 years. I don't use it myself. You know, hey, how you doing on the jazz.
Anyway, however, I, I'm not offended when when others refer to me as that but it's yeah it's been it's been, but ZZ came up with that because you know, metal, right, I guess.
More metal is better.
He keeps wanting me to start the piano on fire and play, you know, a lot of metal music, but I won't do it great balls of fire.
He's, you know, he wants like, I don't know, Megadeth. He wants some Megadeth covers with the piano burning.
I think that'd be a fun, a fun new addition to the pre show at Penn and Teller. Don't, don't give them any ideas.
Have you ever played any kind of stunt piano for any any kind of gig. I have not.
Absolutely. Um, I, I mean, in my youth, I would do my Jerry Lee Lewis impersonation and you know hit the piano with my feet and stuff like that. But, no, I, you know, I try to respect the instrument.
It's when I would when I would play in in in in like lounges and some asshole would set his drink on the piano right in front of me while I'm playing a song, I would scream it's not furniture asshole.
You know, you want to set your drink on somebody's violin. Really smart. Thanks. But, and that got me a lot of tips. No, that's why I was so successful.
Hey, could you play some Billy Joel? Why don't you fuck off?
Our piano player here is great. He takes requests, but only the requests he wants to take. Exactly.
Our musical director, Mike, at the Second City.
He, you know, they had a piano that was there on the stage all the time. And this is when we were sharing the stage with the ex burlesque dancers, so they would come in and do the show late night after we were done.
And there was one day we came in for rehearsal and there was an unmistakable coochie print right on the piano top that you just couldn't get away from.
And we all just spent the day kind of oogling it. Mike just kind of had to play around it.
You didn't clean it? No, we didn't clean it. It was, you didn't go get some fucking furniture spray.
Oh man, it's like Jesus is facing a piece of toast or something. You don't fuck with that shit.
You guys just kept taking turns blindfolding each other playing pin the clip on the pussy and you just kind of just move it around and see if you could.
Yeah, so there's definitely lots of respect for the instrument out here in Las Vegas.
Yeah, yeah. I had a bit of a reputation because many, many years ago, this is way before the Internet Times, there was a cartoon in the New Yorker that showed a guy playing like cocktail piano.
And the caption underneath was, "You people make me sick. Nevertheless, here's another toe tapper."
There it is. That's great.
I got like seven copies of that in the mail to me. Sure.
So I guess I had a reputation. Your friends know you, your friends know you.
Now, at this point, you've been with the Penn and Teller show for quite a while.
There have been many different iterations of the stage there.
Have you ever considered talking them into maybe having a Batman-like secret two key press that would then sink your piano into the stage or open up a secret window?
Yeah, Teller has been talking for years about wanting to make the piano float somehow over the stage.
And I think hopefully they've gotten that out of there, that's passed them by.
I'm hoping they'll age out of that idea.
I've been with them almost half their career now, 25 years almost.
I mean, it's great. I'm bad with time now, but several years ago, they surprised me with a Mike Jones corner on the right side of the stage with the neon sign and the Mike Jones duo.
But yeah, I'm happy with the piano. And also, just from a practical standpoint, you can't...
That is very practical. That's our sound effect for telling you to get the fuck out of here, Mike. Take the directions and go.
No, no, no. I gotta go? No, no, no. Technical issues on our side.
So yeah, you had the surprise of the reveal of the corner there dedicated to you.
Yeah, that was nice. But I don't think you really should move a piano often because...
I try not to. Yeah, well, they're heavy and also they go out of tune.
But I think the teller's idea may be more in line with having a car appear on stage, you know what I mean?
So I leave that up to them. But I'll play wherever they put me.
I've been doing these 50th anniversary gigs with them and it's been really fun.
And we were doing Boston a couple of weeks ago and Glenn said, what if we put you up in one of the boxes?
And I said, well, I'd sort of prefer to be on the stage.
And so they made it work. It was great. But, you know, there are shows, as you guys know, many, many shows now.
The orchestra is not in the same theater as the performance. They're in a basement somewhere.
Oh, yeah. You know, and it's I sort of draw the line there.
I'm disappointed when I find out that the orchestra is in a different space, like in a room next door.
Yeah, the first time I came across that was many years ago.
There was a puppet show, Avenue Q, I think it was, at the Wynn.
Yeah. And I went to it and they're like, and look out about the TV. There's our guys in a suite for, you know, four floors away.
And I was like, well, that's kind of a ripoff. And it was crazy, too, because in that room we had an orchestra pit.
We just didn't use it for Avenue Q. Too good for them. That's right. That's right.
That's weird. For Spamalot right after Avenue Q, we had like 28 orchestra members down in the in the orchestra pit right there.
I don't know why it didn't get used for Avenue Q. Yeah, they they name it an orchestra pit because there's an orchestra in it.
You know, you don't want to put you in a suite and keep you away from people.
You don't want to be in illusions with pianos. What illusions do you want to be a part of, Mike?
All of them. I'll do anything.
Can we get get in Georgie's Queen of Hearts dress for the for the one bit? Yeah, yeah. I you know, I it's funny.
Someone just asked me last night at the show, are you part of any of the tricks?
And I don't think there's there's never been a trick that I've been a part of except for doing all the music.
And I mean, and also the girl, the gorilla where I did the narration, which was actually fun,
which I had like a whole thing alive, alive, alive, you know, and on the inside, Zomofo, the gorilla girl.
And I did a whole carnival barking thing while I played like silent movie music.
But mostly, I mean, an air sax, I mean, we were I was in center stage for that with right.
But yeah, but I mean, they're not asking me to, you know, do any tricky shuffling or hey, let's, you know, come on up for this trick.
And let's let our piano player shuffle these cards.
I think you would have made a really great ball pit troll.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Exactly. I remember that. That was a bit that was done. Oh, what? Twice?
Twice, yeah. It was it was it was teed up. If you see it on the Foolish show, it's my son.
Yeah, I know. I was there. I was playing the ball pit troll music.
I'm also talking to the audience listening to our podcast. Oh, oh, oh, you have listeners.
At minimum, the ones that are here now. I'm working on that.
And we found that on the Internet in front of me at the end of the day.
And they're like, do they still do that bit? I was like, they never did that bit.
This was it. I was like, you are the only ball pit troll, buddy.
Yeah, I think that there's only I don't there's not many tricks,
not many bits that they've only done that limited amount of times,
except for stuff that they did, especially for for for television.
But I like specifically was done the year before covid.
So their ambition for it was to do it in the summertime where they got more families.
Right. Yeah, I remember actually going to recruit a kid each show before it happened.
And then covid happened. And then three seasons of Foolish happened.
So by the time the show came back, they weren't like, let's dust off that old chestnut.
Yeah, that's like, you know, and the crew loves it.
Cleaning all those balls and setting up the perimeter and getting a kid to do magic.
Yeah, I walked past about it. He's like, oh, I would love to have done it again.
And he is now like two feet taller than he was when he did it.
I was like, you can't do it again. Everybody get in the thing. Yeah.
You're out. You are out. It's over. Yeah, it's over.
That part of your life is done.
Well, I yeah, I walked by a couple of months ago.
I walked by Robbie Living like after after the end of Haystack and he's like, you know,
sweeping the hay up. And I said the glamour of showbiz, you know,
like he's, you know, picking up piles of hay and pulling cards out of it, you know.
But there's a lot. Tell us a story.
Tell us the story of Jessica Jane and I.
He was talking about they were working on Broadway.
He had like a boil on like the inside of his thigh or whatever.
And it was his costume is irritating him, especially after they did water tank or something.
So they had this flamboyant costumer on Broadway who basically had to help tell her pop the boil.
Oh, boy. Yeah.
And he said he just dressed up and wardrobe people on Broadway go above and beyond.
Above and beyond. Right.
And he said he just looked up a teller from down on his knees going, ah, showbiz, the tinsel and the glamour.
That's disgusting. Oh, yeah.
The glamour made me laugh so hard.
Well, Jonesy, you are a podcaster now.
I am a podcaster in conjunction with the great Jennifer Szabo.
She's actually running everything.
I but yeah, yeah, yeah. She's she she she makes it happen. But I it's you know, it's you've been on it.
It's now actually a thing. It's I just started talking to people that I knew about music and what they liked and music in their lives.
And, you know, I had these I had the idea came through working with David Silverman from The Simpsons because obviously he's not known as a musician.
He's known as a great animator and and he but he he's a serious tuba guy and he plays the tuba.
And so I said, you know, and then Bill Prady, who does The Big Bang Theory, who wrote that show and many, many others, he started playing the saxophone like when he was 60.
Wow. And I said, you know, I know all these people. Yeah, I know all these people that that that music's important to them, even though they're not known for music.
And so that sort of opened the door.
And then I started talking with more musicians and also a lot of critics and people that are around music.
And I just did. I'm very excited. I just did a great conversation with Eric, Eric Mingus, who's Charles Mingus' son.
And, you know, you don't get much higher up in the jazz royalty than Mingus.
And your stories of him growing up and being there when Mingus met Joni Mitchell and, you know, it's really cool.
I mean, I'm enjoying it. I mean, maybe maybe my audience is 10 people, but I'm loving it.
You know, you should have Jacob on to talk about Kiss because he loves Kiss.
Yeah, yeah. No, I mean, that's I'm not, you know, I've I've had I had Scotty Meltzer on who's a juggler.
And and I just said, you've got the worst taste in music of anyone I've ever met.
Tell us about it. And he did.
You know, it was great. But Scott is his worst singadoes.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, that's impossible.
That can't be true. No, it's true.
I mean, the only difference between Scotty and Godot is and I will give Scotty the edge on this.
I believe Scotty can also appreciate good music better than Godot.
You know what I mean? I I think I think Godot has just got, you know, really pedestrian music and and, you know.
And you're right. He just doesn't care. Yeah.
But Scotty, he actively seeks out every horrific show tune you've ever heard.
And and, you know, he was he was in he was like a musical kid.
He was in like, you know, musicals as a child and stuff.
And it's just so deeply disturbing.
And I was in a lot of musicals as a child. I don't listen only to show tunes, though.
I was in other music. He can appreciate Miles Davis, too.
But I don't think Godot cares whether it's Miles Davis or Bette Midler.
You know what I mean? But so I give Scotty the advantage there.
But but but my point is that everybody's got really not everybody.
But most people have the people I want to talk to have really interesting stories about growing up with it
and what they listen to as kids and how they got into music and sort of when they realized that music
they were listening to music different than all their classmates.
You know what I mean? The music became more important to them, usually at an earlier age than than every than most people.
Because I as I used to have to tell my father, who always promoted me, oh, my son's a great jazz piano player.
I say nobody cares about jazz, dad, and even less people care about solo piano in jazz.
So, you know, I'm looking for the people that care about that stuff that are also creative in other ways.
Writers, you know, and everybody. I mean, just, you know, if you've got interesting stories to talk about kiss, I want to hear them.
You know, I mean, you know, Matt and I talked about some guy from Jersey, some singer, singer, songwriter.
That's South Side Johnny of the Asbury Jukes did an hour.
We did an hour on South Side, Johnny. But but that's been a lot of fun.
It's really it's the stereo image. It's called the stereo image image.
And we got a great logo done by Matt Rockman, who's doing all the stuff for Penn and Teller these days.
And he came up with this really cool like it's like 3D glasses with VU meters on it.
And it's really because it's sort of retro and it's sort of, you know, it's got a little bit of everything.
And the stereo image is on all platforms or the stereo image dot com.
And I'm going to do I'm doing Oscar Peterson's daughter next week.
And she's got great stories. Yeah. I mean, we're really getting I've got I if I were smart,
I would have the list of people we've done in front of me. But I don't.
But no one's that smart. No one's that smart. Well, I'm you know, it's but it's Piff and Jade on it.
I had Piff and Jade on and it was hysterical because we did it from the Piff.
We did our first remote podcast from Piff's Lair. Oh, nice cave. Yeah. And it was it was.
Control freak like Piff making sure you did it in his studio, not yours.
Well, Piff, so unlike him, Piff has horrific taste.
That's what I was curious about. Yeah, I don't know what music he likes.
Suicidal coffee shop plaintiff, plaintiff, wailing singer, songwriter, 18 year old.
My boyfriend left me and I kill myself music. He lives the most depressing.
It's I mean, and he loves it and he just listens to it, I guess, according to Jade all the time.
But yeah, we we did. Yeah, well, we did.
Dara Godfried, we did, you know, talked about Gilbert some.
And I mean, we did a lot. We've got about maybe like 30, 30 done so far.
But but I'm looking at Gilbert's taste in music.
Gilbert, I don't I don't know if we did if we did have her very early on.
I don't know. We talked about Gilbert's podcast, of course, which was great.
Yes. He didn't really we didn't really talk about his music taste.
I don't I don't know if Gilbert knew music existed.
Yeah, I'm very curious about that. I'll tell you one thing. I'll tell you a Gilbert story.
I was so Gilbert was over at my house. This is 20 years ago, 15 years ago.
And we're just hanging out. And I told our friend Michael Lynn, we had a mutual friend,
Mickey Lynn, whose whose father had passed away. And he asked me, Mickey, his father loved the Marx brothers.
And he asked me if I would play a version of Hello, I Must Be Going for him to play at the funeral and recorded for him.
So I did, you know, and I was telling Gilbert that story who knew who knew Mickey as well.
And all of a sudden, Gilbert launches into a perfect rendition of of old Groucho singing Hello, I Must Be Going.
I totally spaced that Gilbert did perfect Groucho is like young Groucho.
You bet your life Groucho and old Groucho.
And he's just walking around my kitchen like, hello, I must be going, you know, and I just lost it.
I was like, oh, fuck, you know, I forgot you're a genius.
But his my favorite impersonation, one of my favorites was his impersonation of Penn.
Because we're at lunch one day and he's and he's sitting there and all of a sudden Gilbert's just looking at the table.
We're waiting for the waitress to come over and he's salt shakers, salt and pepper shakers.
He goes, oh, salt, salt. Oh, let's look at the salt today, this week.
And then he goes into Penn and he goes this week on bullshit. We've got the National Salt Association.
Because salt is pro salt. And then we've got the Anti-Salt Association. Salt is bullshit.
He did five minutes of Penn talking about salt and it was just genius.
But yeah, he I miss him. He was great.
But anyhow, but we got off on but yeah, the podcast is great.
And everyone should listen and subscribe and make me famous.
And then also, because, you know, how long can I play this piano?
I really belong in podcasting the nonstop world of podcasting.
That's right.
Do you really see like a world where you're you're you don't play piano?
Yeah, that world is when I'm dead.
Yeah, I often want to be I want to be like the 93 year old guy that they wheel out in the wheelchair chair and say, you know, jazz legend Mike Jones.
And I and I eat a little pudding and I play a couple of songs.
Isn't it amazing to still play at this age?
This is great. OK, get him off the stage. You know, that's that's what I see my I just saw a video, a tick tock with an elderly woman who's suffering from dementia.
She's I believe 93. And yeah, maybe you saw this, Josie.
But she's a classically trained pianist, but she doesn't remember that she's a classically trained pianist anymore.
However, they consider in front of a piano and say, could you play such and such?
She's like, well, I don't know it. But then she'll do it.
You know, right. I have seen it. Yeah, it's remarkable.
And the way it is, the way music acts in the brain is something special.
Oh, it is. Jonesy, would that be better or worse than current life?
Would it be better or worse if you could still play anything, any piece of music that you could play now?
You can play it, but you don't remember any of the music.
So you don't ever think about any of the music in your day to day life.
This is a dream. I just want to.
I just want to sit somewhere and have them give me pudding.
That's really all I want. I don't really care about putting.
But but I'm so we're used to you were saying something, Matt.
Yeah, well, to two different ways.
One, I think you're the kind of kid that you didn't have to be like encouraged.
Like your parents enough like overly encouraged you take piano.
If anything, they took piano away from you as a punishment. Right. Yeah.
I was when I was like two and a half, my brother, who's five years older, was taking lessons.
And I guess I would crawl up on the piano bench and play what he had been practicing.
And so my parents, unfortunately, thought, well, we can make money off this kid.
We'll send him to less. You know, and no, they just they just they always encouraged me.
I had two player pianos in my house, so it was always around and it's all I wanted to do.
And when I was in the third grade, my piano teacher said, you know,
I don't ever get up before 10 or 11 in the morning.
And it was a job for me. You're like, yeah, I hate it getting up in the morning.
Now, wait a minute. You said you had to play your pianos.
Yeah. You know, the you know, the like with the scrolls, like the scroll of paper running through it and everything.
Now they're now they're all, you know, now they're like Yamaha Disclavier and they know it's all it's all.
But yes, in the old day, it was a paper roll and it would go over a vacuum system that would cause the keys to go up and down.
And we had an upright piano in my basement.
And then in my living room, when I was about probably six or seven, my dad bought what was called a reproducing grand,
which was 1926 when it was made, was the state of the art for rich people.
And he made these rolls. They were called expression pianos and they got louder and softer and sustained.
So it didn't sound mechanical like a player piano.
All right. Like so I grew up with George Gershwin playing Rhapsody in Blue as if he was sitting at the piano in my house playing it.
And they made a you know, there was a company called Dewart and Ampico and Welty Mignon.
And they were all these they made these for the super rich, you know, I mean, when you're watching or when you're seeing that happen on that piano machine,
are you beyond just hearing the intonations and the ups and downs and the very, you know, the very nuanced playing of these masters?
Are you also able to pick up on the mechanics of it? Does it does it come through and like the pedal step moves and all that kind of thing?
The pedal doesn't move, but the keys obviously go up and down.
But for me, that was was that it was great. Yeah.
Because like if I put a Fats Waller piano roll on and I wanted to see what he was doing with his left hand.
Although it was many, many years, maybe like till I was 11 or 12 when it dawned on me.
Wait a minute. Sometimes there's 11 keys going down.
Maybe there's one person playing here. Then I found out it was they would double track them a while.
Right. They would, you know, they would wait. And I've made piano rolls.
I got to go to QRS and make piano wasn't the same piano that Duke Ellington and Ella Fitzgerald and Rachmaninoff and everybody played.
Is there like a whole bunch connected to the to the piano key as well?
No, it was more crazy than that. It's ink things.
So the sheet of paper goes through, you press the keys down, it puts ink on the paper.
And then somebody stands, somebody sits there and cuts out a master roll by hand.
Not at all. And then they then they make the master roll and then they produce them from that.
So it's it's amazing. And I mean, at a time they had like 40 people in a room cutting out master rolls every day because it was so popular in the 20s and 30s.
You know, and it's incredible. Yeah, it was really, really, really, you know, like old timey technology.
And but the piano was so cool because it was an old I think it was a Steinway.
But it had been played so much that the ivory keys were all like scalloped in. Yeah.
So, you know, it was like soft. You know, there was there was like that much.
Wow. He can down on the keys just from the millions of people that played it out for a hundred years. Yeah.
And like the lip on the edge of the key is just completely gone.
Like that little lip is worn away. Yeah, it's worn away from ivory.
And and I think it's in the Smithsonian now. But but it's it was really cool.
I in the 80s, the guy actually turns out that because they let black people play the piano, it had to be taken out.
Well, they took it to display down. Yeah. It happens. It happens. Ouch.
But anyways, so that's yeah, I've been, you know, so no, I was I I want to play, you know, I mean, as they say, I'll play till I drop dead.
You know, if I can't like arthritis or I'd rather not have that.
No, I actually I mean, certainly I have I'm always on the edge.
I I I have I I can do I have like some tendonitis and some carpal tunnel, but not not to where it's affecting me.
And I think the reason it doesn't is because I play so much.
But I relax long enough for it to set in.
Well, what happens is, yeah, I take tumor, turmeric and glucosamine and can go eat and, you know, to stave off stuff like that.
But what one of the great things about playing with the show on their 50th about in the last five years, they develop this new technology for I couldn't play a keyboard ever.
That was why it was always we can't take you on the road because we you can't play a keyboard because when you play a keyboard real quickly, pianists will know this.
There's a there's a thing I think it's called the escapement at the bottom of when you press a piano down.
If you press a piano key down very slowly, there'll be this little hitch at the very bottom and then it goes to the bottom.
And that absorbs all the shock of the piano key hitting the bottom of the keybed.
And even though they developed weighted keys for keyboards, there was never that kind of cushion.
So your arm absorbed the entire shock of the of the key hitting and it would set me off in 20 minutes.
Wow. And I never realized that.
That's crazy. And just in the last five years, Yamaha and Kawhi developed this new technology in their keyboards that has that feel.
And I can play them all day and it doesn't bother me at all.
And and it's actually better for the show because they don't have to mic the piano when I get there or anything like that.
They just I mean, it's not the same as an acoustic seven foot piano, but it's really close enough for for for them.
And and I like playing it.
So so Kawhi is you know, I'm a Kawhi artist and they just have one there for me.
It's really great. Did you hear how he said it was good enough for them?
It's good enough. Well, no, I meant it's good enough for a magic show for the people setting up this fucking keyboard that don't want to go to the trouble of setting up a piano.
That's right. That's right. It's good enough for them.
Also, it also means that the floating piano illusions back on the table.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Have you got a piano?
We don't knock it out of tune. You don't want to you don't want to make that piano around.
I'm happy to be in the floating piano illusion.
I'm very happy to be in it. I just don't want to be responsible for it.
I don't want to have to tune the piano after it's done.
Yeah. Yeah. It's like I had this stupid idea for Andy cheek in the chat kiss fans won't hear the difference.
Fuck you, Andy.
Tough talk. Wow.
You know, some of the some of the 100 members of Kiss of the past two centuries actually no more than two chords.
That's true. Well, no, Ace Fraley died. Not anymore.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's anyhow. Yeah.
The piano with the piano situation has gotten really good finally.
But so my hands don't hurt. You know, I'm really lucky.
I mean, I I've been playing for I've been playing the piano for almost 60 years.
But you know, and and a lot of old piano players that I've known over the years, you know, have not had problems with arthritis.
But then again, like Oscar had it really bad Oscar Peterson and and they just play through it, you know.
But I've been lucky. I mean, I still have most of my faculties, not mental at all.
I'm but I overrated. But anyways, and so if this is going out, but I will in self promotion to jump off.
If this is if anyone's hearing this on Monday in Vegas and have nothing to do tonight,
meaning Monday, go down to Vicks at 7 p.m. because I'm recording two different live albums in one night.
Oh, nice. Or so at 9 p.m. to for the second set. Vicks downtown by the Smith Center.
Yes. Oh, I would have put this through. I thought I thought this episode was coming out too late.
It's coming out. Oh, no, it's no it's it's Monday night.
OK, tonight, tonight, ladies and gentlemen. And it's it's the first set is going to be me and Graham.
Yes. Yeah. Every time I say Graham's name, Matt coughs.
You can't help it. He's allergic to Graham Decker.
I'm doing it with Graham Decker, who's an amazing guitar player and Alex Frank, who's an amazing bass player,
who found Penn's bass for him, who is a great he runs.
He plays the bass in Jeff Goldblum's band, which is all hot L.A. studio players and Jeff Goldblum.
But it's but it's it's really it's we're doing like in the 1940s and 50s right after World War II.
The most popular jazz combo setup was piano, bass and guitar.
And so Nat King Cole's trio was piano, bass, guitar. Oscar Peterson had a trio.
Art Tatum had a trio that was like the thing.
And then sort of in the 50s, drums work their way in, you know, because they felt sorry for drummers couldn't get a gig.
So they gave them gigs and that that format sort of went away and nobody does it really anymore.
And I got together with these guys sort of as a tribute to that kind of music.
And we did a record in my living room a few years ago and the record label said you guys should do a real live album because it's really good.
And they're they're so much fun to play with that I'm really looking forward to it.
And then. Because of a lot of behind the scenes stuff that Graham at the last minute wasn't sure he could do it.
So I hired a drummer and then when Graham said he could do it, I said to the label, hey, why don't we just do two albums?
I'll do one with the trio with the drummer and one with the trio with Graham.
And the label loved the idea because Capri Records is not a mega mega corporation.
So basically he's getting two records for the price of one. Right. And and it's just twice the work for me.
So I was going to say you volunteered to do all of the extra work and they didn't have to. I'm an idiot.
Yeah, that isn't clear to everyone listening now. I am an idiot.
And so, you know, not only are there going to be killer bands that Jonesy has assembled here, but if you have not gone to Vicks, it is a great Vegas.
It's a nice room. It's really the sound, too.
Besides the fact that the staff and the food is great and the staff is amazing and everybody wants to be polite and helpful.
The room, I believe I may be talking out of my ass, which I have been since I got on the call.
But I believe that the room was designed by the guy that did the jazz at Lincoln Center Room.
They brought him in for the acoustics. And I'm telling you, you can play that place with no amplification.
It's eighty eight seats. And is that a reference to the it is it is one for every key on on the saxophone.
I would have to be the person at that venue that is in charge of making sure they're always exactly eighty eight seats.
I'm sorry. We can't let you both in. We can only let one of you in.
We can let eight more people in and we'll call it a Bozendorfer.
But no, it's it. But the room is great.
The sound is great and they record really well.
And I think it's going to be a really fun time or it's going to be something that people want to witness for other reasons.
You know, I'll be having a meltdown on stage doing the 14th of a song.
None of it's right. None of it's right.
You know, no, no, you know, because I'm going to warn everyone, you know, they know we're putting all the social media is saying live album recording.
So it is I was I was on Sunday school and I said to Penn, Penn said, oh, so you can tell them if they heckle, it'll come on to the record.
And I said, oh, that's great. You know, I and the hecklers, what we'll get are like, wait a minute, that's the mixolydian mode.
Did you just play a flat five on that chord? What's wrong with you?
Yeah, jazz, jazz, jazz, hecklers are the worst. Yeah, yeah. Wait, did was was that a Bill Evans quote you just played?
Come on. But but anyhow, it'll be no, it'll be a lot of fun.
And and I'm really I've been trying to get this done for two years.
And I think that, you know, I so I in preparation, I had my head cut open.
So yeah, yeah, because, you know, I said to Jen, I hope your Photoshop skills are good enough.
Are you not going to wear a fancy hat?
Well, here's the problem. I probably will wear a fancy hat.
But I tried to wear a fancy hat in the show last night.
We were back at the Rio and I wore one of the hat from Blue Kazoo bit, which is a fancy hat.
I mean, those hats like are expensive and I had a kazoo is outrageous.
Well, the budget was I threw the roof.
I mean, but I look horrible in hats.
I just don't have a head for hats.
And but I put it on and Penn says to me, it looks like it's going to fall off your head.
Pull it down. It's supposed to be, you know.
And so I put it down. Yeah, that's a lot better.
So I work for the whole pre show. Right. And I come back to my dressing room and from here to here is bright purple.
All of the front of your head, your whole forehead. Yeah.
And I'm like, oh, my God, I screwed up everything. It cut off the blood flow.
What's going to happen? I go to go to the emergency room because I don't worry about anything.
And it's like there was like a ridge and it had just like cut the I guess because it's just all sensitive from the surgery.
And they pull all your skin together. So it gets super tight. Oh, yeah.
So for three nights, I couldn't sleep because if I did this, it hurt up here.
And touch your chin and the top of your head would start hurting.
Yeah, really? Seriously, I was trying to shave yesterday and Mike.
But so anyways, but luckily it's gone away now and I think I'll be OK.
But that goes that idea for that hat in the chat is suggesting maybe you could use one of our fezzes.
We do have patented fez. Oh, I thought about that.
I also thought about, you know, like just like a knit cap, like I'm going on a killing spree.
I like a dainty bonnet or something like that. Have you thought that would be recommended to do rag a full bottle of water?
Kind of wild, man. Just look at the chat says a chef's a chef's hat would be great.
Well, the problem is, and I mean, I know we're all just joking, but the problem is they all have a thing that will cut off the circulation.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I figured it out. Bucket of chicken, bucket of chicken right over the head.
Yeah, yeah. Buckethead. Jazz Buckethead. I tribute the Buckethead.
Oh, you know, that'd be awesome. Won't touch the head at all.
Lampshade would also work. Yeah, lampshade.
You could do a popcorn bucket and cut a hole at the top and be like, I'm wearing this completely wrong.
Right. I am bad at this.
But I need one of those things that they, you know, they screw on your head for brain surgery.
Oh, yeah. A halo. Oh, God. A halo. And they just drape something over it.
Now you're thinking. I know this is the kind of thoughts that get you get you a real, real career.
But anyhow, no, it'll it'll all be fine. But but it's it's healing up well.
And hopefully by by the time I play the Green Mill next week, I won't have to have a bandage or hat.
I'll need a hat for Chicago. But but it's yeah.
But it's it's it's the the the Monday night thing is going to be something that I've I've been looking forward to for a few years.
But also, yeah, there's a little bit of pressure on me.
But it's I think that the jury will outweigh the pressure.
You want the pressure. You want the pressure. You need the pressure. You need it.
Yeah. Yeah. Pressure cooker. No pressure. No diamonds. I perform best when under pressure.
No, I think that the fun will weigh out. Beautiful jazz is best under pressure.
Damn right. Well, all of the stuff that I'm doing for this, like producing it.
And Jen, of course, is like making all this shit happen, too.
This is not the way I make records.
Usually the company says we got a recording date and who do you want on it?
And I go into the studio and I make it. But this record and the record before this,
I'm doing all the work because the labels in in Colorado and he can't leave to come to Vegas.
And the last record was with Penn and Jeff Hamilton.
So I have to make sure that Jeff Hamilton is happy and I have to book the studio and I have to do, you know, and all this stuff, I'm incompetent.
I don't I can barely fucking feed myself. You know, right.
So I, you know, it's it's all of that on top of trying to play good songs for people and not, you know, make a fool of myself as a musician.
You know, it's just a lot of different pressure. But but it's it but it's fine.
I mean, we get we'll get there. It'll be fun.
And and they wisely give us a meal.
So I know that I'm really just working for food at the end of the, you know, I when the recordings done, I get fed.
It doesn't matter what level of fame or fortune the musician is that if you give them food, they're going to be thrilled.
Right. Absolutely. I mean, you know, and I mean, you know, I say that by you go to you go to craft services after after the after the after the sound check.
And, you know, my bosses are down there.
They're eating, you know, because, you know, that's what you do.
I mean, it's it's it's the risk. It's the reward for, you know, a lifetime spent banging on a piano.
You get a free meal once in a while. If you ever want to just like please an artist, just feed them.
If you just feed the artist, they will be they will be so happy.
I know I am. I forgot, Mike, that your that your camera follows you around with the with the AI thing.
So when you just leaned over to get a drink out of your cup, I was really wondering why you were moving the camera to follow yourself.
I see. I see. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Man, he is really into this camera thing. Damn right.
But no, it's you know, it's it's funny when I was doing gigs in in in in Boston when I got out of college and I did the whole circuit.
Like there were 40 or 50 places in Boston that had live music every night from like five o'clock at night till nine.
There was a shift and then nine to one and I played a lot of cocktail shifts and a lot of night shifts and all of these places.
Their reputation among musicians was who had the best employee cafeteria. Yep.
You know, that's all we cared about.
It's like, oh, man, I got a gig next Friday night at the Ritz, you know, and you would go up to the top floor on the Ritz.
And the food up there was better than most restaurants for the employees.
You know, and if you didn't like what they were offering, they would make you a burger, which at the time, a Ritz burger was like twenty dollars.
You know, and they would just make it for you.
And you go up there and they would have like a prime rib hash that was out for the for the for the in the street bar.
That, you know, I mean, this stuff was I still think about that. You know, it's like we're talking about it.
Well, it's so funny. And I'm going off. I'm taking up your whole show.
Well, why not? You were stupid enough to have me.
I would I would see these old musicians like guys that I worshiped when I was in Boston and I got lucky enough to be friends with and play with.
And I'd be on this gig after seeing Dave McKenna, who was a great jazz pianist.
And I would be in a room with Dave McKenna and Dick Johnson, who was a great clarinetist, who led the Artie Shaw band.
And he's these guys are legendary musicians and Herb Palmer and Dick Johnson and Gray Sargent and all the guys from from Boston.
And they all played. I mean, Herb Palmer played with Charlie Parker.
You know, that's the level of these musicians.
And I'm sitting there as a twenty two year old guy wanting to suck up all the all the stories and all the energy.
And you know what they talked about? Oh, remember that diner on Route nine?
The fucking mashed potatoes there were unbelievable.
You know, and Dave McKenna is like, oh, this white pizza at this place in Hartford.
I do the gig just for that. That's what they're talking about.
You know, I played with Ella Fitzgerald for six nights and, you know, they don't care.
They're like, that's food. Food, food is important.
That's what I've learned in life.
Anyhow, Jonesy, when do you think the albums are going to come out?
What? When do you think the albums are going to drop?
Oh, the albums? Oh, not until I mean, with Locke, you know, spring or summer of twenty six.
OK, I mean, I'm going to push him a little bit more, you know, maybe maybe even as soon as March or April for one of them.
I don't know if they'll do two of them at the same time.
I don't know, you know, as I said, in dealing with all of the machinations to make these records,
Johnny Katz asked me what the title was going to be.
And I said, we don't have them titled yet, which we don't.
But as I said to Jen, the title of the first one is going to be Never Again.
And the title of the second one is Somebody Kill Me.
This was your chance to see me do this. I'm not doing it again.
Yes, exactly. Title. Exactly. No, no.
I mean, we'll come up with something, you know, a little bit a little bit better than vamping at Vicks.
Not much better. Not much better.
Go and see Jonesy tonight at Vicks. Subscribe to the stereo image.
Yeah, thank you. Yes. Thank you, Jonesy, for coming out and jamming with us.
God bless you, Matt and Jacob and Paul and all of the scoops out there.
And yes, do do whatever you want.
Come on out and and subscribe if you want to hear me talk more about music with people that are smarter than me.
There you go. All right. Thanks, guys. Really, really appreciate it.
Thanks, Jonesy. Bye. Bye.
So shy. Yeah, yeah. It's tough to get him out of his shell.
One day, one day, though, he's going to really start talking.
It's going to be violent that Jonesy. Yeah.
He's a he's a fascinating guy. He is absolutely and that podcast is great.
I've listened to a couple of episodes. Yes.
He gets he gets deep with some of his guests.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They're talking about like a personal relationship with music, which is always it's always going to be fascinating.
And then you add knowledge into it on top of it.
And it's it's exactly it's a really it's a really great thing coming from a very educated place.
Yeah. Well, I had a scooper to hear all picked out because Jonesy was with us.
He's gone now. We're going to play it anyway.
Here comes a scooper.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
We got a scooper to come into us today from the OG scoop.
The categories are rock with strings, bond theme artists from Broadway to pop and old ass songs.
That's right. It's a music scooper.
Oh, I'm first.
I'll start the top left corner rock with strings for 200.
Kansas basically says we are all dirt in this 70s classic.
But it's the shit.
The name of the song, Dust in the Wind, the horse with no name, horse with no name.
Dust in the Wind is it. Matt, you're up. I'll do rock with strings for 400.
Let's see here.
This moody blues song speaks of written letters that were never meant to be sent.
Nights and white satin. I think so. All right. Nights and white satin. Nights and white satin.
Letters I've written never meant to be sent.
I'll do rock with strings for 800. Let's go. Whoa.
Skip it over. This zeppelin song name drops a region of the Indian subcontinent.
Yeah, you're glad you skipped over the $800 question now, aren't you?
Cashmere, I think.
Let's try it.
It's cashmere.
Damn it.
See, I always thought it was referring to Ed Wood's sweaters, but I guess I was wrong.
You thought Led Zeppelin made it.
He played all the coffee houses when I was coming up, you know, the 90s. There's a lot of coffee houses.
Scott Hathaway would mic his guitar all over the place and he would play cashmere by wearing a jangly bracelet, hitting certain guitar strings and playing the drums on the bottom of the guitar. It was insane.
I've seen people do that. It's a little one-man bandy.
Yeah. And I, my son, my youngest son brought up a clip of someone doing that who is younger and doing it. And I, this proud dad moment, bit my tongue and didn't say, I know someone who did that when I was young also. I just let him appreciate the new young guy doing it for the first time.
And I was like, yep, that's awesome. Way to find that. Way to discover that.
Way to discover this brand new thing. No one has done before.
Let's see, it's me. I'll try old ass songs, 200.
This Queen song is almost always played with their song "Bicycle Race."
Ooh. Which one did they play with "Bicycle Race?"
I'm going to feel really dumb here in a second. I'm going to pass. Matt.
I think it's Fat Bottom Girls. Is it? All right, let's try it. It is Fat Bottom Girls. Look at that.
Yes, I always play them together.
Smart.
I will do, let's go from Broadway to Pop.
Daily Double!
Yvonne Elliman had this hit from "Jesus Christ Superstar."
Go get Jesus and hang him on the cross.
What's the hit from "Jesus Christ Superstar?"
I need this problem like I need a hole in my hand.
Get the fuck down, someone needs the wood.
I'm going to shroud a turban all over your face.
Man, it's a Daily Double, so I have to guess.
It is. Let's see, "Jesus Christ Superstar." You got all the Judas songs.
Jeepers, creepers, where'd you get those peepers?
Sure, yeah.
Jeepers, creepers, where'd you get those eyes?
Rub-a-dub-dub. I was washing my feet in the tub.
Yep.
One, two, three o'clock, four o'clock, it's Jesus.
Five, six, seven o'clock, eight o'clock, it's Jesus.
I'll just say "Jesus Christ Superstar," the hit.
There you go.
Let's try it. I don't know how to love him.
Also, let's play the game. I don't know how to love him. It's also the answer to this.
Paul, you're up.
I will also try "From Broadway to Pop."
Let's try it. This Wiccan song was inescapable in the early 2000s.
I believe it's "Let It Go."
No, it's got to be "Defying Gravity."
No, I'm sorry, Paul. It was "Letting Go," from Wiccan.
I have green skin, look at me.
Please don't eat the green snow.
I'll try "Broadway to Pop," 600.
Oh shit, I did the wrong thing. I did old-ass songs.
According to Trace Atkins, the subject of this song has got it going on like Donkey Kong.
Oh, for a second, I thought I wasn't going to know the answer to the question that I accidentally clicked on for myself.
Now you do.
Fortunately, it's the song that is my wake-up tone. It plays on my alarm every morning.
I listen to it before I go to bed at night.
And of course, honky-tonk, badonkadonk.
Correct.
Yes.
Matt, you're up.
By the way, that was from old-ass songs, not from "Broadway to Pop."
Oh, good.
I'll do "Rock With Strings," for 600, please.
ELO added strings to this amazing cover of a Chuck Berry tune.
I don't know, pass.
Well, goodness.
I think this is also "Let It Go."
It could be "My Ding-a-ling."
It's the string version of "My Ding-a-ling."
The silver bell's hanging on a string.
I'll pass.
Oh, it passes to me. I don't know. I'll pass.
"Roll Over Beethoven."
I've never heard the ELO version of that.
I don't think I have, either.
Paul, you're up.
"Broadway to Pop," please.
For 600.
Susan Boyle shocked judges on "Britain's Got Talent" with this song from "Les Miserables."
Les Miserables.
It was--I don't know how to love it.
Yeah, right, that's my favorite, but that ain't doing anything.
This is the song that I sang.
Oh, is it? No, it's not "Where Is Love."
Not "Where Is Love."
What's love got to do with it?
"Where Is Love" is from Oliver.
Shit. What is this one?
Please, sir, can I have some more?
I'll have to pass. I don't know.
Pass it to me. What did she sing from--
Yeah, I don't remember.
That's the whole question, isn't it?
"Master of the House," this is not the song that she would have sung on the talent show.
It's not the "I'm John Valjean" song.
It's probably not "I'm John Valjean."
It's probably not--yeah, it's probably not--
Who am I? I'm Susan Boyle.
That'd be great. That'd be so great.
It fits the meter.
Empty chairs and empty tables, that doesn't feel right.
Oh my god, dude, have you heard the empty chairs and empty tables Muppets mash-up?
No.
Dear Christ.
The Muppets did, like, miss.
No, it just fits perfectly with the Muppet Show intro.
And it's just as haunting and tragic.
That's great.
All right, I'll have to look for it, or send it to me.
Why am I looking for it? You send it to me.
I gotta pass. Matt?
It's "Dream to Dream."
Oh, it's the only song I couldn't think of from "Les Mis."
Yeah, I couldn't remember it myself.
Matt just knew it.
It's me. I'll close out "Pop to Broadway," "Broadway to Pop," you know what I mean.
The other songwriters, Benny Anderson and Bjorn Ilvisis, along with Tim Rice, penned this tune from "Chess."
I had no idea that anybody from ABBA worked on "Chess," so I'm gonna pass.
Matt?
Oh, shoot. My wife loves "Chess."
Everyone loves the soundtrack to "Chess," and no one loves the show.
That's exactly right.
I mean, this is the one hit. I got it.
Paul, go.
It's "One Night in Bangkok."
That's what you're going with?
Yeah.
It's "One Night in Bangkok."
That's just right.
It's the only song there is in "Chess" that made a hit.
I don't know. Are we supposed to "Chess?"
Do you need us to shout you're right?
What do you need us to credit? You got it right. I don't know why.
I need more credit. More credit.
Paul's right. Paul's right, everyone.
One night in Bangkok and your cock gets banged on.
Matt, you got Bond-themed artists or old-ass songs. What you want?
Hand me that hammer, gonna bang some cock.
But for one night--
I'll do--
Bangkok, Oriental City, where you have to bring your hammer 'cause hammers ain't cheap.
Hammer's got a lot of--
I'm gonna do old-ass songs for 800.
Bring your hammer and disinfect it 'cause you're gonna be banging on your cock all night.
Casey and the Sunshine Band got scores of us to do this in the '70s.
Have unprotected sex.
Oh, Casey and the Sunshine Band, you rascals.
There's several possible answers here.
I think it's get two little dance and make a little love, get down tonight.
Or--
Let's try it.
Shake, shake, shake. Shake, shake, shake.
Oh, shoot, it's gonna be that. It's gonna be that.
What do you think, Matt?
What's your final answer? You gotta pick one.
Your answer fits better to a question than mine does.
I think that's why I went there, is shake your booty.
You say you're gonna shake your booty?
Yeah, shake your booty.
Let's try it. It is shake, shake, shake, shake your booty.
There we go.
Way to go, Matt. You and your booty got that right.
Paul.
Phew.
Bond theme artist, what the hell?
Let's see.
Singer of "Nobody Does It Better" from "The Spy Who Loved Me."
I think that's Eartha Kitt.
Let's try it, Eartha Kitt. Carly Simon.
Shit on me.
The Eartha Kitt of James Bond music.
Carly Simon of Eartha Kitts.
It's me. I'll close out old ass songs for $400.
Sir Mix-A-Lot's favorite body part of the opposite sex is obvious from this song.
I believe it's "My Humps, My Helumps, My Lovely Lady Lumps" by Sir Mix-A-Lot.
That would be the butt song. Baby Got Back.
Yeah, there it is.
Matt, you got Bond theme artist for $400, $600, or $800.
I had to really shuffle through all of the Sir Mix-A-Lot hits in my brain to get to that one.
Did Mix-A-Lot do one of the Bond themes?
He did. Under a pseudonym, though.
Oh yeah, score check. Paul has $1,800. Matt has $1,400. I have $1,200.
I think there's a daily double left as well in one of these three questions.
I like James Bond in "I Cannot Lie." You other spies can't deny.
When he rolls in with a car with tricks, it shoots somebody from the roof.
It's James Bond's car.
All right, let's do Bond theme artist for $400.
Let's see it.
Not Guns N' Roses, but this group recorded the soundtrack theme from "Live and Let Die" first.
That'd be Big Buckethead.
Big Buckethead, of course.
What was the name of that group?
Paul McCartney.
But it was a group.
Is it a group?
Yeah, it's a band.
Oh, Wings.
Wings, there you go. Paul McCartney and Wings.
Paul, you got theme artists for $600 or $800.
You're currently tied with Matt at $1,800.
Yeah, I'll go $800. Let's go.
$800?
Yeah.
It's the daily double.
I knew it. I knew it.
Now it's for $1,800.
But I had to do this.
You had to.
I did.
In my opinion, this Goldfinger theme singer started the tradition of epic Bond songs.
If that's your opinion, OG Scoop, you're correct.
I think this is Earthy Kit.
Oh, it is not.
Oh, fuck me.
It is Shirley Bassey.
My ass.
Shirley Bassey, my ass.
Oh, I clicked the wrong thing.
I clicked it.
Paul got it right, which he definitely did not.
Bond theme artists for $600.
That's what I'm closing it out with.
This R&B diva legend graced us all with the theme from License to Kill.
This was, of course, Earthy Kit.
It's not.
It's Lattice Night.
That's the game.
Did Earthy Kit do a Bond song?
I don't think so, no.
That's the game.
Matt wins with $1,800 points.
I'm in second with $600 points.
Paul is in third with zero points.
Not according to the scoreboard, though.
According to the scoreboard, Paul crushed us with $3,600 points.
And that's from OG Scoop.
Thank you, OG Scoop.
Everyone knows Shirley Bassey was secretly just Earthy Kit.
So there you go.
It was three Shirley Basseys in a trench coat dressed up as Earthy Kit.
So do we have time for me to share my winter stories for you?
Well, tell us, Paul.
Or let me tell people this.
If you want to send us a Scooperty, Price is Right, Jock vs. Nerd,
any kind of Jock vs. Nerd, or an email, heyscoops.com.
That's where you can go.
Send us all those things right over there at heyscoops.com.
Paul, do you have a tale of winter?
I have a couple.
So it's colder in Wichita and Nebraska out here.
It's freezing.
And we got our first significant snow the other day.
And it happened between my improv classes.
So one improv class I went to on Monday, no problem.
Tuesday, a little more treacherous.
The roads are pretty fine because out here they know how to deal with snow.
They plow and they salt and it's all good.
So the roads are not a problem.
They plow, they salt, they plow, they plow, they plow, they plow.
Plow and salt, salt and plow.
You may remember--
It's just fine, it's fine, it's fine.
You may remember outside of the Skit Theater area,
there is a large section of stairs.
Do you recall these stairs?
Oh, yes.
Right.
I do.
Well, I came upon those stairs on my second night,
not thinking anything of it really.
They looked trod upon,
but they didn't look like they weren't snowy.
So I thought, okay, we're fine.
Well, it had gotten to about 35 degrees that day.
Okay.
And then by the time I got to the stairs,
it was back down to about 30.
And so the stairs were basically covered in black ice.
I took my first step onto that stairs.
My feet went out from under me.
I was lucky to have hold of the handrail.
I swumbled-- I didn't fall.
I swumbled down to my ass onto these frozen stairs,
and I could not get my feet under me for the life of me.
Oh, no.
So I scooted on my ass down 15 stairs
all the way down on ice,
and my butt was just soaking wet for the rest of class.
It was disgusting.
And in my terror of my near-death experience,
I quickly texted Justin.
I'm like, oh, my God, I almost died on the stairs.
You have to tell everybody.
Send emails out.
Someone could really get hurt.
I must have freaked him out.
I was in such a tizzy.
You do get in tizzies.
It's bad.
Then last night, it's getting down to 11.
And Anne suddenly remembers, oh, shit.
We don't have the external hose hookup covered for the winter,
and we didn't turn the water off.
That could lead to frozen pipes.
That's not a good thing.
So she remembers this last night at 9 o'clock PM
when I've been asleep for almost an hour and a half.
And so she wakes me up from a dead sleep
to tell me, oh, God, we've got to get this thing fixed.
Where is this?
She's got like a glove for the pipes.
Where's the glove?
I don't know.
I have no idea where the glove is.
It got removed in the spring when she started doing watering stuff,
and it hasn't been replaced.
And I don't know where the fuck it is.
But I managed to go get some pool noodle, because I have spare pool
noodle around for such an emergency.
Cut up some pool noodle, fashioned a crude glove,
if you will, for the external piece.
And we duct taped it up, and there you go.
All fixed.
Then I turn around, and she is back in bed.
Meanwhile, I'm up.
And I was beside myself that she had been able to go right back to bed
after that so quickly and left me to fiddle with the dogs.
It was really funny to me.
But then this morning, I get the call that she got her karmic comeuppance
for waking me in the night.
Oh, good.
It's about time she learns a lesson.
No, this is tragedy.
She's drinking her coffee this morning that she's made out of her little
machine.
And the coffee is off, right?
It's off.
Something's really off about the coffee.
And she doesn't know what.
But she knows it's off.
And she goes to open up the coffee machine.
And there is a stink bug in the coffee machine.
And she is beside herself.
She cannot handle this revelation.
This is like -- this is the thing that puts her over the edge.
She gets violently ill from the stink bug in the coffee machine.
She's throwing up everywhere.
She's -- because she's drank stink bug juice.
So she's just like, dear God.
So she's done.
Not only that, not only that, she is so upset that I had to buy her a new
coffee maker today.
She will not use the stink bug.
What?
I said there's nothing wrong with this coffee maker.
She's like, I can't even look at it.
I couldn't even be in the kitchen without getting violently ill.
Okay.
So if there's one Achilles heel on old McFeeters, it's stink bugs and
liquids.
It's stink bugs.
There you go.
You got to get a new coffee maker and put a fake stink bug in there just to
start it off right.
Lauren Shreve says if you've smelled stink bug, you'll understand.
And it's true.
They are foul, foul things.
We didn't have any.
We don't have any in Vegas, thank God.
They are nasty, nasty critters.
They're really, really gross.
So anyway, she's got a nice new coffee machine now.
And hopefully that will be all good.
There they are.
We got the small brown ones.
Oh, my God.
No.
Just get all these, just a bunch of plastic bugs to just fill the coffee
maker with it.
No, no, no.
Oh, she'll be so sad.
Don't send fake plastic bugs.
Honestly, she wouldn't care.
A fake plastic bug wouldn't affect the taste of her coffee.
It's the fact that this bug actually put all kind of goo in her coffee and she
drank it.
It was nasty.
Oh, that pervy bug.
What would disinfect it is if you peed all over the old coffee maker and that
would be, that would help.
I told her we could do that.
That's if a jellyfish gets into your coffee maker.
It's just as well.
It's an older model.
It still works great.
I'm going to give it to the goodwill.
Her name is Anne.
Don't call her an older model.
But the other day when she was really, really sick, I guess it was Thanksgiving
Day when she was really, really sick.
She was making coffee for herself and she forgot to put a cup in the machine.
And I came in.
I'm like, Anne, what the fuck?
She was just spilling coffee all over the machine.
If your coffee maker does that, then you do need to get a new coffee maker.
Your coffee maker is out of date.
Yeah.
So she was like, I don't even know what I'm doing.
But it got coffee all in the base of the machine.
So it can go now.
Oh, that's really funny.
It served its time.
It's time.
Poor thing was just out of it.
Well, I for one, I'm certainly glad that Anne finally got her comeuppance for
waking you up earlier than you wanted to wake up.
Yeah, she got her comeuppance.
Serves her right in the form of a brand new coffee maker.
No, it's all good.
She's dead right.
And I would be the most upset if we had any kind of water damage happen because
that's coming right down here to the old Batcave.
You know, it's not going anywhere but down.
And I've got plenty of stuff that won't be too terribly affected because most of
it's all plastic.
But there's plenty of paper down here to get fucked.
I've got to believe, Paul, even if you weren't there, I think if the basement
started flooding, I think the squirrel would get most of the stuff out of the
basement.
I think the squirrel would save most of the possessions down there.
Do you think they're that sensible to get everything out?
I do.
I think the squirrels have taken full ownership of the basement and everything
in it.
They want to take care of it.
All right.
They don't have an insurance policy.
One night at Paul's house and the world's my oyster.
I creep and crawl in whenever I want to.
Sarah Boyle?
No, that's the scoop.
Susan Boyle.
That's the name.
Shit.
Susan Boyle.
One night in Susan Boyle.
I want to thank Mike Jones for coming on the program.
Absolutely.
Go to his podcast.
Yeah.
Go get his live album.
Go to VEX if you're around Vegas Monday night.
I also want to thank all the scoops who joined us here on Twitch.
Yes.
I want to thank all the scoops who joined us here on Zoom.
That's right.
And there's no way we thank people in the show.
It's a new month.
We haven't got our thank you lists coordinated yet.
But I want to thank, of course, everyone who supports us over on our Patreon.
All the people who find it in their hearts and in their wallets to go over to preachingfun.com.
I'm really looking forward to the day that I don't have to play that whole theme manually.
I've gotten it all inked out on a piece of paper.
And I'm going to have somebody cut out all the little holes in it for a player piano.
But in the meantime, check out fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can upkeep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon subscribers.
So if you are not a Patreon subscriber, preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz, head over there.
If you think this show is worth more than $0, you can upkeep this show on the air.
And we sure do thank you for it.
If you can't do it, if you can't go over and do the monetary value thing, that is okay.
Not everybody is able to do that these days.
Tell somebody about us.
Tell one person, one person only.
Don't do the two friends and then they tell two friends things.
That is a pyramid scheme.
It is unethical.
We don't get into that.
We do an obelisk scheme.
You tell one person, one person only.
It's vertical growth.
But you're going to find that one person that really kind of digs this weird thing that we're doing over here.
So go let them know about us.
Let them know about the obelisk scheme.
One person and one person only.
But that person has to dig this thing.
And probably, preferably get on there and support the Patreon within the first, I don't know, 10 minutes or so of you telling them about us.
That'd be really convenient for us.
Also, don't forget about our billionaire experiment.
Don't forget, get each of us a billion dollars and we will see if we can be better billionaires than the current ones.
Oh, shout out to Radioactive Scoop for doubling their Patreon.
Thank you.
Thank you, Radioactive Scoop.
Yeah, we had a little a little bump in our Patreon this month.
Thank you guys so much.
Love it.
Line go up.
That's what we want.
That's right.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
JonesJazz.com is by Jones website.
Go check that out.
Follow him on social media.
You'll get all the hints and tips.
We're French and punny.
See ya.