Why does the black flat cap feel more pretentious than the other caps it looks good
I would say it is no more or less pretentious than your other cap. Thank you. Definitely looks very peaky blinders
Yeah, that's what I mean. You look like you look like you're you're you're a bit of a patty enforcer
You are a patty enforcer, man. Hello. This is my favorite part of this show my drag name
This is the part of this show where we thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you ice cream truck drivers. I don't have a new list for the month yet
We want to thank each and every ice cream truck driver
And we will we will thank each and every one of you by name before this month is over
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, maybe you just want to be a patty driver
I don't know head on over to preaching fun comm preaching fun comm is we're gonna sign up to be an ice cream truck driver
And who knows?
Life you save maybe your own
It's time for a program. Hey Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
A bunch of where the fuck were you? It's time for Matt Maddly's ice cream social sitting in prison. That's Matt
Pittsburgh that's called Maddie Lee. I'm Jacob in Vegas
We're preaching fun fun. So I I know exactly what you're talking about that big
Nabi thing I have one too
Yes, so it's the
Shore the shore little
microphone connector
Adapted to an XLR connection is what you're referring to and it gives power right? It gives power to the microphone
Yeah, the the your your recorder is sending phantom power to it as well, which is I think
Forty something volts. I don't remember what it is. So I you know pack my heaviest stuff and put it on my carry-on
To get weight out of my case for when I travel with my magic stuff
Ah, so one of the items is shackles. They're actual iron shackles
And then my jar of rings
My thing of rope and so I got it got pulled out at the Fort Lauderdale Airport
and I
You know
I'm thinking it's gonna be about the shackles which only one time someone was like you can't you can't travel with these and I was
Like oh, I sure can and for some reason that worked and then they let me go
Yeah, I was like no I travel with them all the time
And and all of a sudden he goes. Oh, it's this right here and he pulls out the microphone
I go what he goes this is this adapter and the x-ray looks like it looks like a high caliber of bullets
That's it my high caliber bullets is this guy bit x-ray my singular shot my my one
My one high caliber bullet. I'm taking with me to assassinate the pilot from the back of the plan with my sniper rifle
back and to the left
Matt the man with the golden
Donnelly exactly
Don't mind me carry just just carries one bullet. Just the jackal making my way through the Florida Airport
I'm actually shooting my target is at the Miami Airport. I'm that good. I'm shooting high wind
From one airport to another it's one of those check the wind first. Yeah. Yeah, it's a whole big thing
It's like one giant bullet will be traveling into a private jet taking out from Miami Airport
Don't be traveling via private jet
Yes, and it's not shot out of a gun because I didn't pack that so it's I just I just wheel my shackles like a slingshot
And they put the bullet in there and I sling it like David and then boom
And then as long as you do it in the plane
Then the bullet is traveling at the speed of the plane in addition to the speed that the earth is already rotating
All the velocity I need just comes from the flight itself. I just have to drop the bullet out the window
It's like throwing pennies off the Empire State Building
That's why I always request the seat with the rolled out window that
the
proposition that you're creating the
Strategic crazy scenario you're creating could actually be the plot of an episode of Gogo 13
Gogo 13, he's an incredible assassin and it one of my favorite anime
Anime and manga of all time and Gogo 13 does constantly those kinds of
Impossible assassinations that he's just a gun for hire. He's like this cold
Merciless killer you pay him enough money
He will do whatever needs to be done and then the investigators are always this close to figuring out
But then they're like no fucking way. Could anybody do this?
Line a lot of other things should use that same plot line and then they go back then they go back and they go
Oh fuck. He did do that
Then they show you how he fucking did it and it's like what holy shit. Yeah, go go 13 is
Unstoppable
Bossy says I'm actually just throwing it like a dart from the back of the plane to hit the pilot. Just yeah
The physics physics checks out nobody check it but the physics checks
All you do is hold it in your body run the numbers hold it in your hand
While you're landing and then just let go and let let gravity do the work. That's right
Like don't like my idea is when they jump up and down inside of an elevator. Uh-huh
Yeah, same same thing. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Yeah
All right
Are any of you?
watching land man
No, man, I love land man. Okay, we have we haven't started the new season yet, but we burned through the first season
I hung back until those four episodes and now I'm four episodes caught up with a new season is this who is this?
Who's the land is Billy Bob Thornton Thornton?
Demi Moore is in it. Oh, he's fantastic
Yeah, the whole cast is really killer. Okay, Myron chat. She's not willing to pay for paramount respect respect on that
There's just there are websites you can go to have to sail the seas
Now you just gotta start now go the full other direction Myron steal steal the show
So
Landman for those who don't watch the show. It's the most popular show on paramount plus and Billy Bob Thornton plays a grizzled
foul-mouth
Smoking land man where he is there meaning what?
So land man are people who own oil fields small smaller oil operators, right?
I weren't working for the big guns, but they're just trying to get by
Which is definitely something that Matt and I knew before watching land man. Sure
What is it? So Taylor Sheridan for whether you want to whether you want to go with cause or symptom?
He is simply basically between Yellowstone and mayor of Kingstown, you know
in
1923 and these shows like he basically
takes pockets of where white dudes might feel obsolete and
Gives them monologues and speeches that that kind of build up, you know, these these broken ways of life, right?
And here's the thing. I
Actually like at first like used to I feel conflicted about this right here because this is you know
The way of the way this country is going right now
It seems like that's that's a big force behind a big imaginary force behind a lot of a lot of actions being taken
Yeah
I'm doing a show on the on the cruise ship and I get this guy up on stage and he is
Basically me like one point five me in size like exact body type just six foot five
and just a little wider and thick arms or whatever and
I
say
You know, hi, you know, what do you do for a living?
You know, do you work that kind of stuff and he goes I work in the oil and gas distribution from Texas
Yes
Yes, and I say because basis like my dad growing up hated law shows
See hated the way the law was portrayed
On television and it made people assume stupid questions all the time
So I wonder if that's better or worse now or if it's just the same
For like new legal dramas because I feel like the new legal dramas try to stay more true to the law
They don't ones do but like they're still ridiculous legally
Yeah, my dad was just laughs like how quickly they can like get like lab results and stuff like that
Like he's just like big in lab results like the next day or the same Leon in the chat is saying they are not much better
Jacob
Okay. Yeah, right
Leon is our barrister. He's yes our law he's there Leon. He's our law man
We need a law man, so I say
Do you love or hate the show land man
Good and he like literally turns to me
Like like doesn't doesn't like he's like we're not having a conversation. He just turns to me and he goes, oh
That is the most accurate portrayal of the oil and gas
I have ever seen on TV or movies and he almost has tears in his eyes
You know now there is fascinating shit in the show there is shit that you do not you never thought about the oil and gas
industry sure there is like really they really do do a good job of like
Villages where the where the workers like live like the box house villages, you know things like that
It's it's really fascinating. It's neat stuff. There's one was like there's an there's an oil
Area left all alone and therefore there's like a toxicity thing that can happen
And so they come across dead bodies and then also they go what's going on on the alarms go off on their uniforms and they go
running
So they don't die and you're like, oh right. I had no idea no idea that that kind of scenario
There are electronic canaries in the coal mine now. Yeah. Yeah, they've got yeah
It's a little like gas meters and by the way the same thing for I think nuclear stuff by the way, Matt
I know this wasn't intentional, but you just basically told a Trump rally story
Saying there was big guy big guy came up to me and I turned to him and I said
Do you like land man or not? And with tears in his eyes big guy big guy tears in his eyes
I love land man. He tells me let me people are saying people and with that I'll finish out
He said no one's ever asked me about land man before only you know, I'm joking
I didn't take the turn. All about no one ever knows it's all about me and how I'm unique
He looked at me with tears in his eyes and said that is the best question anyone has ever asked me about land man
Sensational question such a good question giant men who weep
You asked the best questions Matt not only my noodler. So it's it is teaching you all kinds of
Actual tricks of the trade within the land man community. It is like any good show and that is a voyeur
It's a it's a voyeuristic, you know
Thing where you're getting eating a pocket of the world. You wouldn't normally get a pocket out of right?
It's still filled with its weird weird monologues, you know and things like that
The season opens with Billy Bob doing a big monologue about breakfast and like the waitress is the most important meal of day and he
Just lectures her about who profits from breakfast and blah blah blah blah and it's just Taylor shared
It just has these monologues that are just atrocious
and one-dimensional
But you tolerate Billy Bob Thornton or Kevin Costner doing them, right? It's almost like a challenge, you know, I
Can do this I got this
Yeah, all I do watching land man all I do is talk like Billy Bob Thornton the entire time and it makes SJ really happy
No, but I was trying I was trying to think about my man on the ship and I was trying to think about like
Even he came up on like my family call like one of my brothers is really into it
my brother's thinks it's a piece of shit show right and it was kind of like right, you know them fighting words and
I mean I kind of I get both arguments
Everyone's right
but you know we talk on this like these these weird times and I and I and I was basically kind of like
thinking about
Basically, it's the word obsolete
That okay, that is the word like I've been trying to find a way
to put my
To encapsulate I think attention that's driving all this shitty decisions
Like I think like so many things that are shitty about this world are not you know themselves?
I think caused by one thing. I think they were dominoes were pushed, right?
Whether we're talking about like trumpism or you know iced tensions that kind of stuff like all these crazy shit that's happening
Uh-huh, and I think like if I'm trying if it was
As I go my walks, I was thinking about my friend on the other ship and then my brother's fighting and and I was like I
think that like part of
Like AI and technology and basically tech tech has taken all of the money, right and
All of the talent and now has seized all of the power right like like tech runs
Washington and Tex runs all of media now, right?
And the billion and the billionaires are more richer than us than ever
Right, and then I think like basically like we're all afraid of
Our ways of life becoming obsolete from one facet or another because of this right? Okay. Yes. I see what you mean now
yeah, and so like if I feel like shit is on my doorstep and
You tell me to help other people because they're doing something
experiencing something less fortunate and
I feel like no one's talking about what's making my life unfortunate
Right, like if I feel like I'm cool and not obsolete if I feel like I am thriving and you tell me to help somebody else
Yeah, I go like cool. No problem
But if you come to me and say, you know, no one's doing stuff about these poor people over here
And you're like wait mom about to lose my whole fucking way of life
Yeah, I just got back from the food bank and you're telling me that this is a problem over here
And I don't process that tension properly, right? I don't process that like I think my way of life is going away
Right, you know like even we do on our show we were do we're like, oh, we're just three white dudes talking
Right and so like we reduce ourselves to be like wait the world should be more diverse. We're not diverse enough
We're getting older. We're done with mainstream things. We're over here in our little pocket, right?
like we do to ourselves a little bit, you know, I would say actually Paul's probably the biggest voice that fights against it and
Like and then you tell us to help go help something else is there's a little bit like I'm trying to fucking hold it down here
Right, but you don't want to admit that you don't want to admit that I'm trying to hold it down
You don't want to admit that you're afraid of losing it all right
You want to have pride and stuff like that. So I feel like this ups and then I think the the
Lockdown and pandemic just poured accelerant all over this tension
And I think like it's really hard to shake that feeling
So like I'm thinking that like I think that's a way
To fight against what we're doing in a positive way
I think you have to identify if someone is feeling like they're being made to feel obsolete
And you have to find ways in yourself and other people make them feel like they can thrive and I feel like if you do
That that would be the first way to put a some force against what we're doing
It's a very deep thought it was on my mind
It is all because I was watching land man and we can we can talk about something else
I have a very embarrassing story to follow up with this if this goes nowhere, but
But well, I think you're seeing it now that
the ultimate solution
For people in a political place where what they're doing is terribly unpopular
Their ultimate solution is I'm going to give people money
But unfortunately that should always be the thing the government should be helping
the citizenry
To elevate their standard of living constantly. Yeah, we came up we came out of the pandemic with the wrong lessons learned
when they did help bolster us and give us what was tantamount to a
Basic, you know median basic income, right? You know subsidy
Yes, which we've got and and you spoke by the way. Here's your money back, right?
But we spoke to pride if that's exactly right Jacob and we spoke we spoke to pride right or you talked about that
Yeah, we need to look at that in a whole nother way
We have conditioned a generation to look at any benefit coming from the government as something unnecessary
shameful and to be repelled
Right, which is crazy
Because what are you paying them for then if not not work for you? We're all working together
They are our society to our our representatives. They are our representatives
They are to represent our interests and if our interests currently require that we get some kind of financial
Benefits and incentives to move forward in proper way. Not just certain groups is that's what's happening already
Farmers are getting a lot of incentives real soon
Yeah again yet again, and it's still not gonna be enough
But we don't even have to we don't even have to bag on the farmers
No, I can just talk about the things we're already talking about. Let's just talk about the people in the oil industry
Oh, we're just being handed money fucking forget about it. Yeah, exactly
People who are being handed money for no reason, but when but when little
People look at the same kind of thing we have we have been
Socially engineered to be like, oh no, I don't need anything. I don't need help. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's a handout
It's a handout on the small scale on the large scale. It's capitalism, right?
Yeah, no, I mean, yeah, it's it's it is strange and complicated are it's bizarre
And and yet these giant men coming to you with tears in their eyes
No, I'll tell you who else has giant men coming on them with tears in their eyes all the time wait
I didn't get that part of the story yet
That's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by the fine people providers purveyors and makers of
Greek yogurt, that's right. It's just a commercial for Greek yogurt for 2022. That's from the scoop Henley
We're talking about Greek yogurt
right
that that it that it that it that it that it that it
Hey
bison
You needed some yogurt. I got you. I got you. What do you need?
Come on over. He said a good Greek stuff. Yeah. Yeah
This here yogurt got a little bit of the tomato and a basil, huh? Yeah fresh from the Greek island
That that that that that that that that that that that hey, why don't you put a little is a Greek yogurt all over your piece?
of pie
Over your piece of pie. How about you put a little bit in it inside of the pasta sauce, huh?
And just a little bit of zest now. That's a Greek
Hey when you're here you the family
Extra Greek yogurt everybody with a breadstick. Yum. Yum. Yum
Hey
Pasta fazul a Greek yogurt. Mmm. Yummy. Yummy
Mangia
Yeah, no, I don't think me it like like basically while I was wrapped up in that beautiful commercial
Sure oil tree sure the farms sure all of college sure all of medicine sure all like like we have been quietly
Always training wheels and pushing every industry, right? And so, you know
We have never the successful industries, right?
And so like we have never
Been a purely capitalistic thing but as soon as we want to point at something and say stop doing that we say like see
It's not capitalism. It's socialism but raw
but the truth is we've buttressed our entire country almost every aspect of our lives with government effort and
It's been successful. Like it's what's made America
And so it's like we improv Matt improv
Improv in all of its forms
Vallis Bolan was paid by the federal government
This is again an initiation of theater games for children during the Great Depression
Yeah
Improvisation is germinated from that government investment an entire my life
My life from this woman's brilliance and the government funding that made it possible for her to do
That's it. I agree the only way for improv comedy to be successful is to have government backing
It's the fucking fact. I would love to have a little look government jingle in my pocket every time I was teaching
Holy shit make things real smooth, but just in general that needs to be
yeah, we and I mean art is the first thing that gets it in the dick and
Yeah, you know and that's things like so like I mean, we're very much out of our depths in terms of talking specifically about
Hello
But I think part of like we're trying to get people to chill is to be like is a little bit of a wake-up like hey
We've been kind of doing this with everything the whole time and it's not just just the lefties
It's not just the righties and it's not just what I'm so mad. What you're saying is the solution to this might be
Education. Oh good
good
Then that's assured that we're gonna move forward in a positive direction then because that's gonna be a priority going forward
Linda fucking McMahon
Is running of all things I can't even watch WWE anymore
Not even no, not even like recap shit. Nothing. I haven't watched it for like a year. It's terrible
It's just like this is your it's the oh, it's because real like a professional wrestling
I know it's done so much damage to the earth. I
Listen to the whole fucking planet. They're gonna have a fucking UFC fight
By the same company
Gonna go
Yeah, you're right
I'm definitely gonna go ice cream socials going to the UFC fight on the front
Press pass, of course, although. Oh, did you turn out ever did you see the explosive new?
Confession I don't know what you'd have you how you actually say it. Are you familiar with the
Canadian screw job
Yes, the Montreal Montreal screw job, right? Oh this this is the the the Bret Hart thing Michael's
What happened so Bret Hart was wrestling in his hometown
he was gonna retire from the WWE or leave the WWE go somewhere else or whatever and
They said you have to turn over your heavyweight belt to the new upcoming star Sean Michaels
And he said not in Montreal not in my home city. Like we have to we'll have to do it another at another match
Okay, and it's like this is where I'm from and this is where I can he's a lot of pride in me being the heavyweight champion
you know, we'll do a fight there, but it's got to be a different time and
Vince McMahon and Shawn Michaels colluded behind Bret Hart's back and the Bret Hart
Is fighting out of some chokehold or something like that and gets basically called out and loses the match and the look on his face
When the bell goes off and thing is over this and they're gonna give Shawn Michaels the belt the look on his face is
Crazy and it is a famously
When the most moment in WWE where they broke quote-unquote k-fabe, right?
When it's a very shoot moment. Yeah, meaning it was happening for real
It was happening for real and I think Brett wouldn't like punched Victor convinced McMahon
I think like or something like that. At least spit on him. I think according to this he spit on him
Yeah, spit on him and maybe punched him too. Yeah. Yeah
so but it made so much news that they had to break k-fabe to break the the the
fakeness of wrestling because it was it was leaking out that this was a crazy thing that happened behind the scene. Uh-huh. Well
Bret Hart has just this past week come out and said
You know Vince McMahon would always come on these specials whenever they were talking about the Montreal screw job and Vince's famous quote was
We didn't screw Brett Brett screwed Brett
Right. That was his favorite. Okay
well
according to Brett Hart
It may be more accurate to say
Vince screwed Shawn Michaels
Wait, there is a rumor now
Hart has put forth that
Michaels and Vince McMahon mate where hat were flatmates at that point and that is a big reason why
Vince put the belt on him and went through all that rigmarole because that was his current love boy
I find it hard to believe that you can sleep your way to the top and WWE under Vince McMahon
I know right unless you're willing to take a shit directly to the face
It's not really uh, you're not your career's not really going to of course. This is what happened. This is obviously what happened
This big man is a depraved animal. So the Montreal mudslide proceeded the Montreal
Exactly exactly and that's how Brett that's how Shawn lost his smile because he got shit
Yeah
Pretty ridiculous pretty finally something that we know about the Leon saying it's the Montreal steamer. That's right
That's a good one Leon. Yeah, so that's I didn't I didn't look into it too far
I just heard enough from what I heard and I was like, okay, but
Brett's usually a pretty straight shooter
Or he knows this is the most scathing thing you can say about Vince McMahon
I may maybe but why now? I guess cuz I don't know I think is he just was that your limitation
He wants to kick him in the nuts. Yeah, maybe he just wants to yeah
He would have come out I did follow this a little bit and I think it would have come out sooner had this actually been
the case
Really? Don't you think they didn't?
Know media if you know anything about the ring boy scandals and all the other bullshit
That's been going on and all this stuff that's followed the McMahons around for decades
It's only really been having a light shown on it very recently that's had any kind of
Consequence or public discussion about it. All right, that's reached. I hear you. I hear that. I hear that that makes sense
Yeah, so I feel like yeah, I feel like there's a great deal more scrutiny
I just think we're more attuned to it now and it's one of those things where back in the day
You get stuff like that. Wow, he's a he's a very successful man. Of course, he's got haters, you know
Of course, there's people after him and gonna start rumors and stuff
But now with all the things that we do know about him and his and his crew
And I don't I don't want to stick my neck out
I don't want to you know stepping at the way these guys are they can be very litigious, but I don't think he's really that
Damn, I think that's I think that's fake
I think basic man as a fake
Don't sue me up
Okay, okay. That was that's Matt at hey scoops.com. That's who said that
Tan is real. I think he's just I think he's just in a tanning bed. I don't think he uses like oh, yeah
He's gone out of the beach
No, so let's fight about that. No, so I speak of the wrestling
I've grown to love John Cena as peacemaker and John Cena as a comedic actor
Sure, and I never watched any wrestling with John Cena. Okay
So five five move Charlie
So he sat down to do an interview with Bill Simmons
My favorite sports podcaster and talked to him for like over an hour. I was like, alright, let's do it
And then it was all about his wrestling career and man
You couldn't pay me to ever listen to John Cena talk about his wrestling career ever again
The problem with that so I bought the I bought the problem with that ball one of the problem
I bought the WWE game from I'm gonna say three years ago two years ago three. Okay three years ago and
Let's say three. Let's say three. Whatever
the
Conceit of this one was Cena right, but not only Cena it was
Cena recapping his biggest losses
So that's the story mode that you play through you play through you play through as John Cena
Through his biggest losses
Yeah, and the thing and he he entered he is interviewed between each match
Talking about what he learned and what the atmosphere was like during this match and special things about the opponent
I kind of thing and it just comes off so crazy
Because like it's very
This isn't real right right it's not real things he's saying aren't really reason
Oh boy, I knew coming into that ring. It was gonna be a real slobberknocker going
I knew my competition with Andre the giant was gonna be exactly. It's like well, I don't think you ever fought Andre
But like an example because I listened to this fucking interview yeah like he had to lose very badly
To Brock Lesnar so that okay put up against Brock Lesnar would be then considered
so
Amazingly great that they had to be a champion so in order to put I think it was Roman Reigns
The belts he had to get beat beat up by Brock Lesnar very badly that'd be okay
They talked about like trying to like you know way that now hard that was physically and everything else and you know
It's not it shouldn't be
Correctly no one gets hurt. I mean yes, it's painful. It's stressful. It's very athletic
But you shouldn't be injuring people. It's dangerous shit. It's dangerous
Okay, hold on because I want to come back to this we do have to go to a sponsor real quick
but I want to come back to this so we're putting a pin in this and
We're gonna talk about this right after we get back from the following sponsor who?
Also, I don't know. Where's a lot of tight spandex shit
Today's show is brought to you by tube
your
Colossus your one-stop shop for tubes tube irk. Oh to
tuberculosis tuberculosis
Jacob go over tube urkulosis toss it to me
Following sponsor today shows, but you might tube urkulosis your one-stop shop for tubes
Nailed it Bell's a triple scoop 2025 go fuck yourself
Welcome to tuberculosis
Your one place to buy tubes. Yeah, I just need a tube
What kind of tube do you want? Oh?
It'll be a drainage tube. How about a cathode ray tube for televisions?
I just needed a drainage tube for a for an ice maker
and
Drainage tube would you like one constructed from?
PVC
Yeah, that that seems yeah, it seems good very well follow me to the PVC
tubile here at
tuberculosis
the largest tube store in all of
Transylvania oh
I didn't see the PVC aisle over here. Yeah, this is good. This is I I can find what I need here
Thanks for your help very well. I leave you to the aisle
Let's see. I just need a continue your shopping on them on molested
Yeah, yep, yep, thanks
Find what you need
No, no not yet. You haven't you never left. I have other options. We have all tubes
How about something few people think of we have two worms?
two
worms here at
tuberculosis
Worms, whatever you want place them inside of you the children of the night
What beautiful music to make oh?
Ever heard the worms make music they ever heard them sing in the moonlight
No, well you could get some and do it and the best way to hear them is by listening through a tube
It will amplify the worm song
You know I thought you were nuts when I came in here, but you're winning me over, but I don't have any nuts just to
Enter a check out
That's a good sponsor seems like a good company. Oh, they are great. I don't know how they make any money I
Think from this just let people buy the tubes they want but the guy doesn't have any fasteners
Tubes ain't worth shit loose tube loose tube loose tube don't do fuck for you
So I'm thinking about pro wrestling now. Oh, oh danger zone is there
Is it just impossible for people to pretend that someone is better?
Than us or has won a championship or something like that
Is it just impossible for us to just pretend that that's happening do we do we just fall into?
The trap of this is real every time
Is that why it matters to the WWF people or WWE people who wears the the fake championship belt?
It's so strange because like I guess
Cena on this last trip around
Came close to if not
eclipsed Rick Flair's
title runs I
Has I have seen that yeah, because it's seen it seen as like I don't remember it
Couple more time 18 or 19 time world champion something like that. Yeah. Yeah anyway, it's but it just like one or two
above Rick Flair
but you know
What does it mean but having having the belt doesn't it doesn't actually mean you haven't actually won
You can't win it 17 times if you don't lose it 16. So I think the fuck is that I think
Good point. That's just good. That's also true. That's math. That's that's just the math checks out on what Paul just said
But I mean like really like you guys there's 16 guys who are clearly better than you
They are still beholden to the crowd
The crowd the live crowds and they're in and their audiences for sure. Yes, if they make the wrong person champion
They hear about it, right? Oh, yes
You know it matters it matters for their business that certainly matters. Yeah
So there's like I'm thinking of is more of like the mental
Is it is it possible for human beings to pretend that someone is the champion?
Without kind of falling into that trap
Well, I think we should have every mouth finger butthole champion on this podcast come back on and talk about their lives after
Winning mouth good boy. Good boy. I don't know eyes have changed you watch enough of that wrestling and it just gets
It gets crazy
I'll never know I will never I will not put myself to that test
My kids I would have if my kids got into wrestling I would have my kids did not get into wrestling
Yeah, and I think thank goodness and I still love the old classic goofy shit
I think it's funny as hell, but I appreciate it just for the the goofiness of it all
But then you start if you start to really scratch at it. It just gets sad real fast
You know, well, you know most things, you know, they're they're playing a spots on me
If you scratch at them long enough, it gets real sad. I
Often just stare at Jacob until I feel sad
That's basically what I do to get it going just stare at Jacob while he's scratching when I want to drum up your sadness
Do that?
Paul yes, what are you asking for your wife for yourself for Christmas? Oh
nothing
Do you guys get each other stuff? Yeah, I got I got and a
New coffee maker and a giant and of Green Gables box set. Oh, by the way
Yeah, I want to step on this for a second the amount of like
Ho-ho-ho someone works for Starbucks didn't have a good coffee maker at home
Stop pretending like every fucking employee of Starbucks becomes like some coffee goddess where they have to be like
Instruments or whatever like it was possible to be a regular human being with an aged coffee maker
This is the problem get a job at Starbucks. It was only it was only like three years old
It was a good coffee maker. It just happened to get a stink bug in it and that made her physically unable
Look at the coffee maker anymore
She legit just vomited everywhere. She couldn't look at the machine anymore without getting physically sick
That's the there was nothing wrong with this coffee maker. It was fancy Dan
You know you press the shit and the new one. I got her fucking fancy Dan
It's got a milk steamer thing on it and all kind of hoodly-hoo. It's fancy. It's a nice coffee maker
It was like, you know almost $200 coffee maker that I got on super sale at my old Target
So that is now paying for itself there a little bit milk that milk spritzer doubles as a Swedish hot bidet
If you use it properly an upside-down Swedish hot. Oh, you just gave me a nightmare. Oh
God damn talk about oh for fuck's sake to the Swedish hot bidet
I can think a few things more horrific then
Superheated items up the asshole and I know that was a medieval staple slow nowadays
Oh, come on take talk it slower. No, no, no
How hot is hot what I just what would you do like the the original the original pain?
of a blistering asshole and then
What happens after that's even worse, oh my god, oh
What happens after you shoot stevie milk into your asshole then the trouble start that's what I but it really does it
It's Pandora's box
It's Pandora's butthole
You have opened Pandora's butthole and she will never shit right again
My wife and I decided last night to not get anything for each other for our anniversary. Our anniversary is December 27th, right?
Leon's got the same situation in the chat here. His December 25th is
Birthday Christmas and anniversary January 3rd. He married the Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. He did
Somebody's got to I'm gonna January 3rd. Hey, technically my mom did for a while
That's true. She was a bride of Christ. That's right. Yep. Well that's separation. That's what she get it
Well, he still owes her alimony. He's real deadbeat that fucker. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
You get hit the holidays hit SJ hard because the my birthday is on December 18th and this Christmas and then they're on our
Anniversary is right after it. And so this year we're just we're gonna take a trip
We've loosely decided there will be a trip for the anniversary at some point. Nice. Well, that is probably
Your guys's love language if I can be corny, I think so, right?
I think so like I don't think you guys care about getting each other jewelry
We get we are people that especially me. I mean, I'm worse about it than SJ is if there's something I want
I usually just get it same
Like in November SJ's like quit buying yourself stuff. Other people need to be able to buy you things for Christmas
I just my luggage. Oh man, so I was
carrying
So I get I get off of the ship at Fort Lauderdale and there's a place about about five blocks away
You got to go down down to the light make a left about five blocks is Joe's Cafe old-fashioned diner
And after you've had like deluxe
fucking opulent cruise ship food for
For me two meals a day
You just go like oh a diner with regular fucking eggs and regular fucking bacon
Let's go and I often just you know, skip the uber line skip it. It's it's chaos in the port, right?
So you just I just drag my bags
This this trip I specifically was only doing 20-minute sets
So I tried to only have one case and so I'm dragging my stuff and I'm going like man
My case is heavy. I could put too much stuff in this case and I get all the way
To Joe's and I don't realize I'm like covered in sweat
And then I look and at some point at some point I busted a wheel off of my giant case and I didn't realize
I was and I didn't realize I was fucking lugging you were just dragging
Dragging a case for blocks. Did it recognize I was sweating? Yeah. No, it's it's toast, right? Oh, yeah
So I should ask for luggage for Christmas when said I went on Amazon immediately ordered myself a luggage thing that I wanted
And
But I was laughing at like I thought I packed too much stuff and instead I lugged something like an ogre
like half a mile
And I was like so gross. I didn't realize how gross I was I go like go to get a table and I'm like just like
Like the waitress is like, you know, okay, can I get you water and I was like using the napkins like wipe?
Cuz it's yeah Florida Florida humidity and I was like, oh, yeah, I just was the swamp
Monster sitting down at the diner was so gross
But yeah, I should have made me bacon bring it to me now
I'm hungry. I have a thirst bring me coffee
But yeah, so I should have I should have asked for luggage but I just got myself it
So you guys had terrible about skip the anniversary December 27th anniversary, do you do Christmas gifts?
We'll do Christmas gifts. Yeah, we're gonna we're gonna go out of town. We're gonna see family
Actually, we're gonna we're recording double today
Because because Matt and I are both in and out of town and around next week
But yeah, we're gonna go see some family and do a little dual holiday stuff with them
And then we'll do as she and I do do gifts for each other
But I mean, well, we'll see we'll see what happens. She
You're not a jewelry person, right? She doesn't get you a fancy watch or something like that
but she might give me a little a little not a watch no, but she might get me like a
Like a ring or a bracelet or something like that every now and then but not not usually no
Yeah, well, she's got to worry about how much weight you're putting on that hand the back of the hand, right? That's right
Another cotton ring
Always did on her own tart. Yeah
Saw the joke it didn't really you think about the consequences but
That's what she's oh I thought about the consequences. I was fine with them. Yeah
But like fancy dinner, do you think like a fancy dinner is your one of your go-tos?
Yeah, well, we'll do like a like some kind of fancy dinner or something like that while we're while we're out somewhere
Yeah, we we do we try to do more kind of celebrations. I think than than gifts Andy cheek says oral
Is that part of your that's everyone's love language there Andy?
Putting the language in love language, you don't need a therapy book to get to the court to the crux of that guy right there
Yeah
Put my dick in a box. Merry Christmas
Who's the box? It's you Paul speaking of things in a box. Let's do a little scoop mail. Oh
Love it because he's taking time to blow himself. Yeah
We got our first holiday card of the season
Sweet oh, we love it from Ryan and Josh
Merry Christmas 2025. It's some lovely pictures on here. It's all the the the the family pictures
My my camera is crazy. So you can't see it, but it's a but it's nice. We love we love getting holiday cards from the listeners
very sweet also got
This little package right here from rich scoop dear Matt Paul and Jacob, please find enclosed a couple of books
I found at charity shops recently. There is a copy of magic for everyone for Paul and a copy of all new
Star Trek from Matt
That's fine
Sorry, Jacob. I didn't find any books on whiskey for you
No ducks. No mayo packets. So nothing for you this time fucking you in the face. That's rich scoop
Rich scoop some people would say it's cruel to send gifts to Matt and Paul through me
But uh, but yeah, that's it seems fine
Paul bought me the Batman absolute Batman
Thing first right you did get through it. It's great, right? Yes. What is that? That's that's the comic book?
What yeah, yeah Scott Snyder wrote Batman for a while the the main title for a while and I loved it
He did the whole court of owls and then on some really wild stuff
really loved that so I
Checked out his new stuff and this absolute Batman is just knocking it out of the park right now
So yeah, I got Matt the first I guess it's the first five books. Yeah in the series
What'd you like about it? I like spoilers possibly I guess yeah
Yeah, but it's right off the top is Alfred's not his he's not rich and Alfred's not his butler, right?
And so Alfred is just this other guy who's like a trained worldwide assassin and he's like he's actually like meant to like track down
Track down a group days of tracking down. He runs into Batman and they realized they have to work with each other
And it's really different deal
And yeah, it's just it's just a it's Batman is younger guy
And he's more this really frustrated almost like UFC fighter type person. It's really it's really clever. It's very cool. Yeah, yeah, I
Quite like it and yes Cooper Nova girl the new absolute Batman drops today
I haven't made it out to the comic shop yet today
I might but I'm not buying it week to week
But this current week's issue the cover is the Joker the reveal of the absolute Joker
Looks insane looks like some kind of fucking creature. I don't know how they're gonna explain it, but it looks pretty wild
I guess again. I'm behind
By like five or six issues. I guess closer to ten by the time the trade comes out
But I guess he went through his whole killer croc thing and a lot of his friends are now becoming
The villains that they were destined to become. Yeah. Yeah, that's happening
Yeah, so it's interesting. Yeah all all his childhood friends end up being the rogues gallery that Batman ends up fighting
Yeah
All right, is the it's just it's just take away take away his wealth being a superpower is probably one of the smartest things and
Coolest things you could have done. Oh
Yeah, that is interesting. Yeah
He's a little more
Gotcha. I mean he he was always making up for it with with more more tech genius stuff
He well, he was always the Tony Stark of the DCU or vice versa
I don't know how you really look Batman and Iron Man are more
akin to each other than you might think and it's always myself but in this like
Michaels right that's exactly right. He's a
He's a construction worker. That's what makes him such a buff freak. That's a big part of it
like he's he's going to school for for you know, Kim and all kinds of
Super science stuff, but he's a construction worker. So like the Batmobile is a giant dump truck outfitted with armor and shit
Yeah
Let's do a little we're gonna save that email we're gonna do a little jock versus nerd oh shit
Yeah, I'm on the hunt for balls
The hunt for balls
I'm Batman a real real quick Batman one last thing lemur creamer was asking do they keep his parents?
So in this retelling he loses his father early on that's definitive, but his mom is still with him
So that's a whole nother dynamic to that. His mother is still
To very much alive and very much part of his life
So that's interesting it is for the city and then they're after like politicians and stuff. So it's neat. Mm-hmm, huh?
All right
We're gonna scoop it today from the Swedish scoop
The categories are Casablanca colors stupid questions and sports Giants Paul. You're up first what you want Casablanca
Casablanca 400 if she can stand it I can play it demands Rick. This is the it
It is the song
You must remember this a kiss is still a kiss. It's a as time goes by
as time goes by
And when two lovers whoo, they still say I love you or that you can't rely
The fundamental things apply
The colors for 400 this color is this
Tickled me this color ends in our pull
Don't overthink this one Jacob. Yeah, okay. Okay. I time I know this one
This color is pinkish purple pinkish purple pinkish purple
It's purple could be nurple. It could be it could have been herbal. I would have gotten that one wrong Matt light herbal
This color that I have recently made up ends in herbal I'll go colors for 800 and striat
Nothing really rhymes with this color, but you can force a half rhyme if needed
door hinge, that's right
That's the one that Eminem keeps screaming about
It is orange
Paul
I'll go with Casablanca again
For 800 there are three bars in the film Casablanca. This is the primary setting for the movie the Blue Oyster
Bum bum bum bum bum I
Think it's just called Rick's but it might have some other
Name to it and I'm gonna know Rick's Rick's cabaret is that strip club that used to go to in Vegas all the time
You just got you god. I think it's just Rick's
I think Rick's cabaret was the strip club in Vegas that got shut down by the city after multiple fatal
Stabbings in their parking lot in a single month. Oh god
What about played against Sam's is that one still going? Oh, that's I think it's still playing
Fucking you can play it again and again
Yeah, I think Rick's. Oh, what Rick's Cafe Americana. There we go. I remember before you hit it. Yep
Oh, he says Rick's is fine. Okay. Okay, but but I remember just for you think
Paul you got it, right? You got it, right? I knew I knew there was a subtitle shit. Okay. Okay good
I'll try stupid questions for 400 this vessel starts with T ends with T and has T in the middle
I will travel I will travel by tit. Yes, I'll say Titanic. Oh
a teapot
Because it's a stupid question because it has tea in the middle. It's like I see what you do
Yeah, Matt
Well, I'm stay away from stupid questions
Stupid I'll go with a sports Giants for 400
One of the NFL's oldest teams. They actually play in New Jersey
That would be the the Boston Steam Party
That's right Giants New York Giants the New York football Giants, of course
Paul
Casablanca
Did you watch Casablanca recently 1200 daily double I've seen it many times though. I really enjoy
There are three bars in the film Casablanca, this is the secondary bar in the city of Casablanca
Oh, it's gonna get me on this one
Does that mean it's the secondary bar in the movie or just the secondary bar in the city of Casablanca?
This is the second best bar in the city of Casablanca it was not mentioned in the film
I mean, maybe not. No, I'm sure it was mentioned in the film
Rick's - I'll say the cafe the Jazz Bistro
the Jazz Bistro is
I'm sorry the Blue Parrot
The Blue Parrot
No, it goes anymore enough. No, I don't like I don't like it to that degree of minutiae yet. No, I
Should not speak. I'll try
sports Giants 800
At 1994 sports comedy starring Rick Moranis and Ed O'Neal
This was also a fake field goal play run by Michigan State to beat Notre Dame in 2010
Are you just asking for the name of the movie I think so
Oh, yeah. Okay little Giants little Giants was the name of the movie and I guess Michigan State ran a play that was called little Giants
Yes, great interesting
Come on is that about
Is that about like peewee football players? Yeah, that's it young that's it. It's um, what's the what's the baseball movie with?
The bad news bears bad news bears. Yes, that's exactly
version of bad news bears got it
Matt you're up. I will do colors for 1200
Kermit taught us all that it's not easy being this color
Purple sorry light purple light easy being light purple green. It's not easy being green
Paul I'll close out Casablanca for another daily double. Let's go
Bar in Paris the last place he saw Ilsa before Casablanca
The Chateau Marmont the Chateau Marmont, I'm sorry. It's la belle horror. Okay
That's me I'll close out colors for 2000
the G in Google's logo are this color the G's and Google's logo are this color I
Think I think they're red. I'm gonna say red
Shit, it's all their blue
That was my second guess Matt a score check Matt is now crushing us 2400
I have negative 1200 Paul has negative 2000 and you got stupid questions or sports Giants
There's daily doubles out there, right? There's one daily double left out there as well
Meet boop. Let's do sports Giants Jacob. Let's do it
Now it's for 2400 originally the New York Gotham's this team changed its name in
1885 and played at the polo grounds until
Matt we were just talking about the polo grounds earlier
You were saying you were listing all the teams that have played there. You love talking about the polo ground. That's Rick's third bar
That's right
Hey, welcome to the polo movie Casablanca the New York Gotham's changed their name in 1885
Come on over to the polo referring. We'll have ourselves a good time. I
Think I think this is shoot. I think it's referred to baseball and I think this is San Francisco Giants
Okay
So what you wanna go with you wanna go John San Francisco Giants, yeah
Yeah, the New York baseball Giants and it is a team that became the San Francisco Giants. Yeah, I think I think you got that
Yeah, okay
Paul
Stupid questions for 2000. Let's try it. This has four legs and bark a
Natural wood table
All right, it's me I'll try fuck you guys look like a sports Giants for 2000
The American Giants a Negro League powerhouse who won seven league titles between 1920 and 1933 played baseball at Southside
Park in Kaminsky and Kaminsky Park in this city with Southside Johnny
Yeah, it's outside Johnny and the Asbury Jukes
Played it Kaminsky, where's Kaminsky?
Where is that who plays at Kaminsky Park now or somebody's somebody's played at Kaminsky Park recently
Shit
Southside Park in Kaminsky Park, I can't I cannot think of where the fuck Kaminsky is it's driving me crazy
Yeah, I guess I'll pass Matt. Oh
Is it just it's just a city
Is the answer for this just the city
Yeah, yeah, just the city. Oh, I think this city. I think it's Chicago. It's Kaminsky in Chicago
It is Chicago. Yep
Really?
Is not Chicago disco is dead riot started
That's right. God damn it. Yeah, you're a Chicago
You got stupid questions 800 or 1200 and by the way, Matt's winning this game you have
You you have two more weeks to get educated about that incident here in Las Vegas. That's right
Disco show it the link is closing by the way. Yeah
Disco show with the hey, you might have a wife again for a little while. I
Seem to have seen that as a silver lining on my wife. Maybe didn't see it one as that sure
Thought is less of one. Yeah
Oh
Stupid questions for 800, please. Let's try it. Absolutely. Everything ends with this letter
It's gotta be Z. Oh
I thought it was gonna be G
Lee
Everything ends with this letter could be G - yeah, it could be G. Absolutely
I'll go with G. Let's try G
It is the letter G. I'm gonna roll guys. I'm on a roll
You know Paul close it out the category and the game stupid questions for 1200
1996 John Landis box office bomb this movie starred Tom Arnold as the lead character Stanley
The stupids
The stupids. Oh my it is the stupids. I forgot about that. What a great book
Turned it
Matt crushed us with 7600 squeaker. I'm in second place with negative
1200 Paul is a third with negative 2800 that's from Swedish scoop
Thank you, Swedish scoop
If you want to send us a scoop and he just like that one or a price of sprite jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock
Versus nerd head over to hey scoops comm hey scoops comm right there on the home page
You can make us any of those jock versus nerds
You could send us an email do all those things over there at hey scoops comm by the way
I should take it when Paul did a real Montreal steamer there. I
Should wait until disco closes to to talk about this pet peeve. I have but I'm not gonna
Okay. Okay, the disco riot Kaminsky Park was not an actual event that killed disco
What it was was an event that was supposed to be it was drummed up by a radio DJ a DJ
I'll do it and it ended up being this incredibly racist event where everyone brought a bunch of blues and R&B records
To it and then it broke out of this riot, but it was basically racially fueled
So it's one of the most weirdest reported things and it's used as a cornerstone in the disco show where I'm like
That's not what happened as a baby child of the 70s. I remember growing up with that whole disco sucks thing
Yeah, coming through his baby turns out that whole mantra that whole movement was just anti
LGBTQ I stuff man. It was just oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. It's all racist and racist
Yeah, but I mean, you know, it's all just stems from don't let people enjoy
The music that supports their their lifestyle and their culture. It's just awful. It's awful
This country is crazy Steve doll. Yeah, that's the DJ. I think right Laurie. Yeah
You know, I think he ended up didn't get in trouble for all that shit
Well, they're like a lot of destruction of property and stuff that happened on his. Yes
It fucked up like the ballpark and stuff. Yeah. Yeah, I think he ended up being on the hook for some financial stuff
Maybe even did some jail time. I don't know back when there's a bunch of like niche cool podcast companies coming out
There's one I'm trying to I can't remember remember it now
But there's a podcast that interviewed basically a black usher from Kaminsky Park and his
And in his breakdown of what happened the day disco died. It was a really great podcast
At one point he basically has to like hide and run
Because of what was happening in the park. What's that on? I have to find it. It's been so long
It's listen to it forever ago, but obviously that a huge impact on me
Swedish scoop is saying that was a doubleheader and the second game had to be forfeited
Laurie is saying it was a huge deal, but I believe they had to just call the game. No jail time
Yeah, oh boy
Yeah, there you go. All right. Well, let's end on that high note, huh fellas?
We're not just a racist cesspool now we always have been
So we got that going for us
If you want to help out though, if you want to just you know, we're living in this terrible racist cesspool
It's awful. But if you want to help out and maybe I don't know
Nick get science back involved get over to preaching fun comm preaching fun commas
We can go to sign up for our patreon and you can be part of our experiment
Oh
What experiment the experiment is we're gonna each take a billion dollars and we're gonna see if we can be better billionaires than the
Current ones out there. That's right
This is gonna be for science people if you don't want to go to farts in a bag
I was sorry preaching fun comm you go farts in a bag dot biz
If you even understand if the billionaire experiment is supposed to work like AGT we're either you can get you know
Parts of the billion over 47 years or you take a one lump, you know buyout for 300 mil
We're willing to do both versions of the experiment. I'm ready for either one
We will do the control we'll do we'll do all the different things that you're supposed to do in experiments
We are willing to do both versions of the experiment. I'm ready for either one
Experiments. We are scientists
Don't worry about it. But if you can support us on hey scoops
Comm no patreon preaching fun comm fun comm that's where you want to support us. Yeah
We really appreciate it
Making us part-time thousandaires really helps out also a tremendous. It certainly does
And if you can't help us financially, can you turn someone on to our podcast?
We have an obelisk scheme not a pyramid scheme. Those are filthy. I would be terrible
you take one person and one person alone and see if they want to check out a few episodes of our pod and
See if they want to buy something from tuberculosis
You know
It's a great store
No fasteners
But yes loose tubes. Thanks for this thing. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
We sell extra-long macaroni, why don't they sell extra-long macaroni that's like spaghetti link?
I want the spaghetti link macaroni
What would that be called? I mean they have kind of that thing. No, they don't spaghetti link macaroni
Buccarini what?
That's not that's not spaghetti that's someone else's lip noodle. Oh, no, it's oh no, it has a dessert
It's they're serving cookie cookie for dessert
No, they've got a it's a long pasta
Bucati and I a long thick hollow pasta from Italy Buccanati
Buccanati
Bucca Bucca Bucca teeny Bucca teeny Bucca teeny is long
Yeah, it's like a long long long macaroni macaroni. Yeah, how about real long? How about like way too long to fit in the pot?
There's one piece of Bucca teeny
[BLANK_AUDIO]