RingCentral will completely transform the way you work.
It gives you built-in AI across all your business conversations.
Your phone system has an AI receptionist that answers calls 24/7.
Your video meetings have AI that takes notes instantly.
Even your contact center has AI, so you can help customers faster.
It all comes together in one reliable platform for effortless AI communications.
See for yourself at RingCentral.com.
RingCentral, voice of your business.
Oh, hello there! I'm so glad you're here,
because this is the part of the show where we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
RingCentral's AI receptionist uses voice AI to answer on the first ring,
so you'll never miss a call again.
In just a few minutes, you can personalize your own AI receptionist
to answer questions, route calls, schedule appointments, and even send texts in multiple languages.
Plus, it's easy to scale.
Create unlimited AI receptionists across any phone system.
It's all powered by one reliable platform for effortless AI communications.
See for yourself at RingCentral.com.
RingCentral, voice of your business.
Now, I'd like to thank Tony Cowley, Travis Jaguri, Wendy Loomis.
I have one other one here.
Technical School Port! Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
Tony Cowley, Travis Jaguri, Wendy Loomis, and Technical School Port.
If you--
RingCentral's AI receptionist uses voice AI to answer on the first ring,
so you'll never miss a call again.
In just a few minutes, you can personalize your own AI receptionist
to answer questions, route calls, schedule appointments, and even send texts in multiple languages.
Plus, it's easy to scale.
Create unlimited AI receptionists across any phone system.
It's all powered by one reliable platform for effortless AI communications.
See for yourself at RingCentral.com.
RingCentral, voice of your business.
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Oh, hello, everybody!
Hello!
Paul has asked Jacob and I to watch the "Masters of the Universe" movie trailer.
That's right.
That's right, for this episode.
This episode is all about the new "Masters of the Universe."
I don't think all of it.
Yeah, all of it!
All episodes!
It's time for Matt Maddly's ice cream social sitting over there in Indiana.
It's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pittsburgh.
It's Paul sitting in Vegas.
It's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're preaching fun.
Are we twitched up?
We're twitched up.
Matt is still freezing.
He took us off over there in Indiana.
Me, too.
Yeah, we're recording this on a Monday.
My feet are a little chilly.
It's just shy of 70 here, and I am slightly uncomfortable.
I have my house shoes on.
They're taking care of most of it, though.
So don't worry about me.
Did you get a snow measurement, Matt?
They said 20 to 24 inches fell here in Indiana.
Oh, my goodness.
That's double what we got.
That's crazy.
Yeah, and because of that, they don't serve breakfast anywhere.
I went on a very long, long, cold walk with Mike Mills on our Tech Guy scooter.
We were inept, but it changed our opinion of where we were staying.
So we were finishing up our show.
We did a show in Leicester, Kentucky.
Then we did two shows in Cincinnati.
And we were supposed to go out to Bloomington and do a show.
It was canceled.
And then we're heading to Chicago.
But it's another show being produced out here by Mike Mills.
And so we were going to come out here to see a preview of that show anyway.
I don't know if it's public yet, so I can't say which show it is.
It's a tradition that people may or may not have heard of.
But so we're deciding whether to snow ourselves into Cincinnati
and then just see if the roads are good to come out Monday to watch the show.
Yep.
And then go to Chicago after that or snow ourselves in in Indiana.
Where you're at and be right there.
And then just be here for three days.
And that will be fun.
And so we voted for going to Indiana.
So we finished our show and it was already snowing when we were packing up our van.
Yeah, it was really exciting.
And then we did you have that like that that that feel of like we got to get the fuck out of here or we're not going to.
Yes.
Yeah.
And and so off we went.
I don't like that feel at all.
Off we went hit the snowy roads driving at a brisk forty miles an hour.
Good as we head out through the snow.
And we're in a big sprinter van.
It's nice and heavy.
So we're not worried about feeling good.
We weren't something to slide last like hour of the trip.
It was supposed to take like an hour forty five minutes took three hours three and a half hours.
Yeah.
And we were following a snowplow, which is one good because we're driving on a plowed street.
The plows go about fifteen to twenty miles an hour.
Yeah, they're not they're not known for their quickness.
No, no.
So we were just like it was a crawl to the to the place.
Now we're staying at the spot called the Grant Street in here in Bloomington.
And we call the head twice to be like we might come out late tonight.
Is that OK?
And then we're definitely coming out late tonight.
And so we pull up and the Grand Street is actually like three houses converted into a hotel.
So, OK, you check in the main house, but then you get sent across the street to the other house.
So we pull up at about three o'clock in the morning.
Mike goes in and we hear nothing for like ten minutes.
We've just taken three and a half hours here.
We're finally at the place we want to be.
And now we're just sitting in the car.
And then Mike says you guys might want to come in or whatever.
So we couldn't find we couldn't find anyone at the hotel.
And then finally someone woke up and came our way and said,
oh, gosh, I don't even have the passwords for the computer.
I don't think I can check you guys in your house.
Right. And this is things like Mike Mills.
I've had him on an abracadabra.
I should have him on here.
It's very funny guy.
Also called calm like jacket again.
Oh, shoot. You're clipping all this calm guy.
Yeah, like at all.
This is what time though.
This is what time in the lobby of the hotel 3 3 15 in the morning.
Yeah. And you've been you've been driving behind the snowplow
for how long about an hour.
And I asked him to chat earlier who drives who was driving.
Initially, I was driving as I picked up the car in Cincinnati
and I drove it to Lexington and I was trying to drive.
And Mike Mills does so much for the tour.
I produce it and also does all of the logistics and stuff.
So I thought I would drive but because it was snowing
and he lives in New York and I live in Nevada.
He thought he was maybe a little more qualified to drive in the snow than me.
He's at least had a more recent practice most likely.
Did you tell him Jersey born?
Yeah, no, he's aware.
He's aware.
Y'all didn't have an argument about it though.
Yeah, much like Springsteen people know where I'm from.
They figure it out.
Yeah. So we go.
So your dreams is where he's from.
Well, we got to stay here.
I guess like in the main building like at least you got to have at least in the lobby.
No, but like a key to open up some room somewhere like they have to be something right.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
So she says yes.
And so we start opening the van.
It's still snowing, right?
This is this is the right.
This is the start of the God.
Yeah. So we're unloading all of our stuff.
And then one of the really funny things that happens that both Mike
and I have tricks that involve can't liquids cans of stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
We can't leave that in the van.
So we bought we bought enough for the whole tour.
So we had to like haul every all of our liquid props flats of cans of water in.
Yes.
So to unload everything and we get halfway through unloading our van.
Oh, no, I figured it out.
We can get you guys checked in across the street.
No problem.
Oh, god damn it.
So then we pick up all our stuff and load it back into the van.
I again, Mike, Mike, when he came out to explain this, he was like,
I can't fucking believe this, right?
Like he occurs.
He never curses.
He's like, I can't fucking believe he's he's shoveling snow off of the thing
because he hasn't told us yet to unload our van, but he's clearing the way
as he's cursing to like he's clearing a path.
So I tried to like do an end around and I grabbed the shovel
and I run across the street to like pre I start shoveling the other house
out so that we can load our stuff into the place that we are staying.
Gotcha. OK, you're thinking ahead.
Yeah, the van can't get out of the parking space that it's in because of the snow.
It's like we're doing the wibbly wobbly, you know, rock it back and forth thing,
trying to get some grip, you know, and we finally get loose.
It goes up at three thirty in the morning.
We finally get loose.
And it's we're on a one way street and it's snow covered, right?
So it's definitely one way street, one lane, one way street.
And we get to the middle and we're about to unload our stuff.
And just another car just pulls up behind us.
Oh, shit.
And it's four in the morning.
Yeah.
Mike drives around the block, right?
It takes like five minutes a good night.
And I'm like just shoveling away.
I have no gloves.
It's 15 degrees and I'm just shoveling away, waiting for the van to return.
Luckily, you're only 19 years old.
Furiously shoveling away.
It's still snowing like a mother.
And then he pulls back around.
Yeah. We open the door and another car pulls up in the morning.
Also, this area is a grid, right?
Like it's not complicated.
You can go around us, right?
Yeah. And then so Mike pulls up and he actually pulls up just so we can
get the car out of the way that reverses back.
Yeah.
And we unload half of our van through the path I've shoveled into the house
that we're staying at and halfway through a car.
I can see it coming from blocks away.
Our hazards are on.
It is a giant Sprinter van.
The doors are open.
We are moving in a chain of four people unloading.
There's clearly something happening.
This thing happening and a car just eases right up behind us and stop.
And I just said, we're finishing the unloading and I yelled at the team
and I shot the dirtiest look to the person in the car.
Like, are you fucking kidding me?
You saw us.
You can literally right now reverse 50 feet.
Yeah, and drive left and just go a different way.
Yeah, so they waited better than where I was afraid.
The story was going.
I was afraid.
The story was going like I saw the headlights.
He was coming ran right into the van.
Oh my God.
Yeah, no, no, no.
But so yeah, so we loaded in.
Thirsty Scoop says good thing.
No, they want to change in your pocket.
Right, right, right.
So anyways, didn't have the password.
It's the wrong place like we were pretty kind of a we were making fun of this hotel for a minute.
You know, right.
Come with it.
So look at us.
We're still doing it.
Got the two mornings later.
We said we're going to try to get breakfast.
Now, you know, famously, there's a restaurant here called The Runcible Spoon, which I have loved visiting here.
I've talked about the Runcible Spoon.
Runcible Spoon is what it's called.
What's that mean?
Who knows?
What's the word Runcible?
The Runcible is the word.
What's that mean?
We looked it up before, but it was unmemorable because we've had this conversation before.
But I because I came here when I came.
I played when I played Washington, Indiana, Aces Bar Grill.
I know that we've had this conversation before because there was it was Google remembered it.
Yeah, because I call it.
What did it mean, Jacob?
It's a nonsense word invented by Edward Lear, most famously from Owl and the Pussycat.
Okay, great.
Yes, he will never remember that again.
No, we'll forget next time.
It's a nonsense word.
Oh, it's like Jaleco cats.
Yeah.
All right.
Great.
But even dumber.
And when I came here, I said I said it was like it was like it was like all the waitresses were like different Manson girls.
Like that's what it was like college kids.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever.
And it's hold the wall.
I remember that part.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, that's what we all remember.
That's why we all want to go back.
Right?
So principal spoons still not open for the blizzard didn't recover at 24 hours.
No dice.
We walk out and about to all of all of Bloomington and all these restaurants are still closed this morning.
Yeah, we came back into the the host house of our three house hotel to get coffee and very kind host who wasn't the guy
who's up at three through the morning is like you guys doing all right, you know, like, oh, well, we just tried to take a walk.
And we didn't make breakfast here this morning because we thought we were going to walk somewhere else for breakfast.
But every place is closed or whatever.
He goes, oh, well, let me see if I can get some at least get some like fruit and stuff together for you guys.
Some vittles rustled up.
Oh, and he goes downstairs and he comes up because, you know, the cook hasn't left and we still have eggs and bacon.
You guys wants to make up some eggs and bacon.
Yes.
Yeah, they went out of their way and gave three of us like an amazing immaculate breakfast.
How kind Wow.
And I was like, we are and I just turned to Mike.
I was like, we are eating our fucking words right now.
We've been trashing this place for 24 hours and they totally outclassed us today and they were just everyone.
There was an incredibly nice.
I went above and beyond and so I have nothing but amazing things to say about the Grand Street in right.
Except that maybe they should have that past check in process is a little little if you take the put a post that know the password
somewhere that everyone knows, you know, so you're like the password password.
Who cares?
And maybe we were just pissed about driving, you know, 42 to 15 miles an hour for three and a half hours.
But you had also called ahead and giving them the heads up.
That's it.
That's a lot of you gave them the heads up a couple of times.
We gave them that's something that is something.
I'll tell you who else is something.
These folks really are something.
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by go.
Go phone go Michael Jackson's my skulls.
Jack's son had exercises for dancers.
Michael Jackson my skulls.
Jack son head exercises for dancers.
Hey, everybody, I just want everyone to know that I have opened a whole new store.
It's called Michael Jackson's my Jackson's skull exercises for dancers.
And many of you don't ascribe to phrenology, but that's ignorant.
That's just ignorant.
Phrenology is key when it comes to dancing.
The way your head's aerodynamics work with the breeze.
That's if you can be a better dancer that way.
Hey, are you saying that you that you're a good dancer because of your head shape?
That's exactly right.
Michael Jackson's head shape is perfect for being a good dancer.
If you know anything about phrenology, then you'd understand, but you don't know.
Phrenology is the study of the shape of the head and the discovery of attributes and traits.
It's been disproven time and again by science, but embraced by horrible racists for generations.
So why are we talking about it?
Because that's the only way I can open my school.
You're ignorant.
I had to open my school based on phrenology because I'm not a medical doctor.
The only doctor I know gives me mama's milk.
Give me milk.
Give me some milk.
I need to sleep.
Give me more milk.
Check out.
Well, speaking of he, it happened.
Ladies and gentlemen, it happened.
There is a new masters of the universe movie coming to theaters this year, June 5th.
Yes.
Are you excited about this?
Paul?
I'm very excited about this.
Okay.
Are you excited about how excited Paul is about this?
Are you excited for the inevitable crash?
I watch.
Oh yeah.
He's going to hate the movie.
He's going to hate it so much.
I don't know.
I don't think I am.
So they've been trying to make different masters of the universe projects for a while and this
one finally came to fruition.
Do you know the story behind that?
Well, I mean, the other ones have been put on the back burner for several different reasons,
probably because they were shit and Mattel didn't want their brand damaged, but here's
why I'm hopeful.
The Barbie movie, the Barbie movie made a fuck ton of money and was also critically
lauded.
So that combo put into Mattel's mind, Hey, if we put some auteurs and some actual directors
in charge of this stuff and maybe hire some actors that actually know how to perform,
we can put a little gravitas on the stuff.
Well, they got a lot of other really great people in this movie too.
A lot of really great people in this movie.
So I think they've learned their lesson with Barbie that this can be another real bankroll
move and possible, you know, legacy protector if they do it right.
And so I don't think they're fucking around.
I know.
So Paul, what are your thoughts on the trailer?
It looks great.
You just think you're just generally excited about it.
There wasn't, there wasn't a single part of it that really stood out to you.
Everything.
I mean, it all looks so like, okay.
So here's the thing.
I already talked to the scoops about this in the chat before, but I'll talk about it.
So you've got Marlena Glenn, who was an astro, a human astronaut from earth.
That is Queen Marlena, Adam's mother, right?
And the trailer focuses on her talking to him as a child, sending him away to earth
for protection because likely because Adora had been captured and war was continuing.
That's all.
That's all a real story.
Yes.
That's all.
That's all a lore.
What's the word?
Cannon.
This is cannon.
Yeah, this is legit.
This is why I'm excited is because the real ones know that this is no, this is real.
So I assumed watching this trailer that this was made up something like this, this whole
premise of like sitting earth and then, and then protecting all this stuff.
Now that never happened.
That never happened.
However, Adora did get stolen away by Hordak and it would make sense for Marlena to want
to protect Adam as the last heir to the attorney and throw really hard to take you seriously
with their names like Hordak involved, just telling you how it went down.
Hordak stole baby Adora.
It's pronounced sex worker deck now, pimp deck for those who know.
He keeps that pimp deck hand strong.
I mean, Hordak's not even in the movie is he's even, he's even higher up than Skeletor.
He's the one that trained Skeletor.
So you know, this is going to be, they're leading, it's going to, it's going to end
up leading to like sequels, which is going to be really cool, but no, this is legit.
Marlena is from earth.
He man is half earthling, half Eternian.
That's part of the lore.
That's part of why he is magically imbued.
That's part of why he is this, uh, you know, character that transcends world or just fuckable
Mormon.
I mean, now the blonde hair and all that, that's an unfortunate side effect from, Hey,
we have to make this unique IP.
Conan doesn't have blonde hair.
Let's do that.
Because the origins of the masters of the universe toy line are steeped in a lot of
weird shit, but not least of which Mattel was in talks with the Conan movie guys to
possibly do a movie line, right?
Yeah.
But some of that, then they had to really deflect hard.
So they made it sort of sci-fi, a little more spacey, a little more weird, a little more
fantasy even than Conan.
And they changed the look of he man drastically to keep him away from the Conan comparisons.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
No, he man and Conan could never change it super drastically.
One of them is a mostly naked dude with a big fucking sword.
And the other one's your mom.
That's absolutely, it's absolutely from Conan.
Let's let, let's don't get it twisted.
I know that.
I know where that stuff like, yeah.
But Fisto shows up in the trailer, which is fantastic.
Fisto's in there.
Spy cores in there.
In there.
There's no Hordak in the trailer, but Fisto's just a coincidence in the IP.
I'm sure Fisto's in it, but it's great.
I mean, they start off with showing Adam in on earth and he's working for HR and they pan
over his desk and it says Adam Glenn, which is, you know, his mom's last name.
And it's got the he, him pronouns on there, which is a hilarious joke.
Of course he's he, him, he's, you know, he man, uh, just fucking hilarious.
Oh, so hilarious.
I laughed so hard when I saw it, but not only was it funny, it's also a litmus test.
Matt, how much would Paul hate that joke in any other movie?
No, no.
What do you think, no, it's a litmus test for people who can't stand pronoun shit.
And if you, if you focus on that as like a negative thing and don't get at the joke of
it all, I don't, I don't have no hope for you.
He's called he man, what the fuck?
He is all pronoun.
So then, you know, he goes into this toy shop, somehow he finds out that the, the power,
the power sword.
Why would I watch the trailer if you're just gonna walk me through it?
This is what we're doing is we're reacting to it.
Have you not watched any reaction videos?
Do you not know how this, how reaction and breakdown videos work?
I didn't know we were turning our podcasts into a reaction video to the trailer that
it wasn't what I would like to do.
That's what's happening.
All right.
Well, what do you want to talk about?
About it?
Hold on.
My next question to you was going to be, why did you make Jacob and I watch this?
What was your plan?
You just revealed your plan so we could talk about it.
Yeah.
I had already figured out that that was his plan, Matt.
And so I was about to pivot by saying, Matt, did you have any thoughts on the trailer?
I here's okay.
Let me just address why I don't think it's going to do the same thing.
Barbie did.
Okay.
Barbie was a comedy.
Yes.
It was like a really like fun comedy, like Casper, like really sophisticated comedic
performers and it had a nice kind of feminist anthem and it was coming out against Oppenheimer,
which was incredibly masculine.
So it was a really good way for like women to rally on opening weekend because there's
a good, any contention that just basically wasn't interested in watching a move, a three
hour movie about a guy who invented the atomic bomb was going to maybe go out and have fun.
This, I did the Barbie Heimer day.
It was a great day.
This movie is made for neither crowd.
I mean, he's made for kids.
It's made for, it's made for Paul.
That's what I think.
I think it's really made for Paul because Paul, you said, can you make your kids watch
it?
I'm trying to think if watching this trailer, whether, whether my kids would be into it
or not, I'll find out.
I'll find out.
That's what I want to know.
I want to know if the, if a generation removed from all the hype has any interest at all.
Does it, does it look interesting to people who don't already know what it is?
Yeah.
I'm seeing, I'm seeing yes from a lot of people who don't know in the chat.
Tell us if I, in the chat, I'm curious if you were not familiar with the he man IP already,
did this trailer make you, make you want to watch it or continue to not care about it?
And actually like, I was just trying to make jokes, I mean, I'm not, I wasn't like, Oh,
what the fuck about this movie.
I just was like, Oh, this is kind of, I basically felt like I thought the trailer was kind of
weird.
And I was like, who is this for?
That's what I thought when I watched it.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, here's the thing.
Uh, we don't know, uh, how it's going to be, uh, and I'm ready to hate it.
I'm ready to hate it.
I hated the first one.
I did not like that.
Paul is always ready to hate movies about things that he loves.
That's what I mean.
Like I'm not, I'm not Paul is sincerely prepared to hate this film.
This is a rare instance though, where I'm optimistic going in even after seeing the
trailer.
I'm just shocked that you're optimistic.
Me too.
When you believe me, I am as shocked as anyone.
I was ready to just be like, Oh fuck, they did it again.
But no, this looks very hopeful to me.
When you text us last night to watch the trailer, I thought it was that we were going to rip
it apart.
No.
I mean, you can rip it apart if you want to do that.
You can rip it apart if you want to.
I've already, I've already erased my notes.
Once I heard your change of the tone, I raised my notes.
No, do you have a fucking notes?
If my notes, full of shit, uh, if there's anything that stood out to you as weird, I
mean, I don't know if I've ever taken notes.
It's hard for them to, it's hard for them to fight the whole Marvel influence.
So that's clearly there.
That's clearly there.
And they, and they've definitely toned down the colors of everything.
So it's not quite like it's not that eighties bright.
I'm concerned, but it's also not as dark and dreary as the first movie.
It's brighter than that first fucking movie about the giant cartoon tiger.
You have concerns about Cringer and battle cat.
I have concerns about the giant cartoon tiger and being able to take scenes with the giant
cartoon tiger.
Seriously.
I mean, see, this is another thing that two options to go with Cringer or battle cat and
you insist on saying cartoon tiger.
I do.
Because that's what it looks like in the trailer is a giant cartoon tiger.
He's a giant cartoon tiger.
Uh, I don't know.
I, I, there's something, I mean, I, I'm a sucker for that kind of stuff.
I'm a sucker for anthropomorphized kind of animals.
I did love He-Man as a kid and I did love it because I loved Coda, Coda the Barbarian.
I definitely did.
I definitely did connect the two and like it accordingly.
Uh, and I watched the cartoon and stuff when I was younger, I say I liked it.
I liked the toys.
I never really watched the cartoon.
You guys are younger than me.
I watched Shira.
Yeah.
No shit old man.
I know, but you really are.
I mean, I was that thing, that fucking show got me right in the zone.
It hit me exactly right.
And I know I'm a victim of the Reaganomics, uh, fair broadcast standards, half hour commercials.
Fuck every Gen X kid, train them to buy shit thing.
I know.
I don't know.
I just, I really, I was impressed with what they're doing with the source material.
I'm pleased to see good performers in key roles.
Idris Elba as man at arms.
That is Idris Elba in the movie does definitely that, that is a check in the plus column for
sure.
That's a big check.
Alison Brie is Evil Lin.
Sure.
Alison Brie is awesome.
Um, and I'm genuinely a bigger Jared Leto fan than you are in general.
Well, that's great.
And Monarella Buchanan is the sorceress, uh, Inara from Firefly.
Right.
Like, yeah, like that's a great choice for the sorceress.
They've made some really good choice and I don't know who the actress portraying Tila
is, but she looks wonderful too.
And you know, you talk about the whole feminist thing, Matt, I think it's not Tila Tequila.
It's not Tila Tequila.
Not get the role.
I think you have to remember, uh, Matt, that I scoop shooter on the same page, that, uh,
women did a really good job of putting female characters forward in a time when that was
not common.
Like Tila was right there with Adam and, and, and he, man, like she held her own.
She held her own.
Same thing with the sorceress being the key to the whole secrets of Grayskull and the
leader of the, of the whole, you know, good guy forum.
And then of course, She-Ra being the evolution of that.
And then it being a very female fronted show.
In fact, they hate women.
No, I'll tell you who else hates women.
And that is the following sponsor by, oh, we shouldn't do this one, but I'll read it.
Bill Cosby's guide to consent with a new special forward by Sean pity P. Diddy combs.
That's an excellent joke.
We're moving on.
I'm reading that for high coup scoop, but we're moving on.
Yeah, this is much, much cleaner.
Gloria's glory hole hand drill from the sound man scoop in 2021 that is Gloria's glory hole
hand drill.
Keep it clean.
Gloria.
I heard you got a hand drill, hand drill.
I heard you use the hand drill and the wiener sticking through the holes.
You don't have to use it.
If you don't want to, it's fine.
Just leave it all behind.
Hand drill Gloria, Gloria, watch out for the wieners.
Gloria, here come extra wieners sticking through the glory hole.
Grip them with the hand drill.
Don't touch them with your hands.
Your clients will understand.
Gloria's hand drill glory hole and her hate scoops to check out.
There you go.
No, what I will tell you, Matt, back in the day, the Mattel executives were very upset
because he man was cutting into Barbie sales because they had, they had some female forward
characters.
And especially when princess of power debuted, uh, you know, that's kind of why they split
the lines.
I hear you and I, I don't mean to cut you off in that.
Like I knew it.
I didn't know that.
I didn't process that.
I was talking about like current marketing power and sure, they have some great females,
some great prominent roles.
The titles, literally he man, it's literally and the masters of the universe and the masters
of the universe.
Is it called, is it called he man and a master's universe?
I think this one might just be another master's universe.
I can't remember.
Okay.
I don't know.
I'm finding that.
I don't know who's got top billing.
I can't tell you what I'm trying to say is like that can all be true from a writing standpoint.
It's not from a marketing standpoint, right?
Like it's, it's not, oh no, for sure.
I was a kid.
I didn't know it was called masters of the universe is called masters of the universe.
Great.
The universe and it's femininity.
Like there's nothing, nothing about the trailer that I saw was like, Oh girl, girls are going
to love and rally around this empowering.
Well, and the poster has, you know, they do love man facing off against scale tour, two
dudes looking at each other to fight.
So yeah, I get that.
But it's not, it's not the same brand as, as Barbie, it's not, but this is, but this,
this is like, you know, when the Barbie, I'm more like coming from this with like the Barbie
versus Oppenheimer thing was such a phenomenon at everyone in Hollywood was racing to figure
out what the takeaways were going to be.
And none of it seemed to be that women led things can be funny.
And instead it was like, we can do more movies with other toys.
And I don't know if that was the right takeaway from an executive lesson, but learn the wrong
lesson or not.
They've got good people on the project.
Look, it is now maybe, you know, it is existing IP that's been out there and those are things
that people want to make movies out of.
And so yes, for people like yourself and other people who grew up with Heman and yeah, maybe
my kids will, their friends will want to go see it and they'll revitalize the franchise
with the kids.
You have to do that.
You have to try that.
Yeah, and scooper Nova girl in the chat is like, what, you don't think women won't love
a mostly sexy, naked man with abs fighting?
Of course.
Good point.
It's not, you know, you can put the, he meant some serious man candy.
He may point, uh, you know, so there's something he said there, episode title.
He man candy.
That reminds me of a story I heard, uh, over the weekend of, uh, uh, your good friend,
Murray Sawchuck, Jacob.
Yeah.
I love Murray.
The guy played, uh, I love how this bit has just morphed into just me and Murray just
being genuinely good.
He gave me that amazing parking spot at his wedding.
That's right.
Um, uh, uh, someone said, uh, they were playing a college gig and they were like, you were
so different than the last guy we had.
And I was like, it wasn't, they go, uh, they go Murray Sawchuck.
And he said sarcastically, did he show you his abs?
Yeah.
And they giggled and said, we touched his abs.
Oh no, he does like an app parade, a big part of his show, the app parade.
You can have his autograph.
He can rub his abs and make a wish.
Just do it.
Just do a pencil, a pencil rubbing, a charcoal rubbing of his abs.
And etching.
And I just, you just push it against his abs and rub and get up and get the, like, like
going to the, going to the, the wall at the Vietnam Memorial.
Vietnam Memorial.
Yep.
Yeah.
I get, I get how it goes.
Uh, that's crazy.
Well, uh, yeah.
Uh, you know, I don't know, I'm just really excited for, uh, I watched a couple of reaction
videos from many of the creators that I follow who are into action figures, of course, primarily
Pixel Dan.
I wanted to get Pixel Dan's take because I've been following him for decades now.
You like Pixel Dan?
Talking He-Man.
Pixel Dan is, he wrote the book on He-Man.
He literally has the full compendium of all the action figures and all that kind of thing.
He did a review for every figure that came out in the classics line as I was collecting
that line.
So he's how I kept up with it.
And he's got two young boys now himself.
And they of course know him as a toy enthusiast.
His livelihood is going to toy shows, talking about toys, creating toy videos.
So he drags them along to toy shops all the time.
They themselves are not really into He-Man, those two, his two young boys, right?
Because that's dad's thing, you know, and that's been his thing since he was a kid.
However, when he showed them this trailer, then they asked to get the castles out and
they're playing He-Man again after seeing this trailer.
So there's something there too.
Interesting.
Like you're right.
Then like as an adult looking at it, seeing it as like derivative of Marvel, but in terms
of like what kids are growing up on, they're growing up on Marvel movies.
So if it feels like it scratches that itch, it's probably gonna make kids more interested
in seeing it.
Absolutely.
That's true.
And, you know, He-Man is a superhero.
That's what it's about.
It's about empowerment.
That's what the whole superhero thing is about.
And that's, you know, I mean, Marvel is no less guilty of going to the lowest levels
of marketing research to do, you know, I don't know if you're familiar with Secret Wars.
You familiar with Secret Wars?
Yeah.
But that all came from just marketing.
Marketing meetings about what do kids like?
They love the word.
They love secrets and they love Star Wars/wars.
And so they go, "Oh, let's just do Secret Wars."
We actually changed the department of our government to the Department of War.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
We love that word.
That's what we love.
That's what the kids love.
Kids do love that war.
And now it's a secret war that's going on in broad daylight that we can't really talk
about.
It's wonderful.
So fun.
All these secret wars.
Where's the fucking Beyonder to fix this shit?
No, he started it.
He started it all.
We need Adam Warlock.
That's what we need.
No, but that's the whole thing of where do you find that-
Wait, if they say that you have a right to carry a thing, but they shoot you because
you carry the thing, do you have the right to carry the thing?
I don't know.
That depends on where your political allegiances lie.
It's so confusing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's weird.
I don't know how it all works.
It's a real head scratcher there, Jacob.
Yeah, yeah.
God damn it.
It sucks to be in 30s Germany.
I'm going to watch the trailer again.
I'll probably figure it out.
This is part of it too.
This is coming out like a week later, so we should say who knows what other atrocities
have happened.
Oh, God.
That's true.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
We are recording this as a couple of days earlier than we usually record it.
That is one-
In the two extra days, who knows?
Right.
One other thing about the Masters of the Universe property and the movie, it filled me with
some hope, which is something we're in desperate need of right now.
It's certainly what cinema should be focusing on, for sure.
He-Man is a bright spot.
The Masters of the Universe has been a big bright spot in my life.
I love the mythology behind it, and that's the thing.
Like I said, they are adhering to the true lore and mythology.
They're playing with it, but that's fine.
That's what it has to ... You have to do that.
You have to toy with it a bit, but I love the interpretation so far of the vehicles
that I'm seeing and all that kind of thing.
They look like rotons going through the sky, but you couldn't have a roton looking like
a fucking roton if it looks stupid, but it looks cool.
It looks really cool.
What's a roton?
A roton is the vehicle that you would push along and it had a-
What's a spaceship looking thing?
It looked like a ... Well, it looked like a spaceship with a giant saw blade.
What is it in the trailer?
It's the spaceships that have two, a little orb being encircled by two spinny big-
Got you.
Because the toy, that was the toy with the ... It was on wheels, right?
It had a wheel at the base and as you pushed it, the saw blade would rotate and it looked
like ... It looks like a saw blade around a car.
Yeah.
Right.
Which, as an adult, I recognize isn't terribly practical.
Mark Gates in the chat.
Yes, you're exactly right.
Roton is the stuff you put in queso dip.
Yeah.
Get yourself a can of roton and melt some ... You are ready for some salsa.
Paul, did you see the Superman trailer before the Superman movie came out and what did you
think of it then?
I did not watch the Superman trailer.
I purposefully did not watch the Superman trailer to keep myself-
Yeah, I was surprised that you were an advocate of watching the trailer because you are traditionally
not a trailer guy.
I know, I know, but this is so dear to my heart and I didn't want to get spoiled.
You couldn't help yourself.
I didn't want to get inadvertently spoiled.
I was like, "I'm just going to go and take it in," and I was pleasantly surprised.
I'm really enthused about the direction I see so far.
There's every possibility it's a shit show.
We haven't heard any dialogue.
We haven't heard anything.
Who the fuck knows how the story is going to play out, but it looks good having Marlena
give that gravitas of like, "We hid you away so you wouldn't be killed by these ... There's
real threat there."
That's kind of cool.
If you had to send your child to another planet in order to not have him kidnapped by an evil
space dictator, that's kind of neat.
That tells me that they're respecting the fact that Adora was kidnapped in the past
and that traumatized the fuck out of Marlena, so she sent her child to another planet.
That's big.
I don't know.
Not since the last Starfighter.
Paul, who are you going to dress as when you go to see it in the theater?
That's a good question.
I've been thinking about it already.
What I'm going to do ... I'm just going to put on my favorite He-Man shirt.
That's all.
I'll just put on my favorite Master's Universe shirt.
You're just going to show up as the OG.
You're just going to show up and be like, "I've been here since the beginning, and I'm
still here."
Yeah.
I mean, I'm a big guy.
I've always contemplated doing Ram-Man cosplay.
You should go as Orko.
Thirsty Scoop in the chat is right.
You should dress as Orko.
I used to have an Orko outfit.
It didn't look good, though.
It was just one of those hoodies that also had a mask and a silly hat.
It was okay.
It just didn't look right.
I ended up losing that in the move, but ... Yeah, and Orko hasn't shown up yet, so that's another
thing that could happen.
But that could be another thing.
They might just be pausing that for now.
That's another whole thing.
I'm going to dress as an incredibly angry goose, and people are going to go like, "Oh,
Fisto.
I get it."
It is a shame how fast I got that.
It is terrible, it says bad things about me as a human being, how fast I got that.
Fisto the goose.
Oh, my.
Yeah, so I don't know.
And then even ScooperDoverGirl was asking early in the chat about popcorn buckets, and I'm
like, "Oh, shit.
Who knows?
Who knows what kind of popcorn we have?"
Oh, the amount of collectible shit you're going to be ...
Oh, well, that's the whole thing.
We've already solicited like 10 new figures, and who knows how long that line will go.
Oh, yeah.
Paul is going to be broke.
I'm already collecting three damn He-Man lines as it is.
Preachingfun.com, everyone.
Preachingfun.com.
Please.
Paul is going to be on the street.
Help me afford my plastic.
Paul is going to be destitute.
Please.
He is going to be on the street, people.
Please, I need my plastic boys.
Preachingfun.com.
I need my plastic mans.
Will keep Anne McFeeters home.
What does it come out?
June 5th.
Oh.
I believe.
I'm so angry that it's not until June, and we have to hear about this until June.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This was going to be ... This is the big discussion I wanted to have.
Again, I just want to lay it out there that I'm very hopeful.
I'm very pleased with what I saw so far.
I am ready to shit on it if it turns out to be garbage.
You know I will.
You know I hate ... Oh, yeah.
I hated that latest Tron movie.
I love the soundtrack.
I'm not partial to my IP.
I'm not blind to the holes in my IP.
But that's also ... You love to hate things that you love.
The beautiful thing about Masters of the Universe is that it really is a tool for imagination
and exploration.
Back when I played with my figures, most of my lore came from what I'd read in the little
mini comics.
I would ignore a lot of the filmation stuff.
I loved Hordak.
I do not care for the filmation depiction of Hordak at all.
That's hashtag not my Hordak with the ... and snorting like a pig half the time.
No, thank you.
That's not evil to me.
That's just a weird ... That was a weird choice.
I said good day, Hordak.
I do say good day, Hordak, because he's a cool looking villain.
So we'll see, we'll see, but I can't wait.
I teared up, the movie got to me, the preview got to me.
It doesn't take much.
I'm on thin ice already.
The whole country's falling apart, and then I see He-Man come hanging around.
I'm like, "Oh."
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, that's ... I had a really weird thing happen to me the other day.
What's that?
I was walking down the Strip and a party bus, like a big limo party bus, which is not uncommon,
comes rolling down the Strip right next to me.
I'm on Vegas Boulevard there, I'm on the sidewalk walking down the road, and this bus has rolled
down windows.
So all the windows are rolled down, and the whole thing is just filled with what looks
like, I don't know, 13-year-old girls, 12, 13-year-old girls, young tween girls, and
they are all leaned out the bus windows.
Heading to the Trumpet Hill?
I am the only person on the sidewalk.
I'm the only person around.
They are all leaned out the window, and when they see me, they all do the hand thing and
yell the 6-7 thing.
And they keep on driving, and I believe that has triggered a full mid-life crisis.
They broke your brain.
I think they broke me.
I'm done.
Oh, God damn.
I am out.
This has ... I stood there for a minute, just going, "I don't even know ..."
Just dumbfounded, huh?
Should I step into traffic?
Should I ...
It's a wrap, huh?
Like, what should I do now?
And I'm walking, I'm like, "I am more than halfway through my life.
I really am."
Like, I have lived more years already than I'm probably going to live.
Yeah, that's probably true.
Yeah.
What the fuck was that?
That was so weird.
That's a hell of a way to measure it with that, with that kind of event happening, to
really clock that.
But yeah.
Those children with their Terminator vision, which they wouldn't understand by reference,
would scan to you and say, "Old man engaged.
Six-seven him.
Six-seven old man."
Also, I was like, I wanted to go and stop them and be like, "Hey, the six-seven thing
is out, guys.
That's done.
I don't know where you guys have been, but that is simply out.
I know that.
It's weird that you don't."
Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Jacob.
Thank you.
It was and continues to be dramatic.
See, if it's any consolation, I think you've lived at least two-thirds of your life, you
know?
I'd be not sorry.
But see, this is another thing, Jacob.
If you were like me and you were obsessed with a childhood toy property for the majority
of your existence and, you know, even when there was lean times, even when nobody was
talking about Mass of the Universe, you were in it, in it to win it.
And now it's back.
Nobody had to take that away from you.
You know what I mean?
But this is the thing.
Nobody wants to.
I was back.
I feel like-
Jacob, think if they were making an Archie Manning video.
Archie Manning movie.
Now, bring it back.
Oh, now I get it.
Now I- thank you, Matt, for clarifying that.
Now I understand the stakes involved.
That's what it does.
That is what it does, though.
It does kind of give you a reset.
That's the level of like a Bobby A. Bear documentary, a deep cut for you fucking Saints fans out
there.
That's right.
Let's do a little Jack vs. Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Of tweets on a bus yelling at me.
To pass the time we took in a comedy special, Eric Dillman recommended his friend Renan
Hirschberg on YouTube.
Okay.
His newest special is called Morbidly Jewish.
And I won't try to do anything butcher too much from it, but the one that really made
me lots of maybe left really hard at it.
But what was he goes?
You know, Harry Potter got in trouble for like, you know, having, you know, the people
run in the bank where these like goblin people and they were like, Oh, that's anti-Semitic.
Yeah.
The green gods.
And that's anti-Semitic.
And he goes, isn't watching made up creatures and thinking they're Jewish stereotypes more
anti-Semitic than the green gods being anti-Semitic.
I put nothing.
Path JK Rowling though.
She's got intentions.
Right.
She's actually, you know, she meant all definitely if you have a chance to got Morbidly Jewish
on YouTube.
That sounds funny.
Nice.
What's his name again?
Renan Hirschberg.
R-A-A-N-A-N.
And you say he's Jewish?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's do a little scooperty here.
We got a scooperty from Smitty Scoop here.
Like you know how, you know how I'm from New Jersey, Paul?
Right.
Uh huh.
That's how you'll know that he's Jewish.
Got it.
Yeah.
Because Matt Donnelly told you.
Got it.
Gentlemen.
Well, Matt won the first Smitty scooperty of 2026, but it may be a bit premature to
declare that Matt has officially dethroned Paul and Jacob and reclaimed the Smitty scooperty
crown.
So I prepared another scooperty for your enjoyment to give Paul and Jacob a chance to redeem
themselves.
Here we go.
The categories are Winter Olympics, Geography, Sitcom Spouses, and Hard.
Oh shit.
All right.
I'll start with hard for 400.
Here we go.
Rachel, what's for dinner?
I'm married to Rachel Maddow now.
My giant brother still wants to fuck my wife.
My mom and dad are mean.
Oh boy.
What sitcom was Paul talking about?
That has to be Everybody Loves Raymond.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
That was so confusing, Paul.
That's a crazy quote.
I'll try Sitcom Spouses for 1200.
Okay.
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Heaton for nine seasons on Everybody
Loves Raymond?
Oh my God.
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Heaton for nine seasons on Everybody
Loves Raymond?
I'm really glad because when I was answering the last question, I did have to pause for
a moment and go like, wait, was it Everybody Loves Raymond or Everyone Loves Raymond?
Everybody Loves Raymond, but the name of the wife.
I got to pass.
I don't know.
I love that Smitty Scooperty is the one thing that drives me to finally watch an episode
of Everyone Loves Raymond, but does it pass to me?
It does pass to you.
It passes to you.
It's a pass for me, Jacob.
Yeah.
It's a pass for me as well.
Deborah Barone.
No way you would have a last name.
No way.
No.
Did she not take his last name?
Who cares?
Theography for 400.
Does Colorado share a border with Idaho?
Yes.
Let's try yes.
No, both Wyoming and Utah share a border with Colorado and Idaho, but Colorado and Idaho
do not border each other.
Dammit.
Oh, I'm seeing in the chat.
50/50 shot.
I'm seeing in the chat.
Barone was Raymond's last name in the show.
He was Raymond Barone.
Oh.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
It's me.
I'll try.
He was his name.
Barone.
R-O-N-E.
I'll do Winter Olympics for 400.
Daily Double.
Here we go.
What country is hosting the 2026 Winter Olympics?
None country.
Not going to happen.
Canceled games.
I mean, that's probably true.
Is it us?
I don't know.
Yeah.
US?
It is.
I'll say US.
Italy.
No, I didn't know.
I didn't know.
No, I didn't think you were doing that.
There's snow issues.
They're having issues that they might not have enough snow for events.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
They should come out to Pittsburgh.
Whoa.
Oh.
Go on, Florida.
Hold it.
Winter Olympics in Indiana.
Horf.
Paul.
I'll go with hard.
For 800, what is the minimum number of darts that have to be thrown to win a single leg
of double in, double out, 501 darts?
Nine.
It is considered to be on par with a 300 game in bowling.
Hooray for me.
Did you know that or did you guess?
I did.
Rock hard for 1200, please.
Yeah.
Including the pincer claws.
How many legs does a crab have?
Oh, Matt, this is so up your alley.
Yeah.
Eight, 10, 12, or 14.
Including the pincer claws now, Matt.
I know.
Usually you don't include the pincer claws when you count crab legs.
This time make sure that you do.
I see the legs as legs and the claws as arms.
That's the way I've been brought up.
Right.
That's the way I was taught in my town.
Yes.
Yeah.
Wonderful to see everyone's favorite, Clawful, in the Master's Universe movie.
Oh gosh.
Clawful, of course, having a big claw pincer arm.
I hope so.
Not at all like Fisto, who has a big fist arm.
Exactly like that.
There was three of those guys.
There was Clawful, there was Fisto, and there was Jitsu.
They all had fucked up hands.
Oh, I don't remember Jitsu.
A, eight.
Eight?
I'm sorry.
It's B, 10.
Oh, you forgot about the pincer claws, Matt.
I didn't count the pincer claws.
I told you to remember the pincer claws.
I was raised to see them as arms.
You will not go back on that.
Lindsey in the chat says she just wants some claws in her mouth.
I'll close out hard for $2,000.
She's got crab legs in my mouth.
Is it possible, while driving on an interstate highway, to travel directly from Nevada to
Utah without passing through another state?
I don't think it is.
I'm going to say no.
Ah.
Yes, but not on I-15, which passes through a small sliver of Arizona, Nevada, and Utah
share a 240 mile long border, and I-80 crosses this border.
I always forget about I-80.
You always do.
Matt doesn't count the pincer arms on the crabs, and I don't count I-80.
I sort of realized that I-80 went that low.
I-80 goes pretty low.
It goes from the Golden Gate Bridge to the George Washington Bridge, so I thought it
would not go that low.
Which are both in San Francisco.
Paul, you're up.
I-40 across the country.
I will try Sitcom Spouses for $2,000 to get some money on the board.
All right.
What is the name of the character played by Patricia Richardson for eight seasons on Home
Improvement?
My God.
How dehumanized was that character?
Tim and ... Was it Heather?
Did he call her Heather?
Did he call her ... Heather Tooltime.
Heather Tooltime.
Samantha Tooltime.
Taylor.
Her last name was Taylor, so she'd been ... Angela?
Fucking pass.
Angela.
Matt.
Katrina.
Yeah.
It's a pass for me, please.
Mrs. Taylor.
People say it's Mrs. Taylor.
You nasty.
This is ... Oh, people throwing straight hints in the chat.
Straight fire hints.
Oh, all right.
Yeah.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I can't see them.
I ... Boy.
I watched this show ... I watched Home Improvement for at least a few seasons with my dad.
Yeah.
Oh.
I watched it all the time.
Yeah.
I'll give you a hint if you want one, Jacob.
Okay.
Jill is in my head.
All right.
So I'm going to go Jill Taylor.
Did I know?
It's Tim the Toolman Taylor, and I think it was Jill.
There you go.
It is Jill Taylor.
Jill Taylor.
Jill the drill, they called her.
They called her Jack and Jill.
There's no ampersand in that name.
Matt, you're up.
Oh, fuck.
I don't want to answer any of these, Jacob.
Fair enough.
Fucking Winter Olympics for 800.
Oh, let's see.
In what sport did Peermann Zabrigan, Alberto Tamba, and Phil Meyer, and Justelle Andre
Amont, short, and Petra Kronberger, Herman Myhr, whatever.
All these people won gold medals.
What did they win gold medals for?
Is this the Jamaican bobsled team?
Jacob, the answer to every question in the Winter Olympics category should be who cares.
Right.
Is it skeleton?
It's skeleton.
It's always skeleton.
I'll pass.
How much is it for?
I don't remember.
I think it's the little one.
I'll guess skeleton.
Alpine skiing.
Oh no.
The skeleton of the Winter Olympics.
It took all my points away.
Skeleton, you betrayed me.
It's skeleton.
Not the first time I've been betrayed by a skeleton.
At Lake Placid in 1980, Eric Haydn won five gold medals.
In what sport did he compete?
Haydn seek.
He's a master.
Nominative determinism.
As is the case in most of the Winter Olympics sports.
That's why Jake Skellington won the skeleton.
Phil Luge?
You can't Luge.
Sure.
That's the only place Luge can win.
Oh, there's a joke there somewhere.
I don't know where it is.
I'll pass.
Paul, what is it?
You won the Luge, you can't Luge for winning?
Eric, where are you hiding those gold medals?
Pass.
Let's see.
Speed skating.
God damn it.
I was praying for the skeleton.
I competed unprecedented sweep, wedding, gold at all five distances, 500, 1000, 1500, 5000,
and 10,000 meter speed skating.
Speaking of praying for the skeleton, have you guys seen the fucking horror show that
happened out here in the Pittsburgh area with this motherfucker digging up all the bodies?
No.
There's a guy out here.
We talked about a heat bed for half hour and you're bringing this up now?
This guy, he dug up so many bodies.
How many bodies did he dig up?
He dug up babies.
He dug up old people.
Wait, is he going to cemeteries and doing this?
Yes.
It's in Philly and so he's breaking into these mausoleums and these old, what do you call,
you know, with the walls and all them.
Yeah, yeah.
The above ground stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Crips.
Crips.
So he's breaking into all these Crips and shit and this has been going on for years.
He's been stealing all these bodies and keeping them at his house and selling some of the
parts and he's just into all this macabre shit and he's got a fucking storage unit.
It's a living.
They just found out he's got a fucking storage unit with more skeletons.
I'd buy that for a dollar.
The police went and raided his house, right?
And the police chief came out like in tears.
Like my men shouldn't have had to see this and all this stuff.
Like there's body cam footage of the police in this house of horrors and of bodies just
lining the walls and everything.
And one of the policemen is like, is that a pacemaker?
Like they're straight up skeletons with, you can see, yeah, dude, it's outrageous, out
fucking rages.
How many skeletons he stole and over girl, he had some stored in his closet.
He definitely did.
And they found, um, they found him out by a couple of different methods, but one of
the key ways that they traced him, he was leaving energy drinks at the scenes.
Guess what energy drink he was drinking monster monster, exactly right, Matt.
Exactly.
You're right.
Yeah.
Finally.
Why are those questions of this scooperty drinking monster energy drinks while he's
stealing skeletons?
It's the creepiest shit you've ever seen.
They're all like super desiccated and mummified.
Most of them.
And it is something else.
So look, he's not keeping them in good shape.
I mean, no, he's, they're in their clothes and stuff, they're in their, they're in their
clothes and everything.
Just sitting in his house, man.
It's crazy.
Like hundreds of people bought, he, he's on a million dollar bail and we talked about
masters of the universe for so long.
Paul, it's your turn.
Winter Olympics, geography or sitcom spouses.
It all comes back to Skeletor.
Let's go to Winter Olympics for 2000.
Daily double.
Yeah.
Now it's time.
Now it's time for me to win.
What is the only Winter Olympics sport in which women do not compete?
This sport is contested solely by men.
Skeleton.
If I get this with Skeleton, if I, yes.
If I get this with Skeleton, what's happening?
I don't think you're going to get it.
Nordic combined.
Bullshit.
This wacky sport involves a cross country ski race that follows ski jumping.
The farthest jumpers get the largest head starts in the race.
Let women do it.
How is that in the Olympics?
It's like biathlon type shit, right?
I mean, it sounds kind of like it, but that's even weirder.
This sounds weirder than the biathlon.
Not the other way around.
Chess is in the Olympics, right?
Breakdancing is in the Olympics for a hot minute.
I don't care.
Geography 800.
He's checking out.
He's checking out the cold.
Does Colorado share a border with Oklahoma?
Oklahoma.
Paul should yell Oklahoma into microphones now.
Do you remember, that's one of my favorite Saturday Night Live sketches with John Lovitz.
He kept saying, "Wedgie fever was the game show," and every time he got a question wrong,
they would pull the wedgie tighter on your ass, and he's getting pulled up by his underwear.
He keeps guessing Oklahoma incorrectly for everything because he likes getting his underwear
pulled, and he keeps screaming, "Oklahoma," and then he gets one right, and he's upset.
Oh my God.
I love it.
Matt, does Colorado share a border with Oklahoma?
Oklahoma.
I don't know.
The frozen Indiana has broken Matt.
Matt is defeated.
Yes.
The frozen Indiana has done what that busload of girls did to me.
It is.
South Eastern Oklahoma shares a 34-mile border with the Western Panhandle of Oklahoma, which
is what Matt was saying.
Look at you, Matt.
Yay.
That's me.
I'll try sitcom spouses for 800.
What is the name of the character played by Gene Stapleton for nine seasons at All in
the Family?
I don't fucking know.
Pass it to me.
I know this one.
Shit.
Pass to me.
I know it.
I've heard you the first time, Paul.
Chong's, we're on your hit parade.
Now the things that something played.
What is it, Paul?
It's Edith.
Stapleton, Edith.
It's Edith Bunker.
I'm sorry, Paul.
Bunker is the last name.
Archie, I don't know if I can take your last name.
I don't want to be a Bunker.
Hitler got shot in a Bunker.
I don't want to get shot.
Paul, your turn.
Will you stifle it, you dingbat?
I'll take geography for 2000, please.
What city is the capital of Pennsylvania?
Oh, Harrisburg.
Harrisburg.
Let's try it.
It's Harrisburg.
Yeah.
Look at me.
Shannon.
Matt.
Freedom Bell.
Geography for 1200.
Name any five of the 26 countries that have five-letter names when written in English.
Canada, Chad.
Not your turn and wrong.
France.
Iran.
That's one.
No.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
France has five letters.
No.
Is it?
Wait.
It doesn't.
It's six, right?
Yeah, it is.
I was like, I know I can't spell, but I can count.
It passes to me, let's see, well, there's France, clearly, there's Canada, there's Chad,
let's see, there's Egypt.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Columbia, no.
Columbia.
Oh, Italy.
Nice.
Sure.
That's two.
Let's see, France, how many letters does France have?
Germany.
Farsi.
Sure.
Aruba.
Yeah.
Brazil.
Nope.
No.
Oh, what did you say?
Hawaii.
Let's see, Benin, Chile, China, Congo, Egypt, hey, I got one, got Haiti, India, a bunch
of them.
We didn't know.
Yeah, there's 26 of them.
There's a bunch.
Yeah.
Let's see, I'm just looking at them real quick now to see if I could possibly get five of
them.
Qatar and Spain.
Qatar and Spain and Syria, those are, those should have been.
I'm closing out the category and the game, sitcom spouses for 400.
What is the name of the character played by Florence Henderson for five seasons on the
Brady Bunch?
Here's the story of a lovely lady whose name we refuse to reveal and a man who has a last
name, but that is all we'll say.
This is Brady.
Here's some children.
Yeah.
They're hanging out.
All right.
So you had Marcia, you had Jan, Jan had little girl.
Of course there was Opie.
Opie, Opie Cunningham, Delilah, Skippy, yeah, my, my, my Delilah, uh, pass.
Paul, uh, what was the dad's name?
That's not the question.
I know.
Alice.
Why are you trying to think about that?
Because it was kind of like the pairing up of, well, they called each other Mr. Brady
and Mrs. Brady all the fucking time, just to throw you off.
They were weirdies like that.
Florence Henderson, her name one Florence though.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's time.
I have to pass.
Yeah.
Carol.
That's right.
It was Carol.
It is Carol.
Brady.
Well, that is the game with that correct answer.
That launched himself into third place with negative 400 points, uh, I am in second place
with zero points.
Paul wins with 800 points.
That was a somewhat low scoring Smitty scooperty, but thank you Smitty scoop, but you got positive
points, baby.
Look at you go for a Smitty scoops.
That's incredible for me.
If you want to send us a scooperty, head over to a scoops.com right there on the homepage.
You could send us any kind of jock versus nerd that we do here.
You can also send us some email over to the scoop mail store.
Head over there.
No, just scoop mail.
It's the scoop mail mailbox.
There's not a store.
There's not a store involved at all.
By all the mail you want to receive.
Yeah.
I don't know.
You can get all the mail.
That's great mail.
Hey, uh, and yeah, we're always looking for interesting stuff.
I just heard, um, my favorite murder there and they're asking for, oh, here we go.
Door jingle.
Door.
A big door.
It's on.
We got a store.
That's the motherfucking store.
It slaps.
It is.
That is the, that is the shit right there.
Well, my favorite murder, uh, gals were asking for people to write in their, uh, stories
where people say, oh, you've got to tell the story or someone asks you to, oh, tell that
story about, that'd be a fun one for the, it's a great prompt, a great prompt, but please,
if you have a, uh, like a, a really wild tale that your family recounts a good party story
or something.
Yeah.
We'd love to hear those from you guys.
You know, we can always also send in your first BJ stories, your first, uh, uh, sex
stories.
We always love the, um, they did what stories, you know, it's kind of like terrible job stories,
something that happened to someone you grew up with a terrible job stories.
We love to any of it.
Uh, Andy's old poetry.
If you want me to just be happy, just send in old high school poetry, uh, the better
mark in the chat and asking for first grave Doug story.
Yeah.
Tell us about the first grave you robbed.
How many little skeletons do you have in your closet?
God, don't watch those videos.
If you're squeamish, honestly, it is fucking creep show.
It is a deep show.
All right.
Uh, thank you so much for your, for your scooper day.
Uh, I would think that the podcast, thanks, Ben, I've got some scoops to thank as well.
We have a few, a few more scoops to thank this month.
Uh, our list is all fucked up this month.
Uh, sorry about that.
If we missed your name this month, we will do better next month.
I want to thank though the man, the myth, the scoop, uh, the Chelsea's far, Timothy
Reed, tipsy scoop, Tom Krieger, Tom Mankerdy, Travis Murray, Tyler, Tyler, Tyler Bartlett,
Tyler scoop, Doug, Virgil, the verge, Walker Ryan, Warren bro, Wendy Bumgarner, will breed,
Will Breeden, will Kellner, winter scoop, Zelda Ray, Skywalker, and of course Canadian
scoop crystal.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air or get a, a myriad of other prizes and rewards, head
on over to preaching fun.com and select a tier that works for your budget today.
Or if you got broken by a bus load of teenage girls this week, head over to farts in a bag
dot biz that along with preaching fun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help
keep this show on the air.
You know, the whole drill, head over there, preaching fun.com farts in a bag dot biz.
We'll love you for it.
All right.
Well, thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Big thanks to all the scoops that hung out with us with a double episode day to day.
Thank you all hanging in the chat and in the zoom.
We love seeing your faces.
It's lovely to have an audience and everybody out there on Twitch.
Peace and love y'all.
See you at the co.
Yeah.
See you.
Ring Central's AI receptionist uses voice AI to answer on the first ring.
So you'll never miss a call again in just a few minutes.
You can personalize your own AI receptionist to answer questions, route calls, schedule
appointments, and even send texts in multiple languages.
Plus it's easy to scale.
Create unlimited AI receptionists across energy.
For more information, go to ringcentral.com.
And if you're interested in more information, go to ringcentral.com.