Oh, hello there! I am so happy you're here! I want to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Right now, I would like to thank Malia, Mike, Paul's brother, Pyro, Richard Dunn, Sarah Boyle,
Sax Guy, Jimmy D, Scoop, Scoop Brady, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Kata, Slippy Kye, Motherfucker,
Thunder, Cougar Falcon, Scoop, and Travis Jaggery.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks and help deliver that fucking ice cream
straight into people's fucking ear holes, head over to PreachingFun.com!
PreachingFun.com is where you can go sign up and who knows, the life you save may be your own!
Now here's a show!
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Happy New Year everybody!
Let's start the New Year right!
A guy was just awarded custody of his brother here in Nevada.
I'm taking that from this because he was sexually abused by his brother when he was a kid.
Turns out he was the father of his own brother.
Happy New Year!
It's time for Matt and Matty Lee's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting in a pool in his own mess, that's Matt Donnelly!
Sitting in a pool in his own mess, that's also Paul Matty Lee!
I'm Jacob, we're PreachingFun!
I was looking at the trending news in Nevada and...
I shouldn't laugh, that's terrible!
It is terrible. It is absolutely terrible.
A man awarded custody.
It's horrible, but it's also horrible.
I'm only asking to empathize with me scrolling to be stopped with man awarded custody of his own brother.
And then you go to click the link, it says like warning, sensitive material.
And that just was like good lord, that's a hard guy to go on a first date with after this, you know?
Oh man!
So tell me about your life recently!
How old is this boy now?
The child that was awarded custody is early teens.
Okay.
The gentleman is in his 20s.
And the mother is in jail.
Good, good!
I'm fine with that.
Honestly, I'm not even fine with that.
I don't want her to be in jail.
I want her to be getting help or something.
It's not a crazy sentence.
It's like an eight year sentence with parole kind of thing.
Good, good, good.
I mean, I say that as if I would last a week in prison.
Right.
I'm just thinking, what are the odds of her being a repeat offender?
I could do a dime standing on my head.
So yeah.
We're not all strong like you, Paul.
Also not all as strong as you.
Did we miss technicalscooport on the chat for the truck drivers?
I don't know.
Technicalscooport, shout out to technicalscooport for the truck driving.
If indeed we did not have your name on the list.
Might just be another list.
What are you talking about?
Technicalscooport in the chat was asking about he didn't hear his name on the truck driver.
Oh, I missed that.
Technicalscooport, thank you very much.
If I missed you on the list, I apologize.
We appreciate each and every one of you guys just being a crybaby.
No, not at all, technicalscooport.
That's what you pay for and we appreciate you guys so, so much.
And we also, you paid for us to change the subject.
Perfect, perfect.
Yeah, no, that was great.
I actually have a topic I wanted to bring up.
There is a news article I read here.
I don't know if you guys have heard of it yet.
A man in Nevada was awarded custody of his brother.
And it turned out there was a twist that no one saw coming.
Oh boy, oh boy.
You know what the real twist is?
What's that?
Personal trainers hate him.
I did the, you know, you're singing a song to somebody else and they hear you do the wrong lyrics and they make fun of you for that?
Yes.
I did that to myself in the car the other day.
What'd you do?
You caught yourself singing the wrong lyrics.
I caught myself.
I was like, that can't be the right lyric.
I had, I had the 90s station on and it was playing, oh, what's that song?
Everlast.
Then you really might know what it's like.
You know what I'm talking about?
No, no, that's not Everlast.
Yeah, that's Everlast.
That's Everlast, right?
That's Everlast, yeah, yeah.
I don't remember the name of the song.
I'd forbid you ever have to walk a mile in her shoes.
That one, yeah.
Because then you really might know what it's like to have to choose.
So I had like the 90s station on and I was doing what Paul's doing.
I'm just singing along with it.
I'm like, yeah, this jam.
I remember this jam from like '96 or so.
This is awesome.
Yeah.
And the hair on his face was dreadlocked for the mange.
Dreadlocked for the mange.
Dreadlocked, yeah, for the mange.
I was like, oh, this man had to dreadlock the hair on his face because he had such bad
mange, is apparently what I thought in the mid-90s.
No.
That's not how it goes.
That's close.
Correct.
It's not how it goes.
How would you handle the mange, Paul?
You don't want to have to comb it out every day.
No, but I'm thinking topical ointment.
A salve?
A salve before dreadlocking it.
Yuck, those things are going to come out in clumps.
Yep.
That's going to just fall right off your face.
Also, it occurred to me as I was thinking about this in the car as I was driving, dreadlocking
hair wouldn't help with mange at all.
That wouldn't even be a good solution for mange.
No.
Well, we do plenty of things in our lives that don't help with the things that they're
supposed to.
Well, that's true.
That's true.
All right.
I'm back to dreadlocked for the mange.
There's dreadlocks for the mange YouTube page, which swears by it.
Oh, yeah.
People who said they've done their research and they have different doctors to testify
that dreadlocking for the mange is perfectly well suited.
What is the actual lyric?
I'm looking it up right now.
It's just like hair full of mange.
The hair on his face.
Oh, I was much closer than I thought I was.
I was going to say you're very close.
Dreadlocked and full of mange.
Yeah.
I'm not as far off on this lyric as I assume.
No, you're being too hard on yourself in that car.
You got to go back there and say, I owe you an apology, Jacob.
Yeah, I owe past Jacob an apology.
I was too harsh on him.
Don't worry.
I'm sure there are other lyrics in this song.
If I go through all the lyrics in this song, I'm sure there are others that I'm just absolutely
wrong on.
If there's a chance you might get interrupted, I might have to leave to show a plumber my
toilet that's not working.
Man has to go fuck a plumber.
Oh, shit.
Nonetheless, I have another story.
I've had so many lately.
The man of the hour intro.
Oh, the man of the hour.
I haven't gotten over the man of the hour.
We'll get through this.
The guy complaining about me in front of me at the cruise ship thing.
My debacle as a soccer coach.
I saw your wife the other night at the show and I did something that I rarely do, which
I stood up to give her a hug.
I felt like she needed it after having heard the boy's soccer story.
I was like, you don't know why I'm giving you a hug, but I feel like you just need a
hug.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're closing out the year strong.
Isn't that what they say about the new year?
When it goes to shit, then the rest of your year is going to be your new year is going
to be good.
And that kind of thing.
I hope so.
That's an assumption, right?
I mean, as Matt Donnelly famous said in 2019, next year has got to be better.
I believe I did say that, right?
That's a legit, that's a legit quote.
I have a neighbor who's a douche.
Okay.
And I don't think I've talked about too much on the, on the pod.
No, you don't want to put your neighborhood on blast.
How far down is he?
He's across the street and down two doors.
He's on the corner.
It's not Chad's old house or anything.
No, no, no.
Across the street.
Not a direct neighbor, which is good.
Yeah.
Close enough.
You can see his home from your windows.
Yeah.
From my driveway, I can see his house, his house, you know, we're, we're, we're caddy,
whatever it is.
I can throw a cat in his house.
Yeah.
Well that ain't that far.
And so in the past, do he, in the past, he's yelled at children in the neighborhood for
things going on.
This is the no cones guy.
Is it?
No.
Right.
So the no cones guy, I think either moved or just, uh, except that maybe he was possibly
going to run over children and maybe chilled out.
I don't know.
One or the other.
Maybe he got therapy.
I don't think he got therapy and once again, my kids got older and more agile.
So it was like, right.
That's true.
It was less of a deal.
They don't need the cones as much.
And, uh, um, no, this guy's yelled at children in the past, but not my children.
Uh, and so I've heard tales of him yelling at children before, but I never came to it
face to face.
Ah, I, uh, was at the grocery store and then my wife and I miss, uh, missed crossed hairs
in the both of the grocery store together, getting last minute things for party.
We're going to throw it tomorrow.
Uh, Jacob, I don't know if you're around tomorrow, but three to three to five for having
people over and, um, and, uh, Paul, you're not invited.
And, um, uh, I knew it, I knew it.
And she's like, I guess the neighbor's just cursed at our kids.
And I was like, Oh, Oh no.
And so I was like, Oh, I got it.
I was like, I go, well, that's not okay.
Yeah.
And I was like, I guess, I was like, I guess I should go talk to him.
How much, how much of your inner monologue at this point is can I get away with not dealing
with this at all?
Well, this is, you know, I mean, there's of course, I mean, I'll say that's always my
first instinct, right?
My first instinct is like, Oh, hide and do nothing.
Right.
Cause I, I mean, like, this is not going to be a fun, this is not going to be a fun conversation.
No, I don't anticipate it going well, because he has been across from us.
Like, you know, I mean, this no surprise to you, we are, we are neighborly, especially
my wife.
Like we know all of our neighbors and these guys have been here for the whole time and
we do not talk at all.
And they've, they've ignored us every time we tried to say hi to them in the past.
Real grumpers.
A just total, total grumpers, a lot of people go in and out of that house.
We don't even know if there's one or two families in there.
It's just one of those.
It goes on.
It's that kind of situation.
There's something, there's fishiness and that's why they're all standoff.
Yeah.
You think it's a bunch of mobsters, uh, go into the mattresses for a potential mob war.
You think that's what's going on in there?
I know.
So there's a lot of district distribution of, of, of ammunition and different guns from
the trunks.
I've noticed a bunch of Tommy guns being passed out over here.
You joke, but there's some shit like that.
The for real goes down out of these Vegas, uh, residentials.
It's no, it's no joke.
There is.
It's kind of a joke.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, this kind of seems to be like in his own business, his own, whatever, any
man, something, some kind of business, but he has two big trucks.
He's loading it in and out all the time.
Okay.
Um, with different stuff, uh, but, uh, yeah, so, uh, neighborhood kid, uh, overthrew my
son and the ball rolled off the street, up onto his driveway, underneath his truck.
Oh, and he came out and screamed at my children to keep their shit away from my shit.
Uh, keep your fucking shit away from my shit.
They were so there was a ball on his property.
Was it, was a kid trying to get the ball at this point, as a matter of fact, because of
the past, my son was waiting for the ball to roll back down the driveway in which it
did.
Oh, so he was even doing what he's supposed to do.
Yes.
Oh, come on.
When we first moved into this house, uh, the house that we live in now, we, we have close
neighbors and we're in a cul-de-sac and, uh, the neighbors that we had when we first moved
in kind of kitty corner across from us, they had a bunch of kids and the kids were always
out.
We're like, we, our, our big cul-de-sac is not technically a street.
It's technically a shared private drive between our four houses right here.
And so, and obviously it's a cul-de-sac, so there's not a lot of traffic.
So the kids would be out riding bikes and skateboarding and doing all that stuff all
the time.
And one of the younger ones, cause they, cause we have kind of a circular drive in front
of our house as well.
And so they would cut through the circular drive all the time.
Uh, not a big deal.
Who cares?
But once or twice, uh, one of the younger ones would come up like all the way up to
our front porch and, you know, just, just skating around doing, doing whatever.
Cause there's concrete all the way up there.
Uh, he, he wouldn't do anything, but he'd just come up, he'd come all the way up there.
And so one day I had to go over and, and talk to his parents who were very nice people.
Uh, just a, a giant Mormon family.
So they just had kids everywhere.
They were, they were just quiver full.
Yeah.
I think there were like 12 people living in the house at one point with this one, with
this one family.
That's outrageous.
Uh, but they were lovely and they were, they were very, they were very nice family.
I miss them.
They're, they're great.
They were, they were good neighbors, but like I had to go have the conversation with, uh,
the dad who's just standing outside.
It's like, Hey, maybe just ask your kiddos to not, like if they're in the driveway there,
I don't care if they're in front of the house.
I don't care if they're in front of the garages.
I don't care.
The front porch, like their windows straight into the house there.
I don't really want them right up there to maybe, maybe talk to them.
And that was an awkward as fuck conversation.
Yes.
And we were both being very civil and I didn't like it at all.
Now this guy's just yelling because a ball was in his driveway for a minute and it removed
itself seemingly of its own accord with, with the assistance of gravity.
It removed itself.
So I was like, it's time to go talk.
That's a lot of, that's a lot of anger.
I know.
And then this thing is like, and I'm, it's, it's my neighbor, right?
So the whole point, tell him I had, I'm like, I have to one, he's going to yell at me.
I have to prepare myself.
He's going to yell.
Yep.
And I'm like, oh, he's not going to be a two-faced person, but you're like, oh no, me, I love
those kiddos.
Like his voice is going to be raised at the first thought would be maybe take him a gift.
Um, well, that wasn't, that wasn't my thought.
But uh, uh, uh, I, a baseball is a baseball because it's been a few incidents over the
years, not a lot, but a few years, I don't know if adult ever got involved before.
So I was like, I have to just go over there and have a conversation with him just to know
that adults is, is, is also part of this conversation, right?
He had been hanging on this car when it happened and he was hanging on his car.
When I went over, he'd been hanging on his car all day doing business from his car.
Oh, oh, this is not a happy person.
No.
So I, I thought I was going to go to the front door.
He was already in his car and he rolls out his window.
And I said, he doesn't get out, he just rolls down the window.
Yeah.
And I said, Hey man, you can't be cursing at children.
And he goes, I didn't, I didn't curse.
First of all, I didn't cause it.
He says, boom, he's out of his door, uh, in my face and tell me I didn't curse at any
children.
And he goes, I have, I record everything.
He points, he gestures as if he has cameras all over his house and his car says, I recorded
everything.
And I said, great.
Play it.
I said, awesome.
Play it for me.
And I'll apologize.
Yeah.
And he goes, I have to fucking play fucking play anything for you.
Fuck you.
Like I am ready to be wrong.
Show me that I'm wrong.
I'm ready to be wrong.
I will.
I will yell at my kids.
I will beat them to within inches of their lives for lying about you saying shit to them.
Show me the video and I will beat my children.
No.
And he immediately starts cursing a lot.
So I'm like, I'm skeptical that he didn't, he didn't curse.
I'm skeptical.
If someone comes to me and says, Hey, you can't curse in front of X, I assume that I
did indeed curse whether I remember cursing or not.
That's where I start from.
And he then he's like, you had never talked to me until this moment, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, which I was like, booed.
I've tried to say hi to you like a million times and you've ignored me.
So I was like, check the recordings, man.
Exactly.
I was like, so I let that pass.
And then I was like, I was like, I was like, and I basically was like, you, you, you can
have everything you want without screaming at kids.
That's been my whole point.
Yeah.
You can keep the kids out of your property.
You can do that without screaming and cursing at my kids, but he's getting, he's getting,
he's getting me.
He's like, you come over here, you're going to get in my face.
You can just see this, you know, whatever.
He goes, kiss my ass, kiss my fucking ass, kiss my ass.
I say, I say, if I kiss your ass, will you be nicer to the kids?
Nice.
That really threw him.
I'm sure.
And he said, but, and I said, if I kiss your ass right now, will you be nicer to the children?
What if I spin you around?
What if I, what if I give you a blow job right now?
I will, I will blow you in this driveway.
He literally like got jarred by that, that he actually like instinctively turned his
butt towards me.
Like while he was still being angry, he was like, Oh yeah, he wanted it.
So then I bent over, but I kissed my hand, I kissed my hand and I, yeah, boop.
I touched his butt.
Tapped him.
Yep.
Yeah.
I gave a little, there you go.
Good, good.
Which triggered his gay stuff alarm.
And then he got even more angry again and was like, don't you fucking touch me.
You fucking touch me.
You say the fuck away from me.
He, yeah, that, uh, Mark in the chat, that was a Freudian turn on the neighbor's part.
For sure.
Oh, a hundred percent.
This guy is filled with self-hatred.
This is becoming more and more apparent.
The, the more we look into all of this stuff and I can speak for personal, not personal,
but interpersonal experience, a lot of this shit is coming from repressed gay people.
Oh, sure.
Don't have a way they, and it just, the self-hatred that gets festered in.
Or repressed, repressed anything.
Like there's, there's something.
Anything.
Yeah.
There's something inside this guy that he's, that he's furious about.
You know, the Kinsey scale is not exactly the most accurate thing in the world.
The idea that we have different wavering amounts of bisexuality.
Oh, absolute.
We're all on the spectrum.
Right.
We're all, but, but, but you gotta be aware enough to be like, oh yeah, there's, I mean,
there's a needle that moves when Trent Reznor comes into the conversation.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
I've asked you over and over again, not to refer to your dick as a needle.
Don't, I want you to be happier about yourself.
No, no, no.
It's, it's, there's more girth than that.
I'm not, we're not, we're not playing records.
Okay.
Good.
But Bruce Springsteen's early success was because he was a piece of ass and men likes
going to see him in concert, but it was, he was an attractive guy.
I mean, the, the, the, what the album cover with his dick on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's an album cover.
It's just like zoomed in on his, on his crotch.
No, you zoomed in.
There's a regular shot.
You zoomed in on his crotch.
Oh, I wondered why a magnifying glass was taped onto that album cover.
No, that's what I mean.
It's like, yes, I do.
I do believe Paul, I actually do, it's like, it just, it's just this gay hatred stuff just
really, really comes from really straight, quote unquote straight men, hating gay men
and gay activities.
Right.
And that's why transfers to trance, because if you were actually attracted to someone
presenting female that was born male, then suddenly you think something's terrible with
yourself.
Yeah.
It's like they just, it's jealousy too.
It's like, how dare someone live their life open and free, embracing their identity that
I don't get to do that.
And that was the thing.
I mentioned this before to Jacob the other day.
Were we talking about, it's not a podcast or whatever it was, but how, when it gets
to a certain point.
No, no, that was just a FaceTime that you and I had late night, our, our, our no pants
FaceTimes.
We were talking about how-
Wait, I got disinvited to no pants FaceTimes?
When did I lose my invite?
No, no, no, we're just, we're splitting them.
We're just splitting them.
The group thing wasn't working.
Disinvited is a strong word.
We agreed, Jacob and I both agreed that we got a little turned off the last time.
And so we wanted to keep it, we wanted to keep it a little more spicy, just me and Jacob.
No, this is the thing.
When a lot of hardcore religious types want to adamantly say that sexuality is a choice,
that is coming from their reality in which they must choose to repress their natural
instinct.
And they think everyone has to undergo that same choice where we do not.
It is, you know, and yeah, it's just, it's hard.
No, I mean, I think there's like, like, uh, um, uh, my buddy, Mike Mills, who's producing
the Joker's tour.
He's also producing this documentary, um, anyhow, I can't, I don't think I can talk
about what it is or what it's about, but one part of it that he was talking to me about
was the studying was basically people did, uh, study, um, uh, basically hook up meters
to people's, uh, penises to, and then show them pictures to like about twinges when they
saw stuff.
Yes.
Oh, wait, that was, that was an official study.
That was an official study.
So if you've been doing it on your own, Jacob, you need to share that data.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I had no idea.
Does my tongue count as a meter?
Yes, it does.
Okay.
It's a meat.
All right.
That and, and, and how you eat a Reese's peanut butter cup is intense, Paul.
It's intense.
We should talk about it.
Brother.
I put the work on them Reese's.
They're never the same sideways like a typewriter, but, um, typewriter and two bites and that's
it.
So this is legit.
Basically just say, does the legitimately study the kind of like self-hatred of feeling
gay feelings is a real, is a real thing.
Yeah.
And I, and I guess much more prevalent than we ever think about.
Right.
And that's the thing is that it's more, that's what, that's what always blows my mind.
It's like, they keep putting out these studies like, Oh, 10% of the population, bullshit.
Yeah.
That's low.
That's right.
That's way, that's gotta be so fucking low.
That's low.
Right.
But that's not always been the statistic that we've always had our whole life.
If you just count the people, if you just count the people that get on television and
yell about how evil gay people are, if that's more than 10% of the population right there.
I mean, if you involve yourself with theater for 10 minutes, you go, Oh yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Yeah.
This is cool.
But 10% no, I don't think so.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Service industry, Sean in the comments saying service industry.
Anywhere.
That's the other thing.
It's not even just, it doesn't have to be theater.
It doesn't have to be services.
Any, any job you go, Oh wait, there's more than 10% here.
Oh yeah, do the math, but we can't do the math because education has been completely
systematically defunded.
We have to bring people in from other countries to do the math.
We can't do that anymore either.
Nope.
God damn it.
They don't like us.
Oh, not only that, that is not allowing it.
Nope.
I guess our shouting was creating a commotion in the neighborhood as, as I was trying not
to shout, but I raised my voice a few times, but of course, but, but the one time I was
like, Hey, the most I yelled was when I was going, I am trying to deescalate.
I'm trying to write this more chill.
I am not trying to be in your face.
I don't know how I would react if someone cursed at my children.
So it was really, I mean, I was drove home steaming.
I was, I wouldn't, I wouldn't react well if I, if somebody told me that somebody cursed
at your children.
Right.
Exactly.
Like if somebody was like, Hey, that guy just yelled at Matt's kids.
I'd be like, God damn it and you have to like, uh, like, you know, it's a neighbor.
Right.
And we've both been there for a long time.
And yeah, that's not going to change.
So you got to watch it because you don't want to just not, yeah, you don't want to be coming
home to eggs.
Do not call the registration car hotline.
Oh my God.
Right.
Can you imagine?
Yeah.
Oh, Myra in the chat wants to know, did your discussion get reported in the, in the nosy
neighbor board?
Oh, I, you know, I honestly have to go check cause I, I, I always end up, I click on one
thing and also they get like a thousand emails and after like a week, I'm like, wait, I want
to stop all these emails and I unsubscribe.
Yes.
It is, it is the flow that we all go with exactly.
So I have to go back, but I mean, multiple neighbors were texting about, I'm yelling in
the first place.
And then I was screaming, but my wife came out and said, all right, basically in the
net.
No, no, just loudly goes, all right.
She, she goes, all right, you tried, you tried to do the right thing and just said that nice
to him.
And we just walked away or whatever, but, uh, it was, it was just the best man.
Yes.
I was about to say there are so many things that I can think of that I would rather have
happened to me than be the neighbor of Sarah Lowe and have her, have her mad at me.
Well, you know, she'll win.
Like she has the whole neighborhood wrapped around her finger.
Right.
Exactly.
So she could probably sell his house, Leon in the chat.
You tried the right thing.
Now kick his ass.
Now loose.
Now that was actually the only like comforting thing is he, he seems, he's always been very
intimidating from his truck, but when he actually got out and got on my face, I was like, oh,
there's a reason why you stay, there's a reason why you stay in that truck buddy with big
old truck.
What do you know?
You should have tried to give him a hug.
Look, I hate when you hug him.
I went further than I thought.
Yeah.
That was pretty far.
That was kissing ass.
That's pretty far.
I'll tell you who else tried to give their neighbor a mouth hug on his butt and that's
the following sponsor.
Today's show, man, manliest ice cream socials brought to you by Karen's cakes and cookies.
That's right.
From New Hampshire caveman in 2023.
It's Karen's cakes and cookies.
Hey, I don't know who made this, but it's not right.
It's just off something.
There's sugar, too much sugar in the mix or something, but the icing is just a little
bit runny or who knows the colors just a little bit off.
Hi, I'm Karen for Karen's cakes and cookies.
Every time you order, you're going to get something a little bit wrong.
It's not going to be quite right.
You're going to have to speak to the manager.
That's the Karen's cookies and cakes guarantee.
You will always have to speak directly to someone in charge to fix the shit you got
from your order.
It will never be right.
It will always have a mistake.
I promise you that or I'll talk about your fucking hair, bitch.
Get out of my store.
I can refuse you.
That's right.
I just wanted cupcakes for my kid's birthday.
Well, you know what?
People wanted to not stare at that fucking bird's nest of a bullshit beehive you got
going on.
Get the fuck out.
I can stun the salon every week.
Whoa.
Oh, salon selectives.
Where are you going?
Salon.
Is that Salon Dion?
Salon Dion.
I go to Salon Dion.
How is there not a Salon Dion in Las Vegas already?
I don't know.
Well, there is now.
I'm sure I'll put it out there in the zeitgeist.
It'll happen.
Come on, people.
Hey, Matt.
I'll cross your hairline.
Okay, go ahead.
Oh my God.
There should be a Salon Dion.
Why is there not?
Oh, that's so perfect.
And it's all that goes between us.
Yeah.
Salon Dion.
Your extensions will go on.
Man.
Forget it.
Your extensions will go on.
Come on.
It's right there.
That's all right there.
This is give me shit.
Right there.
Matt.
Yes, sir.
Speaking of your children.
Yes.
I have been watching Keeler in Pluribus.
Is there a good reason to say that?
I've been holding off because my wife watches like two episodes out of a year.
Her New Year's resolution is to watch television again.
Like she has stopped watching television.
So when you guys watch Pluribus, there will be moments where you go, our son is starring
as an angry, lonely lesbian fighting a world plague.
It's pretty amazing.
I didn't think about it.
I didn't think about it until Paul said it.
We're two episodes into Pluribus and Paul is just correct.
I'm right.
I mean, I'm not out here to talk shit.
I'm not talking shit.
You got a handsome lad.
He's got movie star looks, clearly.
He is right now.
TV series looks.
He is currently Bowie-esque, so I understand what you were saying about him.
Yes.
He's got the longish hair.
Yeah.
He's got this kind of perfect androgynous thing going on.
Something about the facial symmetry with this woman in this movie.
When he was younger, he looked exactly like Charlie from Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
in the movie.
Right.
Yes, he did.
It was a really weird thing.
From Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory.
From the old one.
From the Gene Wilder one.
Yeah.
Your son is absolutely carol.
If someone's watching Pluribus and you don't know what Keeler looks like, yes, you do.
Yeah, that's it.
Yes, you do.
That's exactly what Keeler looks like.
If my son can act half as good as Ray Seahorn, then we're in the money because Ray Seahorn's
absolutely amazing as an actor.
No problem there.
No, no.
I am, where am I?
I finished up Mayors of Kingstown.
Oh, good.
Probably the best season.
This is the first season.
Season three.
Season two and three were a little wonky, but season four was really good.
But it's still hilarious on these shows, these Taylor Sheridan shows.
When you can commit mass murder and then just go eat afterward and be like, "Oh, now that
that's over with, let's chow and talk about it some other time," is always the funniest
thing to me.
Not like we should seek trauma counseling or whatever.
But ...
We should seek trauma counseling.
I would love it if Taylor Sheridan shows just got really real, just really real.
I'm only one episode into the lowdown, have you guys been watching that at all?
No.
What's his name?
Ethan Hawke.
It's on Hulu.
Okay.
Oh, my plumber's here.
All right.
Good.
I was only talking about TV shows, so it should be hard to hand this off.
Okay.
All right.
Paul.
Yes.
Rating the Rock Vault closed last night.
Oh, you know, and it really broke my heart.
I saw all these postings from SJ and other folks because I follow a lot of Rock Vault
people and Rock Vault itself.
I did promotional work for them for a couple years.
Got to see the show many times, early, different iterations.
Then got to just see it as a fan to go see SJ a couple times.
This is heartbreaking.
This is definitely a ...
It's the end of an era.
It's a victim of where Vegas is right now with the decline in tourism.
And I think, you know, just shifting trends, like always.
What's your take on it, Jacob?
I mean, I think it's part of that.
It's certainly part of that.
I think that has to do with it.
It's also, I mean, when we first moved here, all the shows at the big casinos here were
Broadway shows.
Right.
Yeah.
The first show I did out here was Spamalot and then the kind of new wave of shows came
in and Absinthe was part of that new wave of shows coming in back then.
And Rock Vault was as well.
Rock Vault was part of that class.
Yes.
And they were just a year or so after Absinthe.
I mean, they were real close.
And there aren't many of that class of shows left in town.
No.
Part of it is just the time.
I mean, it's so goddamn hard to run a show here, especially a show of any size.
Yes.
Where you're trying to get hundreds of people in every night to come see it.
There's so much competition.
There's so much competition for people to spend entertainment money on here between
other shows, clubs, gambling, celebrity chefs, all these things.
But yeah, going and watching the end of Rock Vault in Las Vegas last night.
And they're supposed to go on tour.
They might do a little bit of touring here and there or I know they're going to do some
touring coming up.
I don't know just how long that's going to last.
But yeah, I mean, it's definitely the end of a crazy long thing.
Matt's back.
We're talking about Rock Vault closed in Las Vegas last night, Matt.
Oh yes, yes, yes, yes.
End of an era.
It's heartbreaking too because losing that stratum of show, losing more of those kind
of shows, because for a long time in Las Vegas, shows and entertainment in general was considered
something of a loss leader.
It was a way to get people into your property.
And you would just, you know, comp some people tickets, charge low fees to have folks come
and watch the show for a little bit.
And it just got foot traffic into your venue and then got people gambling.
That was the thing.
Now.
And it was, you know, it was the building that you were in owned the show that you were
seeing in that building, right?
And it was all, it was all part of the same ownership group that was doing everything.
Now everything's four walled, if that, and you're still being treated as a loss leader,
but you've got to try and make profit for yourself.
And it's just kind of the whole, the whole thing is backwards.
How to, you know, because now instead of Sid Caesar sitting up in the, in the office at
Caesar's Palace, I assume he owned Caesar's Palace.
It was Sid Caesar.
Yes.
Yeah.
Instead of Sid sitting up there saying like, this is going to be here and this is going
to be here.
You know, he's just up there renting out rooms and like, Oh, you can come rent out my show
room and put on a show and you can pay me a lot of money per week to use my show room.
And I, I sure hope you sell tickets and you're able to make money and keep on paying me my
rent.
Right.
Because that's what I care about.
Good luck and God bless.
Yep.
They don't give a shit.
Uh, and, and that's, that's just more bullshit because it's just different.
I don't even look at that as a bad thing.
I just look at that as a different thing.
I look at it as a different setup.
I think basically like, um, the problem is all these casinos that are still operating
are holding on by a threat right now.
Yes.
No, that's it.
And so like, there's no place to innovate or invest.
And so they're all just saving their own asses.
And so like basically innovation part, I think we're, I think we're hurting from the lack
of innovation.
Now someone new needs to see an opportunity in this space, specifically in Las Vegas strip
to come in and do something crazy.
And the last person tried was resorts world, which their big innovation was three hotels
or one hotel Voltron Voltron was their plan.
Remember the original plans for their resorts world member.
They had a Panda habitat.
They are going to have a stadium.
They were going to have all this stuff.
And then all of a sudden when, when push came to shove, it was no, just three hotels.
Yeah.
And, and so like it's going to take like a big sweeping thing from an order of magnitude.
But basically these companies have all found a way to not go away.
Like normally some of these companies would have shuttered in the past, which would let
someone else come in and dig over a big exception is what's happening at the hard rock, uh, which
Jacob point out before the show came out of where they're building a giant electric guitar
tower that's going to change the, the look of the strip, whatever that's, that's a different,
that's totally different casino company than the ones that have come in in the past.
That's the, um, seminal, right.
The seminal, the seminal tribe, I believe.
Yeah.
They own the hard rock, but even they like they're doing something like what they're doing.
It's the old mirage.
It used to be the MGM mirage and they tore down the volcano and everything in the, in
the front of it.
And they're building a giant guitar shaped, uh, tower of a hotel suites there in the,
in the front.
And then they're going to revamp the mirage towers as well and make that part of the hard
rock and, uh, for people who don't know, but the guitar, even that's not even exactly innovation.
That's something new in Vegas, but they're just copying something that they've already
done in Miami.
Right.
They also had a big ass guitar in Vegas a couple of years ago.
It wasn't as big, but they had, that was a big one in front of the old hard rock, uh,
casino.
This is a, yeah.
Yeah.
This is a building.
No, I know.
It's a, it's a mega structure at this point.
Yeah.
This is like, that was a big guitar set up in front of a building.
This is an actual building.
Yeah.
It's pretty crazy.
It's shaped like a guitar.
Yeah.
Anyways.
But rock rock fault is closing up, which is such a shame.
I just went on disco last night.
Disco is closing this weekend.
Um, and, uh, but these are shows that these are shows that would have worked in the past
where people are coming here going like, what should I do and what's around, you know?
And, uh, it's just not, it's just not the way Vegas operates anymore.
So in the short term, what would help is, uh, right.
Maybe if foreigners didn't hate coming here, that would help a lot.
Yeah.
That might be a plus.
Yep.
I think they said, uh, November was the, uh, the biggest decline in air travel to Las Vegas
since they started, uh, keep checking those numbers.
Yeah.
No, that's rough.
But I don't know.
And the big picture thing is just a matter of it.
Like we have, uh, we, with the sphere of the Raiders JDM, we have F one ourselves all the
time is basically like when, when, when the whole, uh, when the whole town is taken up
by one event that really hurts these side endeavors, cause now it's whether the crowd
that's going to that one event also likes this.
So does everyone going to see the wizard of Oz also want to see rock vault?
I don't know.
So then it's not that weekend that weekends out for rock vault, right?
Like it's just a, it's just a weird thing.
Uh, and I guess we also just say that we also are speaking from entertainers perspectives.
Like we're, we're, we're pro entertainment.
Of course.
Um, because like, uh, uh, Leon brings up Macau and Macau has never been an entertainment
space.
It's always just been a gambling space that shows the shows.
The shows in McAlvin and Torsley done terribly.
Um, even way back in the, like, Franco Dragone's company, they, they had a show over there
for a long time.
That was spectacular.
I mean, they, they had a, uh, I forget what the name of the show was, but it was, it was
such a great show.
I knew a lot of people in it, uh, just, just hella talented people over there.
And boy, they just could not, they couldn't pay people to come watch that show.
Yeah, and it was like a, a job, it was basically a giant Cirque de Soleil show.
Uh, it was super impressive and they just couldn't get butts in the seats.
No.
And it'd be more gambling beyond that.
Yeah.
Beyond that.
It was, uh, even the restaurants were doing well.
Uh, it was the food, right?
The food, if you were, if you opened up a spot in the food court, you were making money
hand over fist.
Cause that's what the gamblers could go there quickly, get food and come back or have some
of the food court, bring the tape, bring it over to their, uh, bring it over to the table
and eat at the table, get the food runners going.
Yeah.
And it's still, it's a little different than, than here, but we'll see.
I mean, the truth is that like, um, uh, tourism is down all over the place, you know, and
that's because people below a certain class are experiencing a recession.
People above a certain class are, are not.
And um, and so it's, it's a, it's a weird time.
Uh, it's a great time for the rich to get richer, which is like, thank God, cause I'm
really as a, as a low end podcaster, I'm ready to make a move, you know, but, um, I gotta
shift these $10 around, Oh, this is a good time to bring up our scientific study.
Give each of us a billion dollars and we're going to see if we can do better.
I knew better than the current billionaires.
I think we really, really could.
I really, I really believe in me.
I think we could do it.
I, I'm, I'm very optimistic about us.
I've, I've, uh, uh, you know, it's funny, it's like, what comes to like something does
come to mind for me when I, when I do hear that, uh, basically Tony shades vision for
all the downtown motels, uh, you know, that's all going away, right?
They're about to demolish all those motels, but I really think there's a way to revitalize
like a small downtown motel areas to do like really cool, distinct things with each motel
to make it much more of like a kitschy place to come visit bar crawl and like, and spend
some time and be away from resort fees and things like that, um, but, um, so there you
go.
So that's plan a for my billion dollars is, uh, is, uh, pick up Tony shape.
We're Tony left off with the downtown motel hotel year.
Yeah.
That'd be fun.
I think so.
Uh, you know, who else I think would be fun to, uh, have them die and then take over their
dream.
Yes.
And that would be the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by a compilation narrated by Jeffrey Jones.
If it's okay, if this is too dark to air, but it's a long shot, wait, Oh, sorry.
Bob Crane's video nasties, DVD compilation narrated by Jeffrey Jones.
I don't know if I understand this joke.
I don't get it.
I do.
Is this too dark to do?
Well, Bob Crane was the star of Hogan's heroes and infamously a porn fanatic and made his
own porn and, uh, Jeffrey Jones is the principal from Ferris Bueller and the dad from Beetlejuice
been outed as a nefarious, uh, and, uh, yeah, yeah.
And bad guy.
Uh, they move along.
So yeah, we'll, I mean, it's a funny idea.
Yeah.
I don't know that I can execute it eloquently enough to make it funny and not.
That's it.
It's a, it's, it's our hay scoops at checkout.
Fair.
Today's show is brought to you by PTSD's Barnum and Bailey's all veteran circus equally
dark.
I think it was that it's the circus.
It's here.
Stay very quiet.
Don't get out of the ring.
Never get out of the ring.
Barnum and Bailey's PTSD circus is here to entertain you quietly.
We guarantee no explosions, no animals, nothing exciting or scary will happen in the PTSD
circus.
It's just clowns with no face paint falling.
That's it.
They just fall.
They just walk out onto the stage, fall down and they get, they get back up and they say,
they speak.
They say, Hey, I'm okay.
So you remember when you lost that good friend in denying, he went down.
He never got back up.
These clowns, they're going to stand up again and they're going to look you in the face
and say, Hey, I'm all right.
It's okay.
We can go home together.
Oh, no, no, no, that's too much.
That's too much.
You're getting people off.
Calm it down.
Never leave the ring.
Never get out of the ring.
That's pretty dark, but not as dark.
I don't know.
Maybe not as dark.
I don't have PTSD from war.
Thank God.
It or hate scoops at checkout.
I guess.
Let's do a little scoop mail.
Physical scoop mail, physical scoop mail, zippity doo.
We got mail in a box.
I love it.
We love it.
We got all our holiday cards here.
Happy New Year, everybody.
Oh, while we're in scoop mail, shout out to Craig Ruth, who just went up to the low tier
to the $20 tier for the year.
Oh, awesome.
Hell yeah.
Thank you so much, Craig.
Thank you, brother.
Yeah.
Thank you, Craig.
Oh, we got one here from the Mass Hole Scoop, happiest holidays.
We love getting the card from the Mass Hole Scoop there.
These are great.
I love getting these.
The Maynards.
We got a great-looking family here, Seasons Greetings.
We got a dog with possibly a Hawaiian lei or something like that around its neck.
I like it.
Whatever it is.
That's adorable.
I'm a fan of it.
That's from Frozen Cusser.
Let's see here.
Merry Cris Bosh to you and the guys and the churn and to your families.
Thank you.
So nice.
This is from...
Oh, that's from the Maple Raisin Scoop.
Very nice.
Let me see if I can get it on the camera.
There we go.
Kind of.
Good.
We did.
We got a lot of Cris Bosh cards this year.
We got...
Oh, I like this one.
Peas on Earth.
It's caroling peas.
Cute.
Very nice.
Oh, that's from Tess, the Slightly Slutty Scoop.
Sitting with you and yours, the very best for the holiday season.
Thanks for all you do for this amazing community.
Wishing you a Merry Cris Bosh.
Thank you, Tess.
What were you saying, Matt?
Just a lot of Iron content in the Peas Chorus.
A lot of good Iron.
Oh, yes.
Peas Chorus Hot.
Peas Chorus Cold.
Peas standing on your doorstep singing songs of old.
We got one here from the Nielsen Family.
Love that.
Very cute.
Matt and Jacob Paul got his on his own.
We wish you a sweltering and sweaty Cris Bosh.
We do have that.
May the new year be lucrative and sexy like your wives fucking you in the face.
That's the Nielsen's.
Hell, yeah.
And their pets.
Oh, we got a great one from LAJ, from the big twisty road in...
Oh, that's a cool looking print.
San Francisco.
Thanks, LAJ.
That's a cool looking print.
All the best for 2026.
Hope you're doing good, LAJ.
Yes.
Ah, let's see.
We got one here.
There is a Snowbuck's Coffee.
And let's see.
We got a snowman has ordered a hot coffee and he is back at the counter wanting to exchange
it for an iced coffee because it has melted the front of his face completely off.
Wishing you the best holiday season, Merry Cris Bosh.
Wait, maybe despite being T DeVore, have we not been saying your name?
I don't know.
You also didn't put your name in this card.
You said, I haven't been saying your name as a Patreon member, but then you didn't sign
your name in the card.
So I'm looking at the return address, T DeVore, if we haven't been saying your name, maybe
it's because you haven't given me your name.
That's Travis.
Oh, Travis.
Have we not been saying your name?
Well, let's make sure we get that.
We got it.
I got to look at the list here.
Travis, we're sorry.
How is that possible?
We have a list.
It downloads from the site.
I don't know.
It's annoying.
I'm going to tell all the listeners right now, all you Patreon supporters out there
and anybody that's ever been a Patreon supporter of us and anyone that ever might be a Patreon
supporter of us, when you tell us something is wrong with Patreon, 85% of the time, we
are as confused as you are.
15% of the time, we fucked it up, but 85% of the time, we are just confused.
Yeah.
I was doing the newsletter again and that newsletter format is bunk.
It's bunkaroo, but I have to use it to include enough images.
I don't know.
It's weird.
Right.
This stuff is not at all conducive to anything, but Travis, thank you for the card and we'll
try and make sure we get you on the list.
We got this one.
This is a great one here.
Much love to you and everything you do, Luke, Angie, Pierce and Frank.
It is a great, a great Chris Bosch card.
Their card.
There.
I got one of their cards too.
That was an amazing Christmas Chris Bosch card this year from them.
The Andersons.
I love the Andersons.
They sent us a great Chris Bosch card as well and the Drabilises.
We got, we got one from, uh, from the Drabilises to Amy and Carl and kids.
And they got them next to the Dippin' Dots on the back.
Right?
Oh yeah.
They're standing next to the Dippin' Dots, uh, standing.
Did you talk about how SJ is playing New Year's Eve tonight over at the, uh, verge?
I haven't yet.
Uh, yeah.
Over at the, uh, well she's at Jason Aldean's bar at the, uh, the city center, uh, first.
Okay.
And then, uh, the Spice wannabe show, the Spice Girls show, they are playing at the
hard rock on the strip tonight.
That's pretty impressive.
Oh yeah.
That's a big deal.
Yeah.
They're booked there.
I think I'm going to run over and see at least the, uh, the second half of the show.
Um, I think it's going to be great.
Let's see.
Let's make a good get.
Let's make a big, big get.
Yeah, I think so.
They've got a lot of, uh, a lot of tour dates and everything this year.
I think they're, they've got some, they've got some new dates coming up here.
Well, it's going to be good.
It's a great show.
It is.
It works super hard.
Let's do a little jock versus a nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is jock.
Jamie and Carl's last name, Lori is fussing at me in the chat about saying your last name.
I always say, well, part of it is I hear it said, it's, it's one of these things.
I hear the name said and I can say it, but then when I see it written out, it fucks me
up again.
I can't see it written out and say it.
Yes.
Anyway, we've got a scooper coming to us today from lemur screamer creamer.
The categories are animals in camo sounds the same mommy and milk dance with a, with
the cane, the categories dance.
Yeah.
Categories dance, categories dance.
Uh, Matt, you're up first.
What you want animals and camo animals and camo for 400, the jackpot reached a million
dollars what animals and what's the, uh, animals in camo again, there's an animal in here.
Oh, I see.
Oh, this has become like a real gentleman's created a monster here.
I see it.
I found it.
Echidna.
It's just in one word.
Okay.
Doll doll jack, the infamous doll don't go near the doll enclosure.
It'll bite your fucking face off.
Actually, I've worked in the doll enclosure, uh, at the haunted museum.
What can I say?
That's what happened to Paul's face.
That's what happened.
Peggy got me.
Oh, lion.
Peggy lion.
There it is.
Lion.
And a million lion, lion, a million.
You lie.
You, uh, sounds the same for 400 a bucket lacking color.
Oh, I, I, uh, pale, a pale.
It sounds the same.
Yeah.
Paul, uh, I will go with, uh, sounds the same for eight, please.
All right.
A type of tree and by the seashore, a type of tree by the seashore.
Uh, Oh, uh, a beach, beach tree, beach nut, beach tree.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
I did not know that a beach tree and a ocean beach were not spelled the same.
The only way I know it is because of all the baby food that beach nut B E E C H. Oh, baby
food.
Yeah.
I mean, I just unload fuck tons of it every week.
That's all I see it going to put it right into a package for Jeffrey Jones and then
mail it off.
Oh, Rose.
Rose.
Matt, you're up.
Uh, it sounds the same for 1200, I would probably be doing a lot better if I was eating just
baby food, a corridor or to drag card cargo hallway all the way.
Oh, a hall hall hall and hall.
Yeah.
Hall and hall.
That's what Darrell Oates fears the most dueling holes and what is the status of their lawsuit?
They were in a nasty lawsuit for, they are still very acrimonious.
They still hate each other.
Yeah.
The one guy bit the other guy.
No, no, allegedly no, uh, Hall is just like, Hall is just like, I just want to be Darrell
Hall and Oates is but, but me, but you need the Oats.
Oh, the lawsuit ended in August of 2025, Darrell Hall voluntarily dismissed his legal action
against John Oates following private arbitration that resolved their disputes over Oats attempts
to shell to share or to sell his share business.
That's their greatest hits album.
It's called private arbitration.
Yeah.
So apparently hall dismissed the lawsuit against oats.
Private arbitration is how we settle our differences.
Me and Darrell Hall get along again.
Private arbitration.
Yep.
Clap.
I'm still mad at them for writing man eaters, so I don't care.
Uh, I'll try.
It sounds the same for 200.
2000 writing man eater.
I'm still mad at them about man eater.
So, uh, fuck them permitted or in a whisper, in a whisper, in a whisper, don't you know
talking about our revolution, permitted whisper, uh, I'm not trying to give you a hint, Jacob.
I'm just doing a Tracy Chapman reference.
No, no, no.
I caught that.
You weren't helping.
Uh, permitted or in a whisper, is this allowed?
That's what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
But in a, in a whisper is confusing on.
But I mean, it's, it's, you know, instead of, yeah, instead of silently, I guess so.
I guess, yeah.
I'll try that.
Allowed and allowed.
Yeah, there we go.
There it is.
In a whisper.
Uh, Paul.
This is Waffarthian.
Uh, I'll do mommy for 400.
Daily double.
Mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy.
Mommy.
This Catholic nun won the Nobel peace prize in 1979.
Mother Teresa.
That's right.
Ooh, mommy.
Matt, you're up.
Um, I'll do, uh, animals and camels.
800.
She's a total shit bird.
The prize bracelets were handed out at the carnival.
Zebra.
It is zebra.
It's me.
I'll try.
Man, you guys are so much better at that animal one than I am.
I'm going to try milk for 400, milk, milk, milk, pecorino Romano cheese comes from this
animal.
Is it not a cow?
It's a mouse.
It's probably not.
Is it a goat cheese?
Pecorino.
Maybe it's a sheep.
Could be.
Uh, or is this one of those, uh, like you, you get a cheese from the, uh, from all the
lady bacterias that are down in the lady bits.
It's, it's Pecorino Romano from unda cheese.
Is it from unda cheese?
Is it lady bit cheese, from unda cheese?
That's why I don't eat that pecorino Romano.
Uh, I guess I'll pass.
Paul.
Uh, give me some of that from under, um, I'll have a smear of that on my bagel, please.
Oh, here you go.
Pecorino.
Oh, my brother is huge.
He wants to fuck my wife.
Um, fast.
Uh, Matt.
Pass.
It's sheep.
That's a sheep cheese.
Sheep, sheep shenanigans.
Um, I'll go on with mommy, please.
Mommy.
This board where electronics are made.
Uh.
These people will not be nice to your kids, even if you kiss their ass.
Signature curl scoop.
We all scream for Mark McLean.
Alice scoop six.
Alice scoop six, six, six, six, six.
Corny scoop.
Cup of scoop.
Dr.
Science scoop.
Duke scoop.
Gizmo scoop.
Holly marshmallow.
Go lightly.
Scoop.
Marble tulip.
Scoopy tree.
Miss Johnny Australia.
Neck pubes.
Proper scoop.
Proto scoop.
Raggedy girl.
Scoopa troopa.
Scoopie Lauren.
Scoopy D. Scoopy JD.
Scoop JD.
Scoopy and the beast.
And silicon scoop.
I like Scoopy JD.
Uh.
And then the, uh, the following people here, I have an, I have more to say here, um, uh,
these, these people, uh, all, uh, would physically kiss the ass of a stranger to help all mankind.
Whoa.
Uh, Ryre Appledorn.
Sackett Mangle.
Scoop Lindsay.
Scoop neck.
Paddywhack.
Scoop Ramone.
Scoop Ashlock.
Scoop Muldering.
Nope.
That's Scott Muldering.
Uh, Scott Schoedfeld.
Sean Kellner.
Sound man.
Scoop.
Steven Clively.
Steven Landon.
Stuart Wilson.
Strange uncle's podcast.
And temporary reality Pierce, uh, Timothy Sutton, Tom Mancordy, Travis Murray, Tristan
Guevara, Tyler Bartlett, Tyler scoop, McDuck, Warren bro, Wendy bum Gardner, Wes Colligan,
Will Kellner, William McDonald, and Neil flash.
The following people saw the final performance of raiding the rock vault, long live raiding
the rock vault, silver fist scoop, Scully wall scoop, turn the page.
The damsels of dorkington, the devil's lettuce scoop, the going over our Fred's podcast,
the ice cream headache, the ice cream headache again, the SC double O P what was like scoop
angry face scoop, Ben Smith, Bob, Brad Martin, Brian Mcleod, McLeod, uh, see wick, Charles
Jashacki, Chris Jorg, Chris K, Chris Melancon, Christine star, Christopher Huff, chronicler
scoop, Clayton Shoney, clown in a brothel, Colleen Fisher, and Craig defarmer.
And the following scoops all have a healthy fear of Sarah Lowe being angry with them.
That's Chris Mayer, Dan Martin, Daniel Mattis Ferrer, Doug Lay, Ed under arms, our Marcus.
I don't know what that, what all that says.
Edward Bender, Aliza Walczak, flat kidney guy, Wade, uh, Ian Soto, Jamison Fisher, Jason
Victor, Jay Shapiro, Jed taxon, Jeff Faust, John Lord, John Holshin, Justin Robert young
K Mattis, uh, K Mathis, Lee forest, Mark Cohen, Mark Gates, Mark Wilson, Mike federally, Nathan
Houghton, Nicholas Petty, Nicole Boozen bark, Nicole Levin, Peter Burford, Philip Guyton,
pick it up, pick it up, pick it up, Ron heck, Rose, Ryan Howard, Sam Reed, Scott, a Scott
Andrews, Scott, headington SF, Sean, Stacy Coleman, Steets, McGreece, super geek, 13
57 nine, Tamera Hamilton, Troy, Anthony, Tanzer, Udo gear, hards, uncle Don's woodshop.
Wendy Cooper and Natalie McGee latin Natalie McGee, a teen.
Oh, I like you a lot.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air or get all kinds of different rewards that we offer,
head on over to preaching fun.com and look at the tier that fits your budget today.
Or if you like me, we're a little upset that Howard lease wasn't wearing his enormous knife
on his hip for the last show of rock vault.
Head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preaching fun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as a $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon supporters, so you are really helping keep the show trucking.
If you like this show, if you think it's good, head over preaching fun.com fartsinabag.biz
like I say, for as little as $3 a month and you can do it yearly.
If you want to do that, you can, you can do your whole support for the year.
You don't have to do it monthly.
If you don't want to and you get a bit of a discount, if you want to do it for the year,
if you want to sign up for all of 26, you can do that.
You can do it month by month.
That is perfectly fine.
And you can give gifts.
You can give the gift of a Patreon subscription to someone that you either love or hate.
Depending on how you think they will like this show, you can give them the gift of us
for all of 2026.
That's right.
All right.
Well, thanks for this everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Happy new year everybody.
Happy new year.
We need to go over our big resolutions.
This is a big deal.
Oh yeah.
Any quick ones?
Resolution speed around.
Spanish.
Paul.
1080p.
Oh good.
Eat better after 10 p.m.
I think so.
1080p is pretty high.
It is pretty high.
It's pretty high.
None of us want to see us in 4K.
No, no.
That's why I didn't go there.
Who is watching movies for nose hairs?
I mean, come on.
We are not made for high def.
What are we doing?
Pop the brakes.
Every time I see like, you know, they take the old footage and upgrade it and make it
all high def and everything.
I'm like, oh, you were, you were just hurting these performers who never thought they would
be seeing this clearly.
There is something.
I'm like, oh, you were, you were just hurting these performers who never thought they would
be seeing this clearly.
There is something to that 30 FPS grain film quality that makes it so much more theatrical,
like fairy tale, dreamlike.
It removes it from reality a little more.
Right.
And it looks so real.
And it looks like a movie.
It's not what I was raised on, but it looks like a movie.
When I see that smoothing and all that shit, I'm just like, get that the fuck out.
I'm watching the Neutron.
I just get, I just get so hard.
The Neutron.
I see all that smoothed out skin.
It was so hard.
Half of it, no, but half of the Neutron looks like a goddamn soap opera set.
I'm like, what the fuck?
Why would you do this to your billion dollar show?
I don't get it.
Love you everybody.
See ya.
Life moves fast, it's fierce, persistent, determined.
At City of Hope Cancer Center, we are too.
Our groundbreaking research and discoveries have impacted millions of lives globally, moving
science forward with the hope, passion, and speed every diagnosis deserves for a cancer
free future.
City of Hope Chicago, pursuing cancer cures at the speed of life.