Oh
Hello there I am so glad you are here because I want to thank you the ice cream truck drivers
Who are the ice cream truck drivers? These are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
It's a brand new month right now. It's actually Halloween as we're recording this, but it's a brand new month for us
So I don't have new lists yet
But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver at this part of the show this month
Yeah, we'll thank all of you every single one of you if you're an ice cream truck driver
You'll hear your name at this part of the show of this month
That's right
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver preaching fun commas ring go preaching fun comm head over there sign up to be
an ice cream truck driver and who knows
The life you save
May be your own
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to
Maddie
Yeah
Even your kids think you die all the time that does one Jacob impersonation his entire family thinks he's dying
That's right. That's right
Well, we get it
We're about to set up our trick-and-treat
Deal as soon as we wrap here. We'll be going outside the city of our house here. Yeah, same here and
I
Well, we did a test run last night basically Ryre Applethorne built me a
Disguised jack-in-the-box giant jack-in-the-box. Yeah, uh-huh. And so yesterday was trunk or treat
Over at the school and so everybody had these ornate
You know trunk they set up their car trunk designs
Yeah, they do like full-on decorations on their cars and everything, right?
Yeah, it's a trunk look like a monster mouth or all kind of stuff like that
Yeah, and my wife signed signed me up for it, but we
We've been crazy busy. And so I basically had
30 minutes to run home and put stuff in my car to make trunk or treat happen and then back to the school
I had the Halloween parade that I had to teach a theater workshop to the kids there and then trunk or treat was right after
And so I rolled up in my Corolla
Yeah
put down a blanket the skeleton a couple a couple skeletons and
then I gave the controls over to my youngest son who scared the shit out of everybody with a jump scare and
With with
With with with basically no decorations. We got third place in the trunk retreat because we were scared
Yes
Ryre Appledorn coming through baby. Well, poor Ryre Appledorn. I have to get him on the phone
The prop did not hold up to the stress test of a repeated truck or treat thing. Oh really?
How many how many reps did the Brock get last night I mean
50 60 reps. Yeah, you know, I don't normally perform that trick 60 times in an hour
Interesting interesting
Will that my now my son to to his content is the the front door broke off completely and okay
Then the fish that the clown was holding snapped out of his hand
And then the finger got of the one clown got caught and something on one of the reloads and snapped a finger
It was a real
And I was also relying on that tonight today so I'm gonna get my neighbor Gary to see if we can fix the front door
On the on the clown now the clown with a snap finger and a couple of broken things doesn't hurt the
Doesn't hurt the bit at all. The vibe is still there for the scare. Yeah and
To Ryre's credit he I for no reason he added two giant loud horns to the prop when I didn't ask for that at all
And it absolutely makes it and my son was way on top of it
Just blasting people with the horn on the jump scare and just really good really crushing it and so perfect
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but yes, this is indeed
See if I can put it to put it back together for the for the for the
Tonight Donnelly the perfect reading. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Paul you're already dressed for trick-or-treat you got your you got your Ninja Turtles hat on there
This is actually a winter to that. I just sport when it gets cold. I was outside doing some chores today
It's freezing out here. It's in the 40s. You're full on Ninja Turtles hat. I'm sorry. It's not a costume
It's just your regular hat. Yeah, it's just a regular hat. I wear my phone. Yeah, of course
I mean I wore Ninja Turtle pants on the airplane for years
That's how that's how I roll. I'll give shit
Yeah
No, somebody was just asking me if I would open up my own comic book store at some point
I don't think I want the hassle. It's too much hassle. Well, my guy my guy is in a new location now and
It's just been challenge after challenge for him getting it all squared away
It's a great new space but just brick-and-mortar retails thriving like no other time in history
Right. No, you know what comic shops are actually doing better this year than they have in a long time. I
Think they're up something like 30 sure. No, seriously. It's a really believe you but I'm
That's a not a great comparison to what comic book shops a few years ago weren't doing well at all, right? Uh
Yeah, I mean, yeah, they've certainly had their ebbs and flows. Yeah, that's all I mean, but they're yeah, I guess that's true
I mean, there are a lot of them in town now that you're right there. I've seen a lot of them just pop up
Anecdotally across Vegas. Yeah coming up coming up from the bottom, but it's a it's a you know, relatively inexpensive form of of
entertainment and
Every comic book shop has always been a labor of love. There's nobody for sure
That is nobody open the comic book shop being like and then and then I'll buy my island
More the more the point when did comic book shops become the collectible shops as well late
Seven when we were kids, they were they were just comic book shops, right or were they were they already not late 70s?
As far as we mean like when it became
about collectibles about the collectibles now they've got like all that all like the
Toys and gimmicks and who have the toys from the different things and there are the collectible toys and the and the Pokemon cards
And all the things don't make me start listing things. I just sound like an old man
There are still some comic shops that are very purist and and really hold mostly
Books and there are the other things like those toys and things have a good margin on them
So yeah, everybody kind of felt fair as it out. Yeah
I'm holding the mug from the wedding the wedding favor mug for the people who nice. Oh nice
Yeah, Jake, I just got out of there. You went you gotta get it. Yeah
Yeah, I have they sent me this one. They sent me this non-descript plastic cup that I'm drinking out of. Yeah
but yeah, we went and
Anne and I had a
Day to go and just kind of do a few little things together
she's been working like crazy and
so we went to get some food at Applebee's and then we went to the comic book store and
then we went to try out this new ice cream spot that we have in town and
It was great. This new ice cream store is great. And yeah, it's called
Crispy cone and what really what's your go-to order at an ice cream shop? I'm usually chocolate
You're just a scoop of chocolate usually but this time the way they do it
I usually just rob them. They just say give me all the money in the register
Smart smart. It's very different
This this place very fancy crunk. Oh, no, he's out there got ice cream shops working for him
My default is probably chocolate chip cookie dough. That's hands. That's what Anne likes
Yep, that's what you got. Go to order is a shake
Okay, shake. Yeah, I want to I want to no labor. No labor for you. Just went down get it done
No, no, I want to I want to take it. I want to I want to be able to walk and sip
Enjoy my shake shakes are so good
And then I feel so terrible with myself after I have them and I don't know why
Big one. I I see people order like the huge ones at everything. I'm gonna you are a crazy person. That's me
I love me a big big chocolate milkshake. I just want I want a little like hand-sized
You know, just a little little little shake little little chocolate shake or maybe a vanilla or something like that
I don't have restraint if I get a shake. It's gone. It's gone
I yeah, it is it is a it is a two-minute treat and then it is I'm with you on that
I have no ability to like casually take a cup. You do have to pace yourself on the old shakes a little bit not me
Now they could take it down
That not only will not pace himself on the shakes, but they I got one that was
What he caught cheesecake, oh
Yeah, so they put chunks of cheesecake all on the sides of it and then drizzled strawberry syrup all over it
Really really fucking good. It sounds like a mess
It was it was really hard to get home and it was really tricky to juggle
But it was delicious. You must have been an Ann's car. No, we were in my
That you would have taken that into your own car I
Know I was like, uh, I had well, here's here's what happened
Paul does not like taking food into his car. I don't we're in we're in the ice cream shop
And I start to get gurgle belly
And I and I know
That time is of the essence
The clock has started and we we not only got we each got an ice cream and we got hot chocolates
So I'm sipping a little bit of hot chocolate eating a little bit of ice cream
Mixing temperatures should really help really help soothe that belly. Well
I get in the car and we're and as soon as we're driving I'm like and I
Got a bucket of prunes. I got some stuff going on things are things are happening and she's like you're gonna make it
You're gonna make it. I'm like, I think so she says are you gonna shit in your cars? I'm not gonna shit in my car
I just cleaned this car. I spent three hours the other day cleaning and detailing my fucking car
Good. I'm glad that factor because if you hadn't clean your car, it would have been an option
Not an option. I haven't cleaned my car in months. I might shit in my car. I don't know I don't know I
Don't know because here's what happened. We got home. I
Was in dire straits. I got out of the car. I
came around the car
Into the house as I'm coming around the side of the car and says are you okay? Are you shitting yourself and I go
Oh, no
As soon as she said it
I
Did she jinxed me and I said, oh no
She is happening. She manifested it. She dream boarded it. She straight up. This is an impression of me
She's doing impressions of me all day. She goes it's happening. Oh, no
And I go running up the stairs
Filling my pants. I'm throwing my jacket away
Ripping my belt off trying to save my wallet and keys
I can feel it ripping out through my underwear into my jeans
I'm like, this is going to drip on my stairs if I don't get upstairs
Run up the stairs run up the stairs
I'm not doing that to my downstairs bathroom. I get upstairs
Get this moment. I am going to the closest bathroom. I get upstairs. I throw my
Hands off. I throw everything over to the side. I
Completely have ruined my pants my jeans my underwear my socks
Everything I sit on the commode and the commode is just the sides are now just
Terrible terrible soft serve of death
And it's just like the stench the stench. I'm like, I know I'm sorry. I can't control
Matt Matt checked out Matt has left the zoom
And is laughing and of course at the same time saying I'm sorry
I know I know I shouldn't be laughing but you're too funny when you're doing this stuff. You're making me laugh. You're killing me smalls
And I did I made her laugh through the whole thing even though
Most women would just leave that's what I tell her straight up
I'm like this is not the first nor the last time I've shit my pants. You haven't just left me. So it's fine
So yeah
Got through all that laughter. It's just it's just gonna be stuff going to a suitcase. Yeah, that's the trouble
Yeah, that's gonna be the bad time, but it was fine
It took me about an hour to get everything
So real quick Leon Kasab in the chat just got back in. Hey guys, I just came back
Should I recommend this episode for an obelisk?
Sure
It sums us up it appeals to a certain demographic I
Guess I mean, I'm just I'm just being honest. I'm just being honest
It was a rough night anyway
but
Finally got everything settled down and then yesterday. I cleaned the bathroom top to bottom
So, you know, I did my part to fix everything. I cleaned the bathroom that day and then I cleaned it again yesterday
So, yes, I did need the muffler
I did not have my muffler muffler would have saved but what a muffler have even would have but a muffler have slowed this down
Yes, this sounds like too much for a muffler. This was pretty intense. I have to say
Bourbon barrel like every really
What are we doing yeah, yeah, I don't know but
It was just crazy how she was like she seriously was like
Are you shitting yourself? And then sure enough I was like, oh god, I am
Wasn't before I wasn't before and now I am and I didn't make it and it was just hell on earth
Hell on the car is fine
Cars fine. I was clear from the car
Everything's fine
Everything's fine now
Well, no, no some underwear got thrown away. Yeah. Yeah. All right and some socks and
Well, no, it's not a good story. It's a nice thing. It didn't get to my socks, but
The socks is an unrelated side effect and some carpeting. No the socks. Here's the sock story
So I have socks on where I have socks that I've probably been wearing for like ten years some of them and now they're getting
real rippy. Holy and so
I
Was a terrible wrestler in the seventies
anyway, rippy, holy
I Bought a bunch of new socks. And so I was like, well as I go through and I find my rippy
Holy socks, I'll just start throwing them away because I've got a bunch of new socks and
Just so happens this coincided with me wearing some rippy. Holies for their last time and then and it was so bad
Taking off everything in such a rush that the top ring of the sock stayed on my foot like a
Rippy holies. I was trying to get out of my poop filled clothes
You have tear away socks
So then I use those socks to start the cleaning process somewhat and threw them away. Oh my god
Yeah, okay. It was intense. It was an intense afternoon
It was a heavy heavy day. It was a lot
So wait, wait, so then was the this Cheesecake Sunday in transit with you while this was happening? Yes
Yes, I said it on the roof of the car and just left it ran
Didn't even get my hot hot cocos till like an hour later. They were not hot by that time. They were delicious
So yeah
yeah, and and got the sundae and put it in a bowl and put it in the freezer for me and then the hot cocos just
Sat in my car till I was able to come back downstairs and get my hot cocos out of the car
It was a you know else event for the love of God needs some roughage and that is the following sponsor
today's show that madly ice cream social is brought to you by the soluble fiber provided by
Sloppy knobby the official glory hole of pot therapy conveniently located in the Hobby Lobby. It's lobby
Frozen Cusser in 2023
Hey everybody
I'm vice president JD Vance and if you're like me you love to go to the slobby knobby inside the Hobby Lobby
Yes, and waiting for me there is a surprise guest. Who knows who it'll be male female
I can't tell all I know is there's an
Old-fashioned country-store looking letter R that has a nodule in the R hole and I put my dick in the R hole and sure enough
I get my slobby knobby. And I do too. It's me, 70s wrestler Rippy. Holy
Holy, yeah, that's right. Rippy. Holy. Did you slobby my knobby? I did I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's me
I need work. So here I am
Just do doing my my closing move as you as it were
Yeah, there's no coming back from the slobby knobby
That is a finisher and a half when I heard you guys my name is Steven
I'm the I'm the manager in this Hobby Lobby. Yeah, and I I am I don't want you guys doing this
Someone needs to be clothesline
Rippy Holy just fucked you up. And now you're gonna have
He's gonna give you a finishing move right on your belly. Yeah
JD III heard I heard you were coming today. So when I went to do my job
I stuff cotton in my mouth. I just put a bunch of cotton into my mouth. So I feel like furniture
It did feel like home. Yeah next time if you could coil a rusty old spring on your tongue
That would just really put it put it over the edge rusty spring my tag team partner
He's right here if rusty spring and Rippy Holy, I mean always loved you guys because you did remind me of the old furniture
I used to have sex with
Don't get me in a goodwill that place would get wrecked
Jacob did you see yes springsteen delivered me from nowhere. I
Attempted to oh and then found out that it wasn't streaming anywhere. It's only in theaters. Oh
Yeah, you thought you're gonna watch it at home. I sat down last night to watch it and went to pull it up
It was like oh, it's not streaming here. Oh, it must be on a different service
I thought I was gonna have to pay for it. I thought it was I thought it was new
Yeah
I have not seen it that puppy needs theaters my friend
That thing needs to blossom slowly
In the seeds of the tens of 12s of people that are going into theater after theater to see a sin of magic
I did watch an extended trailer of it last night and I and I listened to
Nebraska in the count Basie theater
I'll tell you that the extended trailer the extended trailer is probably as good as the movie
Did genuinely make me want to watch the movie? So I think you might be right. Yeah
When we saw the movie Paul was a Paul was respectful
We got the car and he's like are we waiting to get on air to talk about this and I said
No, we can talk about the car. We just rehashed it on there. Yeah. Yeah, and he goes well, you're the springsteen fans
I I'll let you talk first
You should start Paul said and with this conversation I defer I defer. Yes, I yield the floor
To the gentleman from New Jersey. So I'm willing to have this conversation
I'm gonna need you to set the tone first of all spoilers
Let's just yes set that out here now spoilers for deliver me from nowhere, which I can't believe that fucking subtitle
It is meaningless
Meaningless
It's a lyric reference, but besides that it is meaningless. Yes
Here's the thing that really sums up this movie for me
I'm watching the film and I'm getting you know as emotionally invested as one can when watching the boss
Deal with this stuff
He's got this long time relationship
multiple-year relationship happening on screen
With this woman and her child and he's very much been to become like a father figure to this kid here and there and you
Know all this kind of thing and also just might be to say that that actor Odessa figure the last name is
She's Australian
She kills it. She steals the movie as far as I'm concerned. Yeah, she was great and I was like, okay Matt
So who was this lady?
Why didn't they stay together what what's what's that? What's the fallout from that? Oh, that says
She's a composite character of multiple ways
This movie forever then yeah, yeah because he doesn't even come off that nice to a composite of his
When out of its way to fictionalize Springsteen leading on a woman with a child and ditching her that's
It is the oddest shit the choices they make are just like if I'm gonna submit my legacy. It's a superstar
I should put out a movie where I'm absolutely
Atrocious. Yeah the most sympathetic people in the world a single mother a single working mother in a diner
Like somebody said somebody in a writing room somewhere said like no
No, we have to we have to do that like he was convinced to keep that bit in the movie
I'm sure I don't know man. It's so weird movie
Right if you just was just old-school movie making
Right, right. You are supposed to ride the dip of that and then that person is supposed to evolve and come back to being a better person
and
There are scenes that set it up
Dramatically so where they follow all the rules of film writing right up to that that that cliff
Where the house supposed to turn around and do make the better choice
It's like nope. Anyways, he went on to go do some concerts. Yeah, it's the craziest thing
He he what happened to that mother and child who knows who knows he meets up with her at a diner where she's been working
Has this big heartfelt conversation was she the best he had ever had not even close. She cries and
Says she's a heartfelt speech like just pierces right through all of his bullshit
Like I hope you find what you're looking for and he's gone. That's it. He never even talks to her again the rest of the movie
She never shows up again. He leaves her he leaves her crying next to a dishwashing machine. That's it. It's over
That's the last thing she said. There's a scene later
The movie is that scene like 90 minutes left. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
Yeah, it's almost over
Like he's just like well, it's a build-up to this moment and this moment is where that
Should make him break down and make the right choice, right? And it's that it's like but that's not what happened in real life
So goodbye and then
Sure, let me composited this together. He even has this epic road trip, which is which is hysterically
Factual and that spring she never drove so someone had a drive to California
Springsteen and Copperfield are two two huge celebrities who just never really drove
and
Like muddling in the diner with his food in the middle of like, you know El Paso or something and he's going like she's right
She's right
But he doesn't act on it
Moves on as though she had never spoken. He doesn't even move on. It's he is absolutely
Just feather on the wind
He does not do anything he directs little anything in this film
Aside from recording an album in his bedroom
That's the only thing that he really does and then that same that same moment of him being out in this
Road trip the guy after he's seen him get all upset with his food
gets on the horn to the manager and
Comically, it's the springsteen is like five feet away from
He's like, I don't know he's gone off the deep end
It's the dumbest thing you've ever seen
It's like they want to talk about all the the the darkness in his soul, but it never really it's just I mean
They they delve into his childhood abuse
okay, but
It's just it's just
abuse in a way that is like if we if you and I went to film school and we're like
How how do we want to want to show you boost?
Let's cut to black and white and do the most like standard bad dad
Scenes you've ever seen in your and the bad dad
His bad dad is a character actor who's been in a lot of stuff and most notably
He plays Italian gangsters and he played Capone and I want to say boardwalk Empire
I could bone and also in adolescence. He's the tough dad and
Adolescence the oh is a big hit the big hit on Netflix that for okay
So he's very pigeon-holed like you see him and you're already like oh
His father was Al Capone. Okay bad guy bad guy
and
Yeah, it's weird. It's weird. I would say has a breakdown at an amusement park. It's
Like you know even Graham is that actor's name. Yes. He's great
Stephen Graham he was really good
Look, you know like he put out he put out this big autobiography and there's a big deal
He does one person show on Broadway and where he was more candid than he'd ever been about his childhood
and this is you know, he was he is the child of an abusive father and
You know as a rock star, you know that obviously has a different, you know, weird weird way of sitting with people
but uh, you know, I
Said to Paul I said basically if you took
Like this moment, right? This is a moment basically like spacing is finally which with the mood is get into but he's passed his lawsuits
He can finally put out music again
He can finally tour again puts up the river the rivers huge and they're begging him to like come back with another killer album
And he instead takes this artistic right turn puts up the brass gal and all that stuff is true
And it's crazy. And so like that is a weird turn and like and I said to Paul like anytime
Springsteen fans talk to non springsteen fans, and they say he's just a cheesy rocker
Most the first words out of most springsteen fans his mouth is something about Nebraska like that album is this totally different turn
With with beautiful storytelling and songwriting in it that's not pop, right?
and and so
You know to tell that story as a moment of triumph, you know
artistically is maybe fascinating and kind of like basically then you pit yourself against the record people and the pressures and all the people want
To be super famous that feels like more of like a typical story and then he's battling depression during this time
That feels like that would be like an underlying kind of B story, right and instead this movie makes the
artistic choice to put up the Nebraska album against all the pressures of fame as this kind of
Dragging B story while we watch this very in-depth arc of depression in the Jersey Shore
Where the only solution is to run away and move to California forever and like she and like that's not a movie anybody wants
to see about anyone
Right. Yeah, so that's that's that's my sum up of it
They flipped the a and the B stories in a way that was so strange
It's just it's it's a weird movie. It's not a bad movie
No, but it's not a good movie. No, it's a problem
Another thing we said in the car was was like it's as if like a bunch of actors got together and we're like
I want to make a movie where all of us get scenes where we get to act our faces. Oh, man
It is acting happening in those fucking moat. Oh my god. Yeah, there's some people just really acting hard
acting
Well, I feel bad for the you know, the bear Jeremy Allen white or whatever like, you know
You know your your basic book on screenwriting is in the scene a character should feel different
Than it does in the beginning of a scene, right?
So it starts off feeling one way and by the end of scene it feels another because that's how we're watching that interaction
That's that's we're watching
Situations where people can possibly change right? That's what makes compelling voyeuristic
Scenic acting movie making work and there are so many scenes where
Bruce's the same exact mood at the start of the scene at the end of nothing changes nothing changes in the same
So nothing affects him. No
But I did just find out that
Matt did you know that the Nebraska and in cold blood were about the same events? Yes, I
Think I think am I the only one who didn't know that I think that common knowledge as a matter of fact
I believe if you listen back to our Halloween episode Jacob just the last episode when Truman Capone stopped by I did indeed ask him
About that he did
It's the start. It's the Starkweather murders. Yeah, it's clear that I wasn't listening at that moment of the last show
You're juggling. You're juggling characters popping by the doorbell. I get it. I'm just letting you know that
Karen and Georgia evidence. I just found that out this week
I didn't I didn't know that Karen and Georgia on my favorite murder just recently covered the Starkweather shit. It's awful and
Yes for a lot, but for a long time it was framed as this sort of Bonnie and Clyde type situation
Yeah, all right sure more and more we're learning. This was a 13 year old girl who watched her parents murdered in front of her
Yeah, not like she really had a choice, but to go with the psychopath. Oh, no. No, it's it's horrible. It's dark
It's dark shit, but but I mean it turns out that story of murder is a bad story well, but
But the fact that we lumped a poor little girl in on it
This country's just fucking dumb
Look at all the things that make this country
It wasn't the Starkville murders
Stark weather murders that they didn't just blame him a 13 year old dragged along for some murders. I think we have indeed figured it out
I think we've righted that wrong ball. I think that's maybe maybe I guess I don't know
Paul Paul Paul I got you the country is in trouble and those murders were horrible. Yes, those are both true
Okay, they might not be related
I don't know it feels like in a lot of ways it feels like he's just misogyny all the way down
That's what it really feels like I went to I told you guys a couple of months ago. I went down to
Prim to look at some of the casinos down there
Just so we can just kind of walk through some of the casinos down there before they shut down right and one of the casinos
Down there has the Bonnie and Clyde car. Yeah, where they were where they were shot to death and
You know, it's got all the bullet holes and everything and it's a tourist attraction and I just stood there and looked at this thing
I was like this this car
was
two people's death site
the evidence of them of them dying is still here and
They they killed people and they robbed people and they hurt people and they and they did all these things
This is not this is not a nice story
And I and I just kind of stood there being disgusted that this car was on display for people to come over and look at
That's me with the Mob Museum people love going to my museum
there's a little like a little little like a mini doc that runs throughout the whole time and there's one words mafia guy is
is talking about being a consultant on a De Niro movie and
They're reenacting the murder and he's describing like how the murder went down and they're like, oh, they're like, oh man
It's got the way he's describing. It's like he actually was there and it's like, oh, isn't that awesome? No. Yeah, it's fucking
Yeah, he was actually there. He was there and he committed fucking brutal murder. I don't know why yeah, that's a
I don't know why that's a taint tickler for you. Oh because Matt, it's the it's the fedora
If you're wearing a fedora
Cosa Nostra, that's right. That's right. Oh, and he's not black. It's those it's those two things put together. Oh, man
Speaking of Vegas icons
Sarah has to Ross was filming a music video and
Yeah, yeah, and I was asked if I would play
Not Elvis. This is key, but a Fremont Street Elvis impersonator. That's that's the key there
Oh, yeah, that is. Yeah, there's a degree in casting there
And if you need an Elvis Matt Donnelly is not your guy if you need somebody on Fremont Street impersonating Elvis Matt Donnelly
so I
My wife
Mistakenly thought I still had this Elvis outfit that I used to have
But it eventually just like weathered away became, you know, I feel like she wore it out
Honestly, if we if we're just telling the truth, it's like she just she just fucked the shit out of
Well, I'm gonna call I'm gonna screen it but
My friend Jeff calls it's Nevada Day
here, that's right and
My friend Jeff knows all the words than the Nevada Day song the Nevada the Nevada anthem
Any calls every single friend who still lives in Nevada every Nevada Day and sings the entire song into their voicemail
And so I have that that's what's happening right now. It's my favorite thing
One of the more fun things about Nevada is that became a state on Halloween. Yeah
Anyhow, so
So I went down to star costume and I was like this is actually is nothing to do with Halloween
I need I need an Elvis costume
and so I look and
In in my sizes they had this really nice red one, it's really nice red one say, okay
That looks really sharp. It was it was a little pricey
But I've been asked to dress up like Elvis on multiple occasions and I don't know if it was figured
You're gonna get another run out of this. Oh, this was a purchase not a not a rental, right? This is a purchase because also
When I did Virgin Voyages and I hopefully that went well enough that they'll invite me back
They do a thing called scarlet night where everyone dresses in red
And I was like, wait a minute
One I can wear this. Yeah
On the Virgin Voyages represent in Vegas. That'll look yeah. Yeah
and so yeah, I bought myself a nice Elvis outfit and then went down to
Fremont and I was like, hey, you guys are just shooting on the street, right? She's like, yeah
Like so there's no like dressing area. She's like knows like so basically I should arrive as Elvis
They're like, yeah, okay
so
Me which coincidentally is the same note that every person who hires Matt to do any gig tells
I knew to ask I knew
It's so common. My my my tear my tear of
Acting is so familiar that I know be like no dressing rooms, right? No makeup
Right is an AAE actor is what they call it arrives as Elvis
I
was just walking up and down Fremont Street dressed I had to tow his Elvis and
Anyone look at you twice?
No, people were loving it
Loving it. And so then I did this at this bit of a Sarah that when the music video comes out
I think it's gonna look great. So I won't spoil it, but it was super fun and
As I'm walking back to my car a guy literally goes like hey
Are you?
Are you like doing stuff here? And I was like, no, no, sorry
I'm just I just actually just got a music video and I'm just walking back to my car. He was okay
Um, can I take a photo of you anyway?
Sure and he's like you like gets down like it's a good angle or whatever. Yeah, it's like
Sorry, I mean, can I do is like a self selfies? Okay, is this selfie? Okay, and I was like, yeah, let's let's do it man
We took a nice selfie whatever and he was like I got to give you some money
This is you better say
You've had a wonderful person I was like
Did you take some money? I hope you took some fucking money. This is the thing
I told the story to Sarah and she goes how much you make I said I said no, no, I'm okay
I want to just want to get home to my kids, you know and
Uh
Sarah was like you you're a fool. Yeah
And I was like, I know I'm dumb every person I talked to it has been like
What was gonna give you it? I was like, I don't know. I don't who knows you probably get a hundred bucks
I doubt it, but you never know man. People are crazy out there. No Jordan Campbell says this is how Matt started on his only fans
Jordan this did feel
It did feel like a moment of like I often gonna rack my brain if I could like make extra money or whatever
it's all the idea if I could just get on a free street just like
It felt like too easy like that's it was like I literally was like trying to not do it and then someone stopped and like
Made sure they are funny and I was getting a lot of attention
You know, I was walking with purpose to like not get stopped, but I was causing a lot of attention walking up and down
Pretty much three dressed at the toe is Elvis. Yeah, so real talk
I think you might be able to make some money doing this especially in like the earlier hours on Fremont Street
Not like 2 a.m. But like the 10 p.m. Yeah. Yeah. No, I'm thinking like 9 or 10
I'm thinking like early early night time and but when the families are still out
Yeah
Because the people the people taking pictures with people on Fremont Street
If you don't want someone to be naked in your photograph, you're out of luck
Like you're just you're just out of luck. Yeah, or if you don't like palm
Crucifixes palm crucifixes are naked people like you do often crucifixes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So everybody's down there though. I did stop and watch a street magician
How was it form for a few minutes? He was really good. He was really good. Well, that's good news
It's after some money in his bucket. He was great
It's hard because there's there's music playing at all kinds of volumes the entire time. Yeah, sometimes it's super loud. Sometimes it's just loud
This guy was a genius. I thought about that while I was watching him. He did it most of it
He did silently right? That's that's what it would take. Yeah
I saw a guy doing that that kind of like over there. They're all silver and money moves them kind of oh, yeah
Yeah with a magic trick kind of attached to that and I was like, yeah, that's all we can do down there. But yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So, yeah, I don't know
Just the second time just to see what it's like to actually give it a shot really
I think I also want you to go down there without getting a spot reserve for yourself
And I want to see if you get some shit for not having a reserved spot
You probably will if you that's the thing if you do it with the intention of getting paid you won't get paid
right people talk about it all the time like when when when folks hit the skids and
They're out on the street begging for money like the first day they feel like oh
We're gonna be alright here. And then after that is this weird beginners luck thing and it just gets really hard
Yeah, yeah, that is a lot of stories. That is a lot of people's stories. You're right. It's all attitude
I think it's all the attitude
I think I think people can I don't even know how to say it because I don't know what it is
But but I think that people can
Sense that what the one thing is soon as you are desperately as soon as you're actually desperate
That's that rippy holy energy. Yeah
I'll tell you who else has got that rippy holy energy and that's the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by the squirrels guide to breaking into podcasting. That's right. This is from cup of scoop in 2025
That's a squirrels guide to breaking into podcasting
Hey
My name is nutso nutso the nutty squirrel
Yeah, and I'm gonna teach you all about breaking in a podcast and
Hey
Say there Matthew, I got a question for you
Do you enjoy fast food I
Have been known to indulge from time to time. Yeah, you're like a baconator
Yeah, I used to do some of the baconator just for the so you like Wendy's nuts in your mouth
You got me good on that one squirrely you got me good
I would normally cut the ad off here, but squirrely actually paid for five minutes
Jacob I heard yes early. I heard you're a connoisseur of fast food eateries as well. Sure. Yeah
Enjoy a vanilla frosty once in a blue moon. I do yeah. Oh, so you like Wendy's nuts in your mouth
Say hey, hey, hey Matt. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know you like a lot of different fast food restaurants
You I do go to the Golden Arches once in a blue moon. Do you oh McDonald's? Sure. I don't oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so you enjoy Big Macs
No, you just get you know the regular cheeseburger the plain one
Okay
I
Really sucked him on that last one there Paul Chamberlain just left the room. It was an unintentional Wallachian impression
I did well, I guess while Sean is just a squirrel
I did sound remarkably like all
I've never seen one Sean and a squirrel in a room together. So I can't I can't say for sure that he's not a squirrel
I was trying to surprise you did play to my recorder
So Jacob is this already played to my recorder, but I was playing the home is Nevada
They think this big if I get them both my mics here
Who's that singing Jeff my friend Jeff well done Jeff. Yeah got some pipes on him
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Oh
Go ahead Jacob. Oh
I was just gonna tag on to the end of Fremont Street. I did see a
While I was down there the other day. I did see a
Parent who was watching a performance
Whose child I would guess?
Six or seven was just sitting on the on the ground at Fremont Street
While the parent was watching something kind of over there, you know a couple of feet away. Mm-hmm
It's the first time I've ever wanted to call CPS on any wait now. Oh
The parent was letting your small child just sit on the on the on the street on Fremont Street
That's that's already disgusting. Yeah, pretty gross
Yeah, I was I was not okay what captured their attention so much. Was it one of the giant gorillas?
No, it was just one of the bands. It was just it was just music going. The band was great
But you see any of the giant gorillas while you're down there, man
No, that's any giant girls. There really it really wasn't actually a lot going on. I know I
Haven't been down there in months without seeing at least three or four giant gorillas. I wasn't I was surprised at how little I mean
We were there. It was a you know, it was I was there from around
Like 330 to five maybe it's like 530
I
Surprised how little was going on?
Like I said, there's a lot of a lot of unhoused people just sitting in the spots that were designated for performers
Yeah begging and then some some some some some crucifixes and then the one guy painted in silver
His bit. Oh
This was also a Tuesday
Maybe don't wake up till later. That's probably that's I mean, that's very possibly true. Yeah, also
I also went to disco the other night
Oh nice and drove down and not since I moved here in 2008 where I stick those back roads to paradise and Koval to get
down to the Venetian
Boy, no one just absolutely no cars. Just driving around absolutely nothing
I've never seen the streets so empty. That's nice. And then I pulled right into the link and
Got in the very first row of self parking just a space wide open for me at seven o'clock at night
Rumors are true Vegas is dead
Or everybody is avoiding Matt
No, I don't think that's it. I could not believe how little
There was anyone around in Las Vegas. That's so like I drive down those streets all the time and they are packed all the time
Yeah, yeah
I have to go down there to fucking the flamingo which has gotten even harder to get to now, which is crazy. I
Should note that they did start building the f1 track. So it could just be a lot of people just avoiding
But that might be it
But also yeah, there was that I mean I walked up and down the link
I was very surprised that that just kind of that's kind of crazy, man. Yeah. Yeah. That's kind of crazy. It was weird
It's anecdotal, but it's weird. Sure still
Still I'm gonna go see disco tomorrow. I'm looking forward to it. I haven't seen it since since the revamp
Oh, I think yes, I think you'll dig it. I'm looking forward to it. I'll tell you though. He recently added
our friends D and
Great grace
Created these clown characters to perform around the venues that are around disco not in the venue itself
The two other people were doing their bit
where they're just oh, yeah, two giant disco balls wearing capes and disco mustaches and
They were killing it. I didn't know I didn't know these people were which is weird
I'm surprised. Oh good. There's two people that were just being that I need to find out who they were
But they were being hysterical so people came out of I always get nervous when people create bits like like Dean Grace did and then
Kind of hand them off, right? The handoff always makes me nervous. I'm glad to hear that. It's going really well
Yes, and so they were just doing a thousand bits and that people nice falling over laughing and I was like, this is great
I'm really looking forward to it. This is gonna be great. Yeah, it's a fun show. I really like that show
It's so different and but it's really cool now. It's super it's super streamlined and it just goes and our friend
Eli is the host
and
He's just so funny. He's just a funny like a full person. Yeah. Well, that's one reason I'm going tomorrow is
Our another friend of ours. Nick is in for Eli. I've seen Nick do it. Nick's great at it. Nick is great at that
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, Nick from banana fame at scoop fest. Yes will be in disco tomorrow. I drank his milkshake
You did you drink it up? I
left a little on the floor for Jonas's wheel, but
a little surprise for Jonas later
Surprise
But the answer is yes, I'll be dressing up like Elvis tonight for my trick-and-treat I'll be Elvis in my neighborhood and yes
I was just about to ask you how long are you because I know what time your trick-and-treat is starting today
I saw your wife last night and she said that you guys are starting at 3 p.m. Today
Well, how late are you planning on going?
We usually go to like 9 or 10. Usually the streets get pretty empty at 9
Okay, and then I just run in a front yard party until until until the streets get rolled up
We have a set time here. It's it's 6 to 8
Yeah, yeah, that's something the high mark, but people come early some people have little kids they go early
Well, it's the light out and then also just you know teenagers and all these other kids that go late and for me for the trick
And treating I like the teenagers. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
for
Magic trick purposes not for yeah. Sure. Yeah
Yeah, it's better to deal with I don't know why Matt thinks I mean something else. I'm talking about his magic trick
No, he's teenagers. I love his magic. I put an audience and we disappear
You want an audience that has grasped the concept of object permanence? That's right before you perform magic. That's correct
Matt's baby magic didn't go well
Yeah, and my my my my big ringer when should I fix the clown in time for it to be a jump scare?
That'd be great. And then I
Got a duck a wooden duck that whoa pecks at cards and and snatches your card out of a deck of cards
Oh, that's pretty good. Whoa
Is it like one of the one of the happy bird? Yes. Well, no, no, no nice
It's like it's like a wooden it's like an ornate wooden
This isn't you'd see it like a kitschy like like a cracker barrel lawn decoration, right?
but it has it has a
Mechanical neck so you push the okay you push the duck's head down and it's just and it just
Opens beacon snatches a card out of a deck of cards. Oh, I wish my wife had that
What it's a what it's an old it's an old it's an old old magic prop. I just bought one. Oh, it is. Okay
Yeah, it's a known thing that the done. Yeah, the duck card picker it be duck. I think it's called. Yeah
Yeah hippie duck dip dippy duck dippy duck dippy duck. That makes sense. Yeah. Hippie dippy duck is a whole different thing
Yeah, you guys want to lose scoop mail, yes, please let's go let's do a little scoop mail
From winter scoop, this is something I've been wanting to talk about for a week
Now the jewelry heist at the Louvre has my brain screaming
The guys use the construction ladder to access a balcony to bypass the front doors
They were work vests and helmets and stole the jewelry after the place opened up guests watched them do it and nobody said anything
They just assumed that they were guys. They're working doing their job the balls on those guys. That's from winter scoop winter scoop
I'm genuinely concerned that the robbers of the Louvre are scoops. I
Have been advocating bring a ladder for years that you can get in anywhere. These people just took that to the nth degree
So I heard also apparently that that kind of apparatus that long ladder
Hooked to a little scooter cart kind of deal is a lot more commonplace out in France because the buildings are so old
That they don't have proper places for you to unload cargo in a lot of these places
Sure. Sure. So it's not like in the states if you saw somebody with a ladder up to a window you go
Wait a minute
right, maybe I
Tell you how you I'll tell you I'll tell you you need
One thing to make it where people don't give you that look in the states when you're when you're doing that and that is an orange
Road cone next to the ladder. Yeah, you're right
I mean that you put a single orange road cone next to the ladder
You're done. The safety vest thing really does a lot does a lot of work. Yep
And if you got a radio like you can just flush this whole thing out. I
Think this could happen all the time. I'm really surprised. This doesn't happen more often
Like you just fit in you just fit in and go do whatever you want
Let's see we got one I
Know people that in magician's world who are thinking that it's a it's secretly a ploy to advertise now
You see me the new now you see me movie coming up. Oh
Could be
That's an elaborate
Well
Was Gabriella one of the Louvre robbers
Jesse Eisenberg is donating a kidney as part of his promotional work, I guess
What? Yeah. Yeah, Jesse. Eisenberg is donating kidney to a stranger and
The bit is they stole his kidney. No, he's just big and what is it with these magicians and donating blood Matt? What's going on?
Does playing with cards enough make you just say that off got way too much blood in me
I'm blanking on her name. She made a documentary about this basically like how it's been it's difficult
Some very healthy people have two functioning kidneys and if you are a very good health
you don't need them both so to speak right and there are a lot of people who need kidneys and
Just did the one on the Satanic temple
Oh, you know what Penny Lane Penny Lane Penny Lane that did a doc on this
She found it very difficult to try to donate your kidney to a stranger. She I remember her doing this doc
I never got to see it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She did a doc about about like rent not even random donations
But like random anonymous donations of organs, right?
Yes
So basically like a lot of times you can put out calls if you need a kidney then then your friends and neighbors or friends
Or friends you put a campaign to do it and that's how right most kidney donation works
But when it comes to just saying like hey, I
Have an extra kidney find someone who needs it for me that that operation wasn't streamlined
But that has improved over the years and so now
People who just kind of are you know, if you're generally, you know, like I said, you don't drink
You don't really do too much crazy shit and you can just be a healthy person
You can go go without go without one of those kidneys. No one has ever asked me for one of my kidneys. Oh
No, I don't know why it's never come up yeah one of your marinated kidneys
Ten scoop in the chat mentions. It's even harder to donate if you bring it in a cooler
Mine I've been sitting on this thing for a week. Come on
YouTube tutorials and now
You made me fill my bathtub up with ice for nothing
Cost me like $23 to get all that ice
We got one from pigases hey Matt Paul and Jacob, thank you guys and especially all the safety cones helper scoops and performers
For putting together another incredible scoop fest. It was amazing seeing so many weird and wonderful scoops
There is a great mix of new and old
Older scoops that hang out with and go on adventures with it's incredible how you can not see a scoop for 18 months and pick
Right back up where you left off from the last scoop fest podcast trivia battles and variety shows
Especially Hollywood squares were some of the very best ever
Although I'm going to try to avoid being conned into sitting in the front from now on
Quick scoop vest that basically proves that I'm a potato
Sunday night after scoop fest I was in an elevator at the Orleans when two very friendly and drunk women hopped on
They noticed my hot dog necklace right away said how much they liked it and we chatted a bit between floors
They were on vacation and clearly having a great time while I stood there being well me when I got off the elevator
I ever heard one of them say to the other it's okay
I guess he doesn't want a party
It wasn't until much later at McMullin's that I realized what was actually happening in that elevator
I just thought they were being polite. I'm already looking forward to the next one
It was great meeting so many new scoops and reconnecting with returning scoop
Thanks again for all the hard work you do to make scoop message a unique and fun gathering
Pegasus will fly again fucking you in the face. That's Roger aka the nest scream our nest creamer aka Pegasus
All right. Thanks Roger sounds like you saved yourself about six to eight hundred bucks, buddy
It's really true. It's probably like you all know you probably were almost about to get rolled
You never know in Vegas, and you know, I think Orleans. It was 350. I thought well, I think I think I
Know for myself just come on
You just kind of default to the no way. This is not happening. This is some candy camera bullshit. I
Have had multiple friends think that they were doing very well with women
Then to realize on their own that they were talking to prostitutes
That's happened to multiple friends of mine and they're sad every time it happens
They still pay for the sex and everything. They still do that
It's a blow to their ego first
It's a blow to their ego that it's a boat
Good day. Good deal fair. Oh
Let's see, oh there's another scoop me or another
What does it think we do scoop fest no I don't need to do the scoop best email right now from bear scoop
Hey, Matt Paul and Jacob in the same vein as the he did what and other tales
I decided to write in with my story of it's actually what a
Time well one of many when my sheer stupidity revealed itself in true glory
For context I live in a somewhat big city not far from Vancouver BC and for years
No decades my commute to and from work
I would routinely see a box truck think a u-haul like a three or four ton with words
diamond delivery
Plastered on the side and back which of course was of course a picture of a huge diamond in the middle now
I don't know if I was just in the monotony of my commute every time I saw these trucks
But I always assumed that I made up a story that of course these trucks needed to be this big
they were delivering diamonds throughout my 1 to 2 million population bustling metropolis and
The safe the safes used to do this probably take up most of the back of these trucks
That was until my early to mid 30s when I saw one of these trucks parked in my townhouse complex outside another unit
I found this odd as why would a residential customer be having diamonds be shipped to them
Oh dear God as I see them taking plants furniture another crap out of the back of the truck
Diamond delivery is a delivery company not a diamond delivery company
So anyway, that's my it's actually what story fucking with the face. That's a bear scoop
Thank you bear scoop. Yeah, I
For a little while when I was a kid. We used to have Schwann's did you go? Yeah Schwann's meal delivery?
Yeah, yeah, the refrigerated trucks and everything. I thought it was delivering swans
I thought these people are getting are getting geese
Swans delivery service. Yeah. Yeah
People used to eat swans, right? That's a thing. I guess you could eat a swan. Why not?
I mean, you did anything with the right attitude
We are one from slurping time motherfucker greetings face fuckers
I'm writing in response to a conversation at scoop fest about bits and how this community attracts people with a fervent love and
Commitment to silly bits. Yeah
It's it's one of the best things about our community
One of my favorite things this year was being privy to scoops sharing their personal bits with each other giggedy
So that we could all go home with fresh road tested material that our spouses and loved ones would still not appreciate
This jogged my my memory of a genius bit
My high school friend Nicole invented that I think some scoops will find useful in their everyday life
Here is what she would do
In the middle of class Nicole would tilt her head up crinkle her nose and say mmm. Did someone just microwave popcorn?
Then seconds later everyone sitting around her would start dry heaving and coughing uncontrollably with laughter
While some managed to choke out a faint fuck you
Let me explain
This is a bit Nicole and her older sister perfected in a prank war as kids
When one of them had a rancid silent, but deadly fart and they wanted to trick the other into smelling
Through many iterations. They found the foulest trick was priming each other from
Microwave popcorn scent as it lowered the victims defenses and when one's olfactory is expecting a sweet buttery scent of microwave
Popcorn the juxtaposition of the actual scent of a putrid ass gas kicks in bad
There is also a delay
So the victim will have taken a full-throated drag and had their lungs filled with the flatuous
Before their senses could smell the the rocket actually been cooking no
That's the result of the prank this is
It's a war crime. It's a hell. I hate I hate what I'm listening. That's a hell of a move
I don't this is actually this is worse than what the u.s. Is doing out in the pacific. Oh
Bung rip a break coughing and retching from my classmates Nicole gave and still gives zero fucks as she did this popcorn bit
Every goddamn time she farts and it was truly one of the funniest things to watch once you're in on the gag
However, she did it to me so fucking bad with this the first time she did it to me
What I was ten years ago that till this day I went when I walked through an AMC movie theater
Feel free to use this bit at your own risk PS. I'm curious what other bits scoops might have to share
And if they could be so good to share them in a fucking scoop mail format
Figgy fucking your olfactory glands. That's slurping chi a motherfucker
That's really funny that that's commitment. I mean that is that is commitment for sure
That is like Geneva wants to have words with you
That's that's just cruel. I mean just do that once is genius to really commit and do it all the time. That's crazy
Yeah
How are you guys on fart humor
Well, I'm very happy with fart humor when it is the the sound of the fart and and the funny like oh
This was this was a fart thing. Yeah. Yeah, this is great as soon as I smell something just rank I
Stop thinking it's funny. So quickly there is there is a my favorite murder animated a letter that somebody wrote into them
About this guy he was working at a post office and he let a fart that was so stank
That the post office had to be shut down and the fucking bomb squad got called
Because they thought it was some kind of chemical contaminant coming in through the mail
It is wild
Wow
Yeah, I never was like all that stuff was farting
It feels like in the in the in the vein of like like bag tagging or like drawing
Yes, if someone falls asleep all that all that kind of stuff puts me in a weird place. I don't like it
I'm with you Jacob. I think the noise is where the funny is the machine. Yeah, make the sounds and all that are great
But like didn't they just have a teacher get arrested for putting fart gas on his students all the time
What? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
There's a story about
to the internet Jacob
When I typed in teacher arrested the autofill was for fart spray. Okay, this was it so share with it
I don't know the exact what what happened, but let's see when it comes to the smell stuff. That's when it starts to get
criminal a
32 year old assistant teacher in West Florence High School in South Carolina was arrested for spraying a foul-smelling
Substance through the school's ventilation system his actions which occurred nearly over nearly a month long period
led to six to six students and over
$55,000 in damages to the school's air conditioning system Lewis face charge of disturbing schools and malicious intent malicious malicious injury to property
I
Questioned the quality of that AC system
Fart spray takes it out
Yeah, that's not HEPA approved. That's for sure
This was and that have you seen the the the cruel thing that the people do for the people who are in the inflated costumes
Yes, because you got a little you got you fart into the fart at the vent
Are you put something at the vent and they're just stuck?
Can you imagine just fart not somebody's vent and it's just like
People take like a fish bait and just throw it up against the fan
My favorite example of that comes from the Harlan Williams
Rocketman movie. He does it he's connected via a tube to another astronaut
That's a part and there's this whole back and forth where they're stuck in there with the fart. Oh
it's funny when it's on TV and it's a sound and you can't smell it, but I think you're right Jacob when you smell it it's
Just I just don't know shit. Yeah. This is why I don't hang out in Paul's bathroom
Yeah, just don't want it just don't want it. What were you about to say Matt?
That I was at a kids Halloween parade
Yesterday where I saw a lot of the idea of seeing these adorable children being assaulted with farts is really just not comforting
You saw a lot of inflatable costumes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So if you yeah, you're gonna get them just hit them with a little fart spray right on the
They're done. Just do it the old-fashioned way and fart on them
Just go in there and fart on them
Let's do a little jock vs. Nerd
I'm on the hunt for balls
The hunt for balls
Explosion up the stairs. Oh, no, it's happening
We got an old-school jock vs. Nerd coming to us today from King scoop King scoop has sent us a timeline jock vs
Nerd, I think he sent us another one of these a long time ago. This one also might be from a long time ago
I didn't see what the date on the email was
but this is I'm gonna give you an event and then I'm gonna give you two other events and
Then you're gonna tell me which of those happen closer to the primary event. Oh, right. Yeah, these are interesting
So the first one and he made this so I can't see the answers. Okay. I like them too. So I can play it too
So these are head trippy
Yeah, so the first one the first San Diego comic-con took place. That's the main event
That's the primary event is that closer in time to the Berlin wall being built or the fall of the Berlin wall?
Ooh
Paul you want to go first on this one you seem like you got a sure some kind of handle
Does anybody know when the Berlin wall was built?
Well, it came down in the 80s so before that I
Asked when it was built. Yeah, it was built before that
But it's like the 90s or right out. It was not built in the 90s. It got built in like
In like the 50s, right
After the war right
Oh
Boy, it's gonna be close
Close close close. I guess I'm gonna say it's closer to the building of the wall
Do you know when the first comic-con was?
78 I think oh
Well, then I would also say it's closer to the to the building of the wall
Matt, what do you think? So I have to get which event is closer to the wall or comic-con
Yeah, it's comic-con is the is the primary event
Yeah, is that closer to is that closer in time to the Berlin wall being built or the Berlin wall being taken down?
I'm gonna say Berlin wall taken down
All right, so Paul and I both think built Matt thinks
taken down
It is the Berlin wall being built right
Comic-con first done in 1970 of the world was built in 61
So off on that one came down in 89
Okay
Let's see we got the first Major League Baseball World Series took place
Is that closer to Joseph Stalin coming to power or Coca-Cola is first sold in bottles?
I'll go first on this one. I think this is gonna be closer to the Coca-Cola. What what's the main event again?
Major League Baseball first World Series, okay
World Series Stalin or coke
Yeah
I'm going world. I'm going
coke cola the stories of like I
Think it was like shoeless Joe Jax in order for being like an early investor in coke
So I'm gonna go with coke as well
Really? Okay. I feel like coke is super old. And so is the World Series. I'll just but this isn't coke
This is bottles. This is bottled coke. I'll go contrary and I'll say Stalin. All right, let's see
It is coca-cola
World Series 1903
Stalin 1924 Coca-Cola first bottled
1894. Oh, wow. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's it. Oh, that's the other bottling. I know. Okay, that's that
bottling thing I
Think that's the non carbonated
Bottling of coca-cola and you had to you had to have the thing to add
Into yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you had to add the seltzer water in maybe okay
I
Think I might be I might be off on those dates. I should know this my granddad worked for him
the first disco world novel by Terry Pratchett was published disk is that closer to
That does say disc world
No, it's a what yes also I have disco on the mind
Yeah, so anyway disc world novel was published
Is that closer to Israel becoming an independent Jewish state or Donald Trump becoming president?
I
have I
Don't have a guess on this really at all. I know that Terry Pratchett is a fairly modern
Author so I'll say Trump disc world was in the 80s. Oh
Okay, I believe
Late 70s early 80s
I'll go with Israel. Yeah, of course is about Israel
Matt I think it's also about Israel. Let's see
Point for Jacob Donald Trump up this world published in 83 right on that Paul
Israel becomes an independent Jewish state in 1948 and Donald Trump becomes president and 2016. Okay, so there you go. Okay
The first time a player Wilt Chamberlain scored 100 points in a basketball game
Is that closer to Orson Welles war of the world's being broadcast or Facebook's founding?
Chamberlain scores a hundred points with the still that's the 70s the Big Dipper. Yep
No, three-point line just scored a hundred points two points at a time that thing was in the 50s
the world of worlds, yep
and
This was found in late 90s, I think Facebook was like, yeah
Something like that. Yeah, it had to been like yeah very late 90s like 98 or something 97
I'm gonna go with Facebook. I think the world of worlds is older than that
I'll go with war of the worlds. Oh
You put me in a predicament
I'll go
I'll go Facebook as well
See here
War of the world's Paul gets a point. We go. Yeah back on the board
1960 sorry
War of the world's is that the hundred-point score from wilt is in the 60s. It's 62 not in the 70s
We were off on that. I also thought that was in the 70s
War of the world's is 38 Facebook 38 2004
so
Basically every single date we said about anything in that question was all wrong
Yeah, we were just wrong about every well and that and that tracks that I would get it right for not having the right math
First ever video game tennis for two was created
Is that closer to the USSR launching Sputnik or the movie Jaws opening in theaters?
Tennis for two is the video game. Is that closer to Sputnik or Jaws?
Sputnik was 60s Jaws was what 78?
Something like that
And what do you think and what's the main thing the though the tent the game
Yeah, tennis for two tennis for two was like 60
I'll go with the Sputnik
Your Sputnik Matt your jaws, yeah
Tennis for two
That's gotta be early, I think Sputnik I'll go Sputnik. Yeah, it's earlier than you think. Let's see here
Wait, it's hard to read this
Sputnik. Oh it is Sputnik. Yay tennis for two 1958
Oh Sputnik was launched in 57
Okay, and then Jaws opened in 75. So Sputnik was really close. Yeah
Rocky Marciano retired having gone undefeated in 49 boxing matches
Is that closer in time to computer game space invaders being released or the GI bill is signed providing financial aid to veterans?
Rocky Marciano closer to space invaders or the GI bill
That's gotta be the GI bill I'll go GI bill. I'll go space invaders just cuz I'm already losing this game
I'll try space invaders -
Let's see here. No, I think it's the original space invaders ball. Okay. Oh, you meant space invaders also. Yes
Let's see. It is the
It's the GI bill. Oh
Rocky is
56 the GI bill is 1941 space invaders is
Let's see, let's do one more Dungeons and Dragons was first published
Is that closer to the International Space Station being opened or McDonald's being founded? Oh
D&D versus International Space Station or McDonald's McDonald's Mickey D's
Okay, I'll go space station then
See
Sorry, this is a like a word document and then I have to look back I like the area. Yeah it is
Space Station D&D
1974 space station open in
2000 McDonald's is founded 1940
Jacob you killed us in this game. You you destroyed it did. Oh
Did I? Yeah, I think you won most of them. Oh
Well good for me in that case. I win
The fabulous prizes that go along with it are mine
Thank you so much. Oh shit, I just closed it out without taking the person again
Whoever you were I said your name at the beginning of that and
Shoot oh
I feel terrible now. I closed it out too early. Thank you so much for sitting that in we really appreciate it
I think that is I think that is that scoops second timeline scooper. Yes, our timeline jock versus nerd
They sent in so thank you so much for that. Hey scoops commas reading go hey scoops comm go over there
You can send us an old-school jock versus nerd just like that one
Just that you just heard there. You can also send us an email over there send us some scoop mail over there at hey scoops comm
Also, you can make us a scooper to you can make some prices right jock versus nerd
You can make us an obelisk jock versus nerd. We're running low on all of our jock versus nerd
So head over to the hate scoops comm and make us some new ones. It's great. It's a it's a big part of the show
Yeah, we could really use them. Yeah, do it
I want to thank
podcast
Thanks, Ben. I want to thank all all the people support us open our patreon page
It's the beginning of a new month, so we don't have any of our new
Thank yous to do just yet, but we appreciate you
supporting us Paul is on a mission to add a newsletter to
Our our deal and yes, we even had an official meeting about today before we got on air Paul's on top of it
He's a motivated man
This newsletter is gonna be great. And so we're doing all kinds of cool stuff just to keep it fresh over there on our patreon page
If you aren't supporting us yet, please think about doing so we have all kinds of different tiers
Monthly or yearly levels yearly will save you some money
And if you can fit it into your budget, it would help us out a lot
So head on over to preaching fun calm and check it out right now
Or if you too are gonna get yourself some new socks for reasons that you would rather not talk about head on over to farts
in a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm it does take you over to our patreon for as well for as little
As three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air. You can do monthly subscriptions
You can do yearly subscriptions. You can also gift subscriptions to other people. We got the holidays coming up fairly soon here
So if you want to gift a subscription to our patreon to someone else
You can do all of those things right over there at preaching fun calm and of course at farts in a bag dot biz
In my mind Paul is still wearing his sock ankle it as we're recording right now
I just want to be clear about that just in your mind
Just in my mind and on your ankle
Close that sock, it'll give you a pink eye. Thanks for listening. Stay safe out there. Happy Nevada day, and we'll see you soon
From all of us here at Mathematical Designs Free Social
Add them and start it
We're preaching fun
We are
See ya