Oh hello there, I am so glad you are here because it is time to thank you the ice cream
truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Jason Klepper, Jeff Harris, Jonathan, Lori Ellsworth, Leon
Cassam, Malia, Mike, Paul's brother, and Pyro.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to preachingfun.com.
Where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows, the life you save
may be your own.
Just may be.
Boom.
A program.
Here we go.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
I also want to thank a ranch slug.
We owe him a bunch of thank you.
That's right, ranch slug.
I'm going to thank him at the top of the show.
Even though he's an ice cream truck driver.
Thank you ranch slug.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, that's Paul Mattingly.
Also sitting in Las Vegas, that's me and Jacob.
We're preaching fun.
Hey everybody.
I tell you what, I am preaching fun, but I accidentally just bummed myself out yesterday.
Oh no.
What did you do?
Did you read the newspaper?
Well, this is the thing, I don't listen to news podcasts anymore, I'll listen to Justin
Robert Young when I feel like I can take it, when I feel like I'm okay.
It's absolutely, yeah.
Because he tells it like it is and the way he's telling it, I don't like the way it is.
And the rest of the time, you normally just play myself with sports podcasts.
And right now, there's not a lot of sports happening.
And so I just go into the back catalog of Pablo Torre explains, what does it explains
at all?
No, that's Clarissa.
I also always get Pablo Torre and Clarissa confused.
Yeah.
Easy to do.
Easy.
Yeah, yeah.
Finds out.
Pablo Torre, Melissa Jonard.
And they're talking about this obscure statistician guy from the 80s is doing a deep dive and
this guy who was kind of ahead of the sabermetrics thing before that became a thing, for anyone
who doesn't know what we're talking about, it's like basically the nerds won breaking
down baseball, then the nerds won breaking down basketball, and he was the first nerd
to break down basketball.
And he was...
Is he the moneyball to basketball that the moneyball guy was to baseball?
Correct.
The guy, Bill James, who started the moneyball craze, he was in the moneyball GM, but he
was the guy who first started kind of breaking down baseball as a solid thing, anointed this
guy whose name I'm forgetting as the-
The moneyball basketball.
Yeah.
But that guy did not go on to have different success and basically, I guess, trigger warning,
suicide.
I don't know.
Well, yeah.
He didn't have depression.
He didn't feel like he should have done something.
He literally laid out an argument, like he laid out arguments for basketball players.
He was a very laid out argumentous guy that he basically wanted to end his life specifically
on his 60th birthday and just be done with it.
And you say this bummed you out, huh?
This super upbeat story somehow bummed you out?
You've got like three years.
What are you worried about, man?
And I'm thinking, I'm reading, I'm at the gym, I'm walking on my kid's soccer practice,
I was reading about this obscure statistician and then it takes a turn and I'm sure there's
a warning in the notes.
I never read the episode notes.
Right.
And so, but it was also fascinating, like he wrote all these emails to his family and
put them to be sent hours after his death.
He made sure-
Oh, so he really set it all up.
Yeah, he made sure to do it at the back parking lot of a police department so he could call
911 so he could be an organ donor and no one who hadn't dealt with death would have to
see him besides people who were in charge of doing that.
Wow.
It was this very crazy-
Intriguingly phone out.
-consuming thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it really-
I'm inspired.
I'm not depressed by this, I'm inspired by this.
Pump the brakes.
What's the scoop fest today, Jacob?
Slow down.
Slow your roll.
Oh, you are not helping your case, sir.
I know.
And I was like, oh man.
And then I was like, well, I'm going to get off, you know, I still had some walking to
do at the soccer practice and so I was like, I'll switch over.
And I decided to listen to two characters and a clown.
Which one?
The last one.
Oh, it's over.
Right.
So I'm just going to tell you this, it is a fascinating one to listen to because when
they start the episode, they don't know they're doing their last episode.
Really?
Oh.
Yes.
It's that much of a thing, huh?
Oh, I had no idea.
Right.
It's not a bad blood thing, is it?
No, it's fascinating.
Again, another really fascinating thing about-
It's just a mutual agreement that they're done.
Yes.
But everybody's still amicable.
Everybody's still friends.
They're still working with each other backstage and still loving each other.
What happens is you kind of listen to the episode and I knew that this was their last
episode so it was fascinating to listen to it unfold.
It was fascinating to hear them realize it.
Yeah.
So I knew it was their last episode, but I thought it was going to be them coming on
air to talk about why they're going to do their last episode.
And instead, I listened to 11 minutes of them talking about crab cakes and fish cakes and
I'm like, "This is really weird."
And then it's so clear that they have, and those who have to forgive me, I'm just going
to talk about it, but it's so clear that there's a bunch of straws on the back of the Campbell,
so to speak.
Right?
Oh.
They're talking about how things are changing at work.
They're talking about how things that they're dealing with at home.
And then they talk about getting a complaint email from a listener.
And then they kind of get into like, "I want to talk to you guys, but I don't want to talk
about stuff on there.
I don't want to worry about what I'm saying to you guys."
And it is a fascinating listen because it's very clear Jimmy is the first one who's out.
Right.
We realize it.
Yeah.
So for this, we have another podcast.
It's two characters and a clown.
It's three friends of ours.
They all work backstage at a Cirque du Soleil show.
They've been doing a podcast for three and a half years.
And...
Well, they all work on stage.
They're all three performers at a Cirque du Soleil show.
Yeah.
They're literally two characters in the show and a clown in the show.
And you still have...
If you're just giving us now, you have three and a half years of fine episodes.
Yeah.
For instance, I just subscribed to it.
I'm really looking forward to catching up.
When there's a half hour left, maybe a little more, RJ makes a big dark night of the soul
speech to Jimmy, really tries to get Jimmy to understand and feel his value, things like
this.
And Jimmy is having none of it, none of it.
And that was hurting me, it was hurting to listen, you know?
It does, it hurts to listen to that.
I was like, "No, come on, buddy."
He's telling Jimmy how valuable Jimmy is, and Jimmy's like, "Eh."
Yeah.
Okay.
And Jimmy's not buying it.
Right.
What?
Come on, Jimmy.
Exactly.
And then it's really funny because then Johnny just comes in, right, and starts talking.
And I timed it.
RJ doesn't speak for 25 minutes after his big speech, nothing.
So I was like, "Oh, Johnny's the only one who thinks this is still a podcast right now."
Oh, no.
I think RJ knew on the big speech when it was just landing with nothing, he was like,
"No."
We're done.
And then...
Wow.
And then so, you know, I mean, spoiler, it's a fast thing, listen, so I'm not even, I mean,
it's all a spoiler, but it's all a fast thing.
Listen.
Listen anyway.
RJ just goes back in and goes, "So why don't we just stop doing it?"
Like right after he's not speaking at all, we're supposed to do it.
Johnny is caught off guard?
I don't think people realize, even RJ's friends, even me, I fall into this trap too.
I forget what a thinker RJ is.
Yes.
So RJ will sit and think and ponder over something.
And then when he comes back into the conversation, he's got it all straightened out.
Totally.
And you don't realize it for a minute or two.
Yes.
Big heart, big brain, that boy.
Of course.
Just really loves his voice.
And he literally just, he says, "Let's stop doing the podcast."
On there, you can't hear, you know, it's an audio podcast.
Johnny's struck and RJ goes, "Look how big the smile on Jimmy's face is."
And Johnny does.
It goes, "Oh, you're right.
It's over."
All right.
Oh my God.
And then, and I was like walking around my neighborhood, like I had to push pause to
like make dinner for my kids.
And I was like, "God damn it."
I was like riveting.
I was just like, crawling with discomfort for my friends and also like totally enthralled.
And then I had to like table it for an hour and then go and finish it on a night walk.
And I was just like, I was teary-eyed walking.
I was like just, it was the most crazy podcast episode ever.
Like, I couldn't believe it.
I think it's hilarious that-
I had honestly been saving it because, I was saving, it's the strong word, but I've been
saving it because I was like, "Oh, they've got their last episode up.
I've got a basic time to listen to it.
Now I'm just fascinated."
Yeah.
I know because like, you know, we were lining them up for a trivia battle, right?
And so that's when RJ let me know that it was like, "Oh, I don't think that's a good
idea."
I was like, "What?"
And same thing.
I was like, "Bad blood?
Anything?"
He's like, "No, no, no, no, no."
Huh?
Everybody's happy.
And so it was just so clear that the choice to be a podcaster just wasn't what they wanted
to do.
You know?
It was a secondary choice.
Well, that's it.
They bring us up at the very end.
They bring up this podcast at the very end and saying they don't want to become what
we are.
Right.
They see our world as a burden.
Well, they also have real jobs.
That was the whole thing.
I could like scream across my headphones.
I was like, "You know, I, we, this podcast is what we are."
Yeah.
Right.
We weren't very successful guys doing something else.
I thought we wanted to shed a little light.
This is our successful thing and then we use this to bounce into other possibilities and
entrepreneurialism.
Yeah.
This is our Cirque du Soleil.
This is our...
Yeah.
This is what it is.
We're walking the tightrope right now, baby.
This is the thing when we tell people about this thing, people go, "Ooh."
Exactly.
When they tell people about Cirque du Soleil, people go, "Ooh."
Right.
We tell people about our little podcast and people are like, "Oh, that's very nice for
you guys."
Yeah.
No one goes up to them after their show.
So it was like, "Should you guys podcast also?
Because I really want more of you guys."
So Scoop Jesus is saying Jacob was successful and that's true, but I think Jacob will also
make the point that as successful as he is, and he is very good at his job and has a lot
of success as a sound guy, he still gets a lot of interactions with fellow performers
who are like...
This is a different thing.
How do you make this podcast thing cook?
How do you make...
Yeah.
This is a very different thing than what I do.
And I'll tell you what, to Matt's point, and you're talking to the guys about doing the
Cirque shows and then doing the podcasting stuff, I would be a very different podcaster
if I didn't have a day job.
Every time I talk about quitting running shows, SJ lets me have it.
She's like, "What are you talking about?
You're just going to podcast all the time.
If you don't run shows, you're just going to podcast all the time.
What are you going to talk about on these podcasts?"
Right.
It's true.
You got to have some external life before it comes in.
Yeah.
But this is a whole different thing from what I do.
When I go and run a show, I sit back there, I'm executing somebody else's vision, I'm
doing all these types of things, here, it's us.
This is our thing.
We get to do whatever we want on this because it's us.
We also all three don't work with each other, right?
I was going to say, we don't share a dressing room.
Yeah.
We get a break.
No, but with that, the whole reason why I wanted to do the podcast with Paul in the
first place was I was a dad and all I liked to do for my entire teens and twenties was
bits.
All I wanted to do was bits.
All I wanted to do was bust balls and make jokes with friends.
I knew that being a dad would make that go away a lot, not all the way, but a lot compared
to what I was doing.
Sure.
I was like, "Oh, let's get in a space where we can make fun of stuff and do jokes."
Good calls.
Good call.
It was definitely a big time branch for me, both personally and professionally, to get
this going.
That's the thing, texting with RJ afterward, like, "Yeah, this is what podcasting is to
me and you guys don't require any of it."
Right.
"You don't require any of it."
So it was really interesting.
I mean, because they do, all three of them share that dressing room, right?
Yeah.
It was there?
I don't know how we would do that.
I would say-
I don't know, if we had a dressing room, if we saw each other off microphone and off camera
all the time, I don't know how we'd still do a show.
Totally.
And especially if it gets like touch and go, whether we can talk about where we work together
or not.
Right.
Right?
Oh, yeah.
That fluctuates.
That's huge.
And I would say that the- I think that maybe the toughest time for this podcast- actually
the pandemic, second toughest time for this podcast was when Paul and I worked together.
Oh, sure.
I think 50 Shades was probably the harder spot.
Yeah.
And it became the dominating talking point.
We had to purposely branch off from that.
Yeah.
I mean, we literally butted heads.
We're like, I didn't care about biting the hand that fed me.
And Paul was like, this is a bad idea to bite the hand that feeds you.
Well, yeah.
And-
And you were both right.
Matt didn't care about it.
And Paul did.
Yeah.
And I shouldn't have.
I shouldn't have given a fuck.
Shouldn't have given a roaring fuck.
But it's easy to say that when we're out of it.
Yeah.
It's easy to say we shouldn't have cared about something that we're no longer inside of.
Yeah, it is.
It is.
It's like people.
It's hard to say you don't care about people while you're inside of them.
It is hard to say that.
I've done my best.
Yeah.
And that's not the only time Paul did that.
We did the Scoop Cruise.
I was making fun of the opening show in the elevator.
That's right.
And our passengers got off the elevator and Paul let me have it.
And by the way, that was very helpful.
Paul was like, do not talk shit about anything.
Everyone reports everything to everyone on cruise ships.
Everybody has ears.
You cannot, as an entertainer, talk shit.
He was right then, even though my pride didn't want him to be.
And now I-
I don't think I was too mean about it.
You were not-
I was probably serious about it.
You were very serious and very direct about it.
You were not-
You were direct about it.
I wouldn't say you were mean about it, but you were direct about it.
Yeah.
Well, because I'd done nine months on a cruise ship.
Yeah, yeah.
You were just real about it.
Live that fucking life, baby.
Yeah.
Well, in some sense, that moment turned out to be very key to what I'm doing now.
There you go.
So I'm not saying you were wrong in any way.
I'm saying in hindsight, I was like, boy, not only were you right then, but I'm even
more grateful now.
I go on cruise ships like everything is bumped.
Exactly.
And it is.
Because it is.
It fucking is.
I mean, seriously.
They need the fucking organ man.
You go to enough ports where everyone's toting machine guns and you get a little sense in
your mind like, oh, there could be some shit going down.
I bet people are really looking out for stuff.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
Like, you know, yeah, you go to enough places where you're like, oh, there's some serious
military hardware like back in these ports.
They're not going to they're not going to let games get played.
Yeah.
I'll tell you who doesn't let games get played in their ports.
And that is the following sponsor today's show.
I don't believe it.
Today's show.
The show.
I don't think anything any time soon is brought to you.
No, they didn't think it was either.
Matt and Mattingly's Meet the Wolfman Act Four Scene Three, Matt escapes the wolf man
by prepping him to perform Unfool Us from Scoop John C.
We now take you to Act Four Scene Three of Matt and Mattingly Meet the Wolfman.
Arr. Yes. Arr. Great job, Wolfman. Love the pizzazz. You have to get that giant, dirty,
thick fingernail underneath two cards, but then at the top of the deck, then hold it
as one.
You're going to lift it up. Oh, man, I'm trying. These paws ain't cooperating. I know. You're
doing very good. It's just called a double lift. You're going to lift up both cards and
show it to the audience like one.
What do you say we rearrange my appointment time for a full moon and I could just do my
straight transformation routine?
The problem is Lincoln at Fool's likes to bump people around depending on the schedule
and your local so he knows he can bump you around. So you're not going to get the spot
that we can't rely on that spot.
I get it. I get it. But I mean, I'm a rare reverse werewolf. I'm Wolfman all the time
except during a full moon. Well, I understand. I understand. Well, let me just rehearse some
of the lines like so so Penn and Teller, did I fool you? You want to try that one? So Penn
and Teller, did I fool you. OK, I think the fool is a little long. Oh, I've been going
to speech therapy for a long time and it just don't take. Yeah. Yeah. No, I understand.
I understand. I think you got a rabbit I could eat. That's the one out of your hat. Yeah,
come on. Stereotype my ass. That's why I got in the biz room. Oh, did you win your
team's high school basketball championship while we're doing we're doing stereotypes
back and forth? Did you come here on top of your friend's van? Just because my best friend
happens to be named Stiles. Very common. Teen Wolf references for modern audiences. Is there
a young lady named Booth that has some of your attention, but not as much as it should?
Booth. I can't believe her name was Booth. Wait, Wolfman, what was her name? Booth. And
her hate scoops at checkout. Oh, Lord. Oh my God. Remember proposing that we should just
end the show at episode one thousand. Oh, yeah. Yeah. And that bothered Paul a lot when
I even just well, I quickly fixed it and said, no, that's the beginning of season two. We're
off to the races. Oh, I saved myself for another thousand episodes. But who knows, season two
might be the last season. It might be the season one might have been the penultimate
season. We're going into third season here. Well, we don't know how long season two might
be. Oh, well, I mean, it's going to be a thousand episodes at least. At least. I guess we know
a season is at least a thousand episodes. Maybe for for for a bit sake, it's a thousand
and one and then season season three starts on one thousand two. Oh, I explained to a
friend the other day that they asked about a friend of mine was asking about podcast
season. We're going to remember that note for seven years. But yes, keep keep going.
I'll remember that easily. We need at least seven seasons, says Bossy. I will be dead
by season seven. So that's going to be tough. That's going to be tough. Not to say someone
couldn't pick this ball up. It's going to be my children and all of your dogs. My dogs
will be long dead before that. You won't get it. Whatever incarnation of whatever, whatever
sled dog thing you currently are adopting or fostering. Oh, my God, you're right. It's
never going to stop. Yeah. So speaking of my dogs and talking to Matt's kids, the reason
I was a little bit behind today was we're working with a contractor who their mascot
is a little corgi dog in a hard hat. So it's really cute. So that helped get all right.
All right. Let's say let's say percentage. Give me a percentage. How much of a percentage
of of of you selecting this contractor had to do with that image? Oh, 80 percent easily.
Good. OK, because because that was part of it. And Ann sent me that link and everything.
And we we saw that. So we're like, yeah, like we're going to go. So yeah, it was really,
you know, they know their market. Yeah. These are exterior house painters. And what do you
call it? And so Ann had been looking to get some work done on the exterior of the house
for a long time. And she's already had, you know, ideas sent out to professional planescapers
that can make it look like, you know, how they want. And so she's got all the great
the paint ideas set, everything set. And we got finally a consultation today. They had
to move their time back a little bit just because they were super busy. But we're supposed
to be meeting at noon. We ended up meeting closer to one. So that's why I got pushed
back a little bit time wise. But looks like everything's going to move forward. And hopefully
by October, we're going to have new exterior colors and things done. And also the big thing,
the brickwork, the brickwork, which I might add, that allowed for the entrance of one
squirrel into my basement. So the so the lack of brickwork, the lack of brickwork. So we're
going to get that all touched up. They can do that as well. So we're going to get that
all patched up. And they're going to do this process called lime washing cutting the brakes
in that truck. They absolutely are. They want in. But we're going to get it limed washed
and it's going to look really nice. So the brick, the brickwork is going to get touched
up, masoned in, fixed up. And what's the line washing do? It makes it look white. Okay,
instead of, you know, different shades of white instead of the regular brick color that
we have right now. Oh, so it's what it makes it lighten up. Okay, exactly. Some of it is
kind of like falling apart. There is a piece of brick missing from the very front of our
house where it's really close to a vent for the air conditioning system. And I could look
in that vent and I could see outside of my house. And so I was like, okay, so currently
well, that's the vent, the Mattingly fix that's going on for that piece of brickwork right
now is a big goopy chunk of great stuff. I scored it into the wall. So you've got all
this brick and then this hunk of yellow nasty just get off the side, but you can't get back
into the towel. I would have suggested just shoving a towel. No, it wouldn't have a towel
wouldn't have worked. It wasn't that big of a gap, but it was big enough. Okay. The great
stuff worked. So there you go. Uh, yeah. Yes. I know ranch slunk. You can't paint, uh, exactly.
So the lime wash allows this. Look at that. Perfect. Ranch slunk coming through with the
info. Ranch slunk in the chat says, uh, brick should not be painted as it needs to breathe.
Lime wash allows for this so that it does not crumble due to weathering. Exactly. Uh,
gosh, that's a big shame because all of the brick on the, on my house is all painted.
We finally gave him his thank you. And then he's coming off everywhere with these facts.
It's pretty great. I know. Well, I'll tell you, I'll tell you, Jacob, your brickwork
is probably safe given the environment that it's in. I don't have any, there's no moisture
getting exactly. It's so bone dry. It's not going to be a thing, but he was just telling
us about a painted brick situation that they're dealing with on another home. They spent four
days trying to get the paint, working to get the paint off so the brick can get worked
on again. So it's just a nightmare if you actually do paint your bricks incorrectly.
So we knew about that. That's what I'm saying. Yeah, I have painted bricks, but maybe, maybe
the dryness will save me in my house. I think that's it. And it's also, it's also probably
depends on the mixture of the brick and what kind of, like, these are like straight up
bricky bricks. Are yours more like, uh, non-bricky bricks? I'm fascinated where this question
is about to go. I am so curious. Number one, Las Vegas masonry podcast. Let's roll. I don't,
I just kind of believe there are different kinds of compositions of the masonry. I am
so curious what Paul, what knowledge of bricks Paul is about to reveal and what level of
brick knowledge he thinks that I have. Are they grade A bricks? Are they grade B? So
I'm looking for to get some work done on my bricks. Now these are bricky bricks, you'll
know. Brickety bricks. Yeah, these are brickety brick brick bricks. These ones have the same
intelligence as a U.S. Senator. Oh my, well, brickety brick. Everything about our, our
house is 1980. The house looks like the Ford Tempo that we used to own. If we still had
that Ford Tempo, it would, you could park the Ford Tempo we used to have right next
to our house and it would disappear like camouflage. You know how, uh, the, the enterprise D has
that beige and, and, uh, wood. Sure. Oh yeah. Yeah. No, Matt and I were just talking about
that earlier. The enterprise D with the beige-ness. The different browns and tans. Extra dick.
The different browns and tans. So it was a Ford Tempo from 80, 82 maybe. It was a Brown
Ford Tempo from 82. Uh, I think Brown Ford, yeah, around 82 or 84. Uh, 84. Go 84. It needs
to be a little bit newer than that then. I love, okay. So we're, we're, for those of
you listening, we're building up the, uh, the pictures here, uh, of a Brown Ford Tempo
from 80. Oh yeah. That's, that's good and brown. Yeah. It was just like your house.
It was two-tone though. Like it had, the top of it was, was light beige and the bottom
was dark beige and then the seats were beige. It was just the beige-iest fucking thing and
our house is just beige. You got a beige house. The crazy thing about it too, they just replaced
the windows before we moved in. She's mighty bland. Boring as all get out. She's a beige
house. No curb appeal at all. Just making you forget it exists. Uh, yeah. It is, I mean,
for me personally, I could give a shit what the exterior of the house looks like because
I've made the interior look like, at least my basement, a vomit of color and craziness.
You know what I mean? It's, it's, it's nuts down here. Yeah. It's, it's, it's, it's special.
I love it. I love it down here. It's crazy. Uh, it makes me happy. Um, and it, and it
is very, a very nondescript home. Like if you were looking for like a place to just
hide forever, this would be it, but, uh, it's going to be this beautiful cottage blue and
whites, but they, when they put the new windows in on the house, the windows that they got
had a green interior trim that was just part of the, the build, like the, it's metal green
and it just looks wackadoos. Anyway, we're getting everything fixed up and it's going
to be really lovely. And the fact that this company can fix them windows, the fact that
this company can fix the brick as well makes me really happy because like I said, some
of it's being held together with great stuff. So there you go. Yeah. Well, squirrels are
being held out with, with great stuff. Yes. Yeah. Great stuff. Single-handedly keeping
squirrels out of the Mattingly household. It's keeping something out. It's keeping some
stuff out. Yeah. Uh, latter day scoop says my basement is the suburb equivalent of stabbing
a person in the attic just to see color. I, I, or the Arctic just to see color. Oh yes.
Okay. Yes. Then that makes more sense. Uh, yeah, kind of, kind of. Yeah. I drive along.
I pull up to my every time I go up into my attic, I go completely colorblind. It's terrible.
I do pull up to my very nondescript drive and then I opened the basement door and then
just hit with a flood of color. And also in the chat, can a clumsy knows what's up because
that dog ain't no dog. That's three squirrels in a dog costume. It's a heist. Oh yeah. It's
a heist. It's a heist. Could be, could be. If only we could get in, but there's so much
great stuff. I'm seeing some, some faces in the chat here that they're going to get thank
you videos of from my son. Uh, uh, uh, but, uh, it's that time of year for my son makes
adorable thank you videos. If you donate to him this year, the theme is, uh, if he wins
his donation contest, he gets a big annoying beach ball. That'll be in the house and annoy
his mother. So he's putting out videos. This has helped me annoy my mom and you can donate
to it and scoops party stepped up. But, uh, but, but, but do, do step up and, uh, and,
and if you want up, up, the link is on my Instagram. If you go to my noodler and click
on my links, it says donate to my kid's school, but you can see the, uh, it's weirdly not
on your wife's social media at all. It's almost like she doesn't want it to happen. So, uh,
public schools still need a little extra funding. Believe it or not. Yeah. No, I don't. I can't,
I can't imagine. You kid me. He is, he is like 150 bucks out of the top 10. So, uh,
he's close to getting some real, real recognition there. That's fantastic. Good for him. Does
he get a prize? If he, if he finishes in the top 10, I think he has an extra like some,
I don't know, some doodad bullshit sticker. Get some graduate eighth grade. Yeah. Look,
they'll, they'll make him stand up at the graduation or something. Yeah. Ooh. Spirit
of the funding drive. Let's go. Spirit of the candy bars. Spirit of the candy bars,
man. That's, I am the spirit of the candy bars. Woo. Spirit of the funding drive. Uh,
I, Jacob, bring our buddy, Jobbeth in here for a minute here. Oh, that's fine. Jobbeth
in here? Yeah. Well, you go ahead and talk and I'll bring you up. Jobbeth is, uh, going
to take his show to Spain. And so he's trying to, uh, crowdfund that effort. And, uh, he,
he was, he reached out to me to say, if you could talk about the show, I said, yes, but
I also wanted to come up with something for the scoops to put on his Kickstarter. And
so, uh, he, he, uh, he's going to announce what that, what that is. Um, when you find
him, Jacob, Jesus, Jobbeth, start talking. I can't find him. Oh, you need me to start
talking so you can find me. I'm sorry. I thought Matt just picked up on it and started running
with it. Oh no, I wanted both of you. Oh, there you are. I found you. Awesome. So yeah,
I, um, producing. I was like, I can't find him in the fucking zoom thing. I don't know.
From times being in the churn and otherwise, uh, past handful of years, I have kind of
shifted lanes a little bit into doing hypnosis shows instead of the normal mentalism that
I was doing before. And it's, it's kind of really blown up and it's taken me all over
the place. So yeah, I got an invitation to go and participate in this year's 2025 Barcelona
fringe festival in Barcelona, Spain, which is exciting. And we're, uh, I'm dragging
my wife along. We're making a big adventure out of it. So we're going to end up hitting
a couple different European countries on the way there. Um, but I'm looking to really build
exposure with this thing. So the, the purpose of the Kickstarter, they all look like they're
there to raise money, which is, which is great. And there's some fun perks. And we'll talk
about some of those that per Matt's suggestion, which I think is fantastic. And I would love
to do, um, some specific add-ons for the scoops really. I'm trying to get this thing to hit.
So it, you know, it triggers the algorithm and I get more of a global exposure for this
thing because it's, if anybody's ever performed at a fringe festival, I know that some of
the scoops have, and I think, I mean, Matt, you did the one in, uh, fallout fringe. It's
one of the best investments that artists can make. It's just, it's just, it's just a license
to print money. It really is, uh, you had a decidedly different experience than, than
I did. Um, almost every fringe festival in the language is like, Hey, we will not let
you make a profit. Like it's almost guaranteed. So like you can, you can ask to break even
at best. There's usually language in the application that says that. So before I decided to launch
this Kickstarter, I talked to my wife into coming with me and I said exactly that in
some version of that. I said there's the best that you can hope to do is break even. We're
going to make a vacation out of this that I happen to be doing a run of shows that way.
Nobody's mad about the money, but I want the exposure. I want full rooms. My shows are
far more fun with a lot more people in the room. And it's a really different type of
show because usually hypnotists, they do their thing, bring people up, get whoever they can
into trance. And then they've got this script of routines that they go through of the silly
shit that they make people do. I am doing a show where as audience members enter the
theater, they are prompted to put down ideas for stuff that they want to see in the show.
And I'm going to write the show basically on the fly. Um, there, there's going to be
some cheating involved with respect to the Kickstarter. So if you are interested in the
Kickstarter, no, I thought you meant you were going to fuck other people's spouses. Um,
just right there on stage. If they wrote on the paper, they wrote it on the paper. Fuck
my wife. The Kickstarter will give people a chance to suggest routines that I'll bring
with me and drop into the bucket as potential things. So ultimately again, I want these
full room, the full rooms. One of my real call to action here is less about funding
the Kickstarter more about, cause right now it's in pre-launch. Okay. Uh, everything is
at carnival of dreams.com. So that's the name of the show. Um, and again, the, the
audience, I'll throw that in the zoom chat for people who were there. If people can jump
on and follow this thing, because the, the follows that you get in pre-launch are also
part of triggering the algorithm and getting it exposure. Um, I'm trying to put as much
of the full court press on this thing as I can. Thank you, Jacob. Um, and, but there
is some cool stuff. So for as little as five bucks, people can join a private WhatsApp
group where I'm going to be giving updates throughout and everything up to getting swag
from it, suggesting routines. Um, everything's got a price. So if you want it to be guaranteed
that I use your routine in a show, there is a level where you and I will hop on the zoom
call before this thing and actually plan out and write a routine. Uh, so you know what
you're getting. I video all the shows. So there's one of the levels that you can get
video of all of the shows from it. And for the scoops, since I'm going to be in Europe
and in three European cities, there will be an ad on there that will make sense to almost
nobody other than you all, where I will yell salt pork in front of some sort of famous
monument somewhere in either Paris or Barcelona. And, you know, you don't even have to put
hay scoops at checkout. You'll know exactly what it is. It actually even says that you
don't have to put hay scoops at checkout. I don't even know if there's promo codes on
it. I've backed so many damn projects, whether they are magic related or other weird tech
stuff and like the number of decks of playing cards that I have that Sean Farquhar has designed.
I could probably build a house with them. But yeah, I'm sure you shoot it with the foam
that Paul used to keep the mice out of the basement. Right. A little great stuff goes
a long way. Otherwise, three squirrels and a trench coat will steal it.
So I thought it was really funny to have Jobeth yelling salt pork out loud at different monuments
and stuff around Europe. Oh wait, are you going to yell salt pork in front of the monuments
or are you going to yell salt pork at the monuments? As though the monuments have done
something to deserve being yelled at. Dealers choice. And for anybody who's back
to Kickstarter before, you know that once it funds, once you get the submission and
everything, there'll be some back and forth. And you know, I've been a member of this community
since I brought Matt to Elkton to really kick off us having the Elkton magic shows. And
I kind of backdoor obelisk myself because of wanting to do some research. For a second,
I thought you were going to tell a fun story about you and Matt in the early days. Hello.
I mean, there's plenty of plenty of fun stories. It's very similar to Wolfman's appearance
on foolish. Very similar. So, you know, the scopes, I don't know that I feel like I quote
a lot to them, but I certainly owe a lot of enjoyment to everything that is here. So the
amount of levity that's going to exist in you sending me a message saying, can you do
specifically this consider it done? Again, the following joke was I came up with an idea
for Africa Babel and maybe other people on here might like that one too. Okay. Same thing.
Only you hold up a Rubik's cube and you go, you know, there's one in 43 quadrillion combinations
of things on a Rubik's cube. Did you know that? And then I'll pan to my wife and she
can do RJ's sigh. So for those listening, it's my biggest pet peeve with every magician
has dumb pet peeves. And mine is that anytime anyone does a Rubik's cube trick, they say
there are over 43 quadrillion combinations you can do with Rubik's cube. And I just think
like that's true. I agree. But do you want me, the audience member to think that you,
the magician knows 43 quadrillion combinations because that's obnoxious. That's obnoxious.
You want me to think you're that much of a math whiz, but also, you know, are going to
find my eight of hearts later. Like it just seems like a really weird thing to add to
a show. You are the smartest person I've ever seen and you're doing Rubik's cube magic.
Exactly. Exactly. Perfect job. I've got a question for you. The shows in Spain, are
they going to be done in English or are you learning them in Spanish? They are going to
be done in English. So that area in Barcelona apparently has a thriving English comedy scene,
which is, which was what became the birth of this fringe festival there. This is the
second year that they've done it. So I'm sure that I'm going to have some Spanish speaking
or bilingual or, or folks who speak Catalan because it's in that region. I took five years
of Spanish in high school and I'm surprised as I'm 60 couple days into a Duolingo streak,
not much I both remember and forget from that time. Gracias. De nada. Perfect. Oh, you're
ready man. I'm going to order cerveza, all that I want. I will have no problem finding
the baguio. I'll be able to find the library. Yup. La biblioteca. Muy bien. You're so fast
on that day. Nada, you're ready. You're ready to be there. Anything else people need to
look for? What's that? Anything else people need to look for? Carnival of dreams, carnival
of dreams dot com over time. That is going to evolve to just go to the Kickstarter site
and then when Kickstarter is done, it's going to be ticket links. So if anybody's actually,
I don't know if you guys have scoops that are specifically in Barcelona or if you happen
to be there, if you're a scoop, reach out. I'll comp you tickets because obviously we've
already written off any profit from this thing. And I'd love to have butts in seats. We've
accepted that we're not going to make money. We might as well lean into it. Let's get the
butts in the seats. Exactly. Oh, awesome. I like it. Cool. Hey, thank you for giving
me a little time and thank you for putting enough time between the recap of two characters
in a clown RIP while you were going through all of that. I'm sitting here, I don't want
to follow this. I hope he doesn't put me on right after. Well, luckily everybody had forgotten
about it until you brought it back. Oh, now we're all sad. I'm here to self-sabotage myself
any way I can. Thanks, buddy. I'm following you on the Kickstarter. Looks good. Beautiful.
All you have to do, go over there to that website that we said earlier that someone
will repeat now that I've forgotten what it was called. Carnival of dreams dot com. Go
over there. All you have to do is sign into your Kickstarter and follow it on right there
and it will alert you when the Kickstarter goes active and you'll be helping Joe without
to go over there. Carnival of dreams. Do that right now, especially if you're sitting there
watching us on zoom. You can just go over there on your device and do it. It's right
here. You're right there. It's right here. You're already here, buddy. You're already
here. I'll tell you who else is already here and will probably be performing at oh, shit.
I just muted Matt. Sorry, Matt. I just muted you on your zoom. Sorry. That was a not too
subtle hint. I understand. I'll check myself. I forgot what I was going to say. Following
the answer. Disco daycare. That's right. I heard somebody say disco daycare. Tonight.
Tonight. Tonight. I'm watching you, baby. Tonight. I'm watching you, baby. Tonight.
I'm watching you, baby. Walk around. Making sure you, baby, stay safe. Watching you, baby.
Don't drown. Tonight. Tonight. I'm watching you, baby. Tonight. It must be real cheap
with the zoom delay. There's not a single chance I'm ending this. This is the rest of
the show. Tonight. I'm watching you, baby. Tonight. Yeah, I'm watching you, baby. Making
sure that your baby gets fed. Making sure that it gets into bed. Get some sleep. Get
a nap. Get a snack. I'm watching you, baby. Watching you, baby. Tonight. Why is my baby
doing cocaine in the bathroom? Look, I'm watching your baby as much as I can. I can't watch
him all the time. And I can't go into the bathroom with the baby. That's against federal
law. Daddy, I need more cocaine. Don't we all. Tonight. I'm watching you, baby. Snug
coke. Off the back of a urinal. Tonight. Not even off a mirror. Off the urinal. Off the
back of a urinal. The baby's not that tall. Oh, man. It's using the short urinal, the
baby urinal. Better hay scoops to check out. Doing cocaine off the baby urinal. Oh, Lord.
I went and saw Clue on the big screen last night. Oh, yeah. That's out in theaters, right?
They were playing it at the South Point here in Las Vegas. I went and saw Tim Curry and
Martin Maul do Clue. Flames. Flames at the side of my face. Madeline Khan, when she enters
the movie for the first time, I started laughing instantly. Holy shit. I love Madeline Khan
so much. She's so good in that movie. So good. So tell me. And they did the thing. They did
the thing, like the original one, where they didn't show all the endings. Oh, they just
showed one. OK. They picked one ending and showed that. Yeah. Yeah, because that's how
they did it when the movie first came out, I guess. That's right. To show all the different
theaters had just one ending. I think Comedy Central started... I think they're the ones
who did all the endings together. When Comedy Central started re-airing the movie. I think
they did it on the VHS. The VHS release had all the endings. Oh, is that what it is? Yeah.
The VHS went, "And maybe it went like this. And maybe it went like this." Oh, so Comedy
Central showed that part. Yes. And I think that kind of inspired Wayne's World. Oh, yeah,
that makes sense. First Wayne's World had multiple endings. But yeah, it was so good.
Matt, what were you going to ask? I forget now. Oh, cool. Nailed it. Yeah, it was great.
I love watching those. I'm no longer a good podcaster. I quit. But I have fish cakes.
Oh, never mind. I'm back in. Oh, good. Urinal fish cakes. They got to hold one podcast together.
Urinal fish cakes. Urinal fish cakes. Yuck. Gross. There was a group behind me who was
just saying out loud every single punchline before it happened. Oh, that's so annoying.
It didn't bother me that much because I knew all of them too. So I was also... I was like,
"Oh, these are coming." Do you think this is an effect of it being a Tim Curry movie
and they're kind of just vibing on that Rocky vibe? Yeah. I think so. I think they were
just having a good time. I wasn't mad at them, but they were doing a lot. I was also sitting
next to a... I don't know. You know me. I can't tell how old kids are, but it was a
little girl. She seemed to be like, I don't know, 12 maybe, 12, 13, something like that.
And it is really great sitting next to someone at a movie that you love. And as you're watching
it, you realize how formative it was to you, especially to your comedy as you're watching
it. And you're sitting next to a preteen little girl who is so unimpressed with everything.
The screen might as well be blank. Wow. It was so great. It made my night. This kid doesn't
give a shit about this at all. Just hated it. Just hated it. Really? It was like just
sitting there. You could tell every reference to it because it's a more dated movie than
you think it is. There are a few references in there that you're like... If you don't
know what... Hoover is on the phone at one point. J. Edgar Hoover is on the phone at
one point. And somebody makes the comment, Tim Curry makes the comment, he's like, "He's
on everybody else's phone. Why shouldn't he be on mine?" Right, right, right, right.
You're like, "Oh, that's a funny J. Edgar Hoover running the FBI joke that is not applicable
in 2025 at all." Now, how old is this individual? Oh, the kid was like 12 or 13. Oh, okay. So
yeah, no, no, no. I was like, "Why did your parents bring you to this? You clearly hate
all of this." Well, and it's also just a factor of movies were a little bit more slow paced
back in the day. A little slower. Yeah. So, you know, that's hard to shift that brain,
especially at 13. My God. I get it. Yeah. I get it. You forget that Mr. Body's a real
acting flex. You totally forget there's a big buildup before the murder happens. And
Mr. Body has to be like, "I'm the greatest actor in the world." He has to come in. It's
like the only actor in the movie you don't know who it is. Yeah, exactly. And he has
to come in and just try his damnedest to take it over while Tim Curry is on the other side
of the room just being Tim Curry. Exactly. Exactly. You just feel terrible for this guy.
I watched it again. I watched it again like four years ago or something. I was like, "Oh,
I forgot this guy really tries to throw a flamethrower. It just really isn't happening." It really
comes across as a big lighter. It's just poor guy. He's just trying. Yeah. When I was younger,
I did not appreciate, I did not comedically understand how subtle and awesome Martin Mull
was being. So we were watching it as an adult. He's so funny. It's like, it's so subtle and
he's such a groveler. It's so great. His looks are great. He keeps on touching Mrs. Scarlet
in just vaguely inappropriate ways. And she just keeps on being annoyed by it and shooting
him looks or hitting him or something. And nobody ever acknowledges it. No. I was just
a little too young when they started doing the Fernwood Tonight reruns on... Yes. It
went over my head. I just wasn't there, but I'm sure now I'd appreciate it a lot more.
I missed Fernwood as well. Yeah. Oh yeah. We did it, guys. All right. We're just going
to sit around now and think about nice things that we enjoyed from our childhood. Let's
just think about old movies for a minute, guys. Just quietly. Remember there were movies.
What was your favorite movie when you were 14 years old? 14 years old. Fern Gullywood.
That's the one where they had to shoot the dog at the end. Oh my God. Well, they didn't
have to shoot the dog. They got to shoot the dog. I'm sorry. They got to do it. They got
to shoot the dog. Spoilers. Sorry, Latter Day Scoop. Spoilers. Let's do some Scoop Mail.
Well, we got a Scoop Mail today from House Dad. After watching Rhea and the Last Dragon,
what is Rhea? Or is that one thing? Is Rhea and the Last Dragon one thing? Oh, okay. So
after watching Rhea and the Last Dragon, I asked my daughters what animal they would
like to put a saddle on and ride around. I told them that I would put a saddle on a hippo
because they are spectacular. Plus the land and water speed and maneuverability really
checks all the boxes if you ask me. The three-year-old chose a cow, which is incredibly on brand
for her personality-wise. The two-year-old went giraffe, which is very koala-like of her
and a solid choice. Please allow me to ask you that same multi-million-dollar question
besides my mom, what would you like to saddle and ride around? Lovingly, that's the House
Dad. So other than House Dad's mom, what would you like to throw a saddle on and give a little
ride to? Let's make it exciting. All the choices are only people in this chat. Okay. Okay. So
we have Jobeth. We have... I would like to do a giant bumblebee. Giant bumblebee. Oh.
Also, we're not even in real animals anymore. We're already out of real animals. I'm already
out of real animals. I'm going to giant bumblebee because I don't want to hurt a real animal.
I want to go with a giant bumblebee because I also want to fly around. It'd be like a
sectar. Yeah. A gazoon type. Yeah. Yeah. You guys all remember sectars, right? Of course
you do. That short-lived toy line, sectars. Do you not remember sectars, Jacob? No. Matt,
do you remember sectars? I don't. So sectars... How many times can Paul say the word sectars?
Sectars is a toy line. And see if Matt and I know what it is before he decides that we
don't. It was a little expensive. The figures were a little closer to seven inches. They
were pretty tall. And they would ride on the backs of giant bugs. And the bugs were the
big feature of the toy line. So the bugs had these big wings that you could manipulate.
But the cool thing was they were puppets. You put your hand into the bug and your hand
became the bug's legs. Oh, I do remember that. I do. Of course you do because sectars were
fucking cool. And so you would fly, you would fly them around and they'd be riding on your
back and they had a huge playset. Their playset was jye fucking enormous. The sectar, it looked
like just a wall, a chasm wall. It was really cool. But yeah, sectars would fly around and
they're redoing sectars now. All right. Say sectar again. Sectar. I think I want to ride
like a giant train, like a mechanical ball. Like, like wheel the giant train. What? You
want to wield a giant train? And catch a ride at choo choo. Come on ride the train and ride
it choo choo. That's what I want to do. All right then. I guess, I guess I won't stop
you. That was bad in the chat with the say sectar one more time over. That was really
fast. Say sectar again. Sectar don't sound like any toy line I ever heard of. You know
what they call a quarter pound of sectars in France? Oh, what? Nerdy. I just found out.
Le bugs and warrior. Le bugs, the finger legs. The bug, the finger leg. That's what sectar
translates into. I just found out in the chat you can ride inside a train. That was really,
what a waste of time. Oh, so silly. Oh, shit man. Oh, Jacob. I don't know. I think hippo,
hippo is a good idea. Hippo is a solid rideable animal. It's tough to ride. I can't get your
legs all spread way out. Well, you can do it in a saddle situation. It's kind of a seat
situation. Maybe a nice side hippo saddle. Paul is holding his phone up to the camera
now to show off what I assume is his amateur porn video. I'm just letting people, again,
this is the benefit of joining up on the Patreon and coming into our feed. You get to see all
the extra content like this. Like sectar, see they're finger fighting. As sad as this
statement makes me, Paul's video has made me, oh Paul, your package has arrived. I like
seeing Paul's notifications. My notifications coming up. It's pretty great. Also, Paul's
video has made me realize I do know what he's talking about. Of course you remember. Everybody
remembers sectars. I'm sad that Paul's video did something useful. They were expensive
back in the day. They weren't- Yeah, I never had any. That's what I'm saying. They weren't
a cheap figure. They were very expensive. Sectars. I have no idea what I was saying
before that. Winterscoop put a cool picture there in the chat as well. Oh, in the chat
here, Loane Buddy McQueen has selected horse. You know, I'm going to go with Buddy on this
one. Horse seems like a really good one. But I got news for you, both. You guys live your
dreams. You can do that tomorrow. Centaur, that'd be a good one, Leon Kassab. It's been
a long- Have you guys ever ridden a horse? I have. It's been forever. When I was a kid,
yeah. When I was a kid. I wouldn't do it now. Do you think you could still ride a horse?
I have more respect for a horse than to put my 300 pound butt on my back. Oh, no, no,
not that. But if you were on a horse, though, do you believe that you could still command
a horse and ride a horse well enough? Yeah, I think I could do okay. It would depend on
the horse, of course. Of course, of course. You really legit of courseed it. He legit
of courseed it. It depends on the horse, of course, of course. I don't know, but yeah,
I think I could. I think I could. I would love to ride a Clydesdale. Oh, those are,
I believe, just impossible to ride. I guess, yeah, they're probably so big. You'd have
to be so bowlegged. Yeah, they're just so massive. Oh, my God. Winterscoop saying Mr.
Hands. That is the horse that rides you, Winterscoop. Actually, for my birthday this year, we're
going to get a pony ride, so I'm going to ride a pony on my birthday. Oh, good, good.
Nice. Do you guys know the horrible story behind Mr. Hands? What's Mr. Hands? Mr. Hands
is the horse that was involved in one of those early freaky online videos that apparently
was a cult of horse fucking people. And the Mr. Hands was fucking guys, right? They were
getting fucked by this horse. You know, the horse didn't want to do it or whatever. But
what? I know. But you were well aware of the whole bean situation and all that kind of
thing. And, you know, horse business is a bit bigger than human business. And the story
was the story was that Mr. Hands got this guy, but ruptured his intestines. And he's
died over time from being fucked by a horse. Oh, I have, I have found it. I found the Wikipedia
page on it. Yeah. This is upsetting. It's dark. It's a real dark thing. And it's one
of those. It's one of those very early internet things. I got to tell you for really remember
for a masonry podcast. Do not screen share. I'm not screen sharing. I'm not screen sharing.
It has taken a turn. Well, of course, of course, you got to fuck the right horse. Of course.
Or don't. How about don't fuck horses? How about that? Oh, I've been watching. I've been
watching a hard knocks on HBO, the season, the season camp for the Buffalo Bills. Yeah.
And one of the linebackers, I think either a linebacker or a defensive lineman. He's
really into horses and he has horses, he rides horses. And so they take the cameras out watching
a huge professional athlete on the back of an equally huge cause he has like very large
horses to accommodate his very large frame. Right. And it is so funny because he's just
an enormous man on the back of a horse. And no matter how big that horse gets, it still
doesn't look right. It looks like, it looks like you ride the kitten. Yeah. Yeah. It looks
like, it looks weird that his feet aren't touching the ground because it looks like they just almost
should be able to Flintstone that shit. Just get aside. He just give him a little kick
to help out the horse a little bit. No big deal. Flintstones the horse. He's just running
with the horse under his legs, touch the ground, cuts into the horse. It's a living. Let's
do a little jock versus nerd cause you're about to lose your living.
We got a scooper to come into us today from Leon Kassab. The categories are before they
wrestled small facts, second biggest facts and cocktails. Leon and Chad.
I'm going to go ahead and before they wrestled for 800, I'm going to shoot the moon.
Oh, before becoming one of the world's biggest, one of the biggest stars in the world. This
wrestler did quote the work of three men in the quote as a farmer. Oh boy.
Ooh, I'm going to guess iron chic. Oh, okay. Let's try iron chic.
Giant Andre, Andre, the giant Leon. Paul hates your game. No, I don't. Not at all. Oh shit. I
also fucked that score up. I put nobody guessed. Paul got it wrong. Well, there's no point. It's
all good. Right. Uh, you should have negative points. Oh no, no, I don't agree with that.
Was that before or after Jack Kerouac drove him to school? I think it was after Jack Kerouac,
but before raw doll. Okay. Um, I will take small facts for 200, please.
At 32 days, this ninth president's term is the shortest in us history. Um, here's William Henry
Harrison. William Henry Harrison is absolutely correct. I died in 30 days, died of pneumonia.
Tippa canoe and Tyler Tyler. That's it. Yeah. Can you and Tyler to Tippa canoe and Tyler too.
Uh, it's me. I'll try. Um, you learn your history. So you don't repeat it. That's why we learned our
history today about Mr. Hands. That's right. That's right. I'm just trying. Don't fuck Mr.
Hands between that and sectors. I've saved some lives today. Good job. Good job. I'll try small
facts for 400 need to be more toys that you put your hand on answers. Oh boy. The smallest
Incorporated town in the United States is Monterey, Nebraska. What is its population within 20?
Oh, I'm just going to say, I'm going to say, uh, 21
one mayor LCM Isler is the only resident. Wow. It's 21 within 20 of one. What's that election
process? Like very simple. It's either very simple or very complicated. Yeah. It takes all year.
Yeah. I think I get that right. I don't know what you're saying. I got it right. Uh, I said 21.
I was within 20. Yeah. Well, Leon said fine. So there you go. Yeah. Great. Uh, Paul, uh, before
they wrestled for 600, despite being part of a famous wrestling family, this superstar tried
his hand at professional baseball before stepping into the ring. Damn it. That's the only one I was
going to get right. My Joe man, Randy said, Oh wow. I didn't know that. Oh yeah. Randy.
Uh, I know that the saints used to have the kid of one of the Legion of doom on there.
Oh really? He was an offensive lineman. Yeah. He was a animals kid, animals child. That makes sense.
Yeah. Yeah. Uh, they might still play. I don't know, Matt, you're up Anthony and buddy are right
next to each other in my chat windows. Are they right next to each other in your chat windows?
It looks like they're trying to punk us by like twinning right now. It looks like they're trying
the same. I can't see even buddy. Now just lowered his screen to match it.
Oh, I see him now. Oh, that's funny. It's like we're playing guess who with our, with our zoom
chat right now. We've been defeated preaching fun.com. Join us on zoom. Yes. You get to see
people do those, those kinds of things. Shenanigans of plenty on the zoom chat. I'll take small facts
for 600, please. This point guard was the shortest player to start in the NBA. Oh,
it's either spud web or Muggsy bogues. Oh, I forgot about Muggsy bogues. It's gotta be spud.
All right. Muggsy bogues.
Y'all are both so confident. I think it's Muggsy, but y'all are both so confident that it was spud
that you convinced me. I'll try small facts. England's shortest adult monarch was Charles
the first who was estimated to be five foot four at the start of his reign. Approximately how tall
was he by the end of his reign? I'd say approximately five foot four. No, he probably lost his head.
Right. Oh, is that what they're doing? They're taking into consideration. He's like six inches
shorter because he got his head cut off or something. Oh yeah. So yeah, I'll say he's
approximately one head shorter, approximately four, uh, four eight because his head was chopped off.
And he answered him in, so he just gets credit. Yeah. Great. Just like what happened with Muggsy
bogues. Just like what happened. He would have been a much taller basketball player. Yeah. Yeah.
If he had kept his head. If he had kept his head. Paul. Uh, before they wrestled for 400, please.
Prior to becoming a wrestling star, he played bass for the band
ruckus presumably before SJ joined. Oh, I think this is Hulk. All right. Hulk Hogan. Yeah.
Matt, this is where he came. He started saying like he almost was in Metallica. It's like,
Oh, that's right. All the way off. You lie. You lie racist. He was supposed to be, uh, Mickey,
uh, Mickey Rourke's part and the wrestler. Oh my God. He's just so full of shit. It's unbelievable.
Yeah. Uh, Matt, you're up. Well, now he's full of dirt and worms. Well, not yet. I don't think,
I think they're still getting an autopsy. There's some, some weird, yeah, there's some weird stuff
about medical malpractice going on with his death. I don't know. Oh wow. Yeah. It seems to be, uh,
yeah, kind of sketch. Gawker will tell us. Okay. Um, I will. Great. Gawker.
Uh, second thing is, no, actually I'm going to do cocktails for 800, please. All right. Three
ounces of dry gin, one ounce of vodka, one half ounce of lily blanc, stir with ice and strain into
a chilled cocktail glass with a lemon zest for garnish. I think this is a Vesper. A Vesper.
You're absolutely right. It's a Vesper. Oh, it's me. I'll try, uh, cocktails for 600.
Two ounces of gin, one half ounce of Maraschino liqueur, one quarter ounce of cream de violet,
three quarter ounce of lemon juice, shake with ice and strain into a cocktail glass,
garnish with a brandy cherry or a flamed lemon peel. Um, huh. I don't really drink much with
the violet in it. Is that the, uh, the old rosy tip flip? Is that what that one is? That's what it
is. The rosy tip flip. It's one of the few answers that's both in wrestling and in cocktails. That's
true. That's true. Rosy tip flip is a move and a delicious drink. I'm passing Paul. I'm not going
to guess rosy tip flip. I don't know. Passing. Coward. I love it. Oh, it was the rosy tip flip.
Oh, so close. The aviation. That's the aviation. That must've been a, uh, Howard Hughes beverage.
Yep. Uh, Paul. Before they wrestled, please. For two hundo. Before wrestling, he was a bodyguard
for the Shaw of Iran. That is the iron chic. That's the iron chic. I knew that one. Matt.
Uh, cocktails. 400. Daily double. Now it's the daily double of the day. Now it's still for 400.
Two ounces of bourbon. Or sorry, bourbon. Three ounces of lemon juice. One and a half ounce simple
syrup. One egg white shaken with ice and strained into a rocks glass or coupe. Interesting. Is this
a proper? This is, I have, I used to make this drink all the time. It's in, uh, my old, old
cocktail book that I have on my bar and I don't remember the name of it. Okay. So it's not like
the first recipe of an original like old fashioned. I don't think so. Okay. Cause the egg white in
there throws that off. Yeah. Uh, what is a Kentucky omelet? Show me Kentucky omelet.
Oh, whiskey sour. Whiskey sour. Oh, that's not what I was thinking of at all. The sour mix. I'm dumb.
But the egg white, I don't get the egg white in there. I think, I think a lot of original recipes
called for egg white because it gave like a froth on the top and you shook it in the cocktail shaker.
That's true. I'll close out cocktails for 200. Oh shit. It's the other daily double. Whoa. Holy
rosy nipple flips. Alex for 1200. One cube of sugar muddled with, uh, I never know how to say
that word. Bitters, uh, the angostura angostura. I think you got it. Bitters, uh, and a tablespoon
of water. Add two ounces of bourbon or rye, stir with ice strain into a rock's glass garnish with
an orange twist. It's a your mom. It's called Chimera bitters. That's it. But go on. Uh,
that's the old fashioned. Yeah, there it is. That's what Ann loves. You got second biggest
facts for two, four, six or 800 score check. I am at 2400. Paul is at 1200. Matt is at
zero. I got 800 to try and keep it, keep it fresh. All right. 800 second biggest facts.
Second most abundant gas in earth's atmosphere. Um, nitrogen, nitrogen is incorrect. Oxygen is
number one. Shit. Nitrogen is number one. Yep. Ah, fart. Uh, Matt, I was told it was hydrogen.
That's why I never lit any campus. Good idea. Smart. Let's play it safe. Stay in the dark.
Um, I will do second biggest facts for 600.
Second largest country in the world by area causing all kinds of hysteria.
This is the worst beastie boys song ever. Let's do it. Uh, I don't know. Do you know there's a,
there's a move, there's like a, a group right now trying to advocate for more accurate maps
because Africa, the way we show on maps is basically seen too small. So they're trying
to like create a different map so that we show how large Africa is. Um, yes, that's, that's,
that's been a movement for, uh, for a while. Yeah. I think it's worth dedicating your life to it.
Um, I don't know. Pass. Oh, that passes to me. Uh, yeah. I mean, it's gotta be second largest
country by area. Oh, I've got points. I can play around a little bit. Um, so Russia's real big.
China's real big. This isn't going to be one of those where like, because the maps are drawn,
drawn wrong. It's like Greenland or something. No, I don't know. Uh, so Russia or China. I would
think so. One of those it's gotta be, I think Russia is smaller than China's also Russia.
Canada blame Canada. I will. Canada is a number two. Russia is number one with 6.6 million. Um,
Oh miles square miles, I guess. Uh, yeah. Great. Canada. That's me. I'll try second
biggest facts for 400. What is the second longest river in the world?
Uh, let's see the Nile. Oh wait, shit. I was, I was getting confused. You got the Nile and the
Amazon, the Yucatan, the Yucca and the Yucatan. Yeah. The Nile, the Amazon and the Yucatan and
the old man. That's it. Yeah. The old man river. Uh, I think, I think those are the two I'll say
the Nile. It is the Nile. Nice. Amazon. Number one.
And Paul closing out the category and the game. Second biggest facts for 200.
Second longest reigning Monarch in world history. Oh, um, the second longest reigning Monarch in
world history. Uh, which Monarch stood in the rain the longest, which Monarch stood in the rain,
the second longest. I think it's queen Elizabeth one. Queen Elizabeth one is incorrect. It's
Elizabeth two. Ah, 70 years. Uh, Louis the 14th of France was first with 72 years. Oh man. Uh,
Paul got that wrong. Uh, but that doesn't matter. I win with 2200 points. Uh, Matt is in second
with zero points and Paul is in third with negative 600 points. If I had done all of the
scorekeeping correctly, that's from Leon Kasab. Thank you. Leon Kasab. If you want to send us a
scooper to your price of Skryte jock versus nerd or regular jock versus nerd. Uh, what's the other
one price of Skryte obelisk. That was it. Uh, those are all the jock versus nerds out there.
Matt is drinking from his phone. So come on over there. Hey scoops.com right there on the homepage.
You can make us a scooper. You can make us an obelisk. You can make us a price of Skryte jock
versus nerd. You can do all the things you can send us some scoop mail all there at Hey scoops.com.
Hey, you know what else you can do at Hey scoops.com? What you could buy your tickets to scoop
fest. That's right. That's what you need to do. Odyssey. Come join us in beautiful Las Vegas,
Nevada in September next month. As you were listening to this episode, September, 2025,
uh, the last weekend, the last Thursday, Friday, Saturday in September, come on down to Las Vegas,
stay at the Orleans, tell them that you're here for scoop fest. They'll give you a discount room
right there and do everything with us there at the Orleans. Uh, come on down to scoop fest. Oh,
there are even still some tickets for the Jacobs whiskey barbecue left. We opened up a couple of
new tickets. So I think there are like four tickets, a handful, a literal available left. Yeah. Yeah.
Jump on it. Uh, only because we opened up a couple of new ones. So we, we have opened up a couple of
new whiskey barbecue tickets. So if you were hoping to come out for that, come on out. We have a,
yeah, do it. We have some fun surprises. We do, uh, for, uh, the whiskey barbecue itself. Look,
that's the second wife spotting, two wives, two wives in a single podcast. Amazing. No one's right.
No one. Trank dart her. Never been done before. Uh, yeah. Get out the best. Uh, did you send us
thank yous? I did. All right. I should, uh, look at those. Okay. I want to thank, uh, the following,
uh, people who supports over on our Patreon page. And these people also, uh, put egg whites in all
of their drinks. Uh, that's Kurt Henderson, Kurt Eggner, Kristen Kledic, Colton Tony, Colin Tony,
Kiwi Fruit, uh, King Scoop, Kim Chi Du Scoop, Kevin Dory, Kevin Chamberlain, Kenneth Soto,
Ken Fargey, Kelsey Kandari, Keith Robert Corning Scoop, Heaster Sunday, Kay Mathis, Justin Robert
Young, Judy Schneider, Juan Galaviz, Jay Rock Scoop, and Joshua Wilson. Big thanks to these
people who only in the middle of it did they realize they were in their last podcast.
Jay Shapiro, Jason Yannowitz, Jason Victor, Jason Vasquez, Jason Street, Jason Speckland,
Jason Horcastis, Jason Klepper, Janine Lankard, Jameson Fisher, Jameson Hubbell, Jameson Dawson,
James Dawson, Jake Schneider, Jacob Dinklaker, I Wanna Scoop Baby, Ice Blue Scoop, Ice Cream Manwich,
Ian Soto, Ian A. Chapman, I Don't Have a Scoop Name, and Hylian Scoop. I want to thank the following
people who all played bass in the Rose Tit Flip Trick band before becoming wrestlers. Uh,
Joshua Wilson, Joshua Tarr, Josh Roberts, Joseph Palrero, Joseph Foster, Jordan Campbell, Jonathan,
Johnny Parker, John Jacob Schuppelheimer Schmidt, uh, John Holchin, John Glore, John Carter,
Jimmy Stonena, Jill Short, Jesse Rain, Jeremy Hudson, Jenny Ebar, Jeff Loomis, Jeff Libby,
Jeff Harris, Jeff Faust, and Jed Taxon. Big thanks to these individuals who also have their
own headcanon for the true ending to the Clue movie. House Dad Scoop, Holly Marshmello Lightly,
Heather Divine Hanson, Hatchet Scoop, Gwarthok, Guy Wade, Grill Sergeant Scoops, Green Wolf Scoop,
Gravel Scoop, Greater Sunday Scoop, Gizmo Scoop, Gerardo Garcia, uh, George Guskov,
Genetic Scoop, Gene Zink, Gelato Steve, Gelato Problems, Gazpacho Scoop, Gas Man Scoop,
and Garrett Godfrey. And the following scoops were all thoroughly unimpressed when their
parents took them to see a movie that was dated when it came out. That's Galen Diggs, Galactic,
President Scooper Star, McScoopsalot, Galusha Scoop, Fudgy the Whale, Frozen Cusser, Frozen 49th Scoop,
Freeze-Dried Scoop, Freehold Scoop, Frankie's Tiki Scoop, Flat Kidney, Finn Steffenson, Fifi,
Fade Out Scoop, Evil Monkey, Erotic Scrape Scoop, Eric Nielsen, Elkton Magic Scoop, Alyssa Walzak,
Edward Bender, Edla Scoop, Ed Wagner, uh, Ed Undrick, Ed, our arms are Marcus, Dwayne Webb,
Duke Scoop, Duck Flambe, Dr. Tobias Scoopy, Dr. Scoop Little, Dr. Science Scoop, Doug Lay,
Don't Say Scoop Name, Don Doty, Doc Scoop, Distiller Scoop, Dirty Old Scoop, Dippin' Dot Jack,
Dole Whip Scoop, Derek Dozer, Dead Lazlo, David Walker, and David Sorensen. Thank you all so much.
Thank you all so much. If you want to be thanked on air, if you want discount code to Scoop Fest,
if you want invites, ad-free episodes, all that stuff, head on over to preachingfun.com. We did
it. We did it. Three wives. We did it. We did it. Three wives. It's better than hanging with your
mom. Or if you, uh, I don't, I don't know. My wife is, and my dog, you're attacking me. Um,
fartsinabag.biz. That's fartsinabag.biz. That along with preachingfun.com. It takes you to our
Patreon page where for as little as $2 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. If you
think this show is worth more than $0, head on over to preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz. I think
I just said two. I meant three. For as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Join us over there at Patreon. It gets you into fun things like our live Zoom sessions during the
show. Uh, and there are also all kinds of fun new things coming for our Patreon supporters over
there. Preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz. Do it now. Yeah. Thank you guys so much out there.
Stay safe. We love you and we'll see you soon. We'll see you soon.
We're recording Matt on a new microphone today. It's very exciting. We're going to see how it
turned out. Oh boy. By this point in the episode, if you're listening to it, you already know how
it turned out. We're preaching fun. See ya!