"She's mighty mighty, letting the shit leak out."
"She's a brick, shit house, not terribly affected."
This is the part of the show where we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Our lists are fucked this month, I am sorry.
We don't have a new list yet, I don't know why, but it's all fucked up.
Maybe we'll have one by the time this comes out, who can say?
Either way though, we're going to thank all of you before this month is over.
Thank you all the new Ice Cream Truck Drivers out there.
Thank you everybody who supports us over there on Patreon.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver.
And who knows, the life you save may be your own!
That's right, Dead Lazlo, professionals!
Bro.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
Right before we got on air, Paula convinced me of the brick shithouse argument.
I'm sorry, brick house.
The pause to brick and house.
It's a brick shithouse!
That's what it's supposed to be.
It's time for Matt Madinley's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Madinley!
Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly!
Also sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy!
We're PreachingFun!
How y'all doing?
I'm doing delightful.
I just told everybody on stream I got a boo-boo from mowing my lawn today.
You hurt yourself mowing?
Yeah, I slipped and fell in wet grass because I was mowing so early to get done by the time
the podcast hit.
Which I did, I got it all done, which is great.
But just injured.
We're boo-boo brothers, Paul.
What happened?
Oh, Matt also has a boo-boo on his elbow!
It's mostly healed, mine's from the water slide in Mesa, Arizona.
Oh, brothers in arms here.
Is this a Corsican twin kind of thing happening, Matt?
Yes.
Is that what this is?
Yeah, we are Corsican.
We're Corsican twins.
I knew it.
Oh, country scoop.
My elbows are fine.
I got elbow boo-boo.
A lot of people got elbow boo-boos.
They're going for like $7.80 a pop, elbow boo-boos.
You know, I have tried to get, I just want a green one.
You want a green one?
If I get a green one, I'll quit.
Quit buying them, no.
There's an economist, which economist?
I don't know, who thinks the LeBouBou craze is a sign that we're about to hit like a really
nasty economic thing in our world.
I concur, and I would say also.
An economist theorizes that the LeBouBou craze is foreshadowing a really bad financial time.
Canary in a coal mine.
Now, I know why he said this, but Paul was really quick to chime in that he also knew,
so go ahead, Paul.
Oh, sorry, Paul.
Why is this happening?
It coincides with the same thing that's going on within the trading card world, for those
of you who play Magic or Pokemon and have ever tried to even buy the shit.
But what it does, it correlates to people feeling frustrated that they have little to
no buying power, and they're seeing this, it's sort of a gambling kind of thing with
the LeBouBous.
It's also the possibility of using their money to then resell it and make a little bit more,
and that kind of thing.
And also, it's not that crazy expensive.
Buying a pack of Pokemon cards is not that crazy expensive, but it's a way to feel like
you have some economic ability within you.
Am I hitting the points there pretty close, Matt?
A little bit.
What you're saying makes sense.
This person simply pointed to what economists have used in the past, what's called the lipstick
index.
Have you heard of this?
So it's little treat, little treat time.
That's it.
The little treat thing is exactly it.
So it's a sign that you can't afford big treats.
So usually right before there's an economic downward trend, a nasty one, the prices of
higher-end cosmetics go up.
So suddenly people are spending a little bit more to feel better about themselves during
the day on lipsticks and other high-end makeups because they can't afford to get on a plane
and go somewhere.
They can't afford to go to some exotic spot.
They can't go to some property.
They can't buy a new fancy car.
This is why I'm glad my wife is in the coffee business.
Fancy coffee is the ultimate little treat.
Man, Starbucks is definitely just trying to create...
That's their bar and trade, yeah, that's the whole thing, man.
High-end drinks for women and drive-throughs, that's all that's happening.
Every drink has a crazy color or crazy object in it now.
That being said, I still like Starbucks.
Starbucks is fascinating.
There's nothing in Starbucks I love.
I don't know if there's any amazing drink there or amazing food there.
Well, and I guess it's from a coffee perspective, it's a very specific, very, is bitter the
right word?
Super roasted?
They do a lot of high-roasted, super-high-roasted blends.
And they're the first ones to really over-roast a Rebecca beans when we were all used to drinking
Colombian coffee when they first came on the market.
And so they torched, because they gave people a really robust flavor and then charged a
lot of money for it.
So we associated that taste with money because they created it.
So that's become their signature thing.
Some people...
Yeah, but some people still like particular blends and things like that from them.
So I don't want to besmirch the grudge.
No, not at all.
Famously, I described when I was a barista, every coffee profile is burnt and gotten troubled
by my manager who's training me.
It tastes burnt.
You mean when you were doing your sample tasting as your onboarding kind of thing?
Yeah.
I'm getting notes of charred grill, campfire, whopper.
That's exactly what I did, Jacob.
But they told me to stop saying burnt.
I started going campfiery, you know.
Oh, this one tastes more like a brush fire.
Overcooked bread.
This has definitely got a crematorium kind of vibe.
Oh, this reminds me of one of the seasons in California.
Oh, fire seasons.
Yes, that's right.
Fireworks, warehouse disaster, notes of black cat explosion.
Fireworks.
This tastes very July 5th.
July 5th!
That would be...
I love the smell of napalm in the morning.
That would be an interesting coffee-whiskey blend, a 5th of July.
5th of July is a very funny...
Right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Make it like a drink.
Embered.
It's a 5th of July.
Right.
Jacob?
Boo sales are down.
You should get on that.
Boo sales are down?
Yes.
Boo sales are down.
I was reading this the other day.
To no one's surprise, Canadians don't feel like drinking American whiskey right now.
Which at least makes me happy.
If they're not going to come see my little American show on the Las Vegas Strip, please
don't buy the easier things to buy too.
If you're going to keep your money away from my shit, go ahead and keep it away from the
other shit too.
It really is funny because we probably have some Canadians here up on our chat.
Yeah, because they're not afraid to travel to our chat room.
Yeah, but it basically is like, when you go like, "Oh, come on Canada," it definitely
is like, "Oh," and then all that comes to mind is like, "We've been giving Canada shit
for so long."
All we do is fucking fuck with Canadians and finally they're like, "No, really, this time
I'm leaving."
And you're like, "No, come on, baby."
Come on.
"She never left before.
She always just came back.
Where are you going, baby?
Where are you going?
I can change Canada, I can change."
You know my heart, Canada.
You know my heart.
Yeah, I mean, look, man, for all the shitty American boycotting of businesses, Canada was
like, "No, no, no.
Really."
No, we out.
We out.
No, no, we really can flex, guys.
We really can.
Yeah, we got a couple of people living here.
Yeah, it's not just some little island.
Yeah, it's pretty crazy.
Pretty crazy.
I just listened to ...
It's nuts.
Oh, that's true.
Scooper Nova Girl with the John Candy movie, Canadian Bacon with the recommend Canadian
Bacon, a fine film.
Oh, yes.
It is a fine film.
It is.
There's definitely poignant at this point.
You heard my favorite murder take on the heist, the big booze heist that happened out of the
Johnny Walker distillery to hear about all that craziness that's happened in the, I guess
it was early '90s.
No.
Did you ever hear this story, Jacob?
I'm surprised.
I don't think so.
Maybe.
I don't know.
This guy ...
Refresh my memory.
What's that really famous old granddad?
Not old granddad.
What's the one that's really high end, the bottle that goes for crazy money?
Pappy Van Winkle?
That's it.
Pappy Van Winkle.
Oh, there you go.
So they had Pappy Van Winkles on display in this guy.
This guy was working for the distillery for years, and he worked his way up from distributing
to being like a warehouse manager.
Basically they had no security whatsoever, and he started stealing Pappy Van Winkle bottles,
and he'd just steal them out of the display cases in the place.
Yeah, he'd just take them from all over the place, and if he saw one not nailed down,
he was taking it.
Yeah, and selling them for lots of money, and just started off small, and by the end
of it, he was just going crazy.
Yeah, there was a Netflix special about him.
Yes, I believe so.
Because it was at the Buffalo Trace distillery.
That's it.
It was the Buffalo Trace distillery.
That's the ones that make that booze.
They make the Van Winkle line.
Yeah, he was taking them, he was selling them to his friends, he was selling them to neighbors,
he was selling them all over the place.
It's a wild story.
Yeah.
And of course, he didn't stop at selling them to his next door neighbor for 500 bucks in
cash or whatever.
No.
He had to put stuff online, got too big, and of course he got caught.
Yeah, yeah, and all the records are on his phone.
He didn't use a burner or anything, it's just his phone, all that kind of shit.
Right.
And like, grand larceny.
Oh.
It reached the stage of being like a big fucking crime.
Totally.
And there's a similar incident in Canada, but it involves maple syrup.
Oh, I was going to guess hockey sticks.
Your mission, should you choose to accept it.
A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A, A. It's a Canadian version.
It's a guy like walking out, but like everything he touches is sticky.
Just like all his papers and stuff just attached to him as he walks out.
I think you might be guilty, pal.
No, no.
I'm just wearing a sponge, I'm just wearing a sponge suit and I dip myself into a vat
of maple syrup and then I'm going to go home and wring myself out.
Gross.
Sell those farmers market.
I'm so sorry to have to ask this, but did you, did you steal that maple syrup?
I'm sorry to ask, but did you steal it?
I don't know.
If something just attaches to your body, is it theft or is, you know, or did it choose
to go with you?
Oh, God.
He stole it.
That's a fine question.
He dipped in it and then rinsed it off and sold rinse, rinsy maple syrup.
This maple syrup that I buy from the store, I mean, sure, it tastes like maple syrup,
but the maple syrup I buy from Ted down the street.
Now it's got an extra little something.
It's got a zing.
He fucking, he fucking baby birded that shit.
It took a giant straws like, and then, and then just waved as he walked out.
Oh, gross.
He kept it in his mouth, sucking up, sucking up maple syrup to a giant straw is so upsetting.
Siphon it into his pants.
See you later.
Oh, that's so horrible.
Bro.
And he just, I don't know why that bothers me more than anything else on this show.
Just a mouthful of syrup, like he's only able to fill up one medicine, go down.
He fills up those little travel bottles every day, just fills up a travel bottle.
He's only making like $2 a day with it.
He's siphoning maple syrup, sucking it into a hose.
You guys can drink these fireball on the plane or you can have grade B tasty maple syrup.
Grade B?
Grade B but edible tasty maple syrup.
Scully's like, now he butt chugged it like a turtle.
Most fun way to get diabetes for 1,000, Alex.
Jason Victor.
Yeah.
The little maple leaf.
Butt chugging like a turtle.
The little maple leaf shaped souvenir bottles.
That's exactly what I was picturing.
Exactly.
Oh man.
But I actually know no details about the maple syrup that you're talking about.
Yeah.
It was a similar kind of thing, like insiders figuring out where maple syrup was being transported
and hijacking entire bus loads of truckloads of maple syrup.
Like hundreds of thousands if not millions of dollars worth of maple syrup.
Billions?
I don't know about billions.
Galactic president.
If you count the tariffs, it's billions.
I mean nowadays it could be.
Nowadays it could be.
Everything's up.
Galactic president says a custom idea, maple syrup leg.
Oh yeah.
Not a bad idea.
Ooze.
I went and saw two shows recently.
Okay.
Oh.
I saw Lucy Darling over at the NGM and she was playing, of course, with our good friend
Sarah Hester Ross.
Awesome.
How was that?
It was incredible.
It was fascinating.
And I say that just because obviously I come to Lucy through the magic world.
Those of you who aren't familiar, you probably have seen Lucy Darling clips on your social
media because she's really blown up.
Right?
Oh yeah.
She's everywhere.
She's still on improper crowd work.
And so it's funny because basically magicians want to hate her for being successful.
You actually hate everyone who blows up, like when Justin Willman first came around, everyone
wanted to hate Justin Willman.
Like it just happens.
But people say like the dumbest shit.
Right?
So at first they were saying, you know, she's putting up, she's selling out these theaters,
but they're very small theaters.
And I was laughing and I was like, uh, uh, yes, please.
Are you selling out a small theater, sir?
Yeah.
Give me, give me that problem tomorrow.
And what are they, what are they making?
So, so they're making fun of her for saying that she is selling out theaters and they're
coming back and just being like, yeah, yeah.
But they're little.
She's the base.
China says she's not as big time as, as you think she is or something like that.
Right.
Okay.
Fine.
Right.
Exactly.
And by the way, like she would sell a small theater, but like eight shows in a row.
So it was like, okay.
Like basically that just means like she could have played a big theater and went, oops,
I booked the wrong theater.
So like, okay, great.
And she's smart.
Like she's figured out, she's figured out something that I am chasing, right?
She's figured out how to, how to, how to put herself online without spoiling all of her
magic tricks.
Yes.
That is true.
Has her interacting with people, getting laughs and it's out.
Right.
Oh, you know?
Yeah, that's true.
She's putting like funny moments of her show online, but not really revealing the tricks.
Man, if, if you had funny moments in your show that you could put online, right?
Oh, that'd be, that'd be so convenient.
The problem is those aren't as easy to buy as magic tricks.
That's true.
So it's like, no foil again.
Now I hate Lucy darling too.
I put the ads out on Fiverr.
I just can't get the jokes.
So then someone said, like, well, you know, obviously people were just getting into her
because they, because of her crowd work, some people were going to show not even knowing
she's a magician, right?
And then.
Oh no.
And then being like, that's what's going to like ruin their experience.
Like I came to see.
I came to see a funny comedian.
She does magic tricks.
I'm fucking out of here.
Now she knows what card I picked.
Fucking out of here.
Disgusting.
Well, I'm here to, to, to go ahead and put a bow on that as well.
Because when I went and saw her in the show, I was curious.
I wasn't, I wasn't, I wasn't in agreement with these people, but I was curious about
what, what am I going to go see?
Of course.
Yeah.
I didn't even know I was going to see Sarah Starrus.
Sarah Starrus was there.
Nice.
And I know those two have been doing shows down in downtown at the, what's that spot
called?
Where, where, where our old improv theater used to be.
The Inspire?
Yeah.
No, no, no.
I know what it used to be called.
The one in square where the onyx was.
Yeah, yeah.
Now there's a venue there.
Anyway.
Oh really?
There's definitely a venue there.
Yeah.
Yes.
Is it, is it that same space?
No, it's a, it's in the middle there.
A new, a newly built space.
Kind of new.
What's his name?
Look at me with all the fucking details.
Left Caesars and started running that space and I saw Sarah Starrus there.
I had all the details when I talked about going to see Sarah Starrus' show.
Okay.
Remember I talked about how she, she packed it on a Monday night.
Anyhow.
Let's see, the Beverly, the Beverly, the Huntridge, third street notoriety.
Nope, nope, nope.
Just looking at downtown theaters.
I don't know.
We'll find, we'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out.
I'll figure it out.
Yeah.
Anyhow.
So, so they have chemistry, like amazing chemistry.
Yes.
Like they really play off each other like very well and it's really, really fun.
Yeah.
And Sarah Hester Ross is so much dirtier than Lucy Darling, which is really funny.
And Sarah is filthy.
For people who have only experienced Sarah Hester Ross on this show, you don't understand
how filthy Sarah can be on stage.
And she's the, she's the headliner, so to speak.
She's the second act.
They just share the stage.
She's a piano player.
Oh, awesome.
They just play off each other.
It is awesome.
And Sarah Hester Ross was a sniper, right?
Like, you know, she's, she's used to running her own show.
She's in like maybe she's like 20% of the show for this show.
And so she just was like stepping up and just killing it every time she needed to.
It was really great to see.
Okay.
The audience, indeed, loves Lucy Darling and just wants her to do crowd work.
And that's what she did.
It was a 90 minute show.
The crowd was eating out of her hands the entire time, like roaring and loving everything
she was saying.
They were saying her lines for her, famous lines from her TikToks for her.
And she did all of two magic tricks, two, did two, two in 90 minutes.
I didn't know she was going to do magic tricks.
Well, it's, it's kind of like Brad Sherwood was saying, crowd work slash improv.
It's a kind of magic trick, just tricks, right?
Sure.
She, she has, she basically just kind of gave like four people roles, two people with big
roles in the show and just kind of dared them to play along with the storytelling stuff
and improv.
And they just roared exactly, right?
Like I was laughing because like Emily Gillette has always been very kind to all of us and
was super kind to me, especially early on in my Vegas time here producing our improv
shows and things like that.
And whenever I talked to her now and I talk about being a magician, she always goes like,
well, like she's always like, and I'm always laughing, like why, why do you hate that I'm
a magician now, right?
And she always goes, I just don't think it's the only thing you're going to do.
I just think you, you're going to do more, which is, which is fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's a fine answer.
But I really didn't know what she was talking about.
When I saw Lucy Darling show, I was like, oh, this is what Emily Gillette would love
if I was doing.
Like this is actually, I did two little magic tricks in the middle and did 90 minutes of
just me fucking around with my comedy friends and just making the audience roar with laughter.
She would love it.
Who was that dude?
You're right.
That very, I don't want to use the word pretentious exactly, but it was a very precious, it was
a very precious magic show.
It wasn't a lot of magic, but oh, I know who you're talking about.
I have, I have his t-shirt.
It's a classic magician here in Vegas.
He's not around anymore.
Hill Bill.
Oh, yeah.
I thought you were going to say, I'm going to say Hans clock or something.
No.
Steve, Steve Weirich.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was a Broadway special that this guy, and he had a moment about three years ago, I want
to say, where he was the kid.
You're talking about Derek Delgadio?
That's who I'm talking about.
Oh, okay.
What's up with his new, is he doing something else now?
Is he just, what's happening?
He's doing a whole fish noodling thing.
Okay.
I ended up hanging out with him the other night by accident.
He's fine.
Okay.
He's always fine.
But, you know, he's very much in demand in corporate and private show settings.
So he's got his niche.
Yeah.
That's great.
We don't need to set up like a Kickstarter for him.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Is he still doing a version of that show anywhere or is that kind of retired?
He's just.
I believe that's retired.
All right.
Right.
Yeah.
He had also had a run before then where he had partnered with this guy Helger, I think
it was his name, Spanish guy, and they did a two person show with like all card tricks
that Neil Patrick Harris fell in love with and produced and it had like a crazy run at
the Geffen Theater, like an unheard of like six month run in Los Angeles.
So he's had a couple of real feathers in the cap already.
So okay, cool.
Yeah.
He's always been a real kind of like highly esteemed magician in the ranks or whatever.
He also famously tried to get Brushwood kicked out of the castle for dress code violations
for performing out of dress code.
So in fairness, any time I go to the Magic Castle, I try to get Brian Brushwood kicked
out.
Why are magicians such catty bitches?
What the fuck?
I mean, this is all old news, but it was just funny.
There's only three tricks for them all to share, Paul.
Because I only ended up hanging out with them in an happenstance way.
And so I literally was like, oh, and that's funny.
I was like, and basically my brain's going like, do not bring up Brian Brushwood.
Do not bring up Brian Brushwood.
Do not.
That's all that's going on in my head.
Because the answer could have been like, oh my God, that's so embarrassing.
I was so into it back then and I was trying to be a castle boy and blah, blah, blah.
Or it could be like, I still think the castle's got too much.
It was like, no, and so I was like, yeah, it could definitely be like, fuck that guy
still.
And I was like, Brushwood even told me this story so long ago, I was like, I don't even
know if he said something.
He probably wouldn't even remember it.
He might not even remember it.
He might have been like, you did not.
If I brought it up, he'd be like, please tell me you did not bring up that.
So I kept my mouth shut.
So you brought it up?
No, this is it.
I'm laughing because 10 years ago, I absolutely would have.
Right.
I've just been like, you know, I had to ask because I got your back, man.
You know, I've learned because of Penn and Teller.
There's having your back and then there's, yeah.
I used to carry other people's water for so many conflicts and they'd be like, oh no,
we buried that.
And I'd be like, what?
Oh shit.
I've been furious at that guy for eight years.
That's really fucking funny.
Even with, I mean, maybe I shouldn't say this, but even like at one point, Tapeface and Piff
had beef and Piff totally forgot to tell me that they absolutely buried it, that they
absolutely made amends and get along and whatever.
And I was like, what?
I was carrying around hatred in my heart.
I was awkward with him at red carpets.
Because they weren't even like big beef.
They were just like, it was like misunderstanding beef and they both knew it was misunderstanding
beef before they squashed it, I think.
Yes.
They were basically both.
They were both okay even before they squashed it.
They ended up being accidentally played against one another via casino people and about like
trying to find homes and casinos and so.
It was just, you know, business stuff that actually is pretty boring when you break down
the nuts and bolts of it.
Yeah.
It sounds exciting on the surface, but it's nothing.
I'll tell you who else has beef with Piff the Magic Dragon and with Tapeface.
I mean the three of these people are going to fight, Piff, Tapeface and this following
sponsor are definitely going to have a physical altercation.
Oh God.
Today's show is brought to you by ... Where is it?
God damn it.
Here it is.
I think I just put it in the more prominent place on my cell phone, not in the middle
of row two on screen four of my apps.
But Cat Scratch Fever Salve, Cat Scratch Fever Salve is our sponsor and it's from Semi Pro
Dad in 2022.
It's Cat Scratch Fever Salve.
I want to tell you about some really good stuff that he's selling that I'm pimping.
It's called Cat Scratch Fever Salve.
You ever get a scratch from a kitty-kitty?
You ever get a little bruise, little scratch on your arm?
Do you want that to get infected?
No.
Here's the best thing to do.
Go ahead ... Oh, I remember his dumb name is Ted Nugent.
Anyway, so what you want to do is go ahead and get you some of Ted Nugent's Paul Stanley
Cat Scratch Fever Salve.
Ted Nugent's Paul Stanley Cat Scratch Fever Salve is guaranteed to end inflammation and
stop irritation and prevent infection.
Yeah!
Some of you might have been using wipes.
Some of you might have been using disinfectant alcohol.
I'm here to tell you what's better is Paul Stanley's Ted Nugent's Cat Scratch Fever
Salve.
It's medicated, it's vibrated, and it is perforated for your enjoyment.
That's right.
Take it from me.
Perforated?
The star child.
I wouldn't lie to you.
Buy it.
Enter, "Hey Scoops at Checkout?"
Buy.
Saying "buy" is hysterical.
I said buy it, but I should have just said buy it.
Oh, I thought you were saying, "I'm done making this commercial now.
Goodbye."
Buy.
It's over.
I'm through.
I'm through with that idea.
Buy it!
There it is.
Cat Scratch Fever Balm.
It's real.
How about old Gene getting into the Kennedy Center?
Gene and Paul both.
You're in the Kennedy Center.
Stop it.
Paul agreed to go?
Well, I mean, Paul and Gene are kiss.
The kiss is going in.
No, I think it's just Gene.
Paul's been pretty adamantly anti.
I don't know that they're going to go together.
I'll be very surprised and disappointed.
I mean, somewhat surprised.
And some of the Kennedy Center honorees this year?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
By the way, I don't have any beef with anybody going in.
Like, the honorees, I'm fine with all the honorees.
Does anybody care about the  are people saying these people shouldn't be going into
the Kennedy Center?
Sharing is exactly what we're talking about here.
It reminds me of when Barry Bonds was breaking the home run record.
Yeah.
A little bit, yeah.
And everyone was like, they want to do all this stuff like launch the ball into outer
space.
You know, all this other stuff.
Right.
Brandon Asterix onto it.
What someone said is like, all that's going to happen is we're going to stop caring about
the home run record.
And that's exactly what we did.
Yeah.
We just stopped caring about it.
That's it.
And then someone who does a trick with baseball cards, I can tell you, the ramifications of
the steroid era are real, because when I ask people who likes baseball, and it's mostly
young people in the audience, no one says yes.
And sometimes, audibly, people go like, "Not me."
Yeah.
"Not me."
And Adam and I go like, "Oh, no."
And I'll even come with them with a bucket of baseball cards, and they literally look
at me like, "No, I hate baseball."
I'm like, "It's a first and a last thing."
"I hate baseball."
Can you chill out?
They hate baseball so much they're like allergic to baseball cards?
They literally recoil.
Holy shit.
It's like some kind of evasive extending pole and bucket.
Sure.
That it might not be-
No, I understand the recoiling.
Might not be.
It might not be just the subject of baseball.
I'm a little off putting myself, but it's a negative impact of baseball.
And even like now, even in my baseball card collection that I use, I have a lot of old
players in there, and I thought about replacing them with new ones, and it's basically-
Nobody cares.
Nobody knows.
I can maybe put O'Tonnie in.
I can maybe put Judge-
A-Rod.
A-Rod's the latest, right?
I think you put O'Tonnie.
I think you put-
Yeah, A-Rod's in there.
That's why A-Rod features in my thing, because I think it's the only one.
I think it's the most-
Is there anyone people know?
And that's just because he was married to-
I think it's the most-
That dancer lady for a minute.
J.Lo.
Jennifer Lopez?
You could maybe do Mike Trout.
Was that her?
Yeah.
That dancer lady.
A very famous celebrity.
She was a fly girl.
Yeah, but everything Paul is saying is true.
A dancer lady fly girl.
Please don't write on saying that Paul was right.
We know he's right.
I mean, if you look up her IMDB, it starts off with famous dancer lady, Jennifer Lopez.
If you look up her IMDB, which no one has done-
We also have owner of the Minnesota Timberwolves as well, as a result of multiple lawsuits.
A-Rod is the owner of the Timberwolves.
Oh, I thought you were about to say J-Lo owns the Timberwolves.
No, no, no.
That was going to be surprising to me.
Yeah.
But I mean, that's it.
A-Rod is featured in the tricks simply because that's the one that I believe that most people
would know if you don't like sports.
Yeah.
And that's an old joke, right?
I made that decision eight years ago, right?
And so-
Right.
That's crazy that it's that old and it still seems like that's it.
What else?
You're right.
I don't even know what other name I even know.
I've been to a couple of Pirates games.
I couldn't tell you any of those players.
No.
I actually, I haven't done that a lot, but I really want to ask my kids, name a baseball
player.
Name a professional baseball player.
Like a current one.
Is there any way for you to get Savannah Banana cards in there?
Because you could put like stilts in there.
No one knows individual Savannah Bananas.
People know what the Savannah Bananas are.
People know stilts.
No one knows individual players.
They will not.
The guy on stilts?
He plays on stilts.
I understand what you're saying.
How do people not know stilts?
I believe that if I were watching a baseball game and there were a player on the field
wearing stilts and I heard people referring to a player called stilts, I would know which
player you were talking about.
You'd be able to pick him out of a lineup that night.
But after that, you know-
I'd be able to, using the context clues, I'd be able to figure out who you meant.
If I were to say scooped up by Roberto Clemente and thrown over to stilts, I don't think the
audience would be like, "Yes!"
You're right.
Ooh, Savannah Bananas!
I don't think-
He just made a Savannah Bananas reference!
What about characters from the Sandlot?
There we go.
I mean, you're right in that I'm trying to consider doing a whole different deal altogether,
like, rather than, I don't want to go back to cards, but I'm trying to think of something
just entirely different.
There are Marvel trading cards.
Everybody knows Marvel characters.
Somebody did say earlier-
That is interesting.
Oh, Marcelo!
Marcelo in the chat said earlier that you could get rid of the baseball cards and just
put in Pokemon cards.
Pokemon would be really funny, too.
I think Marvel is a stronger move than- we've turned this into a brainstorming session,
but I think-
Stronger grip on the zeitgeist.
Everybody knows Marvel.
Not everybody knows.
For Matt Show!
Except it's my production.
It's the My Newly Magic production meeting.
Production meeting for Matt Show.
No, Marvel characters are smart, and they're actually smart, too, because I also really
want to get a Disney cruise ship.
Oh, yeah!
There you go.
That's the way to go, man.
Go with Marvel cards.
Oh, well, they've got to be just Disney trading cards.
Well, there's Lorcan-a.
That's got to exist, too.
You don't want to do Lorcan-a.
Jacob, mine are fake anyway.
Yeah.
No, but there are Marvel art cards from back in the day.
What?
Oh, shit.
This is what happens when people pretend to steal.
I have Mickey Mantle and stuff, and they pretend to steal it in their pocket.
In fact, someone has stolen a card from my-
Oh, no!
Outrageous.
I thought it was a valuable baseball card.
Someone stole a Cal Ripken thing.
It was a valuable baseball card.
And so, when they do it, I go like, "And if you think you're taking an actual baseball
card from a working magician, you go ahead and keep that in your pocket and you tell
all your friends."
If you think this working magician has a Cal Ripken rookie card that he's passing around
to you.
No, the answer is fucking Marvel superheroes.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
It's easy.
That's just the answer.
Yeah.
Anyhow, that's not what I was trying to talk about.
Do they have to play baseball, though, for the trick to work?
Yes.
They have to play baseball.
That's going to be a little-
It's Iron Man playing baseball.
People don't know that this is a secret softball game that takes place every year between DC
and Marvel.
Just go Marvel.
Fuck DC.
No.
I am just going to go Marvel, because Disney owns Marvel, right?
They do.
And doesn't own DC.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I'm just going to just go Marvel.
And then, no, I can narrate an event, Paul, instead of narrating a baseball play.
Oh, fantastic.
I can still narrate an event.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
That'd be very cool.
Because even my intro of it is like ... The intro of it is, when I was a kid, like the
movie Field of Dreams.
That's getting diminishing applause.
Sure.
Now, eight years later.
Yeah.
It was really nice when Kevin Costner was hitting again with Yellowstone, but that's
gone now, too.
Well, yeah.
That's gone.
I think Puddles has stolen all the Costner fire.
That's just-
That's true.
There's nothing left.
And then, when I was doing it, Heidi Klum came in off the street and said, "Stop stealing
everything from Puddles!" and then went back out on the street.
Just wanted to make sure she-
Puddles.
I think Puddles did that after you started talking about it, so.
Well, our attorneys will figure that out.
Sure.
I'm referencing, by the way, when I failed on America's Got Talent, and while they were
judging me, I pulled out an apple and I sliced the apple with the knife I used for my card
stab and started eating the apple, and Heidi Klum yelled, "You can't steal everything
from Piff!" at me with a hatred that was like trying to stop a protest or something.
It was with a family passion that she yelled at me.
It was really startling.
But we're talking about our blood oath loyalties.
In the chat, we're getting some really good people talking about the times they were convinced
to take a good blood oath, maybe.
Let's see here.
Too many people have chatted.
I've lost track.
But someone in the chat was like, an Olive Garden fired their cousin, and so the whole
family protested all of Olive Gardens.
The long-term grudges?
Yeah, long-term grudges.
Oh, I see.
I see.
The blood vendettas, not the blood oaths.
Right.
Jason Victor.
Jason, are you un-muted?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So what happened?
You were fired?
No, who got fired?
No, my cousin.
My cousin was ... Actually, it was kind of messed up.
He was singing.
He was like a waiter at Olive Garden, but he was really theatrical, and he would sing
at tables and do all this ... He was like a tremendous performer and everything.
He was in all these plays and shows.
He would use tongs and pretend to be a crab and scuttle across the floor.
So everybody loved him.
A week before he was set to retire, they fired him without cause.
My grandmother was like, "No, we will never go to Olive Garden."
A week before he was set to retire, did he get knocked out of benefits and things because
of that?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Whoa.
It was messed up, so ... Also, I'm finding out right now that Olive Garden has retirement
programs.
Now, this is like third-hand storytelling from ... We're built on hearsay and conjecture.
That's fine.
We don't have the authority to be a primary source podcast.
That's not where we're at financially.
Also, we don't have an ombudsman.
It doesn't matter.
We do not.
Nobody's checking.
Who knows?
It was one side of the story, times three times people I've heard it from, so I don't
mean to create a beef for the whole podcast here.
Oh, jeez, we're getting a phone call right now.
It's the following sponsor, but the following sponsor is Olive Garden calling in to rebut
this story.
So here we are with Olive Garden and their rebuttal, "Take Away Olive Garden."
Hey, it's a me, Mario Olive, and that's my brother, Luigi Garden.
And today we are going to tell you that we don't fire people because we don't want to
pay for their retirement.
We fire them because we hate the singing.
We hate singing so much.
We hate theater.
We often will not deliver food to any Broadway show.
We will not offer endless breadsticks to anyone who knows how to play piano.
We have a very firm, we've been against music from the inception of the founding of our
company.
How are you going to come to Olive Garden and sing one of endless breadsticks to cover
your face?
How are you going to sing endless breadsticks and a bottomless bowl of soup?
You ever hear the phrase, "You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel"?
That's the truth.
You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel, so don't do it.
It sounds a little different in Italian.
It's more poetic.
In Italian it sounds like, "You sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel."
But translated, that means you sing at the table, the devil will dance on your navel.
That's much better.
I'm sorry if I lost anybody there in my old country talk.
Boy, I feel like I'm back at home.
I feel like I'm back at home like a big old macaroni in my mouth.
Enter in scoops and check out.
Luisa got a little occasion at the end there.
Oh, I like me some macaroni.
Oh, boy.
What?
I guarantee.
Go ahead, give me one.
I'm going to roll this game.
I'm going to roll this LP roll all the way over now.
I'm going to give me some macaroni.
Watch out.
Go ahead, give me some of that.
You're going to make my bolognese really spicy.
I'm looking for some of that delicious lasagna.
Wait.
One last question for Jason.
Did the protests hold?
Have you never gone to an Olive Garden and do you know that no one in your family has
ever gone to an Olive Garden?
I think most of us have kept away from it for the most part, but if anyone did go, they
would definitely.
Wow.
I don't think it's a real awkward Thanksgiving.
I think it should be like, really, still none of us, not one Olive Garden.
It's so affordable.
It's right near the movie theater where I take my kids, are you sure?
It's not great, but it's pretty good.
You know, this is a blood feud that actually benefits your blood from a salt perspective.
So that's kind of good.
This is like decades ago too at this point.
This is a really old, this happened a while ago, but I still remember she's like, no,
she called up everybody.
She's like, we can't go to an Olive Garden.
Was there a lawsuit after all that with the-
I don't think so.
I got to actually, I got to call him.
Is he okay?
We got to get it.
Yeah.
You get us an update on your cousin.
So busy hating Olive Garden because of the foiled retirement.
We never forgot the check.
Oh shit, my cousin died in 2020.
This was before GoFundMe's could help people like him.
Turns out he died right before COVID hit.
That's terrible.
My father won a defense case on this, like everyone presented all of these evidence of
like threats and all this other crazy stuff and phone records and all this stuff.
And my father on cross-examination was like, anyone check on him?
Anyone see if he was doing okay?
Like anyone ever talk to him about the threat?
The answer was no.
No one actually went to see if the person actually had anything threatening happening
to him and he got him off.
Wow.
Logic wins the day.
Never get tired of hearing stories about Dave Donnelly getting guys off.
I know he's happily retired now, just so everyone's not worried about Gary, but he's okay.
Does he sing at the table?
I saw him recently and I think he's still performing in community theater down in Florida.
Every Christmas he's like, "When they fired me from Olive Garden."
Oh, it's the story.
Oh, Gary's doing his song again.
Gary's doing his story song again.
We've heard this song.
Why is it every Christmas?
"I was only a week away from retirement, they cut me loose."
Shut the fuck up, Matt.
I love this song.
"With no excuse."
Oh, this is your first Christmas with our family, I forgot to tell you.
My uncle sings about the time he got fired from Olive Garden.
"When you sing at the table, the devil dances on your navel."
Oh, everyone knows that expression, we all know that expression.
Have you guys never heard that?
No, I've heard it in the original Italian, obviously, but never the translated version.
How was the Italian again?
"When you sing at the table, the devil dances on your navel."
That's it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry for that.
That's what I remember.
Bossy understood that, but nobody else got it.
Sure, sure.
Very clearly.
Thank you, Jason.
Thank you.
Oh, my heavens.
I hope his cousin is okay.
I mean, he's alive at least.
I think he's fine.
I'm sure.
I went into a bathroom the other day.
Stop it, gross.
Public bathroom.
And I was going to use the said bathroom.
And they had recently, it seemed, made a video, and I was like, "Oh, my god, I'm going to
die."
I went into a bathroom the other day in a public bathroom, and I was going to use the said bathroom, and they had recently, it seemed, maybe painted the floor in the bathroom.
What?
And the paint they had chosen to use was that black paint that always looks wet, depending
on how you look at it, like from what angle you look at it.
So I'm in the bathroom, and I thought the whole floor was just wet, and I was trying
to move her.
I was so confused.
Oh, no.
You know, when you walk into a public bathroom and you just see a little, like, some wet
on the floor there, you just walk around it, you know, whatever.
This was, like, it was everywhere, and I had a moment of just sheer panic and didn't know
what to do before I realized it was just a terrible choice in paint by someone.
We had this happen when I was a kid.
Back in the day, we used to go to Kings Island as a family, back before I was working there.
And way back in the late '70s, which is when we went as a family, they used to have these
caves, these man-made, they were basically, what do you call those, like, holes?
Drainage tubes, big enough that you could walk through, you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
But they built it like a half tunnel.
So they made these tunnels, and they were these themed tunnels on, one of them was like
a Tom Sawyer, so you'd walk through and you'd see Injun Joe and Becky Thatcher, you know,
it was little static scenes of statues and things, but kind of retelling moments in the
stories.
Well, we go walking into one of these tunnels, and it had been raining that day, and there
was a pool of water in the tunnel, and the light was hitting it just right.
It looked like a pit.
It looked like a deadly pit that you couldn't go any further.
You would walk on it, and you'd fall to your death.
But what it turned out was it was a reflection of the ceiling from that water puddle.
Gotcha.
Yeah, yeah.
A precise optical illusion that it made it look like you were gonna fall and die, but
there was nothing.
But I take your point on the freakiness of walking around on a floor.
I was like, "Why would you paint this floor with this paint?"
Because then when it is wet, ugh.
Dead Lazlo's been boycotting Boston markets since 1998 because they wouldn't let him get
two of the same sides out of order.
Stop it.
Fair.
That is a reasonable reason to boycott Boston markets for 30 years.
And also that your boycott might work is really funny.
You indeed might have put them out of business.
Well, you didn't help, you didn't help.
Boston market had a smell, didn't it?
It did.
It had a very particular chicken seasoning.
It was real strong, real pungent, almost like a, not as offensive to me as a Subway, but
same kind of vibe.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, that Subway smell.
In Portugal, there was a Subway in Lisbon, a Subway sandwich shop in Lisbon, and I went
and stuck my head in just to see if they had the same smell.
Yeah, this is a true story.
And they did.
They did.
Okay.
Same smell.
Overseas Subway shop.
Didn't matter.
I think it's just when you handle meat, it gives off a certain odor.
I think it's a meat handling odor.
I think you're right, Paul.
If you suck it on maple syrup, it gives a different flavor palette.
Yeah.
Ugh.
My, especially with my syrup, it was baby birded to me by someone who worked at a Canadian
maple plant.
God damn it.
That's why you got fired from the Olive Garden, because he was spitting the linguine onto
the tables.
It was, it was baby bird, how many times do I have to tell you not to baby bird the linguine
to our customers?
You fired, you fired my uncle for his singing.
No, we fired your uncle for spitting food in other people's mouths.
I've got some grated parmesan, say when?
When?
I didn't want you to win.
Win.
Okay.
An hour ago win.
An hour ago.
Okay.
I'll be back if you need anything.
I'm sorry, do you have any, do you have any fresh black pepper?
Hold on, I got some between cheek and gum on the other side.
Oh no, God damn it, why did I ask?
Oh, I regret this.
I keep several different kinds of cheese and spice in my mouth while I'm serving.
So that I can dispense it at any time.
It does sound like Cher.
I'm sorry.
Now, if you want to know how to impersonate Cher, all you got to do is imagine you've
got a mouth full of paprika.
We should say, we have to address some housekeeping over here, a little stuff on the internet
and some confusion in the chat.
So I accidentally, when I uploaded our last episode, uploaded it with today's episode
number.
And so it came out as 1236 to 1235.
And then people thought a crazy trend was happening because they said also we can't
find another episode on there and I won't even name the number.
And so the answer is one was my error and so you're not missing two episodes.
You are missing one.
Yeah.
And that's temporary.
Yes.
But a listener, just like Jason came on here and shared a lovely story there.
If all of a sudden his uncle was like, what the hell?
And also, sorry, gang up on his uncle on the internet, then we would maybe try to not be
the cause of someone's heart.
Mitigate that.
Yeah.
So yeah, it turned out someone was getting picked on by jerks on the internet.
And so we took down the episode to stop being a source of woe to one of our listeners.
And I'm going to edit that episode out.
I've got, I've got all the little spots to edit it out.
I just haven't been able to do that yet.
I'm hopefully going to, by the time this episode comes out, I'm hoping that that episode will
be back up as well.
It will be back.
In the meantime, please help yourself to one of our 1,230 other episodes, which, which
I am proud to say, I am proud to say we have stuck to it.
Our base episodes have been up and free and unpaywalled from the jump.
Yes.
I am really proud of that.
Except for this one.
This one is behind the paywall.
It's not behind the paywall.
It's not.
Oh, you can pay me and I'll send it to you.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
There's ransomware here.
It's also not even the-
@AudioGuideJacob, pay me.
I'll just send it right to you.
It's not even the first time we did this.
We did pull down temporarily the one where I wasn't going to get sued by the people who
made Maryland.
Let me put that back up.
Right.
That's fine.
Yeah.
These things happen.
We got the finger on the pulse, people.
This is what you get.
You caught up in the mix.
Sorry.
Sorry for misnumbering to point of the fact that we did take down an episode.
So yeah, right now you're missing one episode.
I'll be back soon.
Two different things happened.
And yeah.
But the one we're ordering, the one we're listening to right now is-
Quantity over quality.
OG.
OG with the zinger.
I know.
You're not wrong.
OG coming in hot.
You're not wrong, Andy.
Yeah.
We're not arguing with you.
We're just laughing at the fact that you said-
But there's also a reason why Subway was successful.
The smell.
So there you go.
The smell and the quality.
Yeah.
They said, "We'd like to make this restaurant smell like the tunnel of the New York City
Subway system."
Yeah.
And much like a Subway sandwich, we were also worth hitting an ice officer in the face with.
Oh, hey, you know, I had a good one on that one.
A friend of mine sent me one of those Gaston flag parodies with that.
And the sandwich was being thrown at his face, you know?
And it's like, it said like, don't- what is it?
It was like, "Don't sub-"
All I know is I'd rather have a dildo thrown at me while I'm playing basketball.
Oh my God.
That's outrageous how much that's happening.
The sandwich thrown at me at any other time.
But it was like, "Don't sandwich on me," or something like that, you know what I mean?
And my quip was, "That guy should be referred to as Hoagy's heroes."
That's pretty good.
Glad we looped around to pick that one up.
I know nothing.
I laugh.
We all get spammed every day with people trying to scare us with different bullshit things.
I had never changed my New Jersey area code on my phone.
Right.
Why should you?
So all my spams are like, "This is New Jersey DMV," or like, "This is New Jersey Power
Authority."
I have a Louisiana number, and it's the same thing.
I've got the 702, which tips me off every time these motherfuckers come call.
I'm like, "Well, you- I don't even know her.
That's my purse."
Anyways, Lucy Darling and Sarah Soros play each other tremendously well.
Sarah Soros is a sniper.
Ninety minutes, the crowd was just loving and roaring with her.
Merch line out the door.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck yeah.
It was one of like a dozen shows where they were all sold out at the MGM in Brad Garrett's
old space.
Brad Garrett Comedy Club moved.
That's how out of touch I am.
And it's Tapeface's theater.
The New Space is good too.
Tapeface, who I have no problem with whatsoever.
Love me some Tapeface.
Yeah.
I kinda like Tapeface.
In his theater.
And it was one thing she was like, "Oh, she's famous.
She's hit."
I'm waiting an hour for her to say hello to all of her fans, and then I can hang out.
And when I looked at her, I was like, "Hey, I don't know what this show is."
And she was laughing.
And I was like, "It's not?
I mean, you're not doing traditional standup.
You did two magic tricks.
It's not a magic show."
I was like, "You're really like keeping a bit in the air?
You keep like five bits in the air, and the audience loves it.
And then you bounce back and forth between these bits, and the audience just loves you
for it.
And it's crazy."
But people loved it, people were just clapping for her, cheering for her, laughing for her.
I was laughing hysterically through the whole show.
I just realized right now that I might have sounded like I was qualifying myself outside
of the laughter.
I was not.
I was part of it.
Also went and saw Atomic Saloon, so I went to see our friend Tyler before he departed.
Nice.
Where's he going?
He's going off on a Broadway tour.
Water for Elephants.
They went ahead and made a musical of Water for Elephants, which is an amazing book that
people love.
And then in it, there's actually a little person in it who's a real three-dimensional
character, not some magical elf, actually plays a dramatically awesome role in the show.
And then Tyler's getting to play that amazing role as the first Broadway tour, and I guess
that's worth doing.
Man, we got to get him back on again after this run.
We got to get him back on to talk the tour.
That'll be fantastic.
No, I'm so excited for him.
I ran into him happenstance at a bar the other night, and so we got to chat for about half
an hour, 45 minutes or so, and I didn't realize he's never done a Broadway tour before.
He's never done anything like this before, so this is just all new experiences for him
as well.
I'm excited for the show.
I'm excited for him.
Yeah, it's going to be great.
Oh, he has to do it, and I was saying, obviously they didn't want him to go.
He's great in the show at Atomic Saloon.
He really, really makes that role so special, and he's so good at it, and he's so funny.
He's so personable.
He really connects with an audience.
He really just is a natural born entertainer, and it's really special to watch him work.
My family and I saw him do a random Panto show in New York, because it was only after
I saw him in Mavericks that I was like, "Oh, we're in New York?
He's doing a show?
Let's go see it."
We kind of knew him.
Yeah.
We weren't as friends with him like we are now.
We just had to see him.
We love Tyler, and so it was really great to see him in the show.
The last few times I've seen it, it's still great.
It's the best it's been.
Atomic Saloon is in the best shape it's been.
I think it's an awesome show to go see.
I'm so glad to hear that, because I really enjoyed the fuck out of that show.
Yeah, it's a good one.
I saw it twice while I was still out there, and it's great.
Yeah, the hosts now and the bits are just so much more present and right with the audience,
and then the kick-ass acts that are in it are well.
Our friend Christian is back in with his little dog.
He does the acrobatic act with the dog.
So good.
It's such a fun show.
I got hit with a bunch of bread rolls.
Oh, good.
Good.
I was the kind of tap percussion duo that's been there from the fucking beginning.
I was looking, I was like, "Jesus, wow," because they were back from Vegas Nocturne.
That's right.
Yeah, Suzanne and Peter.
Suzanne and Peter have just been in this town, entertaining.
That's nuts.
They do a bit where they do this percussion, but they're like the whatever, the hillbilly
twins or whatever.
He has a bunch of bread rolls in his pocket, and you don't see it.
He snipes people.
He just dances around, and all of a sudden, boom, a bread roll just comes flying across.
It's great.
And right before the show, I was in the back of the main little orchestra section.
They're like, "Do you want to move up?"
And in my head, I was like, "How much do I want to get hit by bread rolls?"
But I was like, "Yeah, let's go for it.
Let's get moved up."
And I was just like, "Oh, man."
I got clunked.
Pelted, huh?
Bread rolls.
Yeah.
Last time I saw it, your wife was in it, and our friend, Matt Morgan, they were the
duo in it the last time I saw it.
So they got me up on stage.
Matt is also a very funny preacher, and I cannot resist that, but he's basically the
director now over there.
But I saw Heidi host, because my wife was not performing.
I still haven't seen Heidi do it.
She's very funny.
It is different.
It is definitely different than Sarah's and everyone else's, and it's really good.
We're talking about Heidi, Brooke, and Morgan, who we've had on the show with Matt Morgan
before.
Yeah, they are just a powerhouse in everything that they do.
Yeah.
But Sarah was not performing with Tyler before Tyler left, so I went and saw Heidi do it.
Nice.
Yeah, yeah.
Kick ass.
That's good.
You've seen Sarah plenty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Over at the Venetian, giant Wizard of Oz display over there.
I have my tickets.
Now the Sphere and Venetian are two totally different entities, right?
They are, but I believe they have kind of a partnership.
Yeah, because basically it just became like haphazard, the only place to park to go to
the Sphere is the Venetian.
Right.
And so the Venetian started charging event pricing during Sphere events.
Which is great for me because it has taken out the question.
So now I just pay the ridiculous amount of money to park at the Sphere because it's close
and it's convenient, because Venetian is now charging like $10 less.
Well, it is worth that $10 to me to not walk across the city and get to this event.
So I guess I'll just pay the extra 10 bucks and not have to worry about it.
Thanks Venetian for being assholes and charging too much for parking.
Yeah.
Country Scoop is mentioning that there's a place called Lambert's in Alabama, famous
for throwing bread rolls across the dining room.
Do you know, Matt, was that taken from that place or not?
Maybe.
I know that it was not.
Okay.
Oh.
Yeah.
Because I know Lambert's and they have a couple of places.
They have one outside of St. Louis as well that I've been to.
And they do.
They just chuck, like if you need a roll, you just like throw up your hand and like yell
like roll.
And they just chuck it across the room baseball style.
We saw some videos of that, Anne and I.
Oh, but I asked about that when Atomic Saloon started and nobody had heard of it.
It became a running joke for Anne and I.
She ended up buying us big Lambert's mugs with the guy throwing the bread roll on it.
Home of the Throwed Rolls.
That's right.
That's it.
Home of the Throwed Rolls.
Throwed Rolls.
The way they say it there.
Yeah.
So are you going to this Wizard of Oz show, Matt, or you just went to the display?
I have yet to see any show at the Sphere.
I don't know if the Wizard of Oz is even open yet.
It is not.
I have tickets to go see it though in September.
I think.
I think I have tickets to go see it before Scoopfest.
Yeah.
I know it is opening soon and our friends are flying out to come see it.
This is going to be a gigantic hit.
I think so too.
I was just talking about this on another show the other day that this - actually on - sorry
Brian and Justin.
I just forgot Great Night's Patreon only section that they do.
Their bonus episode that they do.
The Bones.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So I was on the Bones with them and we were talking about that and that is what I was
saying.
I was like this is - they tried the Nature video.
They tried all that stuff.
The thing to make money when they don't have the giant concert going in the Sphere.
And I think Wizard of Oz is going to do very well in that regard.
And they are hiring live entertainers to be a part of it.
Yes.
And so some of our friends are getting really good gigs out of this as well.
Yeah.
That is great.
And so it makes me more hopeful about it.
Oh and Scoopanova Girl is in the chat saying that she saw the morning video on CBS and
it didn't look good.
I believe that because nothing is - other than I think the movie itself, I don't think
anything else is done.
I think they are still creating everything.
So I believe that the advertising for it at this point would look really bad.
But I think also it is unfortunate that I think they are incorporating some AI gobbledygook
into the side effects around the giant screen kind of thing.
So I have seen some clips that - because like there is - you know they are doing like -
AI is going to be a part of fucking everything but AI is going to be in there.
I hear that it is not going to be the film in its entirety.
It is a lot - I am going into it with a positive outlook on it and I am hoping that it is going
to be great.
Right.
Yeah.
And I am not -
If it is not, I will let you know.
Look, I am not a big Backstreet Boys person and I cannot speak to whether that is a good
thing.
It is a hit.
Yeah.
I can speak to the fact that the Backstreet Boys are punching up.
Like that was a way over achieving experience.
Yeah.
Like I want to go see their show at the Sphere.
So I am saying it is going to be a gigantic hit.
I don't know if it is going to be like My Cup of Tea.
I am just saying.
Yeah.
It is going to be good.
I am looking forward to it.
And as the Sphere exists as a black hole that is slowly sucking and destroying every other
piece of entertainment in this town.
That is true.
I can speak objectively to all of those things.
Like that giant snow globe is going to cause a lot of my friends their jobs.
Yeah.
So I am only happy to at least create a couple on the way out.
There is at least that.
Yeah.
There is that.
Because we have become a, the town, basically Sphere is slowly becoming Disneyland or Disney
World.
Metallica is the next one that is rumored, but more than rumored I think.
I think they are aiming.
I think they are pretty strong.
Pretty strong.
Yeah.
There are so many more steps to saying yes to playing the Sphere which is why you will
hear so many more rumors along the way and it is because it takes millions of dollars
on any artist's back end or front end, on the artist's end, whether they take it from
the back or front.
Don't you worry about which end I am on.
You have to invest millions and millions of dollars into the graphics that fit on the
Sphere to go to your concert.
Right.
Scully is like, "Guar please."
Yeah.
Guar.
A Guar show at the Sphere would be in fucking Sain.
Hey, did you see that they just created some Guar action figures?
I want to do a Lambert's Dinner show before all the concerts where they have bread rolls
come from thousands of feet away.
That would be amazing.
Every which way.
Just launching them.
I just want to do the fucking billion dollar Lambert's Dinner Theater before any production
at the Sphere.
With Guar?
Every night.
With Guar.
Yeah.
Guar is the band that would sing at the table while the devil dances on your neighbor.
That's right.
They would be able to shoot fucking blood soup at you while you eat it.
Be amazing.
Instead of blood, hear me out, drawn butter.
Right?
You had me at drawn butter.
Ghee.
Just millions of gallons of ghee fired right at you.
Daft Punk, that had to be--
Paul, I can't believe that you just said millions of gallons of ghee fired at your face because
that is the prize today for the winner of Jock vs. Nerd.
Oh, stop.
Millions of gallons of ghee.
Fuck yeah.
On the hunt for balls.
Millions of gallons of ghee.
No.
So much ghee.
Millions ranging from $200 all the way up to $5,000 and of course the winner will be
covered in ghee.
Let's see.
The first question is $200.
It's coming to me first and it's true or false stars.
Nobody wants to steal this early so let's see what the question is.
Warning, difficulty steps up fast.
Clint Eastwood has a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
A. True.
B. False.
C. Blank.
D. Blank.
Okay.
Just to tell you how the game works, I have a 50/50 lifeline that I'm not going to use
right now.
Good idea.
I'm going to go ahead and just say true.
A. True.
Oh, B. False.
Now.
Clint Eastwood does not have a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
Does that mean that it never happened or that because those go in rotation?
No, no, no.
No, they don't go in rotation.
What?
You have a star.
No.
Yeah.
You're kidding me.
Yes.
It's there forever?
Yeah.
Get the fuck out of here.
Ask Fatty Arbuckle.
It's still there?
Hold on.
Fatty.
Fatty, it's Jacob.
Hi.
It's me, Jacob.
It's been a minute.
How's your star on the Walk of Fame doing?
I'm okay.
What seems to be going on?
I was in the middle of eating a lot of food as I want to do.
Oh, I'm sorry, Fatty.
I think I called the wrong Fatty.
I'm dipping all of my food in ghee.
Oh, never mind.
I called the right Fatty.
Yeah.
This is a PB in ghee.
Peanut butter in ghee.
PB in ghee.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm so upset.
I'm choking on my PB in ghee.
I'm just going to reveal this true-false weather question and hope to move on.
Tornadoes have appeared in every state of America.
True or false, Paul?
Oh, man.
I'm sorry.
Are we boring you?
No.
I'm just trying to think.
You've got to define a tornado, sort of, but I can't.
Let's hear you define a tornado.
I'll go false.
Let's try it.
That's true.
Ah.
Shit my ass.
Two questions that were 50/50.
We've not done well.
Why?
You don't hear a lot about Alaskan tornadoes or Hawaiian tornadoes.
Yeah, but I don't hear much about much.
Aside from Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, am I right?
Let's go for it.
Give me the question.
Let's see.
How many movies have been produced in the Harry Potter universe?
Eight, nine, ten, or eleven?
Eight.
A.
No.
Eight.
What?
It's my answer.
I'll go.
Okay.
It's D. Eleven.
I was answering for speed, not for accuracy.
Alright.
Five hundred dollar question.
We've all missed a question so far.
Eight hundred dollar question.
We suck.
Corporate history.
Oh, the Harry Potter universe has those newer movies too, right?
The Johnny Depp ones that were big failures.
The mythical beasts and how to find them up your asshole.
That one.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Johnny Depp was in those?
Look up your butt to see a mythical critter.
Huh.
Yeah.
Harry assholes.
I mean, I did that.
The butthole you're finding.
Yeah.
Yep.
Let's see.
Corporate history.
Anybody want to steal anything?
We're getting into some stealing territory now.
What is it called?
Corporate history?
Corporate history.
Nah.
No, not that one, Jacob.
No one wants to steal corporate history.
Yeah.
Corporate history.
Come on.
What year did Walmart start?
1968, 1969, 1970, or 1971.
At least the options are nice and spread out.
So if I know like a rough time that Walmart started, I might be able to guess them.
My question is when will it end?
Am I right?
Talking to you, Boston.
Talking to you, Boston market.
I smell partnership.
I have no idea.
Boston Walmart.
Oh, I can't pass.
I'm not going to use my 50/50 on this.
Boston Walmart.
I guess, you know what?
1969.
Nice.
Yeah.
Come on, Walmart.
Sexiest year ever.
Fuck yeah.
It was.
It's so filthy.
Filthy Walmart.
Oh, now I'm holding onto control.
Actor origins for 1000.
Actor origins?
Anybody stealing?
I'm super stealing.
I want all of your 800 points.
Don't think we're going to get any other right.
That is coming in hot with the super steal.
What country does Cate Blanchett come from?
Australia, the UK, Canada or America?
Australia A.
Australia is correct.
And I don't have any points again.
It's just like the old times.
Oh boy.
Arkansas represent.
$1,200 questions.
Drinks.
Oh, I want nothing to do with it because I know nothing of drink.
Let's see.
Which country consumes the most tea per capita?
The UK, America, Turkey or India?
Well, this is where it gets tricky here, right?
Does it ever.
Per capita.
That's that magic word right there.
Yeah.
Per capita.
Who's got the more capitals?
Right.
So India is too populated.
There's just no matter what the tea is, it's just, it won't add up.
You are spilling some tea on that.
Americans I bet drink way more tea than UK as a whole.
But I don't think, I don't think per capita, right, because then we're.
I think everybody in the UK drinks tea and a lot of people in the States drink tea, but
maybe not everybody.
Actually, I'm just going to say Turkey gets no respect.
I'm going with Turkey.
Yes.
Gobble gobble.
It was Turkey.
It's Turkey.
Look at you.
It's fire.
I'm on fire.
Thanksgiving every day with this motherfucker.
Can't stop, won't stop.
Let's see, '90s music.
Anybody want to steal my amazing amount of points?
Yes, I'm going to, I'm going to steal.
Paul's going to steal.
Do I?
Yeah, I just did regular steal.
What is the most successful one hit wonders from the 1990s?
What is the most successful one hit wonder, wonder maybe from the 1990s?
Baby Got Back, Ice Ice Baby, Macarena, or Mambo number five.
Which is so strange because Mambo number one through four is pretty amazing.
But no respect.
No respect.
This is all of these.
I'm going to, I'm going to go with Baby Got Back.
I'm going to go with my gut.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Macarena.
Hey Macarena.
Aye.
Your guts filled with regurgitated linguine from Olive Garden.
Clearly.
Paul got that wrong and it's back to Matt.
Failure, failure.
$1,600 question.
American history.
Fuck it, I'll steal.
What?
Unless, are you going to double down, Matt?
How far are we?
Oh no, we're not close enough.
Go.
Which state was the last to declare Christmas a legal holiday?
Arkansas, Georgia, Louisiana, Oklahoma.
You know what?
Arkansas is a little slow.
I'm going to say Arkansas.
There we go.
Aye.
It's Oklahoma.
Oklahoma where Christmas we don't give a shit about it.
Where the reindeer come whipping down the plains.
To steal, to try to wrest control away from Matt Donnelly.
That's right.
They've both been unsuccessful.
It's still Matt Donnelly's board with the $2,500 question.
Body science.
You guys can super steal me on body science.
Up to you.
Body science.
Oh, I can super steal body science?
Thanks, Matt.
I'll do it.
What the fuck?
All right.
What is the name of the process by which DNA is copied to produce an RNA molecule?
Translation, replication, transcription or mutation?
I'm going to go with transcription.
Transcription C is correct.
Oh shit.
Who's got the points now?
And with that, you just transcribed my points to yours.
That's right.
You could call me CRISPR because I'm modifying your fucking score.
Boom.
There's three questions left.
Paul is now in the lead with 5,500 points.
Matt and I are tied at zero.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Oh, but you can't super steal me.
$3,000 question.
Philosophy.
I can't super steal.
Matt is stealing.
Which of these ancient philosophers is credited for the allegory of the cave?
Aristotle, Plato, Socrates, or Homer?
E, your mom.
Oh.
That's right.
She is a cave allegory.
Sit down, mom's cave.
Do you call the come in there stalagmites or stalactites?
That's right.
I stalagmite.
I'm gonna 50/50 it, Jacob.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
That got rid of Aristotle and Homer.
Oh, Plato came second?
I think Plato was after Socrates.
Which had the barbershop playset?
That's Plato.
Okay.
That's the one I'm familiar with.
The wacky hairstylist.
Yeah.
Right.
All right.
I'll go Socrates.
Socrates is incorrect.
It was Plato.
Socrates nuts.
Just like that.
Let's see.
Eurasian history for 4,000.
I am going to supersede.
Oh no.
My money.
Eurasian history, my specialty.
I'm always talking about Eurasian history, guys.
You know that.
Well, I mean, every other night you're going to P.F.
Chang's.
Yeah.
Exactly.
The Congress of Berlin in 1878 aimed to resolve which conflict, the Russo-Turkish War, the
Crimean War, the Franco-Prussian War, the Austro-Prussian War.
Well, shit.
I seem to have stepped in it.
I guess I'll use my 50/50.
Yeah, you got this.
You got this.
Oh, well, you got a 50/50.
That's pretty good.
All right.
That got rid of the Crimean War, which is what I was aiming for, so that's good that
you got rid of it.
Look at that.
So you saved yourself.
And the Franco-Prussian War.
You saved yourself.
So it's either the Russo-Turkish War or the Austro-Prussian War.
War huh.
Good God, y'all.
What is it good for?
Absolutely nothing.
Say it again.
Let's see.
I'll say, you know what?
Those Prussians, they were a feisty people.
So I'm going to say the Austro-Prussian War.
Here we go.
Final answer.
Oh, it was the other.
Russo-Turkish War.
And Paul closing out the game physics for $5,000.
We could do nothing about it.
Paul, you could double down.
If I double down, I lose everything though, right?
Paul's doubling down.
Which law of thermodynamics states that in a closed system, entropy increases over time.
First law, second law, third law or fourth law.
I like that you just have to know the laws of thermodynamics to get the answer to this
question.
First law of thermodynamics.
Shoot, this guy used to sing it to me in Olive Garden, now I forget it.
Oh yeah.
That was everybody's favorite.
Well, they fired him.
The first law of thermodynamics song.
Could you bring us a basket of garlic bread and sing the thermodynamics song?
You got it.
You fucking got it.
First law of thermodynamics states that entropy increases over time, but only in closed system.
I'll use my 50-50.
That got rid of first law and fourth law, so it's either the second or third law, Paul.
It feels like third to me.
Oh, does it?
Okay.
Let's see.
So that's what I'm guessing.
Fuck my dick.
It's me.
Shit my butt.
Second law.
Poop my ass.
I think that means that we all missed the question that we used our 50-50 life right on.
But I didn't lose anything.
That is the game, Paul wins, but only with 500 points.
Balls.
You lost 5,000 points.
How did I lose anything?
In a game that goes-
Because you lost 5,000 points.
Bullshit.
In a game that goes from 200 to 5,000, the score is 500 to 0 to 0.
This is-
That's why-
That's from the winter scoop.
Obelisk is a great game.
This is why it could actually work on TV probably.
Yeah.
People only give away 500 bucks.
No, Obelisk is our best, that's our best on-screen game for sure.
They're making a ton of TV right now, so it shouldn't be a problem to pitch this, don't
play.
Yeah.
TV sucks anyway.
No issues there.
Fuck TV.
They're making so much, they're making so much programming.
I don't know if you subscribe to the apps, but a ton of new shows are coming out left
and right.
Thank you for running that Obelisk.
That was a great Obelisk.
Yes.
That was Winter Scoop.
Thank you so much Winter Scoop.
If you want to send us an Obelisk or a jock versus nerd of any kind, head over to HeyScoops.com
right there on the homepage, HeyScoops.com.
Make us an Obelisk.
Make us a Price is Skryte jock versus nerd.
Make us a Scooperty jock versus nerd.
Do all of those things right over there at HeyScoops.com, where you can also, while you're
there, purchase your tickets to Scoop Fest.
Yes.
That's right.
It is coming up here at the end of September in beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada.
It's going to be fantastic.
It's going to be at the Orleans Hotel and Casino.
Get your rooms there.
Stay there.
Just walk right down to the convention space, walk back up to your room when you need something.
It's really convenient, it's really nice, and the Orleans is going to give you a really
nice room discount offer if you just tell them that you're staying there for Scoop Fest.
Or you can use the code, Paul.
What's the code?
S-C-F-I-25...
C?
Yep.
C.
K?
No, no, no, C.
Yeah.
That's right, S-C-F-I-25-C. Head over there.
Get yourself a cheap room at the Orleans.
It will be fantastic.
If you don't have anybody to come with, it's great coming by yourself.
That's right.
If you haven't purchased your ticket and you want to, go to SeeYouAtTheCone.com and purchase
your tickets to Scoop Fest today.
Is that true?
Yep.
That's what I just found out.
Click in the chat.
There.
Cone.com.
SeeYouAtTheCone.com.
Yep.
There it is.
SeeYouAtTheCone.com.
Which is awesome.
You guys are fast on that shit.
All the people that joined us in the chat, if you want to join us in the chat, you need
the link.
If you want the link, you got to go to our Patreon page and support us at any tier you
feel like supporting us at, either yearly or monthly.
Yearly will save you some jingle, and getting on there will save you some jingle.
If you want to go to Scoop Fest, you'll get a discount code that will save you a good
amount of money on your Scoop Fest ticket, and all that can be done at PreachingFun.com.
Or if you got fired for singing at an Olive Garden, even though you didn't work at an
Olive Garden, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com.
It's extra to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month, you can upkeep this
show on the air.
Thank you so much.
We love all of our listeners and supporters out there.
Yes, we do.
At least one of, and maybe two of, our listeners are getting married.
We had some physical Scoop Mail that came in today, and part of the physical Scoop Mail
was a wedding invitation that we got for Macy and Danny, so congrats to Macy and Danny out
there.
When's their wedding?
Their wedding is September.
Oh, it is September the 27th, 2025.
I think we're busy, and it seems like they might not make it to Scoop Fest as well.
Ships in the night.
Unless they're getting married in Vegas.
That's true.
Boy, what a honeymoon.
If you're getting married in Vegas, come right on over to Scoop Fest right after the wedding.
Let's see the details.
They're going to have an open bar, they're going to have a cigar bar, they're going to
wear formal attire, and it's going to be an unplugged ceremony.
That sounds really nice.
I will be there.
Wow, Jacob.
Okay.
What a commitment.
Scoop Fest, and I'm going to go to this wedding.
Brock, we've ever needed you more, buddy.
I hope you're listening.
All right.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you with a cold.
Thanks for joining us in the chat, everyone.
Lovely to see you all.
We appreciate you, bud.
If you have a public restroom that you are in charge of, don't paint the floor so that
it looks wet.
That is off-putting inside of a public restroom.
It's gross.
It's really gross.
See ya!