Hello everybody, right now I'd like to thank all you ice cream truck drivers out there.
Thank you so much to all you ice cream truck drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Jason Klepper, Jeff Harris, Jonathan, Lori Ellsworth, Leon
Kassab, Malia, Paul's brother, and Pyro.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
And now, a program.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
Beautiful day in Las Vegas.
Well I hope it is.
It's a night show.
If I type you here, there's going to be chaos out there though.
It's time for Matt Maddenley's ice cream social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt Maddenley.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Maddenley.
Sitting also in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob.
We're Preaching Fun.
Hey guys.
How's it going, Jacob?
Good, good.
We're doing a little bank show action.
I'm going to be out of town next week, so we're doing a little bank show here.
I saw Sarah Hester Ross's show the other night.
Oh good!
And she makes a joke on her show that she is a Ferrari.
They're both red and like three Italians inside them.
Great.
And there's a guy who's a little into his cups.
First of all, shout out to Sarah Hester Ross for packing the composer's room.
Oh, fuck yeah.
It's a hard room to pack and it was on a Monday night.
It's such a nice room.
It's such a nice spot.
That whole building is such a nice spot.
It's just in a weird area.
Yes, it's in a weird area of town.
I keep being told that that area is about to get revitalized.
I've been being told that area is going to be revitalized any second now for 11 or 12 years.
Yeah, I've been hearing that forever as well.
Now, inside the composer's room is a very affordable bar and affordable food and good bar food and good drinks.
It's a spot that's really kind of angled towards Las Vegas entertainment professionals.
Yeah.
They want entertainment folk to hang out.
Sarah, she wanted me to follow and take some notes kind of thing, like little comedy notes, possible punch up kind of thing.
So I sat in the back and then on the table in front of me.
I don't know if they knew what they were signing up for or whether they were at the composer's showroom and they got like waved in or something.
I don't know what happened, but it's just a hammered guy named Dominic.
When you know the name, when the name comes out.
I can hear it now.
If it's the Dominic that I think it is.
Oh, I think he is either part of the ownership group for the composer's room or the owner.
OK, well, he was shouting after I think he's a big wig.
After she's after he said three times to me, he just started going like I'm Italian.
Hey, hey, as if as if Sarah's or else would have stopped like, oh, you you are everyone.
We should fuck. We should fuck now.
Let's get me right now. Get inside me.
Call to why are you in me? Hurry up.
Call two friends and let's go.
Call two friends.
He'll call two friends. They'll call two friends.
They'll call two friends and they'll call two friends.
And if he was part of the ownership group, then I mean, he seemed like a younger guy.
But at one point, maybe it's not maybe it's a different Dominic Dominic involved in all that, though.
No, no, no. I mean, I think I know who you're talking about.
It was definitely some young Italian guy named Dominic.
Oh, good, good, good. OK.
And he could not stop. It's funnier if it's the odor, though.
He could not stop sharing his thoughts with his table.
It is what's going on. Of course.
Whatever. Yeah. One point.
Sarah Saras. And I'm sure this is an old an old line, but she goes shut your mouth because this one's making money as she points back to her.
Oh, I haven't heard that before. That might be new. I like that.
Shut your mouth because this one's making money.
That was a really good line. Really funny line.
And then, like, you know, she sings like stop giving men microphones.
She sings like really inspiring songs to women.
And it's hard to not take that one a little personally whenever she sings it at our events.
I like she has a point.
Sarah Hester Ross comes to our events and sings stop giving men microphones.
It feels a little like an attack. She has a point.
Not an unfounded attack, but an attack nonetheless.
I know I even had her show in the fringe. I got to be in the chorus singing it in the background of my chorus robe.
I loved it, but he was doing the like drunk magnanimous thing at the end.
Like, no, no, I like her, you know, like she's good, you know, and then waiting for her to come out so he can like pay her the compliment of like even I liked your show.
I thought you were great. Remember me, the one who ruins your show?
You were fantastic. I normally hate people with vaginas, but you're all right.
Scooper Nova Girl in the chat saying bring bring her back this year with Lucy Darling.
She has been teaming up with Lucy Darling, which is the craziest thing for me.
Just just two people from very separate worlds in my life suddenly teaming up and working together out of nowhere.
It's been really cool, but they are their social media fame combined.
They've been doing stuff and Sarah's actually going to go on some of the tours.
I'll just let you know, Scooper Nova Girl. Lucy Darling is out of our range now.
I think so.
We tried to get her in ScoopFest a few years back and she had to cancel the last minute.
She wasn't available.
Not a problem, but now she's playing MGM for two weeks here in town.
She just sold out two nights at a three thousand seat theater in Seattle.
Yeah, she's busy.
If she comes, it will be as a favor and as a friend.
Yes. Yeah.
And therefore can't ask for like a full show kind of thing.
Right.
But I will. It's ScoopFest.
I always I always reach out to people so you never know.
But oh yeah, I'm I'm skeptical.
We'll see. We'll see.
But anyways, yeah.
So Dominic was just really like just into his cups and really letting letting us know that his opinion mattered the most, which was good.
So besides deciding to add more Dominic bits, was there anything else that you came up with?
No, hiring Dominic full time.
My big legal pad just said D-O-M and that's it. I just handed it to her.
All Dom. All day long.
More Dom.
More Dominic as much as possible.
I mean, this is not, you know, I'm not going to actually like, you know, share note stuff, but she has a new bit in her show where she's asking people for their red flags.
A red flag bit. Yeah, we saw that. We've talked about that on the show on her at the what was the Fringe Fest called?
Fallout Fringe.
For her for her show at Fallout Fringe, we saw I think the inaugural.
Yes, that was the first time trying out that bit.
And after she's like, maybe I'll cut that bit.
And I was like, well, don't you dare?
No, no, no, no, no. That is a good bit.
And yeah, we talked about on the other woman who her mom was at the bar getting getting a guy drinks or whatever.
Yes.
And then so she I basically just, you know, it's not a big deal to say, like, move it earlier so that you can talk to them more like she has it later in her show.
And I'm like, no, no, this is you want more of this.
And that way it creates more opportunity for the rest of the show for callbacks and stuff like that.
Yeah.
Girl raised her hand like this bit so good, I want to figure out a way to put it into my magic show and like make it some kind of prediction or something, because having people share red flag stories is great.
It's a great idea.
And woman goes, I goes, secretly had a kid was what she said for like, what's your one sentence for it. And she goes, my guy was dating secretly had a kid.
And then she goes, wait, what happened because I was dating this guy, and he had a woman who had a kid. And then I found out about the other one.
And then so he had two other women with two kids that he wasn't talking about, or being with. And it was the third one that was the deal breaker.
He found out that this person had three kids with three different women that he wasn't acknowledging until later on when they were dating was like, okay, it's time to get out.
Sarah has Sarah's arrest goes, but you did have a kid with him right and she goes, yeah, yeah.
One point for clarification.
Just, just before I go, where's your one more thing.
Holy shit. So this guy's just got it like that.
Yeah, because magic did he have something going on be Christine the chances I think I know that guy.
Sean congratulations.
But, yeah, so I was like just there's there's no end to the red flag bits. It's a great thing to ask. And then of course, in Sarah's show.
She just Sarah quickly notes, by the way, it was only women who raised their hands, I did say anyone had a red flag story but only women stories.
It's possible. I don't know that I would raise my hand and Sarah showed to to tell a red, a red flag story either. Yes, that is a good point. That is a good point. Yeah, yeah.
There might be a little self censoring going on there as well. Look, I mean, there's a lot of women out.
And this is what's cool is it like just Sarah has her audience right like it just it is a mostly women in the crowd and she does rip a lot of dudes and of course all all all all validly.
I would say at least most of it has it coming. Yeah, exactly. So I think it's a fine she's she's lending a fine specific voice through tick tock and now her live show so it's all good when she sings stop giving men microphones and then just plays
actual clips of men talking into microphones saying horrible things it's it's hard to argue. Yes, yeah. And that clip is great. The clips that she's another montage where she talks about not wanting have one.
She doesn't want to have kids.
That one, she has also a montage of like, basically, children being disgusting in a montage that was a little tougher to watch, because it involves like kids pissing and shitting and stuff and you're just like, oh god.
It is definitely a form of birth control the montage she has cut together.
Other people's kids are the best birth control.
Yeah, it's a it's it's a it's a tough one. And one of the lyrics is, it's like keeping come as a pet, and that one's a little strong.
I like that because you because you have your pet come. And you were offended because I had to think about my own children to think about that line and be like oh god.
It is like that.
Kids.
I can't even say it.
Hypothetically, listen here come one and come to
Keeler Hillier, you could just as easily have been remnants on a napkin.
And now, like Pinocchio, you're no longer a napkin fodder. You're real boys.
And you're turning into donkeys for reasons.
And as you went to Paradise Island, as they cry, everybody comes on napkins, as they cry and hug, hug me for that storytelling.
chaotic clumsy with don't open daddy sock drawer all your brothers and sisters are in there.
No, no, no. It's Donnelly's. It's only brothers. He's hung out for a few episodes now. Her favorite specific about men is that they jizz in socks. That is her favorite specific.
chaotic has got a lane.
Don't be surprised that that's it's a fine topic for a Sarah Hester Ross song. So, what can I say I know men.
Socks standing up on their own is a fine Sarah Hester Ross song. It's a stiff lane. Yes, it's not a stiff competition.
Wait, some of these jokes are getting crusty chaotic if you don't mind unmute yourself. I want to I want to ask you a question about this.
If you're that you're worried about it. Imagine what all the things you could ask me in the world. And this is what you've said. I'm excited. That's it. That's it.
Do you remember the first time you found out this fact?
Oh, do you know what I do have this really horrible. It's a funny joke specific now but I imagine the first time you're you must have been like, what?
I don't know how I don't know when I found out this specific fact but I do have a really horrible memory of going home with a man after a date. It's gone really well. It wasn't great, but you know.
I apologized. I apologize. Come on.
I don't know if you want to own up to this. I do remember getting out of the bed, walking across the floor where all of you know messy floor, and I do remember walking across the room and putting my foot down standing on us like a sock or something and it was like calm.
I probably went back for a second date.
Girls get lonely.
So do pieces of shirts and.
So, unfortunately, I don't think they got that lonely that was the problem.
Maybe I just look particularly like a sock.
Sock appeal.
When we brought up any red flag stories did any red flag stories pop in your brain.
Him.
Only bad. I've got so many bad date stories it's unbelievable.
Just, just one of them just one of your favorite bad date stories.
Okay, I'll tell the very short version of this because it's so fresh in my head, because I bumped into them in the gym, which I feel like is a very woman thing to say that a stranger talked to me in the gym.
Right.
And he didn't, he recognized me and I didn't recognize him.
Have you ever approached me to have a random conversation with me in the gym under any circumstance.
Grow boobs, I really recommend it because it really.
No, I have those two it does not work.
Not perky enough.
I understand.
A little bit of height, you'll be fine.
I do lack perk.
Get some tape, get some tape.
I've often said that about Donnelly.
A little wonder bra.
And now I do remember being on a date, and I tried really hard.
And I've got, you know, new clothes and I've done my hair and I've done my makeup and I thought, oh, you know what, I'm killing it today.
I recognize now I look like I own an OnlyFans.
I don't, but I recognize that's how it comes across.
I didn't back then, and I had significantly less confidence.
Okay.
And I went out and he wasn't very chatty, but I'm from North of England, so that doesn't really matter.
And so I had owned most of the conversation, I thought it was going really well, and then at the end of the day, he walked me back and we were walking down the street.
And I thought, I've done really well and so proud of myself.
Nailed it.
And without looking at me, he walked down the road and sort of said, out of nowhere, usually I don't really date women who wear a lot of makeup.
A particularly red lipstick because I, and I recognize that we're, for you guys, this may be a career decision.
But he said, red lipstick, I always think makes them look like a clown.
And unfortunately, I was wearing red lipstick at the time and I've never worn it since I was mortifying.
What?
He was basically trying to confess that he was turned off by your makeup, just your makeup.
I really can't believe that he ghosted me afterwards.
I did bump into him at the gym.
He did say, I am usually a very lovely person.
And you said, you said, you said, smell my flower, then you squirted all over his face.
No, I really wish I'd been that nice.
So a really long story short, I didn't recognize him until he said his name and then somewhat like I had PTSD from being called a clown.
Yeah, well, that'll, yeah, that'll happen.
Which is not my career choice.
I'm changing my name to John Wayne Gacy.
He said, he said, he looked me up and down, which really grossed me out.
And he said, it's a real shame it didn't work out.
And then said something like, this guy is the worst talker.
Wait, wait, wait, one second.
He looked, he physically looked you up and down.
And then his comment was, it's a shame it didn't work out.
It didn't work out?
Yeah, followed by.
Holy fuck.
It's a shame it didn't work out.
And then said something like, I feel like, I feel like I really missed out.
Something, something along those lines.
That's terrible.
To which I, with my blood, the same temperature as lava, looked him up and down and said something like, I think this was a worse scenario for you.
And then I laughed.
Good.
Looked him up and down and said, I'm fine with my existence.
Oh, really?
Age had not been kind, but also, you know, venom, I assume, as it flows through your body does somewhat ruin you.
But he was about 18 at the time.
And I am now 33, and this happened about a month ago.
So I do feel like I should have had, you know, the wisdom on my side.
But unfortunately, that was the kindest thing I could say.
I think that was absolutely fair.
That clarification is interesting because one, the 18-year-old thing, everyone says something stupid things come out of your mouth at 18.
So there you go.
Stupid things come out of my mouth now, every day.
No, I'm talking about him.
So many stupid things went into my mouth when I was 18.
His, I guess I missed out.
That's how I ended up in the sock scenario, Jacob, I'm afraid.
His, I guess I missed out comment at the gym a month ago is idiotic.
He should have better ways of talking to you.
Yes. Well, clearly he hasn't developed that muscle in those winning years.
So, yeah.
And it doesn't sound like he's hyper attractive either, because there's a level that you can be at.
There's a level of attractiveness you can be at and get away with saying stupid things like that.
And it doesn't sound like he's even at that level.
Well, unfortunately, the first thing that came into my head was don't get cocky, kid.
He might laugh and then I'm really stuck in that scenario.
I didn't want to make him laugh.
And you said you missed out and then you and 18 of your friends packed into that tiny car and drove off.
No problem.
What I should have told you is that I've become a party clown.
But I do feel like if I'd stood in the gym and loudly announced that I was for hire, I don't think anyone would have thought I was a clown.
Once again, looking for that page.
Sometimes I consider it, you know, mortgages are expensive, you know.
Sure, me too.
It's 2025. We need that additional income.
I have legitimately thought about photographing my feet.
I think you should, Paul.
Paul, we're talking about ways to make money.
No, I'm going to put clown makeup on him.
So may I recommend bright red lipstick?
OK, there you go.
All right.
Bright red lipstick on my feet dot com.
Well, you're getting a lot of support from the chat here.
That idiot. What a stupid asshole.
That sounds like he was trying to nagging.
Yeah, there you go.
So Gerardo mentions that it sounds like he got tips from one of those bro podcasts.
He could have taken Paul's pickup class.
Yeah, he should have come to my improv class that I taught for the pickup artist kids.
Although I wasn't teaching any pickup stuff.
I was just teaching straight up improv.
Well, that's why I do.
I look like the poster girl for a pickup artist.
I get it. I get it.
I've got piercings, tattoos, long red hair.
I totally get it.
Do you find yourself being approached by peacocking dudes often?
All the time.
Which isn't, believe me, is not a brag.
Sometimes they don't have teeth.
No, it doesn't take a lot to peek.
They just put on a funky hat.
I apologized for speaking to you.
I don't know why you keep bringing it back up.
I keep touching your hair in my defense.
It's, you know, I can't help it.
It's all attention to that.
No, I do.
But unfortunately, I'm also quite the nerd.
So usually when they figure that out, that's also...
What I love is that nerds don't talk to me
because we're too socially awkward.
So the only people that talk to me
are the people you really don't want to talk to.
It's always true. It's always true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why I got a podcast.
Here we go.
Thank you, Matt, for bringing up this traumatic event in my life.
I'm so grateful to relive both the sock and the gym bro.
All right. Well, my pleasure.
You're welcome.
You're welcome so much.
Once again, thank you because you sharing that with our community
has helped some people grow, I'm sure.
Nobody's going to wear red lipstick anymore.
I'm sorry, guys, wear it. It's exciting.
No red lipstick, no socks.
You know who else is going to help me grow?
He could be wrong.
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Manley's Ice Cream Social
is brought to you by...
Where did that page go, guys?
It's the ad page.
I don't know.
I have it.
Hey, guys, today's show is brought to you by Steve.
Piff the Magic Dragon's older brother from Magic Shell Scoop in 2024.
Steve.
Hey there, I'm Steve.
Yes, I'm actually Piff's older brother.
Yeah, I'm the real one though.
Yeah.
Look, I'm not a clone.
Or am I?
Maybe I am.
Maybe I'm not.
You won't know.
What's in that banana?
Oh, look, it's a dollar bill in the banana.
[imitates gunfire]
Where do you think he got all of it?
Every bit.
From me.
Steve.
Originator.
Original creator.
Oh, gee.
Original dragon.
Yes, that's right.
Steve.
I'm the one that came up with it.
Who bought him the first dog?
Me.
It was me.
Yes.
[imitates gunfire]
Explosion.
Enter HeyScoopz at checkout.
Jacob, find KingScoop up there and bring KingScoop on here.
Oh, where's KingScoop?
KingScoop, unmute yourself.
Reveal yourself, KingScoop.
Hello.
Hello, can you hear me?
Yes.
What is your red flag story?
So, went on a first date with somebody.
It was going all right.
We sort of went for drinks about an hour in.
And then suddenly it got very serious as she just started discussing meeting her parents
soon, when we would get married, and how many kids we would have together.
Was inclusive of you, not discussing it as a goal, but talking about it to you.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Basically, I want you to meet my parents soon.
I want to get married soon.
I want to get married.
This is going to go well.
We're going to get married.
We're going to be like three kids, an hour into a first date.
That's a pretty big red flag.
And so how many kids do you have together with her now?
Three.
I think it's funny.
They're all secret kids.
Hide them.
I think that's the reputation when you first start dating as young adults, that women are
looking for the hardcore relationships and blah, blah, blah, and men are worried about
being tied down.
And that's the stereotype of it.
But when you say that story, I don't think about people I've dated as a whole.
But one person comes to mind who was just a friend of my wife's.
You don't think about people you date as wholes?
No, I think of them as socks.
I only think of them as wholes.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, OK.
I was like, what?
OK, yeah.
What's the point?
Just like one person who's just, no matter what, after it, just had a goal of wanting
to wrap it up, settle down, have kids do it.
And every person she dated would just see it from a mile away.
And she'd come over and cry to my wife and just be like, it didn't happen again, and
blah, blah, blah.
It didn't happen again.
I mean, she didn't say those words.
She said that.
But you know what's funny, Matt?
You say that.
And Kingscoop, thank you for the story.
You know what that is?
To put it in a improv context, because I'm getting my brain more and more back into the
old improv zone.
That's that scriptwriting stuff that we try and knock out of folks early on, right?
You enter a scene and you've decided where it's going to go and how it's going to play
out.
And that gives you no room to actually play off of and discover stuff with your partner.
Yeah.
Right.
So if you come in to a relationship and you've already decided how it's going to go, it's
over.
That's not you're not going to have any kind of reciprocal interest because you've decided
you've already got this thing in your head.
So you've got to have a much more open view to even possibly get things cooking.
Wait, Stephen Eames, unmute yourself if you can.
Oh, here we go.
Hey y'all.
So it says in your chat you had an ex that was dead set on getting married and having
kids before her grandma died?
Yeah.
So she, what she wanted, she wanted to give her grandmother, like grandkids, great grandkids,
I guess, or grandkids or at least acceptable grandkids, right?
Yeah.
Moderate grandkids.
Moderately acceptable grandkids.
Yeah.
Thing is she already has a sister that had two kids of her own.
There were already great, great kids out there.
Yeah, I already had them.
She thought she could give greater grandkids.
I guess so.
I thought that she could improve on the situation.
Was she competitive with her sister?
Clearly.
Only when it came to quality of children.
Yeah.
Now, I wouldn't say she was competitive of her, but although the sister did literally
go next door to her mom and dad's house.
So I don't know if there was some kind of weird competition thing going or what the
deal was, but yeah, no, this is also the same one that we had been dating for about a month,
I guess.
And we came back from a trip and picked up some fried chicken on the way back to her
parents' house.
And we're just sitting around the table.
Her mom comes in, starts talking with him.
And stuff, and mind you, this is like, I think this was the first time I'd ever met her mom.
And she along the lines of just says, well, I mean, y'all might as well be married now.
I mean, you're sitting around my table eating fried chicken.
That is almost exactly the conversation that I had with my future mother-in-law the first
time I met her.
Listen, things just operate differently here in the South.
It really does.
That's a fucking fact.
And honestly, you eat somebody's homemade fried chicken, you have made a sacred bond.
That's true.
Oh, no, no.
This wasn't homemade.
This is church's chicken.
I'll grant you.
I'll grant you that.
But again.
Your honor.
I think she was just looking into the future of when she was going to cook you a meal and
it was all going to lock in like that.
I'm not saying this conversation is violently American.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
It absolutely is.
Yeah.
That is just true.
That's true.
But fried chicken in someone's home, that's an intimate thing.
That's an intimate thing because, you know, at least the way I eat fried chicken, I could
very easily lose friends and influence.
My wife wanted to stay with me after seeing me eat fried chicken is also a big hurdle.
Right?
It's a litmus test.
It's an American coupling litmus test.
You don't think when you think the grass is greener on the side or you want to, you know,
get out there and stretch it, you don't think about someone watching you eating something
for the first time and taking that in.
Can they eat fried chicken?
We eat fried chicken with fork and knife.
Bossy, get out of here.
Portuguese.
That's not true.
Is it bone in still?
If it's bone in, you got real problems, Bossy.
Bossy.
You're super talented with that fork and knife.
Yeah.
This is amazing to watch.
Unless you really can just like, like, like all the bones that I completely cleaned at
the end.
Yes, chef.
Watch me cut up this chicken.
The bones actually spell out less.
Yes, chef.
On the plate.
Everybody's done.
Chaotic says I assert dominance by maintaining eye contact while eating fried chicken.
Yeah, I would.
That would be my move.
It's a power move.
Like, people literally lose, like, the New York City mayor's election for being caught
with a fork and knife on a piece of pizza.
Like, if there's just a photo, it's like, it's like it's over.
That has happened.
That has happened numerous times.
I can imagine down south eating fried chicken with a fork and knife might be a deal breaker
for political office.
It might be.
Come on.
Fried chicken with a fork and knife.
Who was it?
Who was the politician a couple of years ago that said Nevada?
Oh, yeah.
They were very, they're very keen on saying Nevada a lot and everybody was just like,
fuck this person.
Can't say Nevada.
They have to say Nevada.
I still remember moving here and being like, oh, come on.
Don't make it such a big deal.
Oh, yeah.
A year later, I was like, Nevada.
Like no.
Just totally switched.
I can't imagine being upset about that.
It's Nevada.
Wait.
So, Steve, was the grandmother in good shape or did you feel like this was like a dire
deadline?
No, grandma was in pretty decent shape, bad manner actually.
It was like, I came home from the hospital and was like, let's make kids.
Let's moan.
No, no.
This, I met grandma like actually, we were returning from the trip to see grandma when
we stopped and got the chicken.
That was apparently my marriage proposal according to her mom.
But yeah, no, she just, yeah.
And yeah, I still ended up dating that girl for about a year.
So yeah, apparently I'm really shitty at picking up red flags.
We all are.
Yeah.
Well, thank you, Steven.
I appreciate you for coming and chiming in.
Yes.
Thanks for sharing.
Yep.
You know who else has some lovely stories about Steven's ex and that's the following
sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Auntie Anne's Ant Coated Pretzels.
That's right.
Auntie Anne's Ant Coated Pretzels from Nesticle Scoop in 2024.
It's time.
Time to get that protein.
Yeah.
You want that protein hit?
You need that straight insect protein brought to you, fresh, hot, and salty by Auntie Anne's.
All we do is open up the back door in the mall, let the critters come in and stick them
inside the pretzels.
Once they reach a certain temperature, they're basically clean.
That's the first thing you need to know.
Like a pasteurized ant?
Pasteurized ants.
Yes.
I'm here from the health department.
I'm here to just do some little quality control on the ants here.
I understand that you have ants in this restaurant.
Yes.
I just wanted to come check them out.
We cook them directly into the pretzel.
Oh.
Oh, you cook them?
Of course.
Also, after you cook them, they're basically clean.
Right.
Once they reach a certain temperature, they're basically clean.
I was worried that they weren't getting cooked, so they wouldn't be basically clean.
What kind of a mall pretzel stand do you take us for, Inspector?
I apologize.
Oh, but seriously, you've got to try some of these ant-filled pretzels.
Not only are they crunchier, but they are filled to brim with protein.
Did you know?
Oh, well, let me try one.
Go ahead.
Have some.
Let's see.
I don't know.
What?
What is that?
They're biting.
They're eating me from the inside.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, whoops.
The ants are eating me from the inside.
So sorry.
There's one of them that wasn't cooked, so those ants weren't clean.
Also they were fire ants and cannibalistic.
Sorry.
I'm dead.
Oh.
Enter Hague Scoops to check out.
Auntie Anne's.
Oh, Auntie Anne's.
Are there any?
Are they even worried about airports now?
I don't.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm sure there's a couple of mall spots.
There's a couple of malls still around.
We have a Grandma Anne's Nut Breads out here by our wall.
Slower.
I'm telling you.
What?
Grandma Anne's Nut Breads.
And every time we drive by Anne's like, "We should go to Grandma Anne's Nut Breads."
I think she's been once.
I agree.
We should.
But it's one of those like definitely like a small entrepreneurial thing and only open
at certain hours and got her regular customers and just doing her thing.
So.
Yeah.
I think he's on like a walk or a bike.
I think he's on a bike.
And like, it's funny because when we make our podcasts, I picture people like listening
to us while they're walking or driving or whatever.
But it's weird to see it in action.
It's weird to see it actually happening.
Oh, yeah.
There he is.
Danny just on a bike ride doing his thing.
It's fantastic.
Yeah.
Just having a good time.
Love it.
Speaking of nut bread.
I just hope we don't see like a bird fly like right into his face or something and he has
to like fend off a bird attacked by an albatross.
Galactic president says nut bread.
I thought socks were bad.
This bread is rather stiff.
Yeah.
I mean, it's very absorbent.
That's the weird thing.
Everyone's in there ordering nut bread and they're all skipping the joke and skipping
the thing in their head, right?
They're all like just like, yeah, just like I can't make a jizz joke, but I do want to
try this bread.
I don't even think.
I would like some banana nut bread.
I don't think that enters the mind of the person that goes to Auntie Anne's banana nut
bread.
It's not even banana, it's just nut breads.
All kinds of nut breads.
Oh, B. Christine also made the same joke at the same time.
I want to give credit to B. Christine and galactic president for making the nut bread
versus socks joke.
We did it.
Nut bread versus socks coming to a theater near you in 2026.
Hey nut bread.
Hey socks.
What are you doing today?
Well, I got to say socks, I went to a bar the other day and there was a horse tending
bar.
Oh yeah.
What do you think I should have said to him?
Hey buddy, why the long face?
That's exactly right.
There you go.
That's what makes them the comedy team of legend right there.
Nut bread and socks are actually good.
They actually know their shit.
If you can't make them laugh, get an attaboy.
Get an attaboy out of them.
You know, they finish each other's words, drinks, drinks, hot dog bun has entered the
chat.
Quick reminder, I'm going to be in Mesa, Arizona, July 31st, August 1st and August 2nd.
If you can't find the ticket link, because I guess it is hard to find, it's in my Instagram
links.
So if you go to my Instagram page, check my links.
You can buy tickets for that.
I'm there three nights, three nights only.
It is a Mystique venue, but it's not a dinner venue.
It's just a fancy theater.
So it's just my show.
Oh, nice.
Coming out for my show in and out, as they say.
So come out and check that out.
Give them the old in and out.
Yeah.
Oh, and hey, if you're broke, wait, Matt, what is your Insta?
My noodler, my new at my noodler over at over at the Instagram's mind.
Noodle are my noodle noodle are.
If you're broke and you're in the Pittsburgh area and you want to come take a free class
with me, that's right on Monday, the 28th, come and do it seven o'clock till nine p.m.
It's happening at duty podcast studio, look up a duty dot com pod dot com.
Scroll down just a little bit.
I'm the first little page there.
See my bright smiling face.
Click on the link, sign up for the free class and come on out.
We had a scoop come out last time was amazing that they made a long journey halfway across
the state to come and take a class with me.
It was fantastic.
Had nine students.
They were really, really great.
So please come on out.
I'm still knocking the ring rust off my improv teaching again.
And I'd love to see some more scoops in the house.
So please come on by.
I've only got a few more of these free classes that I'll be doing before I'm actually teaching
professionally again with skit.
Nice.
What?
What if I don't have anything to plug?
What if you aren't broke?
Paul, can you still take the class?
You can.
Not only can you take the class, but the fact that it's free, you can then kind of just
do the math in your head and go, Oh, I should give Paul the pretend money that I was going
to spend that I would have spent on this cloud.
I'll just give smart, smart money.
That'll work.
And it really will work.
It will absolutely work.
And I will accept any tips.
Even a dollar is fine.
Yeah.
Uh, Paul, and since you're not getting paid, you will be accepting just the tips, brother
right in the nut bread.
Oh, this nut bread can stand up on its own.
Steven Eames is asking you to define ring rust, please.
Uh, so that's a wrestling term for guys who haven't wrestled in a while.
They have a rust, but it could also be, that man's done could also could also be a twink
out of the game a little long, you know, okay, this great bit of minutes since I had my spinner
game down, I need to people's snacks and particles free.
I don't know.
I know what beef is.
I have had beef experience.
I know beef, beef, curtains, uh, ring rust is why you use a muffler.
That is great.
Be correct.
Be Christine.
Uh, yes.
Uh, yes, I will accept just the tip into my rusty ring.
As long as, as long as it's us legal tender, let's go, uh, whatever you got to, whatever
you got to do.
If it's us legal tender and a flared base, let's dance.
I'm sticking up my ass.
We got to get you a bidet.
You ain't kidding.
Country scoop.
I am still, I am still Jones in for that Japanese toilet.
One of these days when I make Japanese toilet money, I'm telling you, buddy, I do.
You have one now.
I have, why?
No, I don't have the full on Japanese toilet.
I don't have the expensive Japanese toilet.
I just have the, uh, the bolt on the bolt on bidet thing that goes on the bolt on bidet
thing.
Okay.
Let real time is great.
We'll talk.
What'd you spend for your bolt on bidet thing?
If you don't mind me.
Oh, probably like 150 bucks.
Okay.
So the one I got was like 25.
So I should probably spend a little more definitely tried to spend a little more plus also cause
it was, is yours heated?
Yeah.
Mine.
Mine has a, you have to have electric electricity for it.
Right.
Yeah.
Mine was going to just squirt straight, icy tank water up your Hinder.
So which I've done those two.
Those aren't bad.
No, no.
I still think that's better than just regular toilet.
That's better than just wiping your ass with dry ass toilet paper.
Tank water up your Hinder.
Was that Dean Martin or Frank Sinatra?
I forget.
Oh, that was Dino.
That was Dino.
Yeah.
Um, go ahead and just relax that asshole.
It's time for me to come on in.
Tank water up your Hinder.
Hey, that's what's been this martini glass of mine the whole time.
Jacob, what about mail from listeners who haven't joined us?
Do we have any scoop mail?
Let's do a little scoop mail.
I had to find it on my screen.
Oh, let's see.
Oh, we got one here from a Hatchet Scoop.
Uh, oh, this is a long one.
Uh, Hatchet Scoop says I was hesitant to write about this because I couldn't find something
to add that I thought might be entertaining or funny.
But you mentioned that you also want to hear sad stuff from people as well.
But I have lots of sad to share.
So here we go.
All right.
Near the end of 2024, I began to hate a job that I loved originally due to many changes
in upper corporate.
I worked in retail as a meat cutter, which was great, but the company was becoming more
and more hostile towards us and was making it clear that they didn't really want us to
exist.
So they were making our lives more and more difficult between that and the almost our
community.
I decided to quit and take a warehouse job that was much harder work with less benefits
and paid less.
But it was seven minutes away from home and the work was actually pretty enjoyable, despite
the difficulty.
This job was short lived, sadly, after a couple of months, the work was mostly gone as the
company we were working for decided to hire their own warehouse workers instead of using
the third party company that I worked for.
This was around Christmas and with no work being given to us, I decided to just quit.
This was also motivated by several unexplained health issues that I was having.
So I figured it would take some time to figure out why I was feeling so ill and look for
a new job after the New Year's.
Well, New Year's arrived, I have several doctor's appointments after several scans and a lot
of prodding.
They sent me to a GI doctor who ran a camera in both ends of me.
As I awakened from being put under, I see my wife in the hospital room with me, which even
in my groggy state makes me anxious because she wouldn't be here if everything was fine.
Everything wasn't, in fact, fine.
The examination found fairly advanced cancer.
I am a little under 40 and all the tests that they did up to this point pointed towards
it not being cancer.
All the doctors repeatedly told me that they didn't see any signs of cancer, but here
I am half dazed with my devastated wife being told that they were all wrong and that is
what is making me so sick.
After many more doctor visits and examinations, they discovered that it's in stage 3 and
will need many months of radiation and chemo followed by surgery.
I'm not angry with the doctors, but this was a gut punch to hear.
Now unable to work because the only skills I have are in physical labor, which I am now
too sick to do, excuse me, I find myself at home a lot with far too much time to think.
I am worried about myself, of course, but also scared for my partners.
My wife has a good job, but is now responsible for all of the bills.
Because of this, I end up cancelling my Patreon, sorry guys, no, don't apologize to us.
I was sympathetic up until this point, now I'm furious.
We'll be ending this email immediately, thank you very much for your past support.
Jacob, please show that letter to the shredder please.
Michael Kennedy, cancer is no excuse to not tithe to the boys.
Agree.
No, no, no, get a little less chemo, that won't kill you.
Of course.
Oh shit, it might.
Of course we're just kidding, but if you can let your wife know about her Patreon.
I'm joking, I'm joking.
You said she still has a gig, right, yeah, yeah, that'd be great.
All this is because we're joking comfortably for what is a horrible situation, so I'm very
sorry that you are, I mean that's things like the health diagnosis is awful enough and the
dominoes it pushes, I mean we think about this all the time and in our country, in America,
they say like that most people are just one major medical emergency away from bankruptcy.
If not for Ann having a good job with incredible insurance and even then, you know, coming
through with a chunk of change to make my operation feasible, I would be dead possibly
by now because the kind of pain I was in a couple, like a year and a half ago, was unsustainable
and I will say for all the awful of that experience, I have gained so much more empathy, insight
and understanding into the plight of folks who have any kind of physical disability.
I'm grateful for it in a sense, it has made me a more grateful person for my day to day
moving around.
Oh yeah, well keep going with the letter.
Okay, well I also have two girlfriends who are equally terrified for me as my wife.
One of my girlfriends also has three kids who I have known since before they were born
and their ages are from 4 to 13, so explain to them what is wrong with me, that's hard
on them as well.
My girlfriends have also had to watch people they love already die from cancer, one her
father and the other a boyfriend, so now all of that old trauma is coming up as well.
Oh and the girlfriend whose boyfriend died also found out at almost the same time that
I was diagnosed with cancer, one of her oldest friends was as well.
So now we are going through treatment at the same time, which is weird, sorry to be such
downer but this year has just been a kick in the teeth, we'll try to write again with
something more entertaining soon, as I have said I have several partners and my life is
rather strange so maybe I'll write in about bondage or kink, oh that reminds me I was
playing with fire on my girlfriend once and the torch got a little too close to my face
and set my beard on fire, not terribly and I tried to act like nothing happened but it's
really hard to ignore the smell of burning hair, oh just imagine you're in like sexy
fun times with your partner and you accidentally set yourself on fire, you put it out real
fast nobody's hurt but you're just trying to pretend like nothing happened so you can
keep on going with sexy fun times.
That's great, that's tough and you got to fight that smell too.
Yeah, anyway thanks for listening, hope things are well for you and all the other scoops
out there and as always fucking you in the face with my now irradiated dick, that is Hatchet
Scoop.
Hatchet Scoop.
Thank you Hatchet Scoop.
Speedy recovery, keep your attitude positive, as positive as you can and we're thinking
about you man.
So yeah.
No, I mean you bring up like even like you said like I'll write in something interesting,
I mean the truth is when we hear about people in polyamorous relationships or however you
would qualify yours, we don't think about the serious stuff so actually what you are
writing is something kind of fascinating which is like most people don't think about what
that means like yeah you're in more people's lives and so when bad news happens it pushes
all kinds of dominoes that you didn't anticipate, that someone in a more traditional relationships
would anticipate rather and so that is tougher and it is different but also offers a different
network of support which is also intriguing as well and really a bigger prover right like
it's like I think people in heteronormative relationships could be skeptical of these types
of things, it could be skeptical of the legitimacy of polyamorous relationships right and so you
are showing that these are indeed as equally fulfilling relationships as anyone could ever
have before by having this network of support.
If not more so, if not more important and smart as far as having a redundant system
of support.
It is, that's it I'm going to tell my wife I need a redundant system of support right
now.
Hold on.
I'm sure she'll buy it, no but really I mean there is something to be said for the fact
that you guys are going to keep calling it right now.
No but really like you know if something happens to one of us heaven forbid something happens
to both partners at the same time.
Oh sure, then there you go.
I mean I don't even know what would happen like if I lost one of my partners and then
I lost the other partner and then the third one just left oh no that's bad, that's a bad
day.
Yeah that's low.
Is that your polymathery is that what that is?
That's polymathery yeah.
Alright.
It's also going to be the name of my assistant in my magic career.
Polymathery.
She's going to do magic squares and all it's going to be great.
Let's do a little hatchet scoop thank you so much for writing in.
We always we honestly we love hearing even the serious sides from our scoops that are
out there.
We just love hearing from you all so much and we love when you include us in your lives
like that and give us a little peek into your real life like that.
It's touching and kind of moving as well so thank you so much for that hatchet scoop.
Yeah thanks for writing us for real.
Gerardo says can I get a couple of boyfriends and girlfriends from here not to do anything
sweat house but just to take the world's stubbornest toddler to bed.
I can cook.
If you're offering to cut people's fried chicken for them I'm sure you're going to get a lot
of boyfriends and girlfriends.
Would you stop with that cutting fried chicken mess?
Who are you even?
Who are these monster people?
Oh wait that was Bossy I was Bossy I'm mixing up my Latin named scoops in the chat.
What a bigot I am what a bigot.
We got a scooper coming at us today from Afro Scoop.
The categories are Vegas, parking and weather.
Hold on I'm trying to get you guys the screen at the same time that I'm talking and it's
not working well.
Vegas, parking and weather, driver trivia, team radio and interviews.
I like how that Vegas, parking and weather bubble became big enough to hold the whole
thing.
Yeah it kind of stretched itself out didn't it?
That's kind of cool.
I'll do Vegas, parking and weather for 200.
On what prominent Las Vegas strip properties parking lot was an F1 Grand Prix held between
1981 and 1984?
No options on this one.
Okay.
Strip properties parking lot, 81 to 84, it could be the MGM, it could be where they end
up putting the wet and wild, I don't know I'm going to pass though, Paul.
I feel like Flamingo or Caesars.
Okay.
But I don't know, I'll pass.
What happened?
Oh!
Somebody's not muted.
Somebody's not muted and it was really kind of kinky sounding.
It was interesting.
Yeah it was nice.
So are you passing Paul?
I am passing.
Matt?
Oh, I will do, I'll do Caesars.
Alright.
Caesars Palace.
Nice.
Bold.
Well done.
I should have guessed it.
I will take Team Radio.
For 200.
Oh!
There's a link in this question.
While in his car which was being pushed by mechanics to the Weybridge at the 2017 Azerbaijan
Grand Prix, what did Kimi Raekkonen demand?
An ice cream, his gloves, the steering wheel or Boa?
Boa?
Boa, I don't know.
I will guess an ice cream.
This question is a car wreck, it doesn't fit in the format, something's going on.
Yeah, I don't know, it was a steering wheel, he wanted a steering wheel.
Okay.
Yeah.
Matt?
I will do interviews for 200 please.
What were Ozzy Osbourne's dogs doing at home when he was interviewed on the grid by F1
presenter Martin Brundle?
Were they pissing, shitting, fucking or having makeovers with Sharon?
Well, I have a feeling if they were shitting we would know about it universally, so I'm
going to rule that one out.
Okay.
I'm also just going to make a quick note, don't include YouTube links in your scooperty
questions.
Yeah, we're not going to watch them.
We're not going to take the time to watch them.
I'm going to do having makeovers with Sharon.
Let's try it.
Nope, it was shitting.
And yet I haven't heard about it.
I have terrible friends, I should have known about this.
I still haven't watched the last Ozzy concert from a couple weeks ago, I'm still excited
to watch that.
That looks like it was an incredible event.
Yeah, I want to watch the whole fucking thing, I want to watch all the intro bands, there
are a lot of bands on the docket there that I really like a lot.
I can't wait to watch that.
Oh, let's see, I will try driver trivia for 200.
What unfortunate translation does Nicky Lotta's last name have in Hindi, boobs, ass, vagina
or penis?
Let's see.
I would like to stick my penis between your Lottas, I would like to stick my penis in
your Lottas, I would like for you to put your Lottas in my Lottas.
Get the ring rust off that Lottas.
Yeah.
I'm going to say vagina, I'm going to say C vagina.
No, it's the penis.
Oh, Nicky penis.
D penis.
Paul.
I will take interviews.
I took my dog to the vet.
For 400.
And I got him to penis.
That's just rude.
It's a Daily Double.
Yeah, here we go.
Victory is at hand.
At the 2006 Brazilian Grand Prix, what did Kimi Rakanon tell Martin Brundle he was doing
when he missed Pele's presentation?
Was he having an ice cream, looking for his gloves and steering wheel, I still don't know
what that means.
Maybe, I don't know.
Or having a shit.
Having a shit.
D having a shit is correct.
Alright.
He was having a shit.
Alright, this is Martin Brundle likes his shitty stuff.
I will do Vegas parking weather, 400 please.
Since 2022, the first Grand Prix in the United States every season is held on the parking
lot of which Southern football team's parking lot.
No option on this one either.
Since 2022, this is Vegas parking weather, so is it the Raiders?
It's the Southern football team, so I don't see why this is Vegas parking weather.
I'm confused and I'm passing, Jacob.
Passes to me.
I think there's one in Houston.
I'm going to say Houston.
Miami.
Miami Dolphins.
Oh, Southern Bell, Miami.
That's right.
I mean, they are technically, definitely Southern.
About as South as you can get.
Let's see, I'll try Vegas parking weather for 600.
During the first run of the Las Vegas Grand Prix in the 80s, what weather conditions caused
significant problems for the teams?
It was raining men.
They wrote a whole song about it.
I bet it was rain.
The windshields just could not handle it though.
They were cracking.
It was everywhere.
Yeah.
I'll try rain.
Oh no, extreme heat.
Oh, what do you know?
In Vegas?
Odd.
Yeah.
Country Scoop notes that "boah" is a Finnish accent and pronunciation of the word "yea,"
often associated with Kimi Rkonen for his stoic personality.
Okay.
Well, there you go.
All right.
Paul.
I will try Team Radio for 400 again.
When Sebastian Vettel was hit from behind by Daniel Ricciardo ... Sorry.
When Sebastian Vettel was hit from behind by Daniel Ricciardo, he exclaimed, "What are
you doing here, racing or blank, NASCAR, WIFWAF, bumper cars, or ping pong?"
Also, I really like WIFWAF.
Yeah.
That's a fun phrase.
When I said WIFWAF, I thought I had mispronounced it and then looked back at it.
I was like, "Nope.
That's just how that's spelled, WIFWAF."
Is WIFWAF an actual thing?
It could be.
I don't know.
It could be a mispronunciation of riff raff.
Oh man, I really like him throwing NASCAR under the bus.
Oh yeah.
Oh, F1 people go after NASCAR.
Yeah.
It's great every time.
I think I'm going to go with A, NASCAR.
Let's try NASCAR.
Nope.
I'm sorry.
It's ping pong.
Oh.
Ping pong.
Would have also accepted WIFWAF, which of course, as we know, was the original name
for ping pong.
Did you guys see the new Godzilla movie?
No.
Oh wait.
Is that Godzilla minus one?
No, no, no.
The one with King Kong where he plays ping pong in Hong Kong with his ding dong.
No.
I did see that one.
Yeah.
I thought it was played WIFWAF with his half-staff in a spacecraft.
There it is.
Matt.
Oh, Godzilla in that stiff ass sock.
Gosh, I know so much about this topic that's in all four categories.
Yeah, yeah.
We're doing great at this.
Let's do Vegas.
By the way, Matt is leading with zero points.
But for long, let's do Vegas, parking and weather.
During the current run of the Las Vegas Grand Prix beginning in 2023, what weather conditions
have caused significant problems for the teams?
Tornado warning, extreme heat, extreme cold, or flash flooding?
I'm going to go with flash flooding.
Okay.
The first season, I remember they had cold problems.
Yeah.
Let's see here, I can get it.
Oh, extreme cold because someone decided it would be a good idea to hold the race at three
a.m. local time to cater to the European audience.
That was 10 p.m. local time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wasn't that ridiculous.
It was ridiculous, but not that ridiculous.
But it was enough to get it wrong and I joined the ranks with negative scores here in our
Grand Prix.
There we go.
Now Paul is in the lead with a negative 200.
This Grand Prix is now racing backwards.
The Grand Prix.
Let's see, I'll try interviews, 600.
I guess it doesn't matter.
Sneak bonus should be a question because I couldn't find another good interview moment.
Which country has the highest number of F1 drivers champions compared to its population?
Oh, so we're looking for the country with most F1 driver champions per capita.
Yes.
New Zealand, France, Finland or Great Britain.
Okay.
Let's see.
I mean, it's got to be New Zealand.
Or Finland.
There's like eight people that live in New Zealand if one of them ever won anything.
Oh boy.
Finland.
Same argument for Finland.
I'm going to New Zealand.
Hey.
That was Finland.
Oh.
Finland, Finland, Finland.
Paul even gave you a Paul clue.
The country where I like to race.
The country where I like to Grand Prix.
I will go team radio again.
Why not?
In the 2013 Malaysian Grand Prix, what code did the Red Bull team give Sebastian Vettel
to signal that he shouldn't pass his teammate, Mark Webber, a signal which he ignored going
on to make the pass later on for his team?
Probably.
Yeah.
So what was the signal, Paul?
Yellow flag.
I don't know.
Let's try it.
I'll.
Multi-map to one.
Oh, I guess there were answers that got cut off too.
Okay.
Oh, oh, oh, great.
So there were.
Yeah.
There were multiple choice answers.
It got cut off.
Oh, you know, Paul just pulled it on.
That should have been easier, Paul.
A little whiff whaff formattingly on that one.
I'll take it.
I'll take a whiff whaff right on the chin.
You know, even though it feels like the scooper is taking decades, we did get whiff whaff out
of it.
And so.
Yeah.
It's still a win.
It's still a win for the show.
We're batting a thousand.
It's absolutely a win.
And people are watching, so who cares?
Other people are suffering with us.
They have equally confused looks on their face as we do.
Let's just let's just keep answering shit every time.
Matt, you're up.
What are the scores, Jacob?
I don't know what I'm chasing here.
Oh, let's see here.
Oh, good news, Matt.
You and Paul are tied for the lead at negative 800.
I'm right behind you, though.
Negative 1800.
Okay.
It's anyone's game.
Creepin'.
As we head to the final lap, I will take driver trivia for 400 since I don't know anything
about anyone.
Which of these totally real names belongs to a current F1 driver?
Scott Speed, Will Power, Lando Norris, or Stingray Robb?
C, Lando Norris.
Lando Norris is correct.
Scott Speed is an ex-F1 driver, while Willie Pete and Stingray are IndyCar drivers.
Hat tip goes to the greatest name in all motorsports, NASCAR's own Dick Trickle.
One hundred percent correct.
Yeah.
Yes.
It's me.
I'll try.
Well, let's see.
What do I need?
I need all the points.
Driver trivia, 800.
What surname does a prominent scoop who is often mentioned and even has guested on ICS
a few times share with the former F1 driver with the first name Antonio and nickname Italian
Jesus?
Italian should be clue enough.
A prominent scoop.
What name does he share?
That's got to be Scoop Jesus.
I think we'll just go Scoop Jesus.
That'll be it.
I don't fucking know.
I'll pass.
Paul.
I don't know.
Matt.
I'm trying to think of Italian names.
I mean, Sloanina comes on a lot, but I wouldn't know if you count it as a prominent scoop.
Giovinazzi sounds Italian, but it's Australian.
Right.
Ah.
I don't know.
I'll pass.
Let's see.
Well, I'm not doing well.
Oh my God.
Giovinazzi.
It was Giovinazzi.
Oh, look at that.
Apparently there were multiple choice questions on that as well.
Paul.
You know, if you don't put YouTube links in the question, it leaves plenty of room for
the other parts.
It does.
I will try interviews.
What the hell?
Why not?
Daily double.
There we go.
Yeah.
Gentlemen, a short view back to the past.
30 years ago, Nicky Laura told us take a place, take a comma place him into the cockpit and
he is able to drive the car.
30 years later, Sebastian told us quote, I had, and then there's the letter T and then
the rest of it is cut off.
Paul, what do you believe is the answer to this daily double question?
I'm going to say monkey.
Let's try it.
It's monkey.
Amazing.
Yeah.
How is it monkey?
How the hell?
Where did that question go?
Because contextual clues.
Take a blank, place him into the cockpit and he's able to drive the car.
He's clearly describing the ease of some vehicle or something like that.
Paul wrote this scooper day is what happened.
I did not write this scooper day, but when in doubt, guess monkey is right.
By the way, the chat is letting me know apologies, Jimmy Slonina for calling him not a prominent
scoop.
I misspoke.
What I meant to say is that he was such a, he's more of a guest and friend than a scoop
in my brain.
I also just say this is obviously no matter what, even with the apology, this is the worst
thing to happen to Jimmy Slonina this month.
So there you go.
Matt, you got driver trivia or team radio.
You're only 400 points behind Paul, buddy.
Oh man.
I'll go with a driver trivia.
For 600, Fernando Alonzo is the most experienced F1 driver on record with a career spanning
20 years between 2003 and 2025, including a two year hiatus, give or take two.
How many drivers in the 25 season were born after the start of his career?
Oh man.
I still think a monkey is a viable answer, man.
Two shitting monkeys.
Ah ha ha.
Oh God damn.
I don't fucking know.
Pass.
Let's see.
That passes to me.
12, 12 is the answer.
Good guess.
Five.
Pretty good.
Pretty close, Jacob.
Horseshoes and hand grenades.
I'm closing out the category and thankfully the game team radio for 800.
In a period when team orders, the team telling teammates to swap positions or not race each
other were banned, what super secret coded message did the Ferrari team give Felipe Massa
during the 2010 and then the question gets cut off?
They told him, they told him don't shit on the monkey.
It makes him mad.
It's a monkey.
Shit some monkey.
Let's see here.
Okay.
So Fernando is faster than you.
Can you confirm you understood that message?
It looks like I got that one wrong.
Yeah, that was D.
By the way, if we had seen questions, if we'd seen possible answers, that was the D answer.
Okay.
And that was from Afro Scoop, Paul wins with zero.
I don't care.
That was fucking great.
That's insane with negative 400.
I'm in third with negative 3,200.
Thank you so much Afro Scoop for sending that in.
HeyScoops.com, that's where you can go.
Send us some scoop mail, send us some scooperies, send us the jock vs nerds, send us everything
over there.
Right at HeyScoops.com.
What else can you do over there?
I'll tell you what you can do over there.
You can buy some tickets to Scoop Fest.
That's what you can do.
We got some whiff whiff out of that and we got Paul just saying the word monkey and getting
it correct out of fucking nowhere.
So it's a pretty...
Yeah.
Two shitting monkeys.
And a partridge in a pear tree.
Monkey!
ScoopFest.com has the tickets there, go there and check it out.
Yes!
We have some really fun surprises for you guys.
Trivia battles are going to be awesome.
Jock vs nerd ball, mouth, finger, butthole, it's going to be great.
So get on out to ScoopFest last weekend of September, September 25th through the 27th.
I'm telling you right now, it is close enough that I am starting to panic.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's close enough that I'm starting to send out travel funds for our guests.
Yes!
Oh yeah.
Celebrity guests, we got celebrity guests, we got lovely swag.
Just get on board.
Come join the fun.
Get that scooperty that we just played again and we're going to see how much better we
do.
Yeah, yeah.
I think the scores would probably stay close to the same.
We're going to play that same scooperty, but we're also going to play every YouTube clip
also.
So that'll be good.
I want to thank all the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
Absolutely.
I have a specific list even.
You guys are going to love it.
Oh, this list.
No one's ever done a better list.
All right, I want to thank the following people who all blew out their monkey's asshole with
an overpowered bidet they bought aftermarket.
Peter Burford, Peter Hines, Peter McDougal, Peter Sansone, Petty Officer Scoop, Phil Rendley,
Phil Tomlinson, Philip Guyden, Pick It Up, Pick It Up, Pick It Up, Proper Scoop, Proto
Scoop, Pyro, Quiet Quiet Scoop, Rachel Forrester, Radioactive Scoop, Raggedy Girl, Raph Barrett,
Randy, and Randy Glenn.
Big thanks to these people who are two shitting monkeys, Ron Heck, Rose, Roy Stansbury, Ryan
Gravel, Ryan Hayward, Ryan Moore, Ryar Appledorn, Second Mingle, Saltlick Scoop, Saltlick Scoop
again, Sam Reed, Sanja Petrovic, Sarah Boyle, Sarah Congdon, Sax Guy Jimmy Dee, Sax Guy
Jimmy Dee, Scoop, Scabby the Rat Scoop, Scoop Brady, Scoop Brady again, Scoop Bucky, Scoop
Bucky again, Scoop Chang the Beijing Bugle, Scoop Dave Hill, Scoop Emily, and Scoop It
Real Good.
Some of those that are on here twice, I didn't read them twice, I think there's something
happened in the extraction of the list.
They're doubled up a lot on mine too.
I just say one of them.
Yeah, yeah.
I like saying twice.
I don't know if it's extraction or if it's just my part.
I think it's like a lucky thing.
Rub it in, buddy.
I think it's a lucky thing.
It's a lucky thing.
Paul, you do whatever you want.
Of course.
Yeah.
I wasn't telling you to do whatever you want.
I was making a statement.
I think the following people whose grandmothers are demanding grandchildren and they want
to watch the making of those grandchildren, Raymond Nortada, Rebecca Boonstra, Rebecca
Gardner, Refrigerator Perry Scoop, Remember the Alamode, Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church
of the Flying Spaghetti Monster, Richard Dunn, Richard Fastnot, Richard Graffiti, Richard
Hill, Robert Paulson, Robert Ward.
I almost said wad, whiff whaff, what a whiff whaff, that's a whiff whaff.
Robots Ahoy, Rodimus Scoop, and Roger Edge.
I want to thank the following people whose super secret F1 code is just the tip in the
ring rust.
Scoop Emily, Scoop it real good, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Jesus, Scoop Lindsay, Scoop Lord Tristan,
Scoop Mipha, Scoop Nurse, Scoop Nurse again, see, Scoop of Saltwater, Scoop Skywalker,
Scoop T, Scoopaholic, Scoopa Troopa, Scoop Paul's Drag Race, Scoop Paul's Drag Race again,
Scooped Mids, and Scooped Mids again.
And the following scoops also don't remember anything that we talked about before.
That's Scooperty, that's Scoop-a-Luga, Scooper Metroid, Scooper Nova Girl, Scoopia Lauren,
Scoopiter Ascending, Scoop JD, Scoop Kada, Scoop Knack Pattywhack, Scoop Lockeesa, Scoop
Neon Black, Scoop Nick, Scoop-a-Metrix, Scoopahazard, Scoop Trek the Experience, Scoopy and the
Beast, Scoopy Dooby Doo, Scoopy Ramone, Scoopy Bartfast, Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess, Scott A,
Scott Andrews, Scott Ashlock, Scott Headington, Scott Muldrig, Scott Schofield, Sean Kellner,
Seanathan P., Subbaskin Robbins, SF, Sean, Shoeless Scoop, Silicone Scoop, Silver Fist
Scoop, and Sir Scoopy McScooperson III, Esquire.
Thank you all so much!
I love you all.
Thank you all so much.
Hey, if you want to be thanked on air, if you didn't have a beard before Scooperty and
you have one now, head on over and support us over at PreachingFun.com.
Or, if you, like me, have socks that can stand up on their own, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz.
That, along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you to our Patreon page, where for as little
as $2 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Head on over there, if you think this show is worth more than $0, fartsinabag.biz, PreachingFun.com.
Yeah, it just helps pay all these expenses that we have, and boy, there are a few of
them.
So come on over, fartsinabag.biz, PreachingFun.com.
A few of them are coming due September 26th and 27th.
They sure are!
But anyways, yes, all you guys supporting us month after month, year after year, it
means so much to us.
We really appreciate it.
It makes everything we do possible.
And we have the most awesome community in the world, and so getting to do events, it
really helps cement our awesome community.
All right, that's it.
We did it.
Episode wrapped.
Stay safe out there.
We love you.
And we'll see you soon!
We'll see you soon!
They don't say he's the best in the business for nothing, folks.
They just don't say it at all.
Episode wrapped.
Sorry, that ending was a bit of a whoop-wap, guys.
See ya!