Well hello there, I am so happy that you're here because I'm going to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. I don't have a new list yet, it's a new month, but we're going to thank each and every one of you this month by name.
So right now I'd like to thank every single person out there who is an ice cream truck driver.
What is an ice cream truck driver? I'm glad you asked. These are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I hope you do, head over to preachingfun.com.
Preachingfun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
The lice you crave can be extracted with a comb.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
C-O-M-B coo?
No, C-O-M-B coo.
Yeah.
Are you voting there, Paul?
Just like my mom used to say.
That comedian has a bit about language, but I can't remember it.
Gallagher, bitchin'.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social. Sitting somewhere, that's Matt Donnelly. Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly.
Check out the audio guy, I'm sitting in Las Vegas.
We're preachingfun.
That's the one that goes into the bomb, right? Boom and bomb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's like a little flip card thing.
Boom.
Yeah.
Man, I know he became a crazy, crazy twit, but I loved me some Gallagher when I was younger, man.
Oh, I loved Gallagher.
Yeah.
Back in the video store days, that was it. You wanted to watch a comedian, you ran into Gallagher movies.
I got really lucky later on running comedy clubs in Las Vegas. I got to work several, like a two or three weeks, all total, with Gallagher as one of the headlining comedians.
And man, the conversations in the green room when Gallagher is on are really pretty great.
When he's not there to hear what people are saying about him?
No, no, no. When he's in there. I'm saying when he's in the green room, when he's back there like holding court and having the conversations, the crazy, like the batshit crazy shit that gets talked about is spectacular.
He really lost it towards the end there, and he developed a rep in Vegas for being a kind of like crazy ass lunatic.
He was trying to like come up with his own version of like a slot machine or whatever, and he was going to pitch a version of gambling, and he was a really, really angry, bitter guy.
But just stand up, man.
And also like, while he was angry and bitter, also stayed super interesting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like he was angry and bitter, but he had his shit together.
He was a compelling person, yeah, yeah.
And like, as we all know, just from I think watching three minutes of any version of Gallagher stand up, he sees the world differently than most people.
Yeah, yeah.
And hearing from those people is always just fascinating.
And of course, yeah, we think we've done this a bunch of times, but he taught his brother his act, then he tried to stop his brother from doing his act, his brother said, no, I'm going to keep doing it.
He sued his brother.
Gallagher's manager took the brother's side and left Gallagher.
Yes.
That's really the most insulting part.
And the brother got the right to perform as Gallagher too.
I think there's nothing worse than thinking like, I could franchise this, finding out you're right, and then you want to be like, no, wait, don't do it, right?
Hold on.
No.
Yeah, when that genie's out of the bottle, forget it.
If anything, you just should have doubled down and gotten more apprentices, right?
Yeah.
Right.
He should have gotten Gallagher three, Gallagher four.
Yeah, yeah.
Release Gallagher four.
Fire!
That.
Also, none of the others should have looked anything like him.
Gallaguy.
They never should have acknowledged it.
Well, they could all have just all you got to do is put on one of them duffer hats with a long wig.
Done.
That's right.
Matt's halfway there.
I'll do it.
I keep switching careers.
I should start doing Gallagher's routines.
Just add a wig to one of your hats, Matt.
I will.
I've always said that when I cut my hair off at some day, that I'll just all attach it to the hat and just keep it around every now and then.
And I've sincerely thought about that, and it just seems like so much work to add it to my hat.
Yeah, if you're not having it done professionally.
That just seems like a lot of genuine work.
Also.
Sewing pieces of hair onto a hat.
You're going to select one hat that you're going to be stuck with for life.
You've got to sew it into a Velcro type mechanism so that it can be attached to multiple hats.
You don't make a bad point there.
It's a fairly good point.
My vision has always been that I would just walk out with the hat on and then take the hat off, and it would just be the, "Oh, Jacob doesn't have any hair."
That's kind of fun.
Of course, when I picture it, I picture myself being like egghead, completely bald as well.
I can tell you, Paul, I'm completely impressed by the Velcro thing.
I was thinking of just honing up for hair for each hat that you had.
Oh, my God.
Are you crazy?
I know.
Who has the money for that?
Actual human hair?
Rockefeller Donnelly over here.
You just saved imaginary Jacob, bald Jacob, hundreds and hundreds of dollars.
Yes, at least.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Jeff Loomis makes a good point in the chat.
Tapeface tried to do the franchising thing, and it really did not work well for Tapeface at all.
But he didn't do it.
He was being very surreptitious about it.
But so was Gallagher.
I think that Tapeface did exactly what Gallagher did.
I think he just didn't get away with it, and he did it in a different time.
Yeah, a time without social media where you can't just go, "Hey, that's not the real Gallagher."
Yeah.
I don't know.
Tapeface, we actually would probably get Tapeface to come on.
I probably could, yeah.
The problem is when he started more, I think it was like Fringe Festival stuff,
he started more theatrically as the boy with tape on his face.
Yes.
He considered it more of like a show than, I think the problem was that he did "America's Got Talent"
and then became a singular character in that moment and changed it from the boy with tape on his face to Tapeface,
and then still, in his mind, saw it theatrically.
And so he could have an understudy or whatever.
Yeah, it seemed like, from what I heard, it seemed like he thought he was looking at it
as though he were putting an understudy into a show, not that he was doing anything nefarious.
Right.
I mean, I'm all for it.
I would love to have that kind of problem.
We'll have him on and we'll talk about it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's going to be awkward next week when Jacob comes on and you guys don't recognize him.
Not me, me.
Paul, could you imagine trying to sell people right now?
You're like, don't worry.
I handpicked this person to train them to be funny like me.
To just have a substitute me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hand chosen.
I mean, there's more than a handful of podcasters who could probably do it.
No, but this is exactly what we're talking about.
Like, it's not, this is an A to A analogy.
Right.
Sure.
But they're just simply not personally invested in someone else who's capable.
Agreed.
Yeah, it is a weird thing.
It is a weird time for all of life on earth and the parasocial relationships, which are
the only things keeping us going day to day.
Let's see.
So if we wanted to build a new Paul, obviously, you know, it would have to involve small,
small barky dogs.
Mostly peanut butter.
Raisins to taste.
That's your base.
Always.
The Ludmilla sunrise.
Yup.
Black t-shirts.
MLK says having tape vision of the podcast like ventriloquism on the radio, right?
Grow up, MLK.
Grow up.
Ventriloquism.
And yes.
Those were the days, right?
To be a radio ventriloquist?
Oh my God.
What a dream.
What a dream that would have been.
Oh.
Hey, Bert.
How you doing today?
Oh, I'd be great if your hand wasn't up my ass.
Oh, Bert, you crazy so-and-so.
But you don't even have to do that.
You're the crazy one.
He doesn't even see that.
Like you don't even have to do that.
I can't believe you have the audio right there to play that authentic clip from the old
days.
I can't believe you just played that.
I know.
Gold.
Yeah.
Mortimer's nerd was a real perv.
What are you gonna do?
ML Kennedy, thank you in the chat, says that my mouth was not moving.
If anybody listening asks, that was legitimate just, what do you call it, throwing my voice.
Yeah.
That's right.
MarbleTulipScoopy says he could learn to love Paul number two.
I watched the special the other day.
There's a special somewhere.
I forget where, but it's on the Astroworld festival, the Travis Scott Astroworld festival
that he did several times.
Where lots of people got hurt.
Lots of people got hurt.
The crowd rushed stage.
There were multiple people that were kind of in charge of the safety of the festivals
and nobody, a lot of people didn't do their jobs.
Were there some deaths?
I believe there were some deaths, like crushing deaths and that kind of thing.
At one point, according to the special, there were four active CPRs going on.
Four people were actively receiving chest compressions and everything.
Whoa.
And that did not stop the show.
Oh, CountryScoop, thank you in the chat, says that 10 people ended up dying in there.
Goodness.
This is from when?
Travis Scott's thing.
This was several years ago.
Yeah, he used to do the festival every year at Astroworld to give back to Houston, where
he's from.
And I was watching this thing and I'm watching, a lot of it was lack of communication.
A lot of it was not telling Travis Scott on stage that things were going on.
Arguably, he was told and I don't know.
There were a lot of things going on.
There were large parts though of this documentary where I was watching horrible things happen
with all these thousands of people there in Astroworld and running around like crazy people.
And I was just looking at this going like, "Holy shit, this could happen to us.
Holy shit."
We could just accidentally make something huge like this and then it just totally gets
out of control.
And all of us look at it at the end going like, "I'm so sorry."
Again, these are the problems you want.
Paul and I are big enough that just the two of us falling over could crush 10 to 12 people.
Sure.
Yeah, it's true.
It's true.
All right.
Scoopfest stampede.
No.
We shouldn't cross off the trampling.
The trampling.
Jake, are you having second thoughts about putting this steel cage around every side
of the stage this year for Scoopfest?
Oh, if anything, I'm more on board with it.
It's going to really...
It's going to be the chicken wire from Blues Brothers.
Oh my god.
It's going to be the Chicken wire from Blues Brothers.
That is the best.
That scene.
Good lord.
That makes me laugh so much.
They just keep throwing beer.
Just throwing beer bottles.
Smash.
God damn.
So funny.
And it's great too.
I'm going to ruin this scene for people who watch Blues Brothers right now.
But if you watch it, you can just watch all of the sugar glass bottles explode as soon
as they hit.
Like the thin little chicken wire.
But they still get all over everybody.
It's still a mess.
Yeah.
We have both kinds.
Country and Western.
That's true.
It's true.
Oh man.
Raw Hyde.
I watched a little bit of Monday Night Raw a couple of weeks ago, Paul.
Take him home.
Before we go, I really do think the Loser Leaves Town match we've set up for two people
with the name I want to scoop, baby, we should really think twice about it now.
What's going to create, it's going to create some real friction.
Let's go.
Stampede.
Go ahead.
There will be crushing deaths, but in the good way.
Yeah.
Careful what you ask for.
Have you watched any Monday Night Raw, Paul?
Here's the thing.
I listen to podcasts about wrestling.
I haven't watched a wrestling match in probably two years.
Now that it's on Netflix, I keep getting ads for it popping up on Netflix.
Really excited.
Go ahead and watch one.
Yeah.
The other day, I'm home by myself.
I'm perusing.
I'm looking for an option to watch without SJ around because we watch a lot of things
together.
I have to do the math of like, what is she not going to be mad at me for watching without
her around?
Right.
Wrestling definitely won't be mad at me about that.
Good math.
Yeah.
I turned it on for a little while.
It seems to me, I haven't watched wrestling in I don't know how many years.
Decades.
Multiple decades.
Long time.
Yeah, long time.
It seemed to me, and tell me if I'm wrong or not, it seemed to me that there was a lot
more talking than there used to be and that the talking is much more contrived than I
remember it.
Yes.
Now, is that me?
Am I right or is that just me, child versus adult, looking at this?
No, you're right.
If you saw the South Park from a couple years back, they really nailed it where it's more
about a theatrical thing than anything else.
The wrestling is secondary at this point, which is so silly.
Yeah, it's funny that you mentioned this.
Just today, I deleted a couple of my wrestling podcasts because I'm like, this is just-
Oh, you're falling off.
Well, I mean, yeah.
Yeah.
Because-
Tariffs?
Oh, sorry.
Triple H was in the White House just a couple days ago.
Oh, is that right?
In the White House.
Oh, right, because what's her name, McMahon?
I mean, she's been there.
It's like the secretary of something.
She's not, you know, she's not really directly connected to the company.
Education, that's it.
Sure, sure.
She's not really directly connected to the company anymore, legacy-wise, for sure.
But to have Triple H-
Well, because Vince is out, right?
Yeah.
Well, so they say.
Who knows, man?
But they might be, yeah, yeah.
Like, I don't want to.
Who fucking knows?
Go ahead, McMahon.
He was at a big party.
I was at a party with Vince and he was making me pee on someone just the other night.
Yeah?
Okay.
Well, maybe he's on his comeback tour.
Yeah.
I keep telling you not to invite Vince McMahon to your pee on people parties, Matt.
No.
Because it turns into a shit on people party.
It does.
That's the problem.
Matt, you have to put Visqueen down.
You're going to ruin your Fardwood floors.
This is so hard.
My wife knows I'm hanging out with them when Visqueen gets delivered to my front door on
Amazon.
Yeah.
But I just, I think for my own sense of self, I'm just like, like, okay.
It's really been these last two months, shit's gotten kind of sketched for me.
Again, and I'm only just listening to stuff and hearing, you know, watching a few little
things on YouTube and whatnot, recaps, things like that.
And I don't know if you're familiar, oh wait, ML Kennedy's saying Linda McMahon just got
hacked at an interview.
Someone got into the audio when she was talking about Department of Education stuff and somebody
played the clown song.
Hilarious.
Oh, the entry of the gladiators at that, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
Wow.
That's amazing, ML Kennedy.
That's fantastic.
Yeah.
Because that's how she sounds and that's how the whole country sounds at this point.
Right.
But yeah, you know, they do this, it's become an annual thing now.
They have a big to-do, the crown jewel that they do over in Dubai, you know, in Saudi
Arabia and that, you know, that's already kind of questionable on a political note.
But the thing is, CM Punk, when he was out of the WWE for a while, for years, he was
giving those wrestlers unlimited shit, like he wrote a tweet that said, "Go suck a blood-soaked
dick out in Saudi Arabia, you asshole."
Yeah, right, right, right, right.
So he was like coming for their throats over this, you know.
He's giving people shit, but also, CM Punk, I think you should talk to somebody.
Well, you know.
Jesus Christ, man.
It looked like he was taking a stand, but just last month, guess who's headlining Crown
Jewel?
Ah, got it.
And then, you know, I watch Bachamania all the time, which is really funny.
And they did the old clip of Krusty the Clown where it's like, "I'm so sorry.
They backed up a Brink's truck to my house.
I'm not made of stone."
You know, it's like, of course, of course, money talks, right?
But that's, it's endemic of everything going on in the whole world.
And the fact that these players from this, you know, wrestling corporation are becoming
statesmen?
They're becoming statesmen.
That's -- Glenn Jacobs is a governor, or a mayor, I don't know.
It's just, it's too much for me.
Why was I going to say Jesse "The Body" Ventura?
I mean, he was the governor of Minnesota for a long time.
Yeah, it's just kind of, it's just a little too much at this point for me.
I don't know.
I just -- And Abe Lincoln was the president.
Yeah.
He wrestled.
He did.
He was a boxer, I think.
Yeah.
Maybe he was a wrestler.
I think he was a wrestler.
Yeah.
The weird thing, though, on Raw, not having anything to do with any of all those things,
was the cameras.
They did, they do so much camera work now, and they switch back -- you know, I mean,
they always switch back and forth between different shots and everything during the
wrestling matches.
Now they switch back and forth between different shots, and the camera speeds on the different
cameras are different.
Like the frame rate is different on different cameras, or something like that.
I'm not exactly sure what they're doing, but that's what it looked like to me.
And so they would move it, and all of a sudden, it would look like the two wrestlers in the
ring were moving faster than they were just a second before, and then they'd switch back.
And it was -- whatever it was, it was definitely on purpose.
Yeah.
It definitely seemed to be something that they were trying to do to kind of add to the
action.
Uh-huh.
It was so odd.
Was it throwing you?
It was throwing me a little bit.
I was kind of hoping that you had heard something about it, if they had said something about
it publicly or something.
I haven't.
Maybe not.
But of that is that they have professional camera crews now.
Oh, sure.
They've had some of their old camera crew -- well, no, it's a huge step up.
Because after the departure of Vince -- Oh, did they have their own people before?
They had Mr. Kevin Dunn.
Kevin Dunn had been there for a millennia, and they finally got rid of him.
And now all of a sudden, the production value has gone sky high.
They got these guys from ESPN.
The guys putting together the NFL best-of stuff and all that kind of thing.
So they got some real high production value going forward right now.
It was a good-looking product for the most part.
That's what I mean.
And the video wall in the back, it was a good-looking product.
No, they have the production -- Also, John Cena, I guess, is retiring.
Yes.
And him going through -- he's on a retirement tour or something, I guess.
Yeah, these are his last year matches.
A pro wrestler going through and playing their greatest hits for an audience is so goddamn
funny.
Yeah.
And well, it's a weird thing that they've done with him because he went heel, you know.
Okay.
No, I don't.
He'd never turned heel his entire career.
Oh, so he's a bad guy now.
Yeah.
But now he's starting to regret it.
It's weird.
Like he is shoot regretting it.
Like he really is sad that he did it, kind of, I think, because he never did it.
So that's kind of crazy.
Yeah, it's something else.
What did you just say before that about Cena and, I don't know, I can't remember.
Oh, just watching him do his retirement tour was interesting.
Yeah.
It's something else.
I don't know.
I just -- I'll tell you who was really excited about seeing Cena 2, though, coming out next
year.
And that's going to be the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Miley's Ice Cream and Social, is brought to you by -- I'm sorry
for the delay.
I just got some Disque Queen delivered to my front door.
Oh.
Ooh!
Matt's having a party.
Shoeless Joe's Bottomless Crocs.
That's from Anonymous in 2024.
Hey, it's Shoeless Joe here for the Bottomless Crocs.
You may be asking yourself, how can I get Bottomless Crocs?
Well, it's simple.
All you have to do is buy them from me, Shoeless Joe.
I have crocs with no sole.
That's right.
Just the top of the croc.
You slip it on just like a normal croc.
Most people think you're wearing a croc, but no, no.
You are wearing a croc with no sole.
You're walking around essentially barefoot.
Now, that in a lot of places is gauche.
We don't want to come across as gauche, do we?
No.
So, buy the topper.
Buy the croc topper.
Put it on top of your foot.
No one will ever be the wiser that you are just ill-billed in it.
Go gauche, go broke.
That's what I say.
It's true.
Go gauche, go broke.
There's a lot of places.
He says it all the time.
I mean, many of you have probably gone into a convenience store and noticed the little
sign.
No shirt, no shoes, no service.
Yeah.
These crocs let you skip that line, as it were, and go ahead and walk on in there proudly.
Even though you're technically barefoot, you have the clam shell of the croc on top of
your foot, disguising your naked soul.
Hi.
I was here.
I'm hoping to have sex with one of your slutty crocodiles.
Oh, okay.
Come into the back room.
Yeah.
Bottomless crocs.
Enter Hasecoops to check out.
Yeah.
That's what really makes the money.
Well, that naked soul turn was actually really poetic and beautiful, buddy.
That was a little too highbrow for the camera.
Oh, you like that?
Yeah.
That was actually kind of poetic.
But Poet didn't know it.
Yeah.
You see, Matt recognized that it had gotten a little highbrow for the show and he commented
on it.
I just made a joke about having sex with a crocodile who was bottomless.
I think we both did the right thing.
This is where we live, right, guys?
It's the same thing I used to talk about with Absinthe.
It's everything from the profane to the sublime.
We like to cover all bases.
We can get esoteric when we want to, but we can also tell you-
We should steal that line.
They're not using it.
They didn't take your-
They never used that because it was my line.
They should have used it, everything from the profane to the sublime.
Believe me, someone who has given them a line, they will take it and use it.
They should.
We'll use it.
Matt Madden is ice cream social.
Profane to the sublime, get on board with our new fucking slogan.
Will you get it?
I'm on.
You know what?
You bring up the no shoes, no shirt, no service, I don't see those signs like it needs to be
everywhere.
As much?
Maybe they're done?
Maybe it's over?
No, I meant did that culture war win?
Do we now know we got to wear shoes into the 7-Eleven?
Or has footwear gone to the point where it's like, well, technically a toe ring is footwear?
I think everybody is more aware that every business can just kick you out for any reason
that they want to now.
That's true.
If you come into a restaurant, or maybe not a restaurant, but like a 7-Eleven barefoot
and you're not being a jerk, they'll probably just serve you and you can leave.
I have memories as a kid like going back and forth to the beach because I grew up on the
Jersey Shore, pinkies out in my county.
How come that's never come up before?
When my chauffeur would take us to the beach, no, my dad would take us to the beach.
We would go to 7-Eleven on the way home or something like that, and I would run in barefoot
and feel like fun.
I was in the store doing whatever.
My kids, I really think the answer is Crocs, like not anything but the fact that we've
made...
A very simple shoe.
A flip-flop was easy, too.
A flip-flop was easy, too, but I don't really ever see any proper flip-flops.
I'll see it in a proper sandal, more like an executive sandal style for a lady.
I don't want to offend anybody, but I feel like people who wear flip-flops, that's what
they wear.
How dare you?
How fucking dare you use this platform to disparage people on that level.
I occasionally wear a flip-flop, but rarely.
But anyhow.
For the most part, honestly, I just wear it when we have a churn.
I just wear it to the churn.
I just wear flip-flops to the churn.
Guys, I'm wrapping up my magic invention.
You guys want to get into it?
It's pretty exciting stuff.
A magic invention?
Convention.
Oh, you're at a convention right now?
Well, I'm at my house right now, but Magic Live is happening at the Orleans Casino.
They always dry run Scoopfest by doing a convention.
That's right.
Right.
They always ride ahead of us, right?
Yeah, they do this convention for 5,000 people to see how it's going to go, and then everything's
road tested for us to bring in our hundreds of people.
That's right.
Well, I mean, we can't help it that we have the better, more elite convention.
That's true.
That's just how it is, man.
It's true.
I was involved in this convention.
No.
Handsap's got a flip-flop.
Look out.
I've offended Handsap.
There you go.
Handsap.
Oh.
Sorry, Handsap.
No, you didn't realize that was a real bomb.
What do they call them?
Chooklas?
I wonder if there's another word people want to...
No.
Chooklas.
The thing you're talking about.
We all know what you're trying to say.
Chooklas.
Yeah, yeah.
They call them choncolas.
Choncolas.
Well, you know, people get really good at throwing those fucking things.
What?
You don't know about that.
I mean, people get good at throwing things that they throw.
No, but I mean, no, no, no.
There is a...
No, no, no.
Nolan Ryan started as a chocolist thrower.
There is...
I believe it's pronounced chikulas, Matt.
Scupacabras saying Spanish grandmas.
Again, not to stereotype, not to get anybody upset, but there are lots of videos...
Too late.
Lots of videos of elderly women taking off a flip-flop and fucking dead-ass nailing people
in the head with it, just whoa.
I never had family members that would throw things.
I would have family members that would have taken off a flip-flop and just smacked you
with it.
That part, too.
I think we had throwers.
Spanish grandmas make a great name for a bowling team, just so we're clear.
It does.
Jeff Loomis, welcome to the part of the podcast where Paul introduces an obscure fact and
then acts borderline offended that no one else has heard of it.
It's not no one else.
Lots of people are saying it.
Listen to this guy.
But your introduction to that fact was terrible.
You didn't know the word and then you gave us no other word.
I said chukula and I know it's wrong.
And then it was annoying that we didn't know it.
Okay.
Whatever.
Anyway, Basi says the flip-flops are a weapon of grannies.
They're in the peninsula.
So there you go.
Oh, there you go.
I just I'm saying there is a a sect of older ladies who have become very adept at flinging
their footwear.
Jacob, hit the production meeting music.
Oh, it's gone.
It's another button that I don't have on this pad.
Where the fuck?
This podcast is falling apart.
I know you're telling me.
Production meeting.
Okay.
If we're going to read a comment from the chat, we have to read the comment from the
chat because for the listener at home, when you go, oh, yeah, so so yeah, like that's
not a good right way to incorporate the chat into the podcast.
We've all been doing it.
So that's why I'm calling it out on a production meeting.
So if you're going to acknowledge the chat, fully acknowledge and fully read the chat
and then that's a good note.
And then we do it because otherwise I think people listening at home are going fucking
nuts.
Okay.
All right.
Production meeting over.
That's the machine, the machine.
Where the fuck is my production meeting?
It's just a machine now.
If we had a churn, this would never have happened.
We would know where their production meeting was.
It's true, it's true.
Possibly true.
It is possibly true.
So I was asked to host a show this year at magic live.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
And it became very clear very quickly that it was a mistake for all involved.
Who did it become very clear to very quickly?
No, no.
So here's the thing.
They always have a big showcase show and a big and a close up showcase.
Right.
And they always experiment with a third show.
And then the experimental third show is it medium, medium pace magic?
Is that what it is?
It is.
Yeah.
It is magic that starts like really far away, but finishes very up close.
Like you run progressive magic.
Think of a card and then you run towards them and smack them in the face with a card.
Oh, God.
The most painful card to get hit with the bottom of his fucking flip flop.
So originally, the show is going to have no no host and it was called the Experimental
Theater Concepts Show.
Yes.
OK.
Huh?
Who's not?
Everybody just I know everyone in the chest just rolls off the tongue.
Why?
Why couldn't I go?
I wish I was there.
I know.
But the Experimental Theater Concepts Show.
Meaning you have to do like an avant-garde or you need a trick?
Yes.
Yeah.
You have to experiment with the presentation of magic in some way.
I don't want to.
I don't want to steal your thunder here.
But when I think experimental and avant-garde magic trick, my first thought is Rudy Coby.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, Rudy was around and Rudy was certainly someone who Rudy Coby is certainly someone
who pushed the boundaries of magic and pushed magic in different directions.
And theatrically, too.
Yes.
If you're going to make it about theatrics, his whole thing was theatrics.
Yeah.
No.
I remember Rudy Coby, a lot of his stuff is on YouTube.
If you go look at his stuff.
Lab man is his alter ego.
Yeah.
Lab man is the bit.
And you really don't see too much like it.
And actually that style of what he's doing is part of like an older vaudeville thing.
Yes.
But he made it so that it was completely felt modern and unique in its time.
It was.
It is great.
It's very, very cool stuff that he does.
Yeah.
He has a lot of legs.
That's fine.
Yeah.
I said it's fine.
It's perfectly good.
So initially I was approached it was actually when I did my run at the Magic Castle, one
of the people who ran the one of the people who runs the festival, my friend, Nick Lang,
said, you know, hey, this show is going to be so experimental.
We're thinking about having, you know, kind of a host to kind of keep it all together
and have fun with it.
And the pitches are like, I'd be able to have fun doing like these different bits or whatever.
And it's the biggest, it's the biggest magic convention in North America.
Right.
It's a, you know, it's a, it's a, you know, obviously I'm going to say yes to the opportunity
no matter what it was.
Right.
You've got to jump on it.
Yeah.
And when I showed up for rehearsal, like the bits were so avant-garde that I was like,
if I'm trying to do like wacky bits in between, I, this isn't going to go well.
So the routines were just too out there to be made fun of or they were too, they were
too, uh, yeah, they were, they were taking such a big swing that if I tried to make a
joke about it, it might look like I'm making fun of it.
Yes.
Was it like the end of my crock bit where I threw you off by being poetic and you were
like, Oh God, that was amazing.
The way he moved that light across the stage without touching it.
I can't make fun of that.
Well, like when, yeah, even as that crock commercial, like I was like, why is this tear
running down the side of my face?
You know, um, so example, like, uh, uh, I'll just go through the, the things that there,
that there were, uh, like one, uh, guy did like a completely AI thing where he sat down
in the chair and a screen popped up and did a complete AI head.
It was like Max Hedrum from the nineties, uh, but I didn't want to make a Max Hedrum
joke to make fun of it.
Both did not date myself.
And uh, I guess while you're looking at Rudy Kobe's magic specials, go ahead and look at
Max Hedrum.
We're in the same time period.
That frewer everybody, Max Hedrum, catch the wave.
Coke.
Yeah.
And then, uh, um, so, uh, you know, another guy did a trick where he was talking, but
then all of a sudden he does this trick backwards and does the whole thing backwards.
Um, and then another guy had a thing where everyone put on headphones, but it was like
more of like a theatrical piece.
And so you were not to be in the room and so they're supposed to make the room feel
empty.
And this was like, it was, yeah.
And so all of us was very, I basically said that we've created a show that's very ketamine
friendly.
That's what I was saying to my friends when I was like, what's the show like?
And I was like, it's very ketamine is the vibe.
Watched a show while sitting in a k-hole.
And so, uh, bringing a wacky improv comic, uh, was, was maybe not, not the best pairing
for, for, for, no, especially like also like when it's like, you know, experimentation
and technology stuff, uh, no, no, the funny thing is that we, I pitched an idea for this
show.
I try to get into the show as an entertainer, uh, and they were like, that's too out there.
Actually I was, we were told it was not out there enough.
So I, cause I did this, you know, I did the, uh, I'm going to be at the magic castle again,
August 20th to 24th, once again with my buddy, uh, Nick Paul and, uh, we did an improv bit
where we, where we, where we did magic, but took made it like a genre roller coaster of
a magic trick.
That's a fun.
Yeah.
It's, it's on my Instagram somewhere.
And um, so, uh, we pitched different versions of using improv games for magic.
So like we were going to do a card step routine, having the audience members be our arms, or
we would be the arms of audience members and do the trick and we're going to do an illusion
to it, to the song of anyone's choosing that could go through Spotify on one of our phones
and choose any song they wanted.
And we were going to, you know, explore doing an illusion twice to two totally different
pieces of music.
Um, and that was considered not different, not different enough.
Now when I just described those pieces I described, you can see that like, yes, I believe we were
below the theatrical bar of what they were looking for.
Uh, but energy wise, they could have used it, I think they could have used it just for
a little, just a little pep in the room.
Little pep, little kick up.
Yep, yep, yep.
And I had to like stall in between, but I wasn't going to do magic tricks in between
because the show was showcasing experimental magic.
So it wouldn't be good for them to do like road tested material in between to stall.
Did you err on the side of Cirque du Soleil?
Did you like wheel in a baby on a giant screen and be like, "I'm the lonely baby who's sad"?
Paul, were you there?
Paul were you there?
That's exactly what I did.
That's what happened.
I mean that Zarkana stuff's got to be laying around somewhere.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, just laying around waiting for somebody that wants to print money.
Print money?
That's it.
Print Monopoly money.
That's right.
That you can only spend at the Cosmopolitan buffet.
Zarkana and run, they're both just sitting around waiting on somebody to pick those up
and just run with them.
Everything from the profane to the sublime.
Now what was your solution, man?
Jeff in the chat mentions that if you can go see A Good Magician at the Magic Castle, it
is an awesome time.
All right, but you should also go August 20th to the 24th anyway.
Oh, I didn't read Jeff's whole thing.
He said if you can go see Matt at the Magic Castle, it's an awesome time.
I messed up, I didn't read his whole post again.
I'll tell you who also is going to go see Matt at the Magic Castle, and that's the following
sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Stinky Pants.
Pants for babies.
That's right.
Stinky Pants.
Pants for babies.
That's from Dead Lazlo in 2024.
Boo boo wah wah, boo boo wah wah, boo boo wah wah, I got a duty.
Hi.
I'm a big dumb baby, and I poop my duties all in my pants.
And I hate it because everyone says, "Hey, big dumb baby who smells like duties, what's
wrong with you?"
And I'm like, because I'm still pooping in my pants with my duties.
But turns out there's a solution.
All I need is these poopy pants for babies that come pre-pooped, and the poop smells
like bananas, so it's not bad.
So now I'm not big dumb baby who smells like poop, I'm big dumb baby who smells like a
pants full of bananas.
And nobody knows any better, but don't ever take me on a field trip to the zoo or I'll
get ate up by the gorillas.
Oh God, I'm in the cage.
He got me.
No, they shot him.
They shot him dead.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
Poop, poop, poopy, poopy pants that smell like bananas, don't go to the zoo.
Enter HeyScoops at checkout.
Again, I was just laughing along with you, Paul, and then you made a Harambe reference
in tears, flowing down my face.
Okay, we learned the last episode that if Paul's too gross and fast forwards the commercial-
That's right.
Do we think she fast forwarded that commercial or not?
Do you think you can tow the lawn?
I think she probably listened to that one.
It didn't get too gross.
Are you now that you know that fact, does it affect the way you make commercials?
No, not at all.
I'm not censoring myself for that woman.
No, 20 years of uncensored bullshit from me.
She knows what's up.
No, but she also did say, because I talked to her about it the other day, she said, it's
not every commercial, just some of them.
There you go.
What a temp.
Always in your corner.
She went over by any of the Chinese bridge arguments we had for your backyard.
Oh, good question.
I don't know that she's listened to that episode yet, because we got to talk about maybe doing
it and having the water flow of flowers underneath, but she could be swayed.
I think she can be swayed.
I was contacted by one Ryar Appledorn, who is apparently in the middle of constructing
a Chinese bridge for his own yard, and with that same kind of flowery solution, I think,
so I said, hey, let's talk.
He's already offered to build me a Chinese bridge, so we've got to see how it works and
see what we do there.
Maybe in a year or two, we can make that happen.
Not this summer.
Always hire Ryar.
You can't go wrong, hire Ryar.
I'll tell you, Ryar was a fantastic co-pilot with me and the dogs to get me all the way
across the country.
That was a very good thing that I had.
Didn't spill anything in the car or anything.
Look, look, that's me.
That's my issues coming out.
That's my weird, what do you want me to call those?
Yeah, no shit.
I've been working on new tricks and I thought Ryar was so wrapped up with Brushwood that
I did not hire initially to make a prop for me, and I had another company make a prop
for me and it did not accomplish what I needed it to accomplish.
Mistake.
I headed over to Ryar and a little bit jaded, I just was like, this company tried X, Y and
Z and said it wouldn't work.
I think that's bullshit.
I bet you could do it or whatever.
And he came back to me basically going, "No, the problems that the company said with the
prop are correct, but I've invented this new way to do it."
So Ryar came up with a totally new proprietary technology way to do the trick I want to do.
Amazing.
I'm being cagey about the trick, not because I give a shit about that, only that I might
perform it at ScoopFest.
So I'm being cagey because I don't want to give it away.
Well, you should be cagey too, because you guys can patent those things at some point.
Oh, good idea.
Good idea.
Right?
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know exactly how all that works with the Magic community.
It's hard to lock stuff down.
Nobody does.
It's always very low key.
It's honor system, right?
Yeah.
People get along all the time.
No one ever fights about it ever.
That's the way it works in the Magic community.
Magic and variety have that in common.
Nobody's ever upset with anybody for stealing anything.
Nobody accuses anybody of theft.
Nobody is to say they've made it their own.
It never happens in the Magic world.
Oh, and if you just want to get really mad about it, listen to burlesque people complain
about it.
Oh, I can't imagine, right?
Listening to burlesque people complain about people stealing bits is...
I mean, listening to Magic people do it, listening to variety people do it, it's already insane
and annoying.
Let me tell you, honey.
When people do it, you're like, what are you actually talking about?
35 years ago, I was the first to reveal my left tit immediately as soon as the curtain
came up.
And those motherfucking bitches stole it and ran with it.
They call it the pirate eye.
That's right.
I had the first pirate eye move, left tit specifically, and that fucking dungaree wearing whore took
that fucking bit from me.
Dungaree?
Yes.
That ragamuffin dungaree wearing?
That's right.
This was 35 years ago when ladies didn't do such pantaloons.
Interhase scoops at checkout?
I don't know.
There was decorum.
Decorum.
There was fucking rules, there were rules.
I was the worst one that put castles on my kneecaps.
Dirty knees, look at these we called them.
Dungaree wearing whore is a scoop fest t-shirt, right?
Well, Brogan's always in the chat here.
Actually Brogan, you're in Las Vegas right now, aren't you?
Do you want to unmute?
Yes, I am.
Because you're at a Star Trek convention?
Yes.
Because you're here to see, was it Dave Davies, Dan Davis?
I'm here to see Daniel Davis.
Daniel Davis.
Yeah.
From The Nanny.
So he was in The Nanny?
The guy from The Nanny?
Yeah.
I ran into JoBeth last night at the bar.
Oh God.
And you were talking about, because we had you on and we were talking about how Daniel
Davis was going to be at the Star Trek convention, that's why you were going.
So you're trying to get Paul to go with Daniel Davis going to be there.
I did not understand the reference obviously in any capacity whatsoever.
But it turns out that Daniel Davis is not primarily a Star Trek person, not a Star Trek
personality person, and in fact he himself, the actor, was debating whether or not to
attend the Star Trek convention because they're not that big of a character on there and they
have a large acting resume outside the Star Trek universe.
He's a Broadway star, yeah.
He's a Broadway star.
And then I understand Chris the Microscope bought a cameo for you from Daniel Davis,
is that right?
That's correct.
Okay.
And then the result of that cameo was Daniel Davis saying, "I was on the fence about doing
the convention, but now I've done this cameo for you and you're going to the convention,
I'll do the convention."
Is that right?
Oh wow.
Brogan, while you're here, just because you brought it up privately and a topic that's
come up on the pod, you've actually, you have come to the United States now three times
or two times, twice this year.
Have you encountered any hassle or fracas coming to the country?
We've had scoops from other countries say they don't want to come to Scoop Fest because
they're worried about things they've posted on social media, that kind of stuff, and there
are stories that's happened.
So I guess broadly then, have you experienced a difference in travel because you've come
here many times?
No.
I mean, don't get me wrong, it was genuinely terrifying the first time, and even the second
time because I flew a different airline this time, and I usually go from Edinburgh to London
to Vegas.
So Vegas is usually my first hit into the States.
This time I went from Edinburgh to New York to Vegas.
So passing through customs was at New York.
I have not had any problems.
No one has asked for my phone.
No one bothered at all, although I will say I got global entry, 100% do that because I
got to New York and they went to the little kiosk, took my picture.
The guy looked at me and went, "Go through."
It did not stop me whatsoever.
Nobody asks you a goddamn thing.
That is genuinely more interaction than I usually have with anyone when I'm doing global
entry coming back in.
Into the country, like I said, from your Portugal stuff.
Yeah, like last week I came back in, like that was more interaction, what you just described
was more interaction than I had with anybody coming back in.
We came back in through Philadelphia.
Global entry.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, Paul, I don't know if they could hear the bunnies on that one.
Now, I was...
Global entry.
When I was partying with Vince McMahon, global entry was very different.
Gobble, gobble, global entry.
But yeah, like nobody asks to see your phone and don't get me wrong, I am very white and
I look like I'm 12 years old, so I look very non-threatening and because I am just a paranoid...
Wait, you bring up your race, I don't think anything race-based has happened with this
administration.
Oh boy.
Really?
I don't think anybody said anything about that.
Oh boy.
I'm only mentioning it because I burn in the Vegas sun, but whatever, if you want to bring
it racist, Matt, okay, whatever.
Brogan was sunburned from sitting under the lights on the plane.
That was a joke, that's true.
Yeah, I was just curious, you know, whatever.
That's all fine.
I'm so excited my accent is getting a bit thick, so I think...
What accent is that you're talking about?
What do you mean?
Shut the fuck up and let me get to my point, Paul.
There's no accent at all.
Brogan, switch over to full Gaelic any second.
I've not detected the slightest change in your demeanor.
Wait, you're both from Kazakhstan?
That's right, Kazakhstan represent.
Engines to full, I cannot hold her together, Captain.
I'm at the table grabbing the bill first.
Oh, oh, I cannot restrain myself here at the table going for my credit card, as it will.
Brogan ordered a pot tea.
Oh, we just let him go.
We just wait until he stops, don't we?
That's right.
You wind me up and I just go.
I just go.
He wears himself out eventually.
At the table.
You want to fuck my crocodile.
It's really more of like a comedy tantrum, if anything, you know, you have to kind of
let it...
It's really a 50-year comedy tantrum, that's my fucking biography.
God damn right.
Let's do some scoop mail.
Message for you, sir.
We got a scoop mail from Sarah Boyle.
We got a physical scoop mail and I'm going to read you this letter that came with it.
Yes, Matt Donnelly.
She's right up there, I'm pointing to her.
Oh, I thought you were just like waving.
Let's see.
This got left at my house.
I walked out of my front door and this was on my doorstep.
I felt so creepy doing it, like I felt really intensely creepy, but I was like, I'm not
going to pay to ship this.
You live like three miles from me, like I could walk to your house with it.
And so I was just like, I know where you live.
As long as you're not wearing like a FedEx uniform, it's all good.
You know, I don't know.
I think we're fine.
I think everything's fine.
I mean everybody that's coming to the whiskey barbecue knows where Jacob lives.
That's right.
Yeah.
I have made my house somewhat public information and yeah, so somebody-
People don't just drop off at each other's houses anymore.
It's not like the 80s when you could just be at somebody's house.
Well, you also didn't knock on the door.
You just left the box outside.
No, I didn't.
I just-
I think everything was fine.
So dear denizens- That hideous house you're trying to convince me to buy.
I don't think anybody should buy that house that doesn't want to spend another $150,000
on it.
No, no, no.
They're asking way too much.
But Steve and I literally like genuinely are considering buying a house that's in a different
cul-de-sac on Jacob's street if they drop the price a little.
And I'm like, "Is it weird to move into his neighborhood?"
You wouldn't be the weirdest people in the neighborhood.
That is definitely true.
I've met a couple of your neighbors.
You wouldn't win that battle.
So there is that.
Dear denizens of Eventually A New Churn, BatScoop and I recently got back from 10 days of puffing
watching in the, what is it say, Westman?
Westman Islands, yeah.
The Westman Islands in Iceland.
Oh, that's great.
Upon our return, there was a package of very- It was 55 degrees Fahrenheit the whole time
we were there and it was 100 degrees Fahrenheit here and I was just like, "I could- That's
like half.
-do this for a couple of weeks.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Upon our return, there was a package of very silly Bloodsport merch.
Like the movie?
Yes.
Like the Jean-Claude Van Damme movie?
Great.
Have you not looked in the box?
No, I haven't.
Let's see.
You had pre-ordered a while back.
I'm going to drop this box off of stuff at Jacob's house and try not to be super creepy
about it.
No, the letter is the only part of this that I've really dug into because when I found
a random box on my front porch, I opened it to see who had left it.
It has- Well, I mean, it has my address on the side because it's still in the shipping
box.
Oh, yeah.
But I broke physical scoop mails if any do on it just so you would know what it was for.
So that's why I opened it.
I didn't explore any of the more- any of the outside.
I was fine with everything.
This was all good.
There is a- what is that?
Oh, a Koumete duffel bag.
Oh, that's great.
For each of you and an Icelandic booze sampler for Matt and Jacob, some coffee, a couple
of spare fancy Icelander travel bags- Iceland Air, the airline.
Oh, Iceland Air travel bags.
And a while ago, Jacob and I discussed the random deal and told-
Sorry, my handwriting is really bad.
Oh, dead and co shirt.
There we go.
Yeah.
The random dead and co shirt that someone bought me that might be good for SJ.
Oh, yeah.
I pulled that out of the box and gave that to SJ.
She says, "Thank you very much.
Enjoy your no holds barred tiny- I didn't go to the show.
And so they were like, "Here's a t-shirt from this show you didn't go to of a band that
you don't care about."
And I was like, "Why?
Why did you spend money on this?"
See you next month for ScoopFest.
You lied about that part.
I saw you today on this Zoom call.
I wasn't sure if I was going to be able to be in one of the Zoom calls, so I didn't-
Ah.
Well, there you go.
Thank you very much, Sarah Boyle.
Thank you for dropping off some physical Scoop mail at the old house here.
Koumete bag.
I can't wait.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they say Koumete on them.
That's fucking A.
Yes!
Oh, man.
That's awesome.
You don't see it very well.
Your background filter is-
I don't.
Hold on.
I'm turning off my background filter.
It's still cool.
Yeah.
Koumete.
Just a pile of dead bodies behind Jacob when he turns off-
It's true.
Oh, man.
And Jacob can just intercept that copy if he doesn't like it.
Is it a backpack?
No, he's always complaining about not sending him a copy.
They're duffels.
Oh, man.
That's amazing.
That's a nice duffel, too.
You can use them in the airport and not set them on the ground in the bathroom, right?
Amen to that.
That's right.
Everybody's getting to see my real background now because I just have mirrors behind me,
which is why I keep-
It looks good.
It makes everything look bigger.
That's true.
Let's do a little Chalk vs. a Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Chalk vs. Nerd.
It's time for the explosion of Koumete duffel bags.
Kaboom.
We've got a scooperty coming out today from HeyScoopGetOffMyLawn.
Hello, all.
I'm answering Jacob's call for some trivia with a scooperty and an obelisk, two for one.
Oh, that's a great point.
Some of you do send multiple scooperties and obelisks all at the same time, which is fantastic.
I love when you do that.
Do me a favor just to help my organization out.
Send them in two different emails.
Do one email per game, and that just makes it easier for me to keep up with everything.
But this is fantastic, and thank you so much for doing this.
Let's see.
Two for one.
I have been out of commission for a while, explaining my absence from making these things.
So first, a PSA, don't get shingles.
Just don't do it, people.
Let me tell you, that's the fucking truth.
I've had it twice.
My job has me lots of different places all the time, so there's no telling how this happened,
but I had chicken pox as a kid, and now here we are.
I'm past the worst of it, but dealing with the nerve damage where it infected over my
mouth later, I got it on my face, my mouth, and in my inner and outer ear, including my
eardrum, 10 out of 10 do not recommend.
Oh my God, I am so sorry.
That happened to a friend of mine with his eyes.
He got it on the backs of his eyes, and now if he walks outside on an overcast, cloudy
day, he still has to wear sunglasses.
His eyes, as a result, are extraordinarily light sensitive.
I know in today's America, this may be an unpopular opinion, but do get the damn vaccinations
for shingles.
I got it the day I turned 50.
I'm under 50 and never really thought much about it, but this got my wife to immediately
go and get her first shot.
It picks a nerve branch and screws it up when you get it.
I caught mine in the first 48 hours and likely shorted the worst of it and still can't survive
without nerve blockers yet.
Just very fortunate it wasn't in my eye.
There you go.
I guess there's that.
Anyway, here's an obelisk and a scooperty.
Enjoy it more than the shooting pain, tingling, and hot and cold feelings that I randomly
get all the time in my face.
That's Chris.
Hey, Scoop, get off my lawn.
So let's see here.
We have a scooperty coming to us from Hey, Scoop, get off my lawn.
I am stalling while I share it with everybody else so they can see it over here and we've
already played that.
Never mind.
Let's see.
So this is why I need multiple emails.
Let's see if we've already played this obelisk as well.
Yeah we have.
But we didn't have the full read through of the email, so that's good.
We had not had the full read through of the email.
That is true.
Yeah.
Give me one second.
I'm going to find us a different one from neck pubes.
Hey folks, I'm a proud patron and wish I could contribute more.
I just want to say to the people that aren't patron members, there is a lot you're missing
out on and it's worth a few extra bucks a month to have it.
The way I look at it, I can do gig economy work for about $20 an hour.
I listen to podcast while I do that, $10 can get me over 30 minutes of content so it pays
for itself.
A question I have for the churn, does it help your numbers if we download the episodes from
a different app than Patreon?
I've picked auto download on three separate apps in case it does.
Anyway, love you guys.
Keep it real.
Neck pubes.
And here is a scooperty that we're going to look at in just a second to make sure that
we haven't already played it.
But yes, good question neck pubes.
Yeah, I think it.
I mean the more the merrier, right?
If you set us to download on any app, it's going to help us out.
So when in doubt, set this show to download and it will be groovy.
And I have found a scooperty that we haven't played yet.
Let me just play the little production meeting.
Great.
That's that's the machine.
The categories are the first, the most, the last and the least.
Paul, you're up first.
What you want?
I will take the last for 400.
Which of these three car brands was the last to produce cars, Oldsmobile, Pontiac or Saturn?
So this means this question is asking who produced a car?
Who went out of business last?
OK, that's what I was looking for.
Yeah.
I think it's Oldsmobile.
Let's try it.
Pontiac was 2010, Saturn was 2009, Oldsmobile was 2004.
If you're keeping track, that means that Paul got it as wrong as he possibly could have.
That's right.
I got it backwards wrong.
Let's see here.
I'm just going to mute that person who is not muted.
Great.
Moving on.
Matt Donnelly, what would you like?
I would like to take the first, since I'm the second one going.
The first for 400.
Which of these platforms was released first, Twitter, TikTok or YouTube?
Oh, man.
I'll go with YouTube.
YouTube is correct.
Twitter was 2006, TikTok was 2016, YouTube was 2005.
Well done, Matt Donnelly.
I'll try the most for 400.
Which of these sports leagues have the most teams named after birds?
Oh, the NFL, the MLB or the NBA.
All right.
Bird time.
I think we've had a version of this question before.
I'm pretty sure we have.
I don't think it's Major League Baseball.
I'm just going to kick them right out.
Oh, I think that's the one that it is, Jacob.
This is where Paul does his subtle hints to help.
I can't think of any bird named teams in baseball.
In baseball?
The Blue Jays?
The Orioles?
The Cardinals?
Okay.
Other than those three though, I can't think of any bird teams in Major League Baseball.
The Reds.
The Reds are birds?
The New York Jets.
The Nickerbockers.
The Raptors.
Those are just pants.
Don't tell me the Raptors aren't birds because dinosaurs are birds.
Okay.
I'll give you dinosaurs.
The Wizards?
The NBA has the Hawks, the Pelicans, the Raptors, the NFL has the Cardinals, the Eagles.
Maybe it is baseball.
I think it is, but I can't remember.
They got three.
Yeah.
Is there another one in the NFL that I'm not thinking of?
We got the Cardinals and the Eagles.
The Ravens.
So that's three for NFL.
The Murderbirds?
The Murderbirds.
The Hawks?
Is there a Hawk team?
Yeah.
That's NBA.
Atlanta Hawks.
The NBA has the Pelicans, the Hawks.
Shit.
I've got three for baseball and three for football.
I got to be missing one in there somewhere.
I'm going to say football.
I'll say the NFL.
It is the NFL.
Five.
Major League Baseball has three.
So we named all of those.
Oh, and NBA has two.
Three.
If you chubby the Raptors.
Yeah.
Which we do.
We're Raptors.
Paul.
Seahawks.
Oh, that's another good one.
Oh yeah.
They're the Osprey.
I think that's the bird that the Seahawk refers to.
I'll take.
So that's four.
Who's that?
I'll take the last again.
The Dolphins.
That's it.
Chicken of the sea.
Yep.
Daily double.
Losing.
Which of these NFL players was the last to retire?
John Elway, Emmett Smith or Deon Sanders.
Emmett Smith.
Emmett Smith is correct.
Retired in 2004.
Sanders retired in '01.
Elway retired in '99.
Yeah.
Matt.
I will do the last for 1200.
The last.
Which Stooge was the first to die?
Last.
Larry Fine.
Last did I.
Sorry.
Larry Fine.
Moe Howard.
Curly Howard.
Pass.
Shit.
That's me.
I think Larry.
Oh wait.
Did Larry die?
No.
I think Moe died earlier.
Stooge to die.
The first is Stooge to die.
I think Moe died earlier.
I think Curly.
I'm going to say Curly.
The last.
Shit.
It was.
God damn it.
It was Larry.
It was Larry and I knew that too and I was still thinking the first.
God damn it.
He was living in the Hollywood retirement home.
It's true.
He was the last of the Stooges to die.
Yeah.
He famously lived in that Hollywood retirement home.
That's right.
Oh, that's me.
I guess I'll do the last for 2000 since I just lost all those points.
It's a Tom Bergeron has lots of stories about as a kid, he wrote letters to Larry Fine and
Moe Howard and actually becoming like pen pals and talk to them and stuff.
We'll call them on the phone and stuff too.
Yeah.
Oh nice.
Which retail chain was the last to close its final location?
Kmart, Sears, or Toys R Us?
That's a tough one.
I think there's still some Sears aren't there?
I think Sears is gone.
Is it?
I think so.
I kind of think Kmart was the last to close up.
I don't know.
Because I think Toys R Us, when Toys R Us closed, like they shut all of those down pretty
quick.
Yeah.
And I think it was very similar with Sears.
I'm going to say Kmart.
It is Kmart, October 24.
Jesus Christ.
Whoa.
Sears, 22.
And Toys R Us, 21.
I didn't even realize Sears was gone.
Yeah, Sears has been gone for a little bit.
That's crazy.
That's because you never bought Craftsman tools.
But I used to just go to Sears all the time.
I don't know what to tell you.
Paul.
All right.
It's gone, buddy.
The most, please.
The most for 800.
Which of these pies sells the most in the USA, apple, pecan, or pumpkin?
I mean, we say it's as American as apple pie.
I say that all the time.
But I got to believe pecan and pumpkin got a hotter business.
I'm going to go pumpkin.
Okay.
It's apple.
Ass.
29% of all pie sales.
Pumpkin number two, 23%.
Pecan coming up at the end, 9%.
I got to tell you, you people are missing out on some pecan pie.
I got October brain going on.
Yeah, you do.
I'm already in spooky season.
As soon as we flip to August, I'm like, "Ooh, ghosts and shit."
The last for 400.
The least, I mean.
The least for 400.
Daily double.
Yes, let's go.
This is where I strike.
Which of these three states has the least religious affiliation?
Vermont, New Hampshire, or Washington?
New Hampshire.
New Hampshire?
It's Vermont.
Only 63% of citizens claim religious affiliation.
New Hampshire is 64, and Washington, 68.
Those heathens.
You were close.
Those dirty.
Those heathens.
Those Vermont heathens.
Those syrup-chugging heathens.
I'll try the least for 800.
Syrup-chugging heathens.
Which of these states has the least trees per square mile?
North Dakota, Iowa, Nebraska.
I mean, here's the thing.
I'm going to say Nebraska, and I'm going to tell you why, because they got all that farmland.
They got so much farm there.
Same thing with Iowa, though.
I agree.
But I'm going to go with Nebraska.
I feel like they've got more farmland per capita than Iowa does.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Nope.
I'm just wrong all around.
It's North Dakota.
North Dakota was the correct answer.
I was just out.
Paul?
I will take the most for 2,000.
Oh.
Which of these celebrities is the tallest?
Alfred Hitchcock, Eminem, or Bob Villa?
Hitchcock.
Joke's on you.
I just had a party with Hitchcock, Eminem, and Bob Villa the other day.
Same height.
Same height precisely.
Bob Villa was the tallest.
5'9", Hitchcock, 5'7", Eminem, 5'8".
Man.
Burned by Bob Villa again.
How's that feel, Paul?
Will it never end?
Matt?
The most, 1,200, please.
Which of the countries read the most in a week per capita, Denmark, India, or the United
States?
No.
Oh, sorry.
United States right out.
No.
Yeah.
Is it Denmark, the one where they do the Christmas Eve, give each other a book, and you go hide
and read it all night?
Yeah.
Sure.
And then if you catch, if they find you in your reading spot, you have to hit them with
a sandal.
Right.
Yeah.
That's the tradition.
I'll pass.
Hit them with a sandal.
Passes to me, countries read, I'll guess India.
India.
Let's try India.
They got a lot of people.
I know that's not per capita, but whatever.
India is the right answer.
10 hours, 42 minutes, Denmark is still higher than the U.S.
Well, yes.
Yeah.
So you were correct about who had the least, Matt.
Great.
Yeah.
It's me.
I'll try the least for 1,200.
Which of these states has the least domestic pigs?
Now, wait a minute.
Does that mean the lowest amount of domestic pigs or the amount of pigs that are not well
domesticated?
I think it's the second one.
I think it's how many, which of them have the least domesticated pigs?
I like to wipe my ass on the couch.
Exactly.
I'm not very domesticated.
Rhode Island, Maine or Delaware.
I'm the least domesticated pig you'll meet.
I mean, Rhode Island just has to be a trick answer there, right?
Who knows?
Who can say it with this game?
Rhode Island is my little state, so you want me to pick Rhode Island because they don't
have the least domestic pigs because they're so small anyway.
Well, I'm not going to do it.
I am going to say Delaware.
So go fuck yourself.
Delaware is the correct answer.
Oh, I just gamed your game, only 300,000.
Now what do they mean by domestic pigs?
Pigs are far?
You know everything that I do, Paul.
It's your turn.
I'll go with the least.
For 2,000.
Which of these states has the least human limbs per capita?
Hint, it has the most amputees, Indiana, South Dakota or Louisiana.
Oh, by the way, there is a player who is signed to an NFL team right now who has six fingers
on one hand, making the average amount of fingers that an NFL player has more than five.
Wow, which is exciting.
Jason Pierre-Paul, who only has nine fingers because he blew one of them off, I think in
a fireworks accident, he's not currently in the NFL.
So the fact that there is one player with 11 fingers and everybody else has 10, the
average is above 10 now, which is wonderful.
Wow.
What do you think, Paul, Louisiana, Indiana or South Dakota?
Indiana, please.
Indiana has the least limbs.
I'm sorry.
It's Louisiana.
I have no data for any other states.
It's just something that Louisiana is proud of.
Well, they don't call it the big easy to lose your hands in for nothing.
That's right.
That is the full name.
Yeah.
Matt, you got the first for 800, 1200 or 2,000.
What are the scores right now?
You have zero points.
Perfect.
I have 2,800 points.
I am in the lead.
Paul is in a distant third place with negative 4,400.
So it's anyone's game.
Anyone's game.
Except Paul.
I'll go with the first for 2,000.
All right.
Which of these three movies came out first?
Lethal Weapon, RoboCop, Princess Bride.
Oh man.
I'm right back in like grade school for all of these.
Yeah.
I remember begging to see RoboCop with my older brothers.
Okay.
Because it was because then Princess Bride, I definitely watched it in grade school like
that was that was okay to watch in the school movie.
All right, man.
I don't these all feel like the same time.
I got nothing.
I'm gonna pass.
I passed the me shit.
Princess Bride is 80s RoboCop is also 80s, but Lethal Weapon is 80s.
You've cracked the code, son.
So you see how I'm doing my math out loud.
I am aware of your mathematicals.
I think it's RoboCop.
I think RoboCop was early 80s.
I think Princess Bride is later feels right to me.
I'm not sure when Lethal Weapon is but I would guess like mid to late 80s.
I'm gonna say RoboCop.
It's Lethal Weapon.
Oh shit.
I was wrong about all.
Oh god damn it.
This is one of these.
They were all 1987.
Lethal Weapon was March RoboCop was July Princess Bride was October.
Wow.
They were close.
I right on the head.
Can you imagine a year where we had those three movies in the same year?
1987.
Yes, but like that's easy.
Just imagine 1987.
I just didn't know nothing like that happens now.
I don't know.
Let's see.
I'll try the first.
Oh, let's see.
Where am I here?
I have 800 points now.
So 800 is enough to get me there.
The first for 800 among these three countries which was the first to learn about the good
news of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ, Ireland, Poland, India.
Let's see.
Brogan did you hear about Jesus before Poland or India did?
Fuck you Jacob.
Brogan the self-hating Irishman.
Who was the first to hear about it?
Poland, India or Ireland?
I mean Ireland is right there.
It's very close to several countries that really dug on Jesus Christ.
He got rid of them snakes.
That's right.
India.
I know we got to India.
I don't fucking know.
Paul, I'm passing.
I'll guess Ireland.
Let's try it.
It's India.
52 AD.
Ireland was 431 AD.
Poland was 966 AD.
Poland held out for a long time.
Paul closing out the category and the game the first for 1200.
Here I go.
Which of these three candy bars were released first?
Baby Ruth, Three Musketeers or the Milky Way?
Here's my math.
Nougat is a scheme.
Why is it that all of Paul's math involves nougat?
It's like they call it the nougat math.
I don't understand the nougat math with these kids today.
I'm going to go with Baby Ruth.
Okay.
Let's see it.
It is Baby Ruth 1921.
Milky Way was 1923, Three Musketeers 1932.
Paul got that question absolutely right, which pushes him all the way up to third place with
negative 4,000 points.
Matt's in second place with a big old goose egg.
That's zero points.
And I'm in first place with an impressive score of 800.
We crushed it.
We tow that scooperty up from the flow on up.
Thank you so much, neck pubes.
If you want to send us a scooperty or a price of Skrite Jock versus Nerd or an Obelisk Jock
versus Nerd, or just send us some scoop mail over there, head over to HayScoops.com right
there on the homepage.
You can send us some scoop mail.
You can do all those things, HayScoops.com.
Do it now.
We're running low on scooperties, Jock versus Nerds, all the Jock versus Nerds.
We're just running a little low on them.
Head over there and do that little thing.
Thank you so much if you do.
I want to thank all the scoops who got to join us today on today's Zoom call.
I want to thank all the people who are watching us on Twitch.
And I want to thank all the people who support us over, oh no, it's an invasion.
What's happening?
We've been invaded.
What?
Look who's on the Zoom.
It's Brian Brushwood.
Oh my God.
I thought there was maybe somebody else.
I was really confused there for a second.
I'm sorry.
I'm taking client meetings here.
What can I help you guys with?
I'm drawing charts and graphs and by God, how do you Zoom people do this?
You just Zoom all day.
It's not casting, but only one person's listening and then you don't get to run ads on it after
the fact.
That, doing the classes, the worst thing we've ever done.
You know what I got now?
Clients.
You know what I'm wearing right now?
A fucking white collared shirt.
The fuck is wrong with this world?
Sellout.
Yeah.
I'm working on it.
You know, it's even worse is you're about to get your ass handed to you at scoop fest
when we do the trivia battle.
So it's even harder day than you thought.
Hang your head in shame.
That is 100% the truth and everyone knows this.
Also I can't help but notice the room that Brian is sitting in.
Brian is in my house.
Brian is on the other end of my house right now.
Which only makes me a bigger asshole for missing the bulk of the program because I'm sitting
here like, oh yes, and this and well, the time we did it on the podcast, we did it like
ah.
Even more while you're racking up dick points, Brian, you were at the Orleans and did not
text me.
Yeah.
You know what?
I was too busy getting cornered by Michael Webber smirking his face off because he has
thoughts about because he's the fucking magic police and he's got opinions of what is good
to teach people.
Yes.
Sorry.
I didn't text.
I was waiting for this moment, but client meetings pushed it.
I was working in my backyard yesterday and Brian gets back from doing all of the things
that Brian is doing in town.
He walks into the backyard in slacks and a button down shirt and I didn't know what to
do with myself.
Well, first of all, SJ yelped and I made a joke, I'm like, I'm just here to check the
meter.
But the strangest thing happened because I walked in and obviously a lot of landscaping
was happening, a bunch of garden stuff and I see Jacob is edging the lawn and then I
look over, I talked to SJ and then my eye drifts down to a patch of Astro turf.
And then I follow the Astro turf over and I see the feet that Jacob is standing on,
on the Astro turf and I golden retriever my head a little bit as I try to consider why
is he edging the Astro turf?
And then I realized that's not an edger, he's pressure washing and we had a delightful conversation
about pressure washers.
We did.
I had just gotten through pressure washing several tons of rock when when Brian came
outside.
Brian because we I won't announce it on air but off air remind me to tell you that two
very high profile people got kicked out of magic life for wearing fake badges just to
go into the dealer's room.
That's okay.
I actually really that I'll tell you what, man, this is one of those things where it's
like if you become a high enough profile person, you better get legit because I used to I used
to be a hacker, pirater and stuff swimming on all the pirate days.
And then I started hosting a show with Tom Barrett called Cord Killers about how to watch
what you want when you want on streaming services.
And I realized how long how long until somebody rings the hypocrite bell on this.
And so I had I had to give up all of that unsavory behavior.
Yeah.
I mean, these guys should have done the same and if not, you heard it here first, Penn
and Teller kicked out of magic life, apparently they were recognized, actually, magic dragon
kicked out of magic live with his fake badge and magic suit in a bit to make it totally
hypocritical.
Well, one pen has no interest in going and tell her actually usually gets a VIP access
to the to the room before anyone else goes to just to walk Teller in and walk him around.
They do the same thing Copperfield and Blaine.
I met David.
I met David Blaine this year.
Oh, that's nice.
Met is a strong word.
I greeted David Blaine this year.
But yeah, anyhow, super fun, Brian, so glad that this is the only way we're seeing each
other while you're in.
No, I'm going to be here all week.
I insist that we meet up in person in fact, as a matter of fact, I'm going to go as soon
as we're done here.
I'm going to go to the Orleans, but I guess you won't be around.
I won't.
My festival is over.
My convention is complete.
So there are on the on the Las Vegas strip billboards all over the place.
There's all of these new ads being run about reporting cybercrime.
There's all these things there's like a Terminator cowboy on these electronic billboards like
if you know of someone committing cybercrime, scan this QR code and report them.
And we're standing outside last night looking at these billboards trying to figure it out
and why these billboards were there.
And then I finally realized, wait, DEF CON is happening this week.
Yep.
And I was like, Brian is staying in my house because DEF CON is happening this week.
I should know this.
That QR code is suspicious because of that.
I was about to say, right?
Talk about a honey pot there.
I will not be scanning any QR codes this week.
I would not be engaging my Wi-Fi anytime this week if you're anywhere around that.
Sorry.
Thank you so much for everybody for hanging out with us today.
We don't have any new list.
We don't have a new list yet to thank new people, but we will thank everybody this month
before the month is over with.
We have had some changes to our Patreon, which is all very exciting.
So go on over there, check it out right over there at preachingfun.com.
Or if you got kicked out of a convention because you're wearing a fake badge and you are extremely
famous, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com, it takes you to our Patreon page where for as little
as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Head on over there if you think this show is worth more than $0.
Also if you just want to piss off Brian Brushwood, listen to our show more and give us more money.
We sincerely appreciate every single one of you who donate, every single one of you who
listens.
We do.
Yeah, we love every one of you guys.
Thank you guys so much.
And don't miss ScoopFest.
There is still time.
Do it.
Buy a ticket.
Fly your ass out to Vegas and have a blast.
That's right.
Head on over there at scoopfest.com.
You can just go to heyscoops.com right there on the home page.
There's a button.
Buy your ticket to ScoopFest.
Call the Orleans Hotel and Casino here in beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada.
Or just tell them ScoopFest or use the offer code SupermanCatwomanFlash.
SCFI25C.
That's it.
Head on over there.
We used to have it written down in the churn.
You invented it, Jacob.
I'm surprised you can't remember it.
Well, you know, it's so much joy and positivity that goes into creating those QR codes, those
custom codes for our discount people over there at the Orleans.
It's too much joy to hold on to, honestly.
But yeah, head on over there.
Get yourself a room at the Orleans.
Come visit us at ScoopFest.
It'll be awesome.
I have some cyber crime to report.
I'll see you guys soon.
All right.
Take care of yourselves.
We love you.
And we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
Oh, Myra in the chat is pointing out right now SCF is for ScoopFest.
SCFI, I don't know what the I is.
It's for September.
Oh, September.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
That's that makes it makes a lot of sense.
That's that's just fair.