Paying extra for tire care is BS, you know, bad service.
So at Midas, we're rolling out our BS-free tire guarantee,
included with paid installation and tax on every purchase.
You'll pay nothing for flat replacements, nada for flat repairs,
and zilch for tire rotations every 5,000 miles.
That's zero dollars for all that.
So with this limited lifetime tire guarantee,
you'll pay a whole lot of nothing compared to what the other guys charge for tire care.
That's the BS-free tire guarantee, only at Midas.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go!
HeyScoops.com, right there, there is ScoopFest Swag.
Over there at HeyScoops.com, from this last ScoopFest.
Get the beds, you can get the robes, you can get the t-shirts.
HeyScoops.com, ScoopFest Swag.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting at C, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting at Pittsburgh, it's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting at Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're pretty much in fun.
Hey guys.
Hey, by the time you hear this, tomorrow night, Friday night,
I'm playing Sparta, New Jersey, two shows, Sparta Avenue Stage.
The 7pm is sold out, but my 9 o'clock is not.
So if you can be anywhere near Sparta, New Jersey,
or know anyone near Sparta, New Jersey,
tell them to come on out for a really fun show at 9 o'clock in Sparta.
It'll be awesome.
Where do they get tickets?
If you look up Sparta Avenue Stage,
you'll find it there or it's in the link of my MyNoodler bio on Instagram.
You can find the link there.
And then just to confirm, if they can't come,
but they still want to buy tickets, they can do that too, right?
Yes. If you love the performance art of buying tickets
and not showing up, go for it.
Also, then Paul and I, our shows are starting to sell pretty well here,
but we're doing stuff at Tierney's Tavern.
A lot of scoops are coming out.
I know, which is fantastic.
It's going to be another good scoop gathering October 23rd.
That's for sale on our website.
That's at heyscoops.com/comedynight.
Tickets are 20 bucks.
Yeah, and we've definitely moved a few tickets for that.
That is going to be a nice little scoop event.
It's a steal.
Get yourselves out there.
If you're in that tri-state area, make the magic happen.
You won't regret it.
Tierney's in and of itself is an experience.
That's true.
Are we going to be up in the upstairs again?
Yeah, we're going to be up in the upstairs.
Oh my fucking God, that spot is just tits.
Get you a can smashed burger.
It's going to be good, good times, baby.
In the old days, when our improv group was in the Twilight phase
of our improv group, we kind of would just throw shows together
up at Tierney's, and we would just do sets.
We would just do a set and stop, have some drinks, hang out,
then go like, ah, let's do another set, and we would kind of get up.
Like, I'm kind of envisioning something as fun and kind of casual as that.
Oh my God, I can't wait, dude.
Kurt's coming by.
We're just going to get up and do some free-for-long form?
Yeah, Dion's coming by.
I'll do some stand-up sets.
I'll do a couple of magic tricks.
Matt, this is a bad idea.
This is a bad idea, Matt.
Because after you sit down for a couple of minutes,
Paul's going to be like, they've seen funny stuff now.
We don't need to get back up again.
What are you talking about?
You're going to do a couple of sets, and then you're going to sit down
and start talking to people, and you're going to be like,
we don't need to do any more sets.
Are you crazy?
No, man.
You don't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know if you see the reaction from your other business partner,
but we both know.
What are you talking about?
No, man, we did double.
We've been doing double bucket shows for the last few Scoop Fests.
It's been great.
Who knows what it's all about?
Yeah.
I know, I know.
I'm not going to--
No.
It's going to be so good.
If we go late enough, we might get a cameo from a New Jersey celebrity.
We'll see.
But I'm not going to put the name out there.
But--
Bruce.
I'm not kidding.
I am down to improvise until the wee hours with new players and players,
players that I know are good.
That's going to be super, super fun.
I'm hungry for that shit.
Yeah, it's going to be so fun.
Just starting teaching--
Can smash burgers.
--just starting teaching this week.
The 20th will be my first class, officially, outside of my free classes
that I've been doing, which were great.
They've really been serving the job of getting my improv muscle back in shape,
and especially my teaching stuff.
Very good.
Yeah.
Yeah, very excited.
Well, in two nights, yeah, I got my improv jam reunion at the Smod Castle.
Yeah.
Kevin Smith is also doing an event that night where he's--
Wow.
--going to do something with mall rats.
So I might run into my old buddy, Kev, you know?
Yeah.
I might be able to--
Hey, man.
--get you a selfie.
--the pleasant trees and--
Yes, toss him a chip, baby.
A friend of mine wrote me.
He said, he's coming.
And he goes, wait, can I get a picture with Kevin Smith?
And I said, I mean, I can't help you with that, but yes.
As far as I'm concerned, you can.
You know, I don't know.
I think--
Either Kevin Smith doesn't remember who I am, which is very likely.
Yeah.
Right.
Or if he does, he's going to be like, hey, let's get a photo.
It's not going to be--
I don't know, man.
You don't think he'll suggest it?
I don't know.
He has become incredibly sentimental and sort of water under the bridge
about a lot of stuff, especially after the big heart attack event.
Yeah.
Right.
And that's only been like five years.
All right.
I think you might--
There's no reason to light this candle of hope for me, Paul,
but let's go for it.
OK.
This is the role I play.
I sit down and say, I've done enough.
And I tell people to go and make up with their mortal enemies.
I've already been funny today.
I don't need to be funny anymore.
I mean, there comes a certain point of diminishing returns, Jacob.
Don't I know it?
I'm getting some good guesses on who the New Jersey celebrity is.
Southside Johnny.
Chris Christie.
Oh, Chris Christie.
Oh, man.
I feel like we could get Southside Johnny.
I feel like we could get Chris Christie.
I should make some calls right now just to put a cap on it.
I think the Asbury Jukes might just be the house band.
Southside Johnny's becoming--
We were going to be there for dinner anyway, so why not?
[LAUGHTER]
Southside Johnny is slowly becoming bit worthy.
I have more scoops to write me.
Be like, wait, who was the guy that you guys always talk about?
And I have to always be like Southside Johnny.
I keep forgetting the name.
I have been trying to get Southside Johnny to be
a bit on this podcast for years.
It is finally reaching critical mass, where it would be a bit to get him
to show up somewhere as a thing.
Yes, yes, for sure.
I'll tell you-- oh, did we say this on air or no?
But there was someone I was trying to get for the variety show that
was going to make the crowd go wild that I couldn't get.
Oh, we did not say this on air.
That is, we took a swing for Scoop Fest, and we weren't able to hit it.
I could not get in touch with Monroe.
I was trying so badly to get Monroe, the retired garbage truck
driver, to come sing a song because he sings in the church.
Couldn't get him, huh?
I was trying very hard to get Monroe to Scoop Fest.
You were.
Matt really worked to try to get Monroe.
You just could not find him.
And I was like, I don't know how I'm going
to dance on this thin ice that we're going
to dance on to get him in and out of Scoop Fest
without him knowing that the joke is that he fucks my wife.
But I was going to try.
I mean, you know, you keep playing with that kindling,
you're going to get a fire.
It's up to you.
Monroe is either going to show up and sing it
in the village or fuck Matt's wife.
That's what I mean, or both, buddy, or both.
Maybe, that's true.
It could never happen, Paul.
I'm always home.
[LAUGHS]
What's that in the background?
Oh, oh, you're on a boat.
OK.
I've been away since the very end of Scoop Fest.
I've been away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there are other semen you need
to be worried about, my friend.
Good gravy.
No, that's going to be exciting as hell.
So this week, you know, I'm still kind of just rolling
from my eye emergency bullshit, which I think
is going to just turn out to be much do about nothing,
Tempest in a teapot type shit.
I hope I get a x-ray next week to see what's happening.
And then I fly away, wee, to New Jersey the next day.
So but, you know, never stops.
You guys know, everybody's busy, busy, busy.
And between all my other little shit that I'm doing,
we're getting our house finally painted.
And has been desperate to get the house painted for years.
Whoa.
Glad.
And yeah, it's a big thing.
It's a big change.
So our house was created in the '80s.
And it very much is that--
I like that Paul's house was created.
Other houses were built, but Paul's house created.
This was created in the '80s.
And it's very much the same color
as the Ford Tempo I used to drive back in the '80s.
And it is-- I picture every Ford Tempo
as being a shade of brown.
It is two-tone brown.
Good.
This is where it's beginning.
And here's where we're going.
And it's already--
This is why you want to be on Zoom and on Twitch right here.
That's right.
Because you get to see pictures of Paul's house getting
painted.
Yes.
Already happening.
Watch pictures of paint dry.
Does anything be more interesting than that?
Nothing could be more exciting.
But it's turning out.
iPhone videos of paint dry.
It's turning out beautiful, honestly.
It's really going to be gorgeous.
And you can see how much brighter and cheerier
it already is just with one little application.
Oh, that is nice.
It really is nice.
And we're going to get white trim.
And the brick's going to get worked on.
And what do you call that?
They're going to lime wash the brick.
So it's kind of light and all kinds of things like that.
So it's going to be really nice.
Oh, is that how they do the light--
the straight brick look?
That is oftentimes what is utilized, the lime wash.
Yes.
And so we are hoping that that all continues to move forward.
We've got all the paint and everything.
But the guy yesterday, as he's leaving,
they had to leave early to go work on another job.
And I was like, OK.
And then he says, oh, I'll be back at 9 tomorrow
in the morning.
So Ann and I both get up.
I get up early on my off day.
Instead of sleeping my little butt away all day
like I wanted to do, I get up and make sure everything's
ready to go, get the garage door open,
get the paint cans set up and everything.
Let the snakes in.
And nothing, nobody, nothing.
Nobody showed the whole day, finally.
Finally, at right about 1 o'clock,
the project coordinator called me up and was like, hey,
yeah, nobody showed up today because blankety blank blank.
And I'm like, OK, well, all right, great.
So but at least they touch base.
This is far more communication than any other contractor
in this burg.
But it's just always the way it is.
But it's fine.
We're already happy with how things are going.
But man, oh man, if it ain't one thing.
That's looking good.
Yeah, yeah, we're really, we're really happy.
And Ann's over the moon.
And I, for one, cannot wait for you to get that white trim.
You're going to be so relaxed.
I just need--
I need my white trim.
Well, we took-- they took down the shutters.
They took down all the shutters.
And these shutters are just these cheap old little plastic
fakey things.
They're fake as hell, right?
They're not even--
What if a tornado comes through?
Then these would be the first things to go.
They're not even-- they're just pieces of plastic.
So as we pulled them all down, we
must have got 10 different calcified ancient wasp hives--
Oh, yeah.
--out of the backs of those things.
It's wild.
Yeah, yeah.
But we've got an excellent anti-wasp plan now.
Have I told you guys about Ann's fake wasp nests?
No.
We have fake wasp nests strategically
placed all over the yard.
Wait, in that-- what's afraid of wasps?
I mean, besides humans.
And then I would make a human, by the way.
Wasps.
Wasps are afraid of other wasps?
If there is a wasp nest already constructed,
they will-- they will make a point
to not build a wasp nest within 40 yards, I think it is,
of that wasp nest.
Oh, that's right, because wasps use imperial measurements.
I have heard this before.
Yes, yes, yes.
They will not use the metric system.
They do not use the metric system.
It is the USA and wasps.
40 yards.
So these nests that she got--
the nests-- they are--
they're basically Chinese lanterns, you know,
without the lantern component.
But it just expands with a little wire frame inside,
loose little wire frame inside.
And it looks like just a little--
it looks like a wasp nest.
You hang them up in the trees and stuff.
And our neighbors were like, oh my god, you got--
and I'm like, no, no, no.
Fakeity fake.
This is keeping the real deal at bay.
Your neighbors were like, you are overrun, sir.
It's true.
There were like three of them.
There's three of them in the backyard and one in the front.
You were in trouble.
It's like--
You need to move immediately.
You guys are about to be inundated.
We're like, we're OK.
We're OK.
So yeah.
My aunt had--
so I never know the right terminology for this anymore,
because back then, it was the Africanized bees in the '90s.
Let's stick with that.
That sounds right to me.
Yeah.
Let's don't change it from anything from that.
Yeah, I just don't know what to actually--
I don't know what the real name of it is.
What the fuck is the real name of that?
Would you have like--
Technically-- technically, Zimbibwe.
Whatever the real fucking name of that is supposed to be--
That's the technical term.
That's what they called it.
I'm not saying that.
That's what they called it in the '90s.
And my aunt's house got overrun with bees--
What?
--to the point that they had to sell the house.
That's one of Kurt Bronneler's best comedy bits.
He closes out one of his specials.
He talks about my aunt's house?
It might be.
Yeah.
He talks about a house being overrun with bees,
and how when they get in there, they discovered-- what was it?
10 million bees or something like that?
Oh, this wasn't that bad.
Still--
I don't think this is Kurt's story, then.
But that's how Kurt closes out one of his comedy specials,
talking about just how the fuck do
you ignore that your home has 10 million bees in it?
I mean, when it happened in my aunt's house,
there was just a constant swarm of bees around the house.
It was horrifying, and no one knew why.
Well, that's the thing.
If you're from Zimbibwe, you don't notice.
That's right.
Where the walls are paved with honey, Zimbibwe.
[LAUGHTER]
Zimbibwe.
I am not comfortable with that.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, Penn's old place, the slammer,
was overrun with bees before its demise, as well.
I do remember that.
Yeah, they had a bunch of nests all over the place in that place.
You just see honey running in from anywhere.
It was really strange.
I just drove past--
this last week, I drove past where the slammer was.
I was thinking about the slammer this week.
Oh, so sad.
Yeah, yeah, just--
You can't even dig just a big bunch of houses.
You can't even figure it out.
Did they develop-- it's a whole development now, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little block in a neighborhood now.
Yeah, there were two really cool houses right in that area.
There was Penn's house, and there
was this giant white house that had four windmills on it.
Yeah, both of those houses are gone now.
Those were two weird houses right next to each other,
and it made me sad that they're both gone.
Yeah, yeah.
Yep.
So I was just down in--
one of my stops was Boston, Massachusetts.
Uh-huh, Boston, Massachusetts.
Oh, I heard all about it.
I talked to your wife the other day, and she was like,
I am doing this, I'm doing this, and Matt's
hanging out in Boston.
There's no getting around it.
This sucks to be her.
I don't know how--
Sorry, Sarah.
And so do I just call it every day,
be like, it's miserable for me, too.
I'm doing nothing.
No, no, I think you're playing the right--
No, because she's not buying that.
She's simply not buying it.
You're playing the right move.
You got to just lean into it.
So one of the comedians on board
is a guy named Rondell Sheridan.
OK.
I know Rondell Sheridan.
He's hilarious.
That's it.
He's a very funny--
He's on board your ship right now.
Yes.
Incredible.
And so Rondell has been amazing, right?
Yeah.
It was funny, because I once saw his show.
It was funny.
And then this guy on board, Tom, who knows, like,
everyone who does Virgin Ships, he goes,
you never see Rondell Sheridan.
You see him do his shows, and you see him come down for food,
and you never see him around.
And then the second night, like, we made conversations
with Rondell, and we started talking sports and stuff.
And then he started hanging out.
Started hanging out with us.
Oh, yes.
So Rondell, most people know him as the dad from--
that's so Raven.
He was Raven's dad.
And he's directed-- he's been and directed a bunch of shows
for Disney Channel.
But you look at his old stand-up bits,
there are old stand-up bits that you don't realize are his.
You go back and look, and you're like, oh, that's his.
Like, the famous parachute man who survived after bouncing
on the ground twice.
I don't know if you remember that bit.
So we're supposed to go to Maine.
The seas are too rough, and the currents are too strong
for us to go to Maine.
So the ship pulls an audible and just says,
hey, let's go to Boston early.
Let's haul ass to Boston and do an overnight.
Yeah.
Overnights are so rare, and they're the fucking best.
I did one in Tenerife, Spain.
And it's just like, you just-- the whole ship's
just excited to roll into town and go out for the night,
right?
So it's just the buzz in the air or whatever.
Wait, what do you mean-- what's an overnight?
You get to Boston at nighttime?
The ship's going to be parked.
Your ship basically becomes a hotel.
You are now in Boston for the night.
Oh, right. OK, great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You don't have to come running back at 415
to make sure you don't get left behind.
Right, OK, you got a floating hotel in Boston.
Floating hotel in Boston.
Everyone can stay out all night, right?
Great.
So Tom--
That was one of the best things.
I still talk about that from the Bermuda scoop cruise.
That was great, because that boat just parked at Bermuda,
and we had a hotel at Bermuda.
It was perfect.
It was so fun.
It was so fun, sailing out every night
and stumbling back to the ship.
Yes.
So I haven't spent time out in Boston
since I was in my 20s.
Yeah, who would?
Who would?
Who would want to?
Indeed.
So Tom does the research, and turns out
there's this magic lab, Boston Magic Lab,
does a magic open mic, open mic with a wink face.
So as I was out shopping, I was like, I'm going to haul that.
I'll haul my ass back to the ship
and throw some fish in a backpack, and let's go.
Matt shows up with a fucking rolling suitcase.
All my two full cases.
Let's go, motherfuckers.
Open this mic.
But Tom does some advanced research.
It turns out, no, it's open mic.
The sign-up is beforehand, not day of,
because people have to work on their tricks, obviously,
or whatever.
And so we were told that, no, it is a set lineup.
I mean, they should definitely have a couple of spaces
put aside if somebody just shows up.
This is the debate.
This is the debate that we were having.
OK?
Yeah.
Tom did his due diligence, because of everything I do,
just being the co-host at Penn Sunday School is the big one.
I mean--
Sure.
--almost every magician listens to Penn Sunday School.
Right.
And so, like--
You were known in the world of magic,
if for no other reason than because of that show.
And then one of the guys in the lineup
has done "Fool Us" a couple of times.
I mean, Tyler Twaldy.
So you've got the connects.
Yeah.
But I-- but no, no, no.
We make no waves.
There's no scuttlebutt that we are there.
We just buy tickets.
We watch.
And then we watch open mic.
And it's an open mic.
It is an open mic, like comedians have an open mic,
like musicians at a coffee house have an open mic.
It is the same open mic.
It's not better or worse.
It is as good as an open mic.
The level of goodness is open mic level.
It is an open mic.
It is an open-faced mic, hot and brown.
But what's cool is because it's like this open mic concept
is that no one was just doing a trick they bought.
And no one was doing like a--
Oh, that's cool.
And no one was just doing like an off-the-rack trick.
Everyone was going for something different, original,
or something with some kind of intellectual bite,
something with some kind of narrative,
something with some kind of feel.
So I did really like that a lot.
And my buddy Tyler did kill it.
He did a really fun couple of routines and stuff.
And that part was great.
But there was a guy who was so socially awkward.
I mean, they were all like college professors
and shit like that.
It's like a magic club, basically.
And he was this older Asian professor
who dressed up like Marty McFly from "Back to the Future."
Oh, I love this person already.
I know.
He was so shy.
But he worked on his script within an inch of its life.
And it was really well-written.
Yes.
And he was doing time machine stuff with an hourglass,
like little mini hourglass.
And then he was doing coin stuff where coins were disappeared
and returned to his hands based on the hourglass.
Oh, he just dressed like Marty McFly.
So he wasn't doing like a Marty McFly bit.
He was doing a time traveling bit.
Oh, this is good.
This is a good-- this is a fine bit.
I'm very happy with this bit.
And sometimes he wasn't laughing at some of his jokes
because he was just delivering so stone cold across the board.
I just turned to Tom and I was like, I love this guy.
I'm in love with this man.
I fucking love him.
And I was laughing at all of his bits.
And I was loving everything he was doing.
Yeah.
And he was making fun of himself for dressing like Marty McFly.
And when he wanted to do time travel that was more significant,
he got a bigger hourglass.
[LAUGHTER]
I got to go further back.
Hold on.
This is like-- I was like, no notes, man.
Let me just buy this routine off of you.
This is great.
All you're missing is decades of social skills.
Other than that, you are fucking nailing it.
Golden.
[LAUGHTER]
But he was so likable and everything.
It wasn't even like-- I'm being harsh.
But he was so likable and funny.
Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, but then afterward it was funny.
Like, I went up to one guy and Tom went up to another guy.
No one decided to hold court.
No one decided to say, hey, you're here.
We should introduce you to everybody.
We should get a photo or whatever.
Oh, that's nice.
No, no one did that.
No one did that.
Right.
That's what I'm saying.
That's nice.
Oh, no.
I thought we should have all got a big photo.
Oh, I see what you mean.
OK.
Yeah, fine.
Because I put a photo up of it saying,
had a blast tonight at Boston Magic Lab
and got all these notes saying, I didn't know you were there.
Holy shit.
I would have said hello.
Oh, I got all this stuff.
I was like, well, I didn't know.
I threw out my name.
As much as comfortable as I am throwing my name around,
I threw my name around.
Right.
There you go.
I guess as I was saying, it's surprisingly
less than you'd think.
[LAUGHTER]
But then, Ron Down wants to come out.
And so--
Right.
Does he come with you to the magic thing?
We find-- he says he's too tired to go to the magic thing.
Sure.
We all are, Ron Down.
And as a comedian not wanting to rush through a magic open mic,
I totally understand.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
But we decide we're going to go to a comedy club
in the middle of Cambridge, the college comedy club.
OK.
And so we roll up with Ron Down Sheridan,
and Guy recognizes him right away.
Of course, because he's comedy royalty.
Right.
He's stand-up royalty, that guy.
And we sit down and we get--
Is this that guy from Boston Commons?
Was he there?
Who's that cat that came up with that TV show?
He was a stand-up?
Oh, I don't know.
I haven't heard of him for like a decade.
Yeah.
Oh, I need to look that up.
But he--
Everybody drink.
He--
Paul brought up a story.
He doesn't know what the ending is.
Everybody drink.
I just don't know the guy's name.
And we sit down.
And of course--
That was the only part of your story.
It's the--
True.
They, of course, come up and say, hey,
we can get you a slot if you want to do time.
And I go, comedy clubs get it.
These magic clubs get one or two from these comedy clubs.
They know.
I could have easily had a spin pad and a couple of fish in my backpack.
Anthony Clark.
Anthony Clark was the comedian I was fishing for.
Anthony Clark, who started--
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for bringing it up.
And just to make sure we're being clear about the story,
Anthony Clark, not involved in the story whatsoever.
OK.
That's what I want.
I thought perhaps he might have been,
because I don't know what he's been doing
besides possibly hiding in Boston hosting open mic nights.
I also don't know what Anthony Clark has been up to lately.
But he might have been up to something with the following sponsor.
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
He might have been up to something with the following sponsor.
It might have happened.
I simply don't know what he's doing.
This was a regular line-up night.
This was not an open mic night.
This was--
No, no, no.
Following sponsor.
Oh, sorry.
I started reading the chat.
I was too clever for my own good.
Yeah, I know.
Today's show is brought to you by the fine people of--
Go.
Go, phone.
Go to the website.
I think I'll just--
Four floors of whores.
If you've got the balls, we've got the whores.
That's from Scoop Me Hard in 2025.
So there you go.
I was at this place last night.
Hello, everyone.
It's me, Vincent Price.
I'm here to tell you about my newest attraction.
Four floors of whores.
Yes.
Open the doors.
There are the whores.
Doesn't matter what floor it's yours.
Because there they are.
Come on in.
Whores.
Would you like some porridge?
I've got some on the stair store.
When you enter the first floor, you may notice many whores.
But I'll have you know, the second floor contains more.
Open the door to the second floor.
You'll find more whores.
They abhor.
Abhor.
So be exciting and give them something more.
Oh, what's in this closet over here?
That's not a closet.
Oh, it's a storage.
That's just storage for the porridge.
That's porridge storage.
You found my porridge storage.
Can I have some porridge?
Sure.
Now go up the door to level three whore.
Guess what?
More whores.
On level three.
Are you surprised?
You shouldn't be.
Because the name of the place is four floors of whores.
I'm just waiting until we get to the fourth floor.
This is Sam Elliott for whores original.
Cool whores original whores whores.
Sam, who would have thought you would have been barring the door for floor four?
Here in my house of many whores.
Can I get by you, please?
No.
Oh.
Well, I guess this is where our tour ends.
No more tours of floors for the four.
You'll have to find out what's on floor four.
I can almost guarantee you it's just more whores, but still.
Don't forget to try the porridge.
And pay scoops at checkout.
I swear, honey, I go there for the porridge.
And the conversations with Vincent Price.
I eat porridge and I talk to Vincent Price.
You should come.
The Nevada DMV doesn't know what happens to snitches, apparently.
No, no, what happened?
The Nevada DMV has started a program to what they say.
Oh, I do know about this.
This is fucked up.
This is stupid.
So Nevada has a problem.
Especially Las Vegas has a problem on the roads.
And that is unregistered vehicles.
Unlicensed.
Yeah, yeah, no license plate on them, nothing.
And so the Nevada DMV, I suppose in conjunction with Metro or whatever,
they have started a program where it's just a tattle program.
They have a thing on there where you can now report cars that are unregistered
to the Nevada DMV.
And I saw a report today that they got 1,500 reports on their first day.
Jesus, it's 1,500.
I don't know.
But there's nothing to be done about this.
I think this is just a thing about people leaving old cars in their yard.
I mean, that's some of it.
Some of it is absolutely neighbors snitching on neighbors.
I'm tired of that junker sitting there.
There's a lot of that.
But there's also just a lot of just snitching.
That's not a good idea.
It's a very bad idea.
They don't fucking know that snitches get snitches.
Ain't nobody told them.
It's a terrible idea.
The DMV was basically dismantled through a hack and took a month to recover.
And they're like, all right, now that we're back, let's start ratting people out.
Sorry, we couldn't get shit done for a month.
I've been getting hammered for this real ID thing.
I traveled with a passport.
Do you not have a real ID yet?
No, so I made an appointment to get a real ID and I went in.
They're like, oh, we got hacked.
We can't get you set up right now.
We have to make another appointment for you.
They're like, we're not recovered from the hack yet.
And I was like, oh, well, I'm glad you guys kept the appointments.
Thanks for letting me know before I got here.
What a bunch of, yeah, our appointments didn't get hacked, but everything else did.
Yeah, but sure.
Let's do that.
The Nevada Department of Motor Vehicles has recently added a Nevada Registration Spotter Report Forum on their website,
which is intended solely for the purpose of reporting motor vehicles operating on Nevada roadways with expired,
invalid or no registration, including Nevada residents operating vehicles with illegal out-of-state plates.
So they want neighbors to report on each other.
They say that this report is not intended for abandoned vehicles, traffic violations.
Oh, and vehicles, parking violations or other DMV related issues.
This is only supposed to be for cars on the roadway without registration.
And we all know that's not the only thing that's getting reported.
Yeah. Why? Yeah. Why doesn't make any sense.
I never understood driving around Las Vegas.
You will honestly see tons of vehicles with just no license plates.
And every time I would see that, I'm like, why would a police officer not pull that person over immediately?
And a friend of mine got pulled over for fucking expired registration just the other night.
And I was like, how? Why? Why did this cop decide to finally pull you over for expired registration
when there must have been 20 cars that drove past while you were stopped without license plates at all?
Yeah. I know that happened to you, Jacob, to another friend of yours when your friend's son was in your car.
That is true. I do. I had a friend of mine's son was in my car with me and then my friend got pulled over in his son.
And me and his son went, huh. Jacob had to talk my son off the ledge.
I was like, no, no, no. Everything's going to be fine. Everything's just fine.
Yeah, galactic president scooper star is exactly right.
It's like, hmm, what else does the government ask people to start informing on their neighbors?
I'm sure it's fine. Yeah. It is maybe not historically relevant in any way.
It's baby steps to some real bullshit, y'all. Just crack a book once in a while, you motherfuckers.
All I do want, though, is to see all of these reports roll again.
I just want to see just every single report that comes in.
I want to see how it's worded. I want to see the report itself. I want to see all of this.
The closest like citizens arrest. We've really gotten here, which is like I'm doing a citizen's arrest.
I'm doing a license plate to a concealed carry for your expired registration.
How about that? I mean, what this is going to this is going to cause big problems.
And I tell you what it's going to do.
This is going to cause a fight where somebody is going to get killed in like a grocery store parking lot.
Because two motherfuckers are going to start arguing and one of them is going to start like reporting it on the on the Web or something like that.
And then somebody is going to get fucking stabbed in a parking lot.
Yeah, all over all over this shit. Yeah, it's going to be bad.
This is a bad idea. If anybody from the Nevada DMV is listening and I know you are.
This is a bad idea. I mean, we're the number one Vegas parking and weather podcast.
So, of course, that's right there. Of course, we are where the cars get parked parking and weather.
No one does it better than I see, especially not the Nevada DMV. No. Get your shit together.
Absolutely right, Jacob. Thank you for bringing this to our attention.
I also have been seeing through the national media what little trickles down that Vegas had some serious flooding this last week.
Oh, yeah, we had a we had a crazy rainstorm blow through here. We had hail at the house.
We had we had hail at my house. Yeah, it was it was this does not sound like much anywhere else.
But but we had over an inch and a half of rain in about an hour. Get the fuck out of that.
No, that's that's insane. I didn't realize it was that major for for Vegas.
That's the death. Yeah. Yeah, that's why I know multiple people died. People died.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Multiple people died. They found multiple bodies drowned.
Yeah, yeah. All that horrible stuff. Yeah, it was it just like it came out of nowhere.
It blew in and it was hard. Apparently it was off of a tropical storm. Priscilla, I think they said it was a remnant of a tropical storm.
Queen of the desert. I believe so. Queen of the Mojave. Yep. Well, she did bring water. Yes.
She left her parents. That's a good question.
Galactic president scooper star McScoops a lot was the obelisk damaged in my in my backyard. The obelisk has been put away. So so thankfully the obelisk was safe.
Good, good, good. Weirdly, my wife didn't want an obelisk just sitting in the backyard year round
because she is a party pooper. Clearly.
Boo her boo my wife. Don't boo my wife. She'll punch you.
When we last left off, Matt was just getting a comedy club with Rondell. Yes.
So Ronnie Sheridan goes in and this is a different open mic. It's a comedy open mic.
No, it's not. It's a regular lineup. It's a lineup. Oh, it's a regular show. Yeah. Yeah.
This is after the magic open mic. This is regular comedy show Friday night in Boston. We're not doing open mics on Friday night in Boston.
We're doing we're doing a lineup of closed mics. Boston's best.
Colin Quinn. Just Colin Quinn.
We can get you a spot up on stage because right now we just have Colin Quinn.
We actually need openers and features as well. Colin Quinn on a series of iPads on sticks around comedy clubs all across Boston.
That'd be great. Colin Quinn performing at every comedy club in Boston simultaneously.
We're in a college town. And so the comedians are all like 30s, you know, late 20s, early 30s, kind of folks.
Collegiate. Rondell gets up and he announces that he is 67 years old.
And he starts doing bits and he just plows through like 15 minutes of just assassinating, just fucking killing and crushing across the thing.
He finds this one guy. He did a little crowd work. He finds this one guy and he's like, he goes, what do you do?
He's like, I'm an MMA fighter. And he's like, oh, shit, I should stop talking to you.
And he goes, what's your name? And the guy says, I think I have it right. He goes, Letremaine Montgomery.
It's like the old Key and Peele bit.
Rondell goes, man, could you have a blacker name than that?
He goes, ain't nobody going to fight you. No one's going to sign up to fight Letremaine Montgomery.
That's it. You're the champ.
He goes, you're a legit fighter. He goes, yeah, I have my Texas fighting license.
Oh, oh, that is legit.
And the whole crowd roars. He goes, do you keep that with your fishing license, with your hunting license, with your fishing only using guns license?
Fishing only using guns.
It is a special license.
Rondell killed it. And then, man, people lined up. We couldn't leave.
We couldn't leave. People just lined up. Everybody wanted a photo with them.
We finally get them out of there. We pile into a pub. Everyone in the bar makes out who he is.
And the waitstaff is all taking photos with him. I had no idea how popular the show.
I just said it.
That's So Raven?
That's So Raven was.
It's a different generation. It's after all of our time. I'm aware of it.
It's the choice of a new generation.
Since then, I've been hanging out with Rondell. So we went out yesterday in Charleston, South Carolina.
Oh, that's awesome.
And I'm just going past Paul's joke.
Good, good. I gave it a thumbs down.
We were stopped constantly. I got on the boat without him for like an hour.
Then I came at him back and we walked from the boat and I walked right back the path that I walked up and we couldn't catch up to our friends because he was being stopped so often by people who were filming out that it was him.
And I was like, my God, I had no idea how famous this guy was.
He's been an absolute gem. We've just been hanging out and joking around on the boat. It's been so fun.
Are you parked next to Disney cruise ships, too?
We're not.
I was going to say, because that would tip it over to like insane.
Everywhere we parked, we've been by ourselves.
Why would the Disney thing be a different thing?
Because it shows on Disney Channel.
Oh, I see.
That's how Raven is a Disney thing.
Gotcha, gotcha.
Yeah, but so it's super fun. Super fun adventures with Rondell Sheridan.
Yeah, nice. Yeah, nice.
So did you get him a chip?
Yep.
Sure.
Do you think we might be able to get him on the show sometime?
Yes.
I do want to get him on the show.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
He's not going to listen, but he'll come on.
I don't care if he listens.
Correct.
I said that as a joke, but we all know it's just true.
It's just true.
Yeah.
I'll tell you who else we might be able to get on the show sometime if we work really hard at it.
And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Four Floors.
No, I'm kidding.
The fourth floor.
Columbastro, private investigator in space.
That's Columbastro.
That is an old bit.
That's from the Microscoop from 2021. So it is. It's requested from 2021.
Is this a bit from Geek Shack?
It is.
Next commercial.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I'm sorry to come into your space here.
I want to get into your airlock just for one minute.
I don't want to deplete any oxygen systems here.
Have I got just one more question there.
When you first encountered Mr. Zambalaxes, did you actually realize he was the president of this alien world
that you were hoping to invade?
Or was that just a coincidence that you two just happened to hit it off, he and your space daughter?
Do I need a space lawyer right now?
Look, sir, I'm not a professional in any sense of the word, but I like to watch, I like to listen, I like to hear.
Even in space, I can hear you scream, you know what I'm saying?
But look, OK, if you tell me that there's nothing to investigate here, I'm going to be on my way.
But you just let me know if I can park my shuttlecraft over on your aft docking port later.
I was just going to leave it there for a half hour or so.
One second. I'm space texting my space lawyer.
That's fine. That's fine. You go ahead and do that.
Future sounds, futuristic sounds as I type it.
Yeah, OK. Well, all right. Well, I'll let you know.
Hello, Matt Notley. I am your robot space lawyer. What can I do for you?
Got him on the line there.
I'm being questioned here by, what was it, Columbastro, you said?
Columbastro, I'm just a private detective, sir, out in space. That's, you know, kind of what I do.
Whatever you do, don't try to walk away from him. He will have one more thing he wants to talk to you about.
No, that can't be true. I'm going to walk away right now.
I mean, that seems a little presumptuous of your robot.
See you later.
Your robot. That's quiet air. But just one more thing before I do go.
I'm just going to float.
I told you so.
I can float here because you're low gravity. I get to float around.
But I did want to know, just want to, are you yourself, sir, an avid collector of phaser rifles?
Do you have a lot of phaser rifles in your home?
Do you keep those loaded? Do you keep the phaser ammunition separate from the phaser rifles?
Isn't it illegal to hold phaser rifles in your home?
Not at all. But, you know, you do want to have a safety precautions. You want to make sure that this...
Alright, I did it. You got me.
Columbastro wins again.
Enter eight scoops of checkout. Get some every time.
He broke me down.
I still think, like, we are not far away. I should fucking write that treatment, because I don't know if you know.
Do you know?
Do I know how much time is being made right now?
Yes.
Right. You're right. But...
Are you talking about the movement?
I'm talking about...
The Lumbo movement?
I'm talking about Catherine Janeway.
Captain Catherine Janeway.
What's that actress's name? I'm fucking blanking on her name.
Everybody drink, Catherine Janeway Jones.
No.
Catherine O'Hara.
Anyway, Kate Mulgrew. Thank you, chat.
So, I don't know if you know, but early in Kate Mulgrew's career, she portrayed none other than Lady Columbo.
So it's not that far to have a space Columbo happening.
She's a space detective.
I think it would be great. I would love to...
Lady Columbo.
Let me text my space lawyer right now.
Get a hold of him.
He doesn't sound happy.
You rang, sir.
Yes. There's a Lady Columbo here.
Wants to talk to me about...
Calm yourself.
I've just got one more thing, please. Just give me one moment. Just one moment.
Oh, Jakote. Jakote, you are my rock. I can't...
You know what I need? I need a stiff cup of coffee. Hot.
What's going on with Seven? Where is she? I like that sparky young boy.
Did you see the movement to replace Christopher Columbus statues with Columbo statues?
Yes. Yes. And I'm 100% here for it.
Man.
It's a great idea.
I am watching Task on HBO.
Okay.
And that is a very dark, dark show. It's in the makers of Mayor of Easttown, which is already a very dark show.
So you've been able to stick with it. We bounced off so early.
It is so good. It is so depressing. And it is so dark that I get anyone...
It is so good at making me depressed.
Yeah. It is amazing acting about a very depressing area of our country.
Yeah.
It is so sad. And...
It's meth, right?
There's a thing with...
I mean, the plot line's a little meth-y, but I don't know.
Got him!
It's more of a history and science than meth.
Gotcha. Gotcha.
No, no, no. There's kilos of... I think it's heroin in it that play a key plot point.
But it more ends up being about is the system like other corrupt people in the system kind of thing.
But Mark Ruffalo just is Columbo. He just is Columbo.
He's just doing a Columbo impression.
He's channeling Columbo.
Exactly like Peter Falk, mosing in and out. He's an older, out of shape.
He definitely has the disheveled thing going on.
That's it. He's got this big disheveled hair, which is exactly like Peter Falk's hair.
Yeah. He's got frumpy, wrinkly shirts.
He's the guy who's been out of the field. He gets called back in the field because it's an emergency situation.
And so he gets called back to head of task force and he doesn't know who he can trust on his own force.
And so he does things where he starts questioning people, trying to break them down.
And I am laughing. I'm like, this is just... He's mosing in. He's aching.
You know? Just one more thing.
He ends up through plot points as having a head injury and a back injury.
And so he's just touching his head and mosing in and seeming kind of out of it and then questioning people and making them want to confess to things.
And I'm like, this is just... This is just secretly high-end Hollywood white trash Columbo at the same time.
This is just all... And it's really distracting because it's such a dead serious show.
I bet. Because he's so good.
Yeah. But no, it's a tough show to get. I love it, but it's a tough show to get through for sure.
If I wasn't on a cruise ship alone, constantly staying up from 4 o'clock in the morning watching stuff, I would do it.
I'm also watching Peacemaker, which I really love. Peacemaker is so good.
We just watched another episode of Peacemaker last night. This new season is kind of amazing.
Yeah.
The writing in this season is just really, really good.
Oh my God. There's a running gag. It is so ridiculous. Tim Meadows plays a character in this season.
Yes! It's so great.
And Tim Meadows says he has a condition called bird blindness, where he can't distinguish any kind of bird from any other kind of bird.
And they find ways for this to come up. You forget that there's a bird in the equation and all of a sudden Tim Meadows talks and he just says something totally wrong.
And then everyone looks at him and is like, "Are you going to be prejudiced against my condition?"
My bird blindness.
You cannot use my disability against me.
His bird blindness is one of the funniest things. Whoever came up with that in the writer's room was just like, "Oh man."
It's probably James Gunn. I don't know.
I don't know anything else about his character and I don't care.
I know.
It's fine. I know he works for the agency in some capacity. I don't know what he does. I don't care. He is bird blind. Nothing else matters.
And they make it important to the plot.
I've got to see it.
It's not just an aside. It is plot crucial.
I love it so much. So good.
Every time it comes up, we just howl. It's great.
Yeah.
That sounds awesome.
Oh yeah. And gives everybody terrible nicknames too. That's true. That is true.
Yeah. But that's still, that's all fine. But yeah, I'm really enjoying that as well. Yeah.
Yeah. Also, we wanted to get into it, but holy shit. John Oliver is just perfect.
I have to catch up.
John Oliver's show is just perfect.
Yeah. I have to catch up. I was watching the season at South Park. I'm enjoying that.
Yep.
But I have to catch up on John Oliver.
Yeah. It turns out, and we all know this. We all comment on this every time it happens, but it turns out when the political leadership in the country is terrible, the comedy does get really good.
That is the upside to all these things is the comedy does get really good.
Yeah. Yeah. I have to.
Not good enough to make it worth it, but still good.
Sorry. I'm just getting a call. I have to take this.
It's Hollywood.
Excuse me.
Oh no. It's a space lawyer.
I'm sorry. Just got one question for you.
No. I'm doing a podcast right now. I can't, I'll have to call you back later.
Okay. You say that. Okay.
Oh, that was easy.
Hey, you guys want to do a little scoop mail?
Let's do a little scoop mail.
Kurt is texting me right now, so I'm texting him.
Fantastic.
Oh good.
Tell him I just brought up his awesome house full of bees bit.
I plugged his house full of bees bit special.
That's why he's texting. He's texting Matt to thank him for you bringing that up.
He suddenly saw a giant influx of bees.
I really do hope we get Kurt back on the show.
You don't know Paul, but he's my comedy partner and he loves the bee thing.
Yeah, exactly.
No, I hope we get Kurt on the show again sooner than later.
We got an email here from nincomscoop.
No, really. ICS is making me smarter.
That seems impossible.
What?
My family has decided to visit Japan next year.
We are all trying to learn some Japanese.
I have been taking a deep dive into learning the language because I've always wanted to and why the fuck not.
One thing about learning Japanese is learning the kanji, those logo graphic characters representing words and ideas.
I believe it's pronounced kanji.
Kanji, thank you.
There are tens of thousands of them and learning them you have to remember the concept and they usually have more than one pronunciation depending on context.
It's kind of a bitch to learn.
One helpful memorization technique is creating mnemonic pictures in your mind.
I've created a handful from ICS concepts.
Here's my favorite.
Oh, the kanji looks roughly like a man sitting in a car with what could be an arm sticking out.
That man is actually Matt.
He's got his hand out.
Oh, no, it's full of coins and he's about to throw it at another car shouting be the change.
This kanji means change.
Hey.
And on of the primary pronunciations is ka.
Thanks for the help, Matt, I guess.
Loving you all sexually.
That's nincompoop.
It's the least I could do, quite frankly, the least.
Literally.
Yeah.
We got one here from Big Sexy.
Hola, mi amigos.
I am loving the streaming and wanted to chime in on the red flag stories.
But I was in the lobby of a hospital waiting to see cardiologists at that moment.
So I didn't do it right then.
So I decided to write in.
I was dating this woman.
We'll call her Evelyn because that's her name.
And she was this beautiful, hard of hearing mother of two.
The hard of hearing part was new to me and it rekindled my interest in learning sign language.
Oh, we got two language emails right off the bat.
That's cool.
The red flags came from two different areas.
First, she was incredibly disorganized and her apartment showcased.
Things were everywhere with no rhyme or reason.
It made going to her place a nightmare for my OCD brain.
Books were piled on floors and dressers.
Clothes placed willy nilly and nothing in the kitchen made sense.
I just have to back up for just a second here.
Big Sexy, I might have just messed up your email.
I said it made it a nightmare for his OCD brain.
That isn't actually what he typed.
What he typed is his OC brain, so I don't know if he's referring to his Orange County brain or his OCD brain.
I suppose those are two very different things.
So Big Sexy, if you meant Orange County and I corrected it to OCD, I apologize.
It was hoarder status, but the kitchen made sense.
It was -- oh, sorry, sorry.
I'm reading two different lines here.
Books were piled on the floor and dressers.
Clothes placed willy nilly and nothing in the kitchen made sense.
It was hoarder status, but for books and clothes.
We couldn't have sex without me kicking over a stack of Judy Blume novels or self-help guides.
Whoa.
The bigger red flag flying from the highest flagpole, though, was her parenting.
First and foremost, like Paul and Jacob, I have no kids.
I did work at a boy's home at the time, so raising kids wasn't a new or unknown concept to me.
I also understood the notion of boundaries, which apparently her children did not.
As the boyfriend, I made zero attempt to play daddy at all.
Not my place.
Deeply known by me, having had several stepmoms in my life and knowing they couldn't tell me shit either,
I made no attempts save for one.
Evelyn and I had just returned from a dinner date and had leftovers.
As we put them in the refrigerator, Evelyn clearly said, "Do not eat my food."
Later, she went to run an errand.
As soon as she left, her daughter, around 16 at the time, promptly made her way to the fridge,
cracked open mom's food, and finished the meal.
When she pulled it out, I spoke up and said, "Hey, your mom said not to eat her food."
I did feel some kind of way since I paid for the meal.
Her daughter said, as most teens would, "Don't worry about it, and you aren't my dad."
Oh.
Wow.
I went via the boys' home to pick my battles with the youths wisely.
This was not worth the fight.
No.
I did, however, mention it to their mom when she returned.
Oh, snitches, baby, snitches.
Big sexy working for the Nevada DMV now.
I did, however, mention it to her mom when she got home, and instead of reprimanding her daughter,
she said it happens all the time and she just let it go.
Growing up, that would have been a stern discussion and punishment in my home.
The fact that it happened often said that her kids have little respect for rules
and that they would have zero respect for mine were we to get even more serious and/or get married,
which is why Evelyn gave me the ultimatum.
Which is why when Evelyn gave me the ultimatum, either this was moving to marriage or we needed to break up,
there was no hesitation when I said, "Well, I guess we're done."
Yeah.
Which took her by surprise.
She walked it back, but it was too late.
Decision made, each of my relationships has had red flags.
Sometimes it was me.
Luckily, the red flags around my current relationship were able to be overcome,
and our marriage is wonderful.
Glad you snuck that in there, big sexy.
Currently in the running for America's favorite couple vote on Facebook.
Shameless plug.
Fucking you in the face and ignoring your boundaries, that's big sexy.
Thanks, big sexy.
Yep, those are things.
That's tough.
I have not had that situation myself, but if any of you have seen Toast of London,
one of my all-time favorite BBC comedies with Matt Barry,
holy shit, there's a hoarder girlfriend that he gets.
God damn, it's remarkable.
They have to crawl into her bedroom over just 10 feet high newspapers and shit.
It's wild.
It's fucking wild.
It's such a funny episode.
I think it's like the second episode.
It's really early in the series.
If you guys haven't seen Toast of London, highly recommend.
If you're What We Do in the Shadows fans, jump on Toast.
It's so fucking good.
Winner scoop.
It's amazing what men will put up with for some strange.
It is true that we can be blinded by a lot of shit sometimes.
It is true.
That is true.
Speaking of being blinded by shit, you ain't going no shit because it's Jock vs. Nerd.
That's your claim.
I'm here to debate it.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock vs. Nerd.
Of dating women with kids.
We have a scooper today from Bearded Scoop 3.
The categories are B&A song titles, B&A movie titles, B&A people and B&A potpourri.
Do I know what B&A means?
What's B&A?
Breaking and acquiring?
No.
Oh, before and after.
OK.
Bearded Scoop sent an email along with it.
Yeah, this scooper is entirely before and after.
So before and after song titles, before and after.
What were the others?
Movie titles, people and potpourri.
Matt, you're up first.
Oh, wow.
This is going to be Matt's-- Matt's going to crush.
I know.
Matt's really good at the before and after ones.
Yeah.
All right.
Way to jinx me before 16 questions.
Let's do before and after movie titles, please.
Let's see here.
Luke Skywalker gets to know his father while Marty McFly gets close to his mother.
Empire Strikes Back to the Future.
There it is.
Wow, he is so good at these.
Right?
Oh, Matt is so good at these.
Paul.
I will try song titles.
Let's see here.
A 1980 Queen hit and one of Kansas's most popular songs.
Oh, 1980.
I can't think of the song by Kansas now.
Yeah, as I say, there's a lot of Queen hits, but I don't know any.
I know Kansas has a bunch of hits, but I don't know them.
We will rock you.
Crazy Little Thing Called Love.
Fat Bottom Girls.
Yeah, I can't think of enough Kansas songs.
I'll have to pass.
That's me.
Let's see.
Crazy Little Thing Called...
Do you know any Kansas songs off the top of your head?
Like Carry On Wayward Son.
That's probably their biggest one.
They've got some others, too.
I don't know.
I'll pass.
Matt, you're really good at these.
What is it?
Pass, pass.
Another One Bites the Dust in the Wind.
Oh, that's a good one.
That is a good one.
That's a good one.
I was like, I don't know Kansas songs.
Dust in the wind.
Let's see.
I'll try People for 400.
When this Cleopatra actress gets criticized for her numerous relationships, she just shakes it off.
So this would be Elizabeth Taylor Swift.
That's right.
There you go.
Yeah.
Matt.
I'll go with People.
For 800.
Lead singer of Blondie meets the 33rd US president.
Debbie Harry Truman.
You were so good at these.
Paul.
I'll try Song Titles again.
Song Titles for 800.
A popular anti-establishment song by CCR and a major hit for Dusty Springfield.
Fortunate Son of a Bitch.
Oh, gotta be.
Yes.
Now it's Fortunate Son of a Preacher Man.
Oh, shit.
I was thinking of somebody completely different.
Oh, buddy.
I was thinking, now you're messing with Son of a Bitch.
By Dusty Springfield.
By Dusty Springfield, which is not Dusty Springfield.
I'll try Movie Titles for 800.
Rufus Sewell wakes up in a hotel bathroom with no memories,
is saved by a heavenly being that looks a lot like Nick Cage.
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Hold on.
Who is that actor?
This is from-- oh, man.
Boy.
Old brain, creaky-ly working.
Creak, creak, creak.
Tell the hamster to run faster.
Ah, it's not Inception.
It's-- what the hell is the first Nolan movie?
Memento?
Memento.
That's what I was thinking.
It says Memento.
Yeah.
But I'm trying to-- I can't remember that actor's name.
Memento.
He's, like, confidential, too.
So I'll pass.
Oh, is it names?
Is the names of the--
This is names, right?
I think so, yeah.
Is this movie titles or names?
I thought it was movie titles.
I don't know.
Oh, no, I think it has movie titles.
Oh, so I was doing the wrong thing.
I already said pass.
Ah, well, Paul.
I'll have to pass.
Dark City of Angels.
Ah.
Oh, I wasn't wrong, anyway.
Dark City of Angels.
I don't know Dark City at all.
No, I thought--
Dark City is interesting.
I had the wrong movie.
Yeah.
Huh.
Matt, you're up.
Movie titles, please.
For $1,200.
The story of Westward and Bernstein--
Woodward.
--breaking the Watergate--
Westward.
The story of Woodward and Bernstein
breaking the Watergate scandal plus an agency
tasked with hiding aliens on Earth.
Oh, wait.
I keep on blanking out on that movie.
It's not-- it's not Deep Throat.
That's what I was thinking.
That's a whole different movie.
An excellent movie.
I'll pass.
A whole different one.
I've got this one.
I'll pass.
Paul.
All the President's Men in Black.
Yes.
That's a good one.
That is a good one.
Yeah.
Paul, you're up.
I'll close out movie titles, please.
All right.
For $2,000.
Daily double.
Oh, now is my chance for redemption.
Redemption.
Tony Stark first dons his armor while Henry
Cavill plays Superman.
Iron Man of Steel.
Oh.
Yeah.
Iron Man of Steel.
That's it.
There you go.
Good job.
Oh, now Paul is commanding lead.
Yeah, score check.
Paul has 2,400.
Matt has 1,200.
I have 400.
How do I only have 400?
I guess I'm bad at this.
Matt's really good at this, though.
I'll do People for 1,200.
The director of Bullets Over Broadway plays
basketball with the answer.
Oh.
I don't know who the director of Bullets Over
Broadway is.
I will pass.
Matt.
Let's see.
That is Woody Allen-Averson.
There it is.
Oh, of course.
I'm mad that I didn't know that Woody Allen
directed Bullets Over Broadway.
Matt.
Let's go with People again.
People again for 2,000.
Last week tonight, Host, has dinner with the
Lord Protector of the United Kingdom.
Oliver.
What is it?
I don't know who the Lord Protector of the
United Kingdom is.
John Oliver Clothes Off.
Good guess.
Pass.
Paul.
John Oliver Cromwell.
Lord Protector of England.
Good job.
Bordens.
1592.
9/16.
28.
September.
It's a Monty Python song.
I've got those dates.
I'm sure I got those dates completely wrong,
but I remember.
Paul, you're up.
Popery.
For 400.
The sweetest and sparkliest breakfast cereal
races against the looming deadline.
What was this one?
Just Popery?
Popery.
Yeah.
Sparkliest breakfast cereal.
Oh, Cinnamon Toast Crunch Time.
Cinnamon Toast Crunch Time is just correct.
Wow.
Paul is also really good at these.
I was about to say Fruit Loops of Fury,
but then I was like, no, that's not what that...
I'll try song titles.
I don't know, for 1200.
I'm getting whooped in this.
A 1978 hit for Bob Seeger and the Moody Blues song about bedsheets.
Song about what?
And a song about bedsheets.
I have no idea.
Pass.
Well, this is so hard.
It's not going to figure out,
because what I have is I'm thinking of night moves,
and then there's nights and white satin,
but you can't do night moves and white satin,
so that doesn't work.
Nights and white satin moves?
No.
I don't know if it's a Seeger song that ends in...
Wait.
Was this the song that Bob Seeger did about werewolves?
Oh, no, I was getting confused.
He didn't do a song about werewolves.
He had the Silver Bullet Band.
Yeah.
I'll pass.
Paul.
Moody Blues about bedsheets.
Pass.
Well, let's see.
Hollywood nights and white satin.
Hollywood nights.
You're halfway.
Matt, you got song titles or potpourri?
I got to chase Paul here, yeah?
So I'll go 2,000 potpourri, please.
Okay.
A documentary series detailing this singer's sexual abuse
aired in 2019, hosted by the woman
who replaced Kathie Lee Gifford on live.
Whoa.
A documentary series?
Uh-huh.
Who replaced Kathie Lee Gifford?
Old Scrawny Arms.
I think she changed her name, though.
I just don't know. I'm gonna pass.
Paul.
Paul Mattingly.
I'm thinking it's not from Justin to Kelly Ripa.
A documentary series.
From Justin to Kelly?
Is that sexual abuse?
A documentary.
From Justin to Kelly, it was a different type of abuse.
Yeah, exactly.
It was like Kelly Ripa, Jack the Ripa, Kelly Jack the Ripa.
I don't fucking pass.
That said, it's Kelly Jack the Ripa.
A documentary series detailing this singer's sexual abuse
aired in 2019.
Was that Michael Jackson?
Michael Jackson Kelly?
Michael Jackson Kelly Ripa?
I can't remember what. Oh, maybe it's P. Diddy?
No, I think it's the sexual abuse of the singer.
Oh.
Yeah, that's what I'm assuming.
So it'd be like if Megyn Kelly were a singer,
it'd be like Megyn Kelly Ripa.
Okay. Well, maybe that's it.
I don't think Megyn Kelly is a singer.
Who?
Is it R. Kelly there?
R. Kelly Ripa?
Oh, it's R. Kelly Ripa.
It's got to be R. Kelly Ripa.
R. Kelly Ripa.
We got there, y'all.
We took a village on that one.
A big dumb village.
Paul, you're up.
Me, us three idiots.
I agree, Lauren, by the way, those points should be shared.
However, there's not a button for that, so they're mine.
Song titles, please.
Song titles for 2000.
Yeah.
A hit from The Doors, self-titled album,
and a 1970 hit for James Taylor.
Oh, boy.
Oh, God.
Like L.A. woman.
I don't know enough James.
It's the James Taylor part that's going to slow me down.
Oh, come on, let me light your fire and rain.
Oh, good job.
Light my fire and rain is absolutely right.
Yeah.
Damn it.
I had that one that I thought you were going to pass.
I did, too.
It's over, everyone.
Go home.
Isn't there one Daily Double left?
No, there's one more Daily Double still in there.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
I think there is.
It doesn't matter.
Look at the scores, guys.
It only matters if Paul gets it and misses it.
Right.
Oh, I understand.
Oh, which I don't think he can.
Oh, no, I can.
I just answered my last question.
Yeah, yeah.
That's over.
I'll do a potpourri for $1,200.
You could get the Daily Double.
There's the Daily Double.
If you get this, won't that take you over?
No.
Oh, OK.
Paul.
I have 2,400 points.
You have 6,800 points.
If I double my points, how many points do I have?
Yeah, but don't you also get the $1,200?
OK, brace yourself, everyone.
Paul's doing Kentucky math.
All right, go ahead.
The Steamy BDSM Best Seller if it were set in Big and Little Eddie's Crumbling Hampton's
Mansion.
Oh, my God.
Hilarious.
Oh, I got this.
I got this one, too.
I know the first part.
50 Shades of Grey.
There you go.
One more word.
It has to do with taking care of plants.
It does not take place in Madison Square.
Right.
Oh, OK.
50 Shades of Grey Basketball.
Oh, boy.
Grey Garden.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
We really helped Jacob today.
This has been a good.
This has been a good day.
We really helped Jacob a lot today.
We did.
Matt Closenhouse, the category and the game, potpourri for 800.
If I get this right.
In second place, it takes a village.
If I get this right, I'm in third.
And if I lose, I'm in third.
Yep.
High stakes.
Prince is iconic.
And if I pass it to Jacob and he gets it, he's in second.
Maybe he loses.
He's in second.
Or if you pass it to Paul and he misses, he's still in first.
Yeah, it's high stakes.
But if he gets it, he's in first.
Prince is iconic.
Movie slash song needs to reschedule for another time.
Oh, oh.
Bassey just typed it in.
Purple rain check.
Thank you for that.
Just type it in the chat.
There you go.
Much easier game if we just do that all the time.
I was I was thinking something like under the cherry moon.
I'll see you next late next Tuesday or something.
Well, I knew it was purple rain.
I didn't know the other one.
I really thought it was under the cherry moon.
The movie under the cherry moon.
I still think it's under the cherry moon.
Good.
Matt, good job on that question.
Good job on that question.
I mean, I didn't get all my questions right by myself either.
But don't worry, Matt.
You're still really good at this.
Paul wins, though, with 6,800 points.
I'm in second with 4,800.
Matt is in third with 3,200.
But don't let that fool you.
He's very, very good at these.
And that's from Bearded Scoop three.
Thank you, Bearded Scoop three.
If you want to send us a scooper to your price, it's great.
Jack versus nerd or an obelisk.
Jack versus nerd.
Head on over to hey scoops dot com.
Let's go.
Hey scoops dot com.
You can make a thing.
You can send us the thing.
It'll be great.
We'll do the thing.
We will.
Bearded Scoop three.
Thank you so much for that.
That was an incredible game.
We appreciate the interaction from each and every one of you scoops.
We're so happy to see so many people in the chat right now hanging out with us here and
on Twitch.
So cool.
Yes.
I want to thank Penjeletic for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I want to thank all the people who are coming out to my show in Sparta or the following
week to my show with Paul at Tierney's.
Yes, so good.
It's a super fun show.
Don't miss it.
And I also want to thank other people here.
Jacob wrote me a list.
I found it.
It's right here.
These following people just have to answer one more question before they get in the airlock.
That's William McDonald, Will Kellner, Will Beardy Dan, Who Dat Scoop, What Was Like Scoop,
Wes Culligan, Wendy Bumgardner, Wendy Cooper, Water Ice Scoop, Warren Breaux, Uncle Don's
Woodshop, Udo Gerhards, Tyler Scoop McDuck, Tyler Bartlett, Tuba Scoop, Troy Anthony Townser,
Tristan Guevara, and Travis Murray.
The following people are about to participate in their very first Open Magic Mike night.
The Upside Down Under Scoop, The Spirit of the Latin Club, The Scoop Lockean, The Salty
Squid, The SCWOP, The Nano Scoop, The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, The Lapis Lagomorf,
The Ice Cream Headache, The Ice Cream Headache Again, The Going Over Our Friends Podcast,
The Famous Ball, The Didgeridooche, The Devil's Lettuce Scoop, The Damsels of Dorkington,
The Civic Crew Scoop, and The Sincy Scoop.
The following people have all called in their next door neighbor's registration to the hotline.
Travis Jurigwai, Tony Scoprano, Tony Cowley, Tom Stott, Tom Mancorty, Tom Krieger, TK4201
Scoop Please, Timothy Sutton, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, Thomas Beach, The Man, The Myth,
The Scoop, The Dirty Scoop.
Thank you so much.
The following people are a lot like Rain in Las Vegas.
An inch and a half might not sound like much, but it can fuck you good.
The Bad Humor Man, That Thing in the Attic, Turn the Page, Temporary.Reality, Pierce,
Technical Scoop Hort, Tamara Hamilton, Take it Evie Podcast Scoop, Swedish Scoop,
Supergeek13579, Sugar Rush Socio, Strap a Chicken on Scoop, Strange Uncles Podcast,
Stuart Wilson, and Stephen Biggs.
And the following scoops all love overnighting in Boston on a cruise ship.
That's Stephen Landon, Stephen Clively, Stephanie Young, Streets, Asteets, Magreets,
Stacey Coleman, Stab and Dash Scoop, Spring Loaded Scoop, Soundman Scoop, Soulless Scoop,
Solar Powered Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Slurpee Caillet Motherfucker, Slightly Slutty Scoop,
Scholarwall Scoop, Six Foot Scoop, Sir Scoopy McScooperson III, Esquire, Silverfist Scoop,
Silicone Scoop, Shoeless Scoop, Sean, SF, Sebastian Robbins, Seanathan P., Sean Kellner,
Scott Schofield, Scott Muldrig, Scott Headington, Scott Ashlock, Scott Ashlock again,
Scott Andrews, and Scott A. Thank you all so much.
Thank you all.
Scott A.
Hey, if you want to help us out, if you want to keep this podcast going,
we need your support month after month, year after year.
Head on over to PreachingFun.com and find the tier that suits your budget right now.
Come visit PreachingFun.com
It's better than hanging with your mom
Better be bad
Or if you don't want to do any of those things, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts
Fartsinabag.biz
That's right, fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com,
it takes you over to our Patreon page, where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
You think this show is worth more than $0?
PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz,
those are the places you can go to help support this show.
And we do need it.
We have a weird amount of bills for such a small podcast.
So head on over there.
And they go up, which is annoying.
They keep going up, too.
Yeah, things keep going up. What do you know?
Thanks, Obama.
Love you guys. Take care of yourselves up there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Yeah.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the cone
See you at the cone, see you at the cone, see you at the cone
Right at the cone
Snitches get stitches.
I don't know who needs to hear it, but it's true.
And there are whores on multiple floors.
PreachingFun.
All these whores on multiple floors.
It's only somebody who was here to give me a tours.
See ya!
Taxis was waiting on the refund you needed yesterday.
All right, your car repair is going to run about $3,000.
Now Taxis is getting back on the road with TurboTax and Credit Karma,
where you can get your refund up to five days faster
and get personalized guidance to take every dollar further.
Now this is Taxis, Intuit Credit Karma with TurboTax.