I'm here on the job site with Dale, who's a framing contractor.
Hey, good morning.
Dale traded up to Geico Commercial Auto Insurance for all his business vehicles.
We're here where he needs us most.
Yep, they sure are.
We make it easy for him to save on all his insurance needs, all in one place.
With coverage that fits his business and bottom line.
Oh, shouldn't have looked down.
It's all right.
We're so far up here.
Look at me. Take a deep breath.
Oh, I'm good. So good.
Get a commercial auto insurance quote today at Geico.com and see how much you could save.
It feels good to Geico.
Now we're recording.
Oh, we're starting now?
Classic Jacob fake outs. Classic Jacob fake outs.
Fake in your ass.
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great. Let's go.
I'm wrecked.
It's time for Matt Madden's ice cream social sitting right across from me is Paul Madden.
Right next to me is Mr. Matt Donnelly.
Over there on his own damn couch is Jacob, the audio guy.
We're gonna go.
We're preaching fun.
Yeah, we are.
And we brought in Mitzi here.
Mitzi is here.
I had a couple of scoops reach out to be like, there's no churn, right?
I was like, that is correct.
I didn't think it was right to invite people both to Jacob's house and Paul's bedroom to
record tonight because those are the two places that we are right now.
It's a little much.
Yeah, I couldn't handle other people tonight.
I had to bribe Paul with noodles.
Reclined.
Paul is supine.
We actually had to push to record because we were losing Paul before recording.
You were falling asleep on that couch.
Well, it's midnight.
It's midnight by time and I go to bed at nine now and that's late.
Yes.
I think I just might need you to sit up.
I think I might just have to have you sit up.
You can ask.
Could I make a formal request that Paul Mattingly sits up?
You may file form B13.
I'm attorney for Paul Mattingly.
File some forms.
I'm attorney for Paul Mattingly and your motion is denied.
There you go.
I was afraid of that.
I decline to incline.
I will remain declined.
Supine.
Supine and so fine.
Oh yeah.
Oh, lupine.
He's a werewolf.
Je suis le loup garou, as the French would say.
That means skin changer, ladies and gentlemen.
Loup garou.
Look, I don't want to change the mood too quickly.
Oh, for God's sake.
Let's pour one out for Terry Fader, shall we?
Oh, baby.
No, you know what?
It's so funny.
We were just talking about this at the restaurant.
We went and got some noodles.
The effort you just put into sitting up was pretty amazing.
That entire sentence that you just heard, listening audience, was Paul sitting up.
No, that was like a 15-point K-turn with your body you were doing to just try to sit up.
There are so many elements.
Remember that scene from "Boston Powers" when he's turning the golf cart around in the tunnel?
So many elements are on their way out in this apparatus.
And this is good hip Paul.
This is Paul.
Paul is pointing at various places on his body.
The hip is fine.
He fruit all day.
It's now shoulders.
Yeah, and he was on a plane.
And boy, are his shoulders tired.
But the shoulders are real bad now.
But whatever.
No, but we were talking about this Terry Fader, the famous ventriloquist.
Well, the first winner of "America's Got Talent."
Yeah, winner of season one of "America's Got Talent."
He's the one who made NBC learn that they had to sign those people to
binding contracts before they got famous because it became much more difficult for
them to negotiate with Terry Fader after he signed a $100 million deal at the Mirage.
That's why some people were saying, "Oh really?
I've never heard of him."
That's because "America's Got Talent" never brought him back.
That's right.
Never put him in a montage.
They didn't.
They don't mention it. He does not come up.
He was the first winner.
He has Terry Fader from memory.
Yeah.
And what we think, what my, I think.
So it's a big news story in Las Vegas because it was abrupt.
He literally just was like, "Oh, by the way, I've done my last show."
Right.
It came out earlier today that tonight was going to be his final performance.
He was in the theater at the Strat.
Paul has a theory.
It's not just a theory.
I think it's legit.
Well, let's go ahead for legal sake, call it a theory anyway.
All right.
Allegedly.
Paul thinking it's legit does not make it so.
I'm pretty sure Terry Fader thought he was going to get raptured.
Do you know that there's like a rapture thing happening right now?
Okay.
I, this was, there's been numerous rapture rumors in my lifetime.
Yes.
Different religious apocalyptic predicted in my lifetime.
The Mayan one, the Mayan calendar.
And we're not talking Debbie Harry Blondie.
This was so, this was so late.
It came out like a day before.
It was so late.
So, so late to the party.
Pretty abrupt.
Next time there's a rapture.
Okay.
Here's what we need to do or someone needs to do.
Mitzi, actually, you might be able to help us with this.
Someone needs to ahead of time figure out what sports teams would be most affected.
You should go around to every professional basketball team,
every football team and figure out how many real big Jesus Christians there are on each team
and talk about who's going to go in the rapture
and how that will affect the team going forward if they don't have them.
Right.
Over, under, number of players.
Who will handle the future's betting?
So like, for instance, like Baker Mayfield's probably
the biggest heathen quarterback we have in the league.
Is he?
Right.
Okay.
I'm just saying, I'm guessing.
Okay, okay, good.
I'm guessing just by his energy.
I've never heard him thank God or Jesus.
Okay.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I don't know.
Somebody could correct me on this.
But I think it'd be hilarious if like Baker-
I don't have any counter arguments.
Baker Mayfield just looks left and right and is like, oh shit,
I'm like one of three starting quarterbacks left in the league.
So, Paul, tell Matt what you were telling me earlier today.
I didn't know that any of this was happening.
So it has come up real quick, but apparently through many
different channels within the social media forums and whatnot,
people really think the shit's hitting the fan.
If you go on Facebook Marketplace right now,
it's a goddamn fire sale.
People are just putting everything and everyone up for sale.
Because they think they're about to get rapture.
People are selling their houses.
Do you want to know why?
I do.
They think they're going to get a rapture.
Yeah.
Tylenol is what's causing people to believe they're going to get rapture.
It might be.
Or is Tylenol causing people to get rapture?
Is it possible that Tylenol has both created a god
and has made that god rapture?
Guys, I bought a pill from Dr. Oz that makes me rapture proof.
So it's okay.
They're like, if Kimmel's coming back on air, get me off this planet.
Maybe.
Jesus, take me away.
They're afraid this is the second coming.
Oh shit, that's what it meant the whole time.
It was three days.
You know what?
It could have been deeper than we even think.
You know, old Orangey Borgie had a little trouble getting the words out the other day
during the Tylenol debacle.
I won't hear it.
He's sharp as a tack.
Well, he may have actually had something going on.
You are saying that this Tylenol could be responsible for rapture type stuff.
He might have actually been trying to say ascendametaphen.
Oh, ascendametaphen.
Not acedametaphen, ascendametaphen.
I feel like that's all the funny that our listeners can handle today.
It's more than they fucking deserve.
Eat all my ass all day.
Wow.
Yeah.
What?
Yes, we heard it.
Our listeners?
I think he means Trump, not our listeners.
Yeah.
Oh, I thought you were talking to our listeners and so did some of our listeners.
Well, some of them too.
They know who they are.
You know who you are.
I know who they are.
Well, he's easier to do the Jack versus Nerd than me.
Fine, Paul, I'll leave.
You don't have to be out.
That's right.
I just wanted to be a little--
You don't have to yell into that mic.
Come on, Mitzi.
We can do the Christian.
We can find out how many Christian athletes are on each team, right?
I got told to eat the mic in the last studio.
But you're doing great.
But yeah, definitely we can find out how many Christian athletes there are in these teams.
We just have to be on top of it next time.
It's the only way I want to discuss the rapture.
Did you hear anything?
I did.
I heard about the rapture this morning.
Performative rapture.
That people were thinking about that the rapture might happen.
And I saw an atheist TikTok.
I was like, great.
Exactly.
But Paul was saying people were leaving notes and stuff for their neighbors.
And I was like, these people think their neighbors are just heathens.
Are they going to get raptured?
All of my neighbors.
Are you kidding?
My whole neighborhood is like, guys,
I'm surprised we didn't just have a bunch of keys in our mailbox.
That's exactly it.
These jabronis are like, oh, yeah, here's the instructions
to how to get into my basement.
And here's my key card.
Two gay pride flags on our little sign in the front yard.
You're going to be feeding so many of their pets.
Yeah.
Oh, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
We've taken care of so many animals.
That's the whole thing.
All of us are going to be left here just raising dogs.
I guess we've been joking around.
I guess we should say wholeheartedly, that's fucking nuts.
That's really fucking crazy.
But it's just that really crazy.
That is one stance that we could take.
And I agree that that is a viable stance that we could take.
A different stance, though, that we could take is give us your shit.
Power for the fucking question.
If you're going to get-- because you know we're not going to get raptured.
Literally, the second word in the description of this podcast is godless.
Yes, godless.
Well, that's the other fucking--
We're not getting raptured.
Leave us your shit.
Yeah, that's the other--
Just give it to us.
The fucked up thing.
There's straight up preachers who got their flock to give them everything.
Of course.
And they are in Barbados.
They are gone.
Yeah, they left.
They did get raptured.
Wait, so straight up religious cons.
Yeah, there have been a lot of con jobs happening.
Was the con job a side effect or the actual inspiration for this?
Was the con job the plan?
Side effect and rapture.
Because from what I understand-- again--
So how did this rapture ever get started?
Exactly.
Everybody's laced up part of here.
We can't pin this one on the Mayans, guys.
I heard this was one fucking guy, one guy on the TikTok somewhere, started this up.
And everybody just started going, oh, OK, that sounds right.
One guy couldn't have started this.
Oh, no?
No, I've got it right here.
If you take one guy, and then you take one religious rapture, and then you have them
give him stuff, nah, it doesn't work out.
Jacob--
The math doesn't check out.
I think you'll find that one guy did change a lot of things.
He had some pretty far out ideas about where we go after we pass on.
We're long hair, walked everywhere, had a lot of people following him,
had a lot of people hating him.
Huh?
Yeah.
Persecution.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That guy?
Yeah.
Pretend.
Fuck you all!
Fuck you all in the face and mouth forever.
Bullshit fairy tale that someone pulled out of their dickhole.
No, no, no, no.
He was a beautifully pasty white Middle Eastern.
Sure, you're right.
You're right.
Golden-haired Middle Eastern.
Golden-haired blue-eyed--
Shredded white guy.
Yeah.
Super shredded.
And if you don't believe--
Mitzi has hit it right there.
If you don't believe Jesus was beautiful and white, then I've had it.
Every--
What has happened to this country?
Every crucified Catholic Christ has five-minute abs for days.
Just fucking washboard.
In fucking Belize a couple of months ago, we went into a church from the 1800s.
They had a painted Christ on the wall there, literally painted on bright blue eyes.
And there's like stone relief coming out of this thing from the middle--
Or like early 1800s.
I think it was like 1813 or something.
It's just all so fucking stupid.
And now we see it--
If you want to sell a religion, you got to have some sex appeal.
We're seeing it all writ large here in our own country,
where it's all like, fuck history, fuck truth.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the sex appeals thing.
No, that too.
Well, people do draw this president in all kinds of heroic, handsome poses all the time.
People do that.
They sure do.
Definitely not for any reason other than truth.
But this goes back to-- we went a little-- we got a little real,
a little heavy in our last episode.
Maybe you did.
Paul's trying to warm up tonight.
That moment of silence was Paul searching for remembering the last episode.
I know, I remember it.
A second ago, it was great because I got to watch him in the eyes,
decide whether or not to just say Jesus was fake
or to name another long-haired celebrity person
that he could have been talking about the whole time.
I was just going to say something real dumb,
and I was trying to think of something real dumb.
Yeah, yeah.
Nothing's funny to joke about anymore.
I was ready for Axl Rose.
What, what, what, yeah, what, what was it?
Axl Rose, but what am I-- who am I going to throw under the bus?
I didn't say it was a good joke.
I'm just saying.
I was ready for it.
Who am I going to even throw under the bus at this point?
Who am I going to say, like, I don't know, I was--
The lead singer of Mr. Big.
It can't be Axl Rose because he's all Matt Steel Horse, so you can't--
He was the lead singer of Mr. Big.
All right, that's pretty good.
That should have been the one I went with.
Jim Morrison.
More than words.
Could have been Jim Morrison.
You know, a long time ago, there was another guy.
He chose to go a different route, if you know what I mean, you know?
Shaked things up a little bit.
Moved to the beat of his own drummer.
A little left of center.
He beat up his own drummer?
He beat up his own drummer.
I mean, probably.
I mean, that's how you get through talking to the industry.
That guy was Peter Gabriel.
He got into a big fucking fight with Phil Collins
and left Genesis.
And that was the Genesis.
That was the Genesis of the Book of Genesis.
That's right.
Yep.
Sledgehammer.
I know it was old, but I didn't know it was as old as Phil Collins.
That also explains why the drummer had to-- the gorilla was the drummer.
That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
They got into a fight and the drummer couldn't go.
There it is.
Yep.
This is how things go.
My right eye is filled with blood.
We're all old hobbling into this school fest.
Nothing has been stressing you lately, has it?
Old damaged men.
I literally had this thought multiple times, Super.
I was like, turnouts are just easier.
I was like, go somewhere else.
Holy shit, are they?
Do it for a day.
All right, everybody enjoy the last Scoop Fest.
Hope you had a good one.
No, no, no, no.
See you at Turnout.
We love doing Scoop Fest, but it is just so hard.
And when it's over, it feels so much cooler to pull off than at Turnout.
Yeah, certainly.
Yeah.
Oh, no, it's so much more rewarding.
Actually, what a great, terrible segue.
We actually can announce something pretty cool that's happening.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah.
So for people who missed out on Scoop Fest,
I have this event that's happening in New York.
And so I asked Paul if he wanted to join me just for fun.
This is a total coincidence, but we're doing just a--
I'm calling it random comedy night for no reason.
But Paul is going to come out to Tierney's.
Paul and I are going to do a show at Tierney's.
This will be great.
Recreate the magic of the first pre-Scoop Fest, Scoop Fest.
Yes.
October 23rd, we're going to be out there.
And part of it is because my buddy Kurt Braunler,
who also performed at one of the Scoop Fests,
he got hired by The Tonight Show.
Oh, good for him.
And The Tonight Show doesn't film on Fridays.
So Kurt Braunler, when he told me he's moving back to Jersey,
I said, I'm so jealous.
I said, I'm going to come back to Jersey.
We're going to do a show at Tierney's.
He's like, yes.
So Kurt's going to do Stand Up.
Great.
Fantastic.
Paul and I are going to do Improv.
Perfect.
I'm going to do a little magic.
And I reached out to my buddy Dion Flynn,
who plays Barack Obama, another character on The Tonight Show,
because he told me he moved to Montclair.
I said, well, Kurt and I and my buddy Paul are going to come out to the thing.
And he goes, I'm in.
I go, this is hilarious.
Fucking A.
So I have Dion Flynn.
This is a no-joke phase.
This is a real thing.
So then I reached out to my buddies from Possible Side Effects to live in Jersey.
And I said, just so you know, I'm doing the thing with Kurt and Dion.
And Paul's coming out.
Wait a minute.
Now I'm mad I'm not going.
That's what I'm saying.
Why aren't you?
So now, Dijory Douche and Pat Shepard from Redbaker are all coming out.
Because all that was before was you and Matt going and hanging out at Tierney's for a night.
And that seems like a lot of money for me to throw away to just go hang out at Tierney's for a night.
Here's the thing, Jacob.
You should just want to hang out with me and Matt to start with.
And then your dick wouldn't be caught in a wringer like it is now.
So if you go to-- hopefully this is in the notes.
But if you go to heyscoops.com/comedynight--
Great.
--you will find tickets available for it.
There's just a--
Not for long, motherfuckers.
Probably not.
It's not a huge venue.
Get on that shit.
It's coming up soon.
We're charging 20 bucks.
30 bucks if you want a guaranteed seat because it's Tierney's and there's like four tables.
Sorry, I just bought them all.
They're now $50 on the secondary market.
No.
On the secondary market.
Minsey Ticks got scalped on us.
So it's a total random Tierney's comedy night, October 23, Thursday.
Paul and I, it's going to be--
And it's an easy jaunt for me.
It's an hour flight.
It's like I'd be losing money, not going.
We're just-- yeah.
I'm just picking up Paul at the airport and we're going to head over to Montclair.
This is hilarious.
Yeah.
So it is--
It's hilarious how much it's blown up.
I know.
It's like exploded.
There's actually another name of a person I want to reach out to.
I won't say it now because I think someone might say yes if I reach out to them.
I think they will.
Is it Letterman?
It's Letterman.
Well, I mean, no.
It's already lining up, so--
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's another Jersey guy that a lot of our listeners like.
Frankie Valli?
Frankie Valli.
God damn you, Minsey.
I told you.
I'm not going to do it.
Sorry, that was totally a confident death.
Yeah, I feel like we'd make Frankie Valli happen.
Danny DeVito.
Buzz Aldrin.
I think I can get Buzz Aldrin to stop by.
I'm standing still as I can.
OK, if you get Buzz to come, I'm in.
Imagine Jackie's like, "God damn it.
I could have hung out with Buzz Aldrin."
I'm alive.
I could have punched people with Buzz Aldrin.
If I could have hung out with Buzz Aldrin.
If I could have just gotten drunk with Buzz Aldrin, I'll be so mad.
If I'm alive or dead, I may be a mannequin who can sing.
I forgot what Bitt Paul's doing.
I'm standing very still.
He's Frankie Valli.
He showed up at Frank Tierney's.
I'm almost motionless.
Can someone put a mirror near my nose to see if I'm breathing?
Hey, man, he's someone who keeps one of our listeners kind of employed.
We've got to be careful with Frankie.
I got nothing but love for Frankie Valli.
They're coming out with a new movie, Weekend at Frankie's.
No one doubts that being true.
No one's like, "I have tied his shoelaces to my shoelaces right now."
They should just call it Jersey Boys 2 and steal the plot of Weekend at Bernie's.
That would be a hilarious thing to film for just the cast.
They should get Kenny's to direct that one, too.
They hollowed my body out and fucking Teddy Ruxpin'd me.
For that one, would they also ignore the fact that they're a movie?
I've got a cassette tape in my belly and I just play the hits.
I'm the fucking Teddy Ruxpin.
Frankie Valli Ruxpin.
And then the tape gets caught.
I went to Sam's Club today to buy some stuff for Scoop Fest.
How deep are we at?
Should we do an ad?
Oh, sure.
Before your transition?
Yeah, let's do an ad.
Not to be.
Following sponsor.
Today's show...
It's going to be a long week, folks.
If you had two eyes, you would have nailed that.
Today's show is brought to you by Pee Pee Vajayjay's Toilet Hole Lubricant.
Get rid of the stick.
That's right. That's Pee Pee Vajayjay's Toilet Hole Lubricant.
That's from Paul's brother in 2024.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm so tired of stabbing my turds down the toilet.
Tired of it.
I got so bad last year after I had some of my favorite milk thistle.
I had to get a fucking rake.
I bought a big garden rake for my toilet.
You believe that shit?
A whole garden rake.
It was said up to 40 pounds and it broke in my toilet.
Anyway, get some of my lube for your pipes.
Basically, it is...
Raccoon squeezes.
Squeezes?
You catch you a raccoon and you squeeze that motherfucker until stuff comes out.
There is nothing slicker than a raccoon squeezes.
Enter Hayscoops at checkout.
Then just the poop goes right down.
Matt.
I just want you guys to know that you guys...
Off air we said we should text Spadoni early to make sure he shows up on time.
And then I told him to come early.
And he wrote back like, "Why are you having me come so early?"
Did you say cuz...
Spadoni.
He's like, "I thought the show was at seven. What the hell is going on?"
I'll be there at six, six and a half.
Because he thinks we're going to stage an intervention.
That's why.
No, we would never.
I don't want to step on that genius.
You ride that white dragon to the fucking cow come home.
A pretty corpse.
That's right.
Matt.
What time is loading tomorrow, Jacob?
It's for another person.
We're meeting at the...
Oh, we're meeting at the house at noon, but he's not meeting at the house.
No.
So Orleans shortly afternoon.
I'll say one.
Great.
We'll be there by one.
One-ish.
It won't take us that long to load up the truck before going to the Orleans.
We hope.
Production meeting.
All right. It's just, it's happening.
That's all. I'm just getting these texts out of the way.
I know this is good.
I don't blame you.
This has been my life.
The last several days.
What are you holding in your hands, Paul?
I hold in my hands more circle dots.
This is for you.
Your son can read it after you read it.
Is this the trade?
This is the trade of absolute Batman.
So this is the first trade.
So when I was young, I liked Batman.
Yes.
And I collected all the comics.
And as the real world has caught up with everything, Batman's got...
You mean the MTV reality show.
The real...
Correct.
No, the real world.
No, no.
Oh.
I mean...
Road rules.
Ah.
Challenge.
Rapture edition.
Where we get our next president from.
Yeah.
What's that empty RV?
Okay. So basically what made Batman fascinating was that through his millions of dollars,
he had advanced technology and military technology and all that.
But now police all have that now too.
Right.
So it's like, it's weird to have Batman show up and be like, but me, but more so.
But mine have bats on them.
So Paul tipped me off to this new Batman comic called Absolute Batman.
Paul?
Yep.
Take it from here, buddy.
It's a reboot.
Paul has made it backwards.
Scott Snyder.
Scott Snyder, the bat genius himself.
Yes.
He keeps knocking them out of the park.
This is no different.
This book is incredible.
It is a re-imagining of the origin of the bat.
He is a...
He's still Bruce Wayne.
Yep.
He is a son's father, but his mother yet lives.
Ah.
She...
Lucky lady.
Does not have the money.
He is a construction worker and a brilliant student.
Okay.
So he's got a lot of the tropes, but none of the cash.
But at the same time, he works construction.
So he is built like a fucking truck and his gadgets are like fucking the constructicons,
basically.
Okay.
He comes at criminals with like backhoes and shit.
He's got...
You see his chest?
I'd be scared.
So he has a very big blunt looking emblem that doubles as an axe blade.
Oh, he just like takes that off his chest.
Yeah.
He just goes, he takes a stick, sticks it at his chest and goes, "Let's fucking dance."
And it's really cool.
So it's like...
His first move in a fight is to stab himself.
Supposedly stab himself in the chest with a stick.
He doesn't stab himself in the chest.
What the perspective from his opponent would be.
Yeah, kind of.
This is a square up with somebody that's going to make you leave.
Yeah, I'm out.
And it's badass.
There's all kinds of...
There's an interesting take on the whole bat background.
I don't want to spoil it all.
That's fine.
I want you guys to read it.
I like that...
It's called Absolute Batman.
The fact that he's not a rich guy is...
It's a big part of it and everybody's slightly just left the center.
Alfred Pennyworth is in it, but he's not the Alfred Pennyworth we know.
It's just all kinds of everything.
It's just a little off center and off kilter, but it's wonderful.
It's the best way to do it, to retell myths.
It's almost like if someone were to take the story of Hercules
and rejigger that a little bit, maybe add a little more of a downer ending.
Let's see where we can take that.
I wonder.
I don't know what you're referencing.
Are you referencing Samson?
I'm referencing the whole goddamn Bible.
Yeah, it's just Hercules, guys.
Wait, Hercules wasn't born in the Middle East?
Take it out.
Semantics.
I would try to call you on this, Paul, but all my Bibles disappeared today,
so I can't find them anywhere.
The Bible's weird.
I can't read them anywhere.
There's several absolutes in the lines.
Aren't there now, though?
There's a couple that have other retellings.
There are.
By the way, I'm just going to go back for a second.
You really don't deserve enough credit for saying
that Terry Fader thought he was going to get raptured.
I really think it's a really good theory.
It's what happened.
I guarantee you it's what happened.
If it's not the whole reason, it's part of the reason.
Yeah, it was in there.
Yeah, I think that.
I hope.
Because every fucking show, he's got to be like, "I love you!"
So those Las Vegas media has listened to us.
We've been quoted in some articles.
It'd be great if we made any of the trades.
Just vital Vegas real quick.
Vital Vegas, hit up Terry.
Or Johnny Katz, hit up Terry.
Did the rapture factor into your quitting?
Maybe he was afraid that his audience was going to get raptured,
and that was like two days of his ticket sales.
That's quite possible.
With the Batman thing, he's also got these funky things on his arms
that more closely replicate a bat's physiology.
So that's kind of neat, too.
But yeah, it's a whole new line of absolutes right now.
There's Absolute Batman, Absolute Wonder Woman, Absolute Flash,
and Absolute Superman, and Absolute Green Lantern.
I have read Batman, and I just got through the first trade
of Absolute Wonder Woman, which is fucking brilliant.
And I picked it up because it's gotten so much hype.
Overall, those are kind of the two standouts.
They're all apparently real good,
so I might even have to dip in some more.
Much as I'm a Marvel kid, I like me some bats every now and then,
and I don't read much Wonder Woman at all.
But that Absolute Wonder Woman is fan-fucking-tastic.
It's a seven-issue arc.
Were you texting anyone?
No, what do you call it?
No, it's really, really good.
No, I was checking on ChatGPT to find out what the origin of this Rapture thing right now is.
Please find out.
I want to know.
No, I've got it.
I've got it now.
OK, so real quick.
I was like, we could text a reporter or two.
So Matt, I really do hope you read it.
See if someone wants to go on air right now.
It'd be really funny.
Well, I really do hope you read it, and I hope you like it.
I'm going to read it.
And then I hope you give it to your kid.
Because I'm leaving from ScoopFest to go on three weeks of cruise.
Yeah.
I was like, you're going to have hours of that time.
Yeah, you're going to have some time.
So I'm absolutely packing that.
So this current Rapture myth is all apparently-- by the way, I feel like me doing a search is,
why is there a big Rapture rumor right now into an open AI chatbot?
It might be a sign of the Rapture.
Sure.
Just saying.
But apparently, a South African pastor named Joshua M-H-L-A-K-E-L-A claims he received a
vision that the Rapture would occur on September 23rd or 24th.
Apparently, Jesus in the vision was not specific between the 23rd or 24th,
or perhaps he hadn't made his mind up yet.
Was there a time zone?
There's always wiggle room.
There's always wiggle room when you go back.
But then that has apparently just gone crazy.
This is where I think we're not a cult.
I really-- I know that we joke going, oh, we're not a cult.
I'm just like, we are a cult.
No, we're not.
We?
Us?
I don't think we could pull off Rapture.
No, fucking no.
I don't think we could pull it off.
I don't think we could pull off anything.
No.
I wouldn't want to pull off anything malicious.
We didn't even win "Best of Vegas" podcast.
There is one thing that I thought about yesterday that I was like, if we did--
By the way, I got straight to-- you were right, by the way.
Did you know that?
Sorry.
We're all over the place today.
No, we're very smart today.
The organization that gave out the awards--
Oh, yeah.
--had editorial license over the awards.
Yeah.
No, I figured that had to be.
And so the popular vote was not the only determining thing.
So the people who won--
I'll just say it.
David Figgler was like, hey, by the way.
And he was like, just so you know.
The reason why is that they thought we were going to buy advertising from them.
And that's why they--
Oh, OK, great.
No, honestly, I assumed that it was because they were looking for podcasts about Las Vegas.
He's one of the people I thought I could text right now.
I'd get on the air and ask him about Terry Fader.
He might.
He might bite.
Yeah, he did.
No, I was like, I thought that they were--
I thought we had been edited out of it, because I couldn't see a way that we
wouldn't have won that when the other two things we pushed both won.
Every year, they tried to look up Jacob's Whiskey Pit.
They were like--
Yeah, I was like, they looked at Jacob's Whiskey Pit and said it wasn't a real thing.
And they looked at us and said, we're not a podcast about Las Vegas.
And that's not what they were looking for.
I mean, I was fine with it.
But I figured that's what happened.
It's not me.
I'm still burning in Vegas.
I'm burning with anger.
What can I say?
I'm going to fucking burn that place to the ground.
I don't remember who was giving out the award, but I remember.
I will burn it to the ground.
Whatever news source we don't give a shit about, it was giving out that award.
I wanted it.
No, no.
We love that news source and think they're very reputable,
because they gave awards to two of our friends.
That's right.
Yes.
We love that news source.
They're great.
They hooked up.
They gave awards to PIF and to SJ.
Tertiary people in our orbit.
Speaking of SJ, this is one thing I thought of yesterday.
I was like, if we pulled the trigger on this, I feel like the scoops--
a group of scoops, perhaps, would be unleashed.
OK.
And that is, there has been, over the last day or so, someone fucking with SJ online,
with band stuff.
And I think it has been quashed now.
I think it's done now.
OK.
Whoa.
But there was a few hours that I was like,
I might just call this guy out online and just say what has been happening with this
and just let the scoops fucking go hog.
Like, basically docks the scoops on him.
Dare we?
I was like, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I can't use the scoops for evil.
But I was like, if I just said--
I don't want anybody to harm anybody, first of all.
Let me be very blunt.
I don't want anybody to harm anybody.
No.
Some of those people that fucked us out of that award.
Yeah, except for them.
I want to harm them badly.
Anyone fucking with Garbage Man Batman.
Yeah.
But there was a misunderstanding through a booking thing and everything with the band.
And there was a request.
It doesn't matter what any of the details were.
Someone took their petty shit to the internet.
That's it.
And put videos out and comments and like--
Oh, no.
Really kind of went like, burn the bridges behind them.
Oh, dear.
Type raid on SJ's social media stuff.
That's--
And I was like, I'm about to fucking turn the digital scoops loose on this motherfucker.
Because I was like, the only things that we could do with this guy we have done,
which is basically reply to his initial message saying, here's why this got lost.
Whatever.
He accused her of ghosting.
This person accused the band and especially SJ of ghosting him.
Said that SJ wasn't a real name.
Made a parody porn thing that we were told about.
So this person really wanted to inflict pain.
Yeah, yeah.
And was going after different--
But apparently, everything's been taken down now.
A parody porn.
We've been told.
I have no idea.
That is the worst--
Don't send that to me.
Don't put that in my inbox.
No, thank you.
Gross.
Parody porn was reported to us by one person.
What kind of URL would that be, exactly?
We didn't see what it was.
Apparently, it was on OnlyFans.
Oh, OK.
Under what, though?
I don't know.
Under what now?
Under what names and--
Weird.
What specific search would you like to do?
Yeah, how would you find something like that?
There's definitely ghosts there.
Paul was talking about this awesome OnlyFans he found at dinner.
Like, the kind you can save to your files.
And can I introduce this guy to my wife also?
And can he put my wife in your wife?
Just because he's so mad?
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
But I was like, if I--
I hope he doesn't get mad with me.
If I start explaining this to, like, publicly, I was like, scoops will--
Oh, it would have gone crazy.
Because scoops would have gone crazy.
There are some scoops, especially, that would go crazier on that than would go--
than they would go if somebody had come after me, certainly.
I have never worried that if any one of us three are wrongfully besmirched,
that we would have not--
Don't you be besmirching.
I say wrongfully besmirched.
We could be righteously besmirched.
There's plenty of opportunity for us.
That's correct.
So please don't do that.
No one righteously besmirches us.
There's plenty of opportunities for us to put our fucking foot in the water.
My life is very fragile.
Or wrongly.
Though wrongly or rightly besmirched.
Just know that it's a house of cards.
You know, any--
We're barely being held together.
My eye is filled with blood.
Take a mess of one eye.
Any one of us could throw rice on the fire.
But we hopefully would not do something intentionally wrong.
But if we ever did get called out for some bullshit,
I know we'd have a lot of--
Scoops would have backs.
In-- we're not-- you basically got squashed today.
I believe it is squashed.
OK.
So nothing new happened today?
Nothing new happened today.
There was an email this morning.
But nothing new has happened since that email this morning.
And it seemed, after we got that email--
I'm not being vague about that.
The email just saying, like, everything is done.
From a-- this was an email from a third party,
saying it appears that everything has been deleted.
Everything looks good.
So someone stepped in.
Well, a third party.
Not an official third party, but like a friend of his.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
You may not be far enough away from it.
But actually, what you've just said is, like, so sad.
Oh, no.
It's horrible.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, in other words, like, that was--
Oh, I'm not mad about it at all.
I am-- I feel horribly for this person.
That's what I mean.
It's like, that person really thought
they were going to scorch Earth.
And the result of it was like, wait, what'd you do?
Yeah.
Like, it's like, aw.
Oh, no.
It's bad.
Yeah.
It's bad from every angle.
It really is.
Because it's like, he failed at that part.
The whole thing was silly.
Yeah.
At one-- yeah, there was a lot of just weird accusations
and weird things and lawsuits being threatened.
And which I'm like, literally made a song request
and is now threatening a lawsuit.
And like, did Alison feel like-- I'm sorry, SJ.
Did SJ feel like--
[LAUGHTER]
Also, like, that's why your real name is a weird fucking
debate to have online.
Pretend that she has a fake name is really funny.
On the internet, like, where people
don't have fake names already?
And I was like, you're-- you are a public figure.
Yeah.
It's easy to find out who you are.
That your name is SJ.
This is all-- this is ridiculous.
That's so strange.
Now, if you want to say that's not her real hair color--
Oh, no.
I'm going to fight you.
Yeah.
It is real.
But on the OnlyFans, the curtains match the drapes.
So you don't have to worry about that.
Ooh, a natural redhead.
Nope.
On my wife, there are neither curtains nor drapes.
Where would you possibly find that?
There are shutters.
Where could that be?
Shutters?
Oh, god.
She just wears a helmet?
Yes.
No, she has like a--
But tornadoes don't affect her.
She has a bevy of ticks down there.
Oh, no.
A bevy.
It's a bunch of-- it's a bunch of engorged ticks.
You know who else has a bevy of engorged ticks
instead of genitalia?
No, no, no.
She got the genitalia.
It's in place of pub-- pubis-- pardon me.
Pubis.
You know who else has a bevy of ticks instead of pubic hairs?
Blood engorged ticks.
The following sponsor, Yeti and Andretti's Spaghetti
and Confetti.
This is from episode 507.
Jeez, that's so old.
This is Ranchan.
I did that already.
Ranchan bringing it back in 2024.
This is Ranchan wanting it back.
This is fine.
This is fine practice because we're
doing Hollywood Squares with you this year.
That's right.
Yeti might be in there.
That's all right, Yeti.
You know exactly what time it is.
It's time for Yeti and Andretti's
Confetti Spaghetti.
That's right.
Everybody love it.
It's a party when the Confetti Spaghetti come out.
It's always al dente when I crash into the wall.
[INAUDIBLE]
You're right.
I drive pretty good.
I make a joke.
But it's no joke when you're hungry for colorful pasta shapes
and you want something to fill your belly.
Go ahead and order up a big plate of Yeti and Andretti's
Confetti Spaghetti just 10 minutes in the pot.
And mom, you're going to love how it tastes.
And dad, you're going to love how it feels.
And babies and kids, they're going
to love how it looks because it's colors, like a rainbow.
[INAUDIBLE]
You're right, Yeti.
I forgot to mention it's loaded with protein
and low in saturated fat now.
So go ahead and eat your pasta confidently.
Yeti and Andretti's Confetti Spaghetti.
Come and get it before it goes cold.
[INAUDIBLE]
And red number five.
Thank you.
Hey, Scoops, a check out.
ChatGPT can't find any credible evidence
that Terry Fader quit his Las Vegas show
because of the Rapture.
He gave no reasons, though.
No.
And didn't return phone calls.
He hits the Rapture.
Because he had been Raptured?
No, he just wanted to be ready.
For Vegas style, like typical Las Vegas stuff, is that--
Well, usually you want to get a last minute boost of ticket sales.
Well, here's the thing.
You want to announce the show is closing.
Right.
And get a little bit of that last minute influx of cash.
Yeah, here's the thing.
Maybe it wasn't him, but he's in those circles.
His fans were getting Raptured.
He was worried he was going to have ticket sales.
Maybe not fans, but possibly family, you know?
Could have been like, Terry, I'm getting ready to go meet the Lord.
It's like, well, I better go down to go see Grandma one more time
because she's going to be jumping off the roof.
No, the Rapture is on the 26th and 27th.
I think he thought--
I think if anything, I think it's more credible
that he thought he was going to be Raptured.
No, it's his next two days.
It's today and tomorrow.
Yeah.
Right.
But no, he wouldn't have like quit the show just to go
visit somebody who was going to go get Raptured.
Maybe he did.
No, maybe he did.
Because he knows down in his heart he's a sinner
and he's not going to go because remember,
he got caught up in some shit.
So you think he quit his show because he's a sinner
and isn't going to get Raptured?
Maybe because he's like, I better really--
he better clean it up.
Maybe he's going to take this next day and after.
In the course of the last 38 minutes.
Yeah, he's going to figure it out.
You've gone from he quit his show because he was getting Raptured
to he quit his show because he is not going to get Raptured.
But others--
I'm sorry, Paul did not answer that question.
I'm his attorney.
I like that question stricken from the record.
To be fair, I'm pretty sure I said--
He got past his first issue.
I said at the top, I said he quit the show
because of the Rapture.
Point and match.
So I think-- I honestly do think, like I bet, you know,
because almost all the religious shit is about guilt.
If it comes out that Terry Fader considered the Rapture
in any way when quitting this show--
Yes, how much money?
I think you're just right.
OK.
I think Paul 100% correct.
All right.
If he even considered for a moment that the Rapture
might play into a part of this.
I'm very happy with this, Terry, only because the other answer
is only that like this Vegas entertainment's becoming
a hellscape and that all of these things that we know
and love are going to go away.
I hope you can program LED lights.
Right, exactly.
I hope you can work with an AI program
and make Dorothy appear huge.
Well, I just did with Paul's with my favorite bits.
I think it's so funny.
I love when on television or movies,
lawyers yell, don't answer that.
And I was doing a show in San Antonio,
and I forgot to put bullshit in one of my pockets.
Uh-huh.
So I went to do a bit.
I was like, oh, shit, there's nothing in my pockets.
And I had the audience member on stage.
I go, quick, stall.
I got to put things in my pockets.
And I ran off stage.
And that thunder you just heard is SJ's car starting.
That thing sounds so amazing.
It really sounded like thunder thunder.
And I was like, what the fucking hell?
That was SJ's car?
And it's speakers.
And it's an electric.
SJ, can you hear my air quotes?
It's an electric.
That's Vivian.
I mean, SJ's car.
It's an electric, and it makes that startup noise.
That's so funny.
It's just from the speakers.
It's just got a Tesla coil in it.
It just fucking rattles.
So I go, be funny.
Tell a joke or something.
And I left.
And I went on stage.
And I put stuff in my pockets.
It was a small venue.
So the stage is right there.
And I just put stuff in my pockets.
And he got comfortable.
Like he said a couple things and got a laugh.
And then he just started talking.
And someone yelled a question at him.
And he was starting to feel himself, whatever.
And I go, do not answer that.
Do not answer that question.
And I went on with a bit like that.
But yelling, do not answer that.
You don't have to answer that.
From anywhere across the room, it's a good bit.
My favorite bit of yours still will always be my pearls.
My pearls.
Yeah.
If the lights go out anywhere--
My pearls.
It's the best.
It's a good bit.
The best.
Yeah.
I haven't had an opportunity to do it
because lights never go out.
We talk about, Paul, you lose power all the time in Pittsburgh.
Yeah.
But it's just me and the dogs.
The dogs don't laugh at the my pearls bit.
They don't.
They hate it.
And they go, no, they hate it.
Terrible.
They hate it.
They all pee instantly.
They're like, fuck you, dude.
That's fucking cheesy.
They're like, you got pearl money
and we're still feeding us this shit?
Yeah.
What do you do?
What?
I just ate a Caesar's dinner for the umpteen billionth.
They love Caesar's so much.
God, they love those little Caesar's dinners.
Your dog--
What?
Does this just make dog dinners?
Caesar's is a brand of dog food made by the Mars Company.
I thought the Little Caesar's Pizza Company as well.
No, because the Starbucks has those weird, like, lippy--
Lick cups?
They have like the dog cup thing.
No, these are--
Pup cups.
Pup cups gross me out, man.
It's just a cup full of whipped cream.
I just look so disgusting when I watch myself eat it.
But the boys love them, so he just gets them every time.
He's just covering your beard.
Did I get three pup cups?
You got a dog?
No.
You got a big old white spot on his nose.
Since when do you ever have a dog?
Yeah.
To order a pup cup?
Don't answer that.
Nazi Germany?
I live as a dog.
Next you can tell me I can't order off the kid's menu,
because I don't have a kid.
My pronouns are bow wow.
They do tell me I can't order off the kid's menu.
So I actually-- I order the kids at Cane's.
I do the kid's menu.
Oh, yeah, yeah, the Cane's.
The Cane's kids menu is perfect.
Two fingers is plenty.
Not Chinese guy.
Do you see the Japanese guy who lives as a dog?
Have I?
Yeah.
No.
He has a custom made--
Listeners, you'll notice I had to do it that way,
or Paul would just repeat that five times.
He has a custom made multiple thousand dollar fursuit
that makes him look like Lassie.
For real?
And it looks so real.
OK.
It will scare your--
He lives as this person or does this as a bit?
He lives as this dog as much as he can.
OK.
He has people take him to parks.
Oh, my God.
And be like, I'm their dog.
And he'll play with kids and shit and have other people--
No, he will not.
Have people--
No, he will not, actually.
Oh, yeah.
It's like kids birthday party entertainment.
Dad went to the park and this guy, just like a dog,
started playing with us.
Don't ever go to that park ever again.
We are moving.
You remember what it was like when you were playing games on--
It's better if I kill you now.
Playing games on the PlayStation.
That's him?
Sorry, Mitch, you just showed me a photo
and I'm seeing a picture of a dog.
That's him.
Dude, that's what I'm saying.
You can't-- from that distance, you won't be able to tell.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that just looks like a dog.
That's what I'm saying.
It does look like Lassie.
Do you see it in motion?
Yeah.
It's like you're playing a PlayStation game.
Like an original PlayStation game.
You're like, the graphics are right.
The internal skeleton is off.
The mocap is fucked somehow.
It's just a little off.
It's uncanny valley to an nth degree.
But for dogs.
For one fucking guy.
Paul, you have to surprise Ann by getting this guy to be your fifth dog.
Dude.
Poor Ann.
He doesn't have a corgi costume.
She--
There is a Patreon level, Scoops, if you want to be Paul's fifth dog.
No, seriously, I think it's like a $20,000 outfit.
Anyway--
Sorry, right now.
Go fund me.
It's above that.
Well, poor Ann.
She's home already.
Today's her first day alone.
Did you get any calls from Ann about anything going on in the basement or anything?
Fuck, I got a squirrel in the basement again.
You do not.
I think I do.
She told me there's a bunch of stuff falling off my shelves.
I'm like, no, that's a squirrel.
But Ann is clearly going to go down into the basement
and take care of the squirrel problem, right?
No.
When Paul first got here, he was like, I just got off the phone with Ann.
She said some DVDs and some figures and got knocked off a shelf.
The squirrel's back.
She said she's going to leave it down there until I get back,
so I'll have to deal with it.
Well, it's getting your time.
They got to come back inside.
You had a guy, didn't you?
Didn't you call a guy?
No, I did it all myself.
Did you consider dressing up as a squirrel?
I called people, but they were like, I can't really do anything.
Good luck.
That's what they say.
Now, the last time you had a hole in the wall--
We still do.
OK, maybe that's the culprit.
No, shit.
That hole is structural.
No, this is--
But now we call that hole off limits.
We're getting the house fixed.
There's a sign with a no squirrel, a big no strike through it.
They can't figure it out.
The house is going to get repaired in like three weeks.
They're coming out to fix the building.
OK.
But of course, three weeks.
And here comes another fucking squirrel, because it was raining so hard.
Now, Ann thinks possibly the sump pump kicked on
and it was enough vibration to shake stuff loose.
But we know.
We know that's not true.
It's maybe.
I'm giving that sump pump vibration.
It's maybe, but I don't know.
I don't think so.
Nope.
Squirrel.
I guess we'll see.
Is it possible that this squirrel only wants to be on this podcast?
This is not the same squirrel.
We don't know that.
I do.
We caught that squirrel and we drove him five miles away.
This is how long it took him to get back.
Five miles.
No way a squirrel could travel five miles.
You might be right.
I don't know.
Do you think it's a Japanese guy dressed up like a squirrel?
If it is, I got it.
I got a very sexy night ahead of me when I get back home.
Yeah, exactly.
Speaking of sexy nights and problems that Paul can't solve,
it's time for Jock versus Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock versus Nerd.
Explosion.
Rapture Teens.
Rapture Teens?
Teens, yeah.
That's the only fancy company that has SJ's face on it.
Oh, shit.
RaptureTeens.org/rapture Sorry, guys, I can't do this.
I got to go check a website out real quick.
At your computer.
Mitzi is here.
We're going to have him come on on Zoom, but he's here in person.
He's been touting this version of Price is Right to us for quite some time.
Yes, that's right.
And he learned what everyone else learns, which is like, just do it and we'll say yes.
Not hard.
This is borrowed from Dropout TV on the internet.
Shout out Dropout TV.
Great.
They had an episode and it was very tilting and fun to watch.
Dropout TV's Emily Gillette called me.
He's like, you have to get these shows on Dropout TV.
They're layups for you and Paul would crush on them.
And I was like, Emily, we're old.
20 years ago, it would have been perfect for you.
Yeah.
Young people were on that.
Young people at the UCB theater are on it.
So they have...
My students became teachers, those students became teachers,
and those teachers taught the people who are on Dropout TV.
Right.
So you're like the great, great, great grandfather of Dropout TV.
Look, you know, when Ben Schwartz was like, yeah, I mean, you guys really
paved the way and put me in a generation above him comedically.
But I was like, you would sit in on my show all the time.
Why am I old?
We graduated together.
And then I was like, oh, I guess he's right.
Yeah.
I looked back and I was like, wait, he's right.
Sometimes they're just right.
We still have a fun podcast.
Paul, thank you for waking up in time to say that.
All right.
So this is second closest scooperty.
The point is not awarded to who gets the answer correct.
The point is awarded to who gets second closest to the actual answer.
OK.
More importantly, there's no price is right rules.
There is no price is right rules.
The only time that factors is if two people are equally wrong,
the person that's lower gets the tiebreak.
Gotcha.
So if you're both five off, if Matt's five over, Paul's five under.
I've never been happier with a game.
All right.
I did add a wrinkle.
If somebody gets it exactly right, second closest gets a bonus point.
Hilarious.
That's really funny.
I like that rule.
Yeah, I like it.
All right.
So these are all numbers.
Even when they're exactly right, second closest is still right.
Yeah.
So even if you're right, the answers are always numbers.
Yes.
Everything is going to be a number.
Great.
I could find a way.
I mean, you can find a way, but it's going to be really hard to input in the spreadsheet.
All of these numbers are based off of Google AI.
So we can trust that source.
As of getting warmed up.
I thought he was just yelling numbers.
Yeah, I'm just yelling out some numbers.
Yeah, you were right.
He's yelling out numbers.
Starting with the first question.
Jacob, you are first on the list.
So you go first.
All three of you will give your answers and then I'll give you the right result.
You're not the boss of me.
How many hotel rooms are there in the Las Vegas Valley?
Las Vegas Valley.
So all of Las Vegas area.
Yeah.
Not just the strip.
For a hint, according to Google, there's 50,000 on the strip.
Yeah, I think it's like 200.
I like 225,000.
225,000.
Some people would say that differently.
Some people might, Matt.
Those people have two not bloody eyes.
I will go with 175,000.
Interesting.
Some people would have said that differently.
175,000.
And Paul?
300,000.
Wow.
Trying numbers.
All right.
The actual answer.
Thank you very much.
Nailed it.
150,859, which makes Matt our closest guess.
One point.
Nope.
That's not one point to Matt.
No, it's one point to Jacob.
One point to Jacob.
Our second closest guess.
Yes.
Damn it.
All right.
One second.
I'm great at this game.
One of my equations got broken.
Mitzi's already having a hard time with it, but I'm great at it.
Okay.
150,000 you said?
I'm locked in now.
I've got it figured out.
Sorry, one second.
I have never been more angry that we're not on video for a show.
I've been on video for how many shows in a row, and we're not on for this one.
Paul is just a face and a sea of comfort around him.
Keeping it in Vegas parking and weather related.
Going with Matt first on this one.
How many jets, blasters, and nozzles are there in the Bellagio fountains?
Oh, fuck.
What counts as a jet, a blaster, or a nozzle?
Well, the jets is a gang.
Blasters are time travelers.
When you're a nozzle, you're a nozzle all the way.
Nozzles are just, you know, idiots.
Muggles.
Nozzles is what we call the people watching the show.
Not just jets, it's jets.
Nozzle squirt, water up in the area.
800.
Matt guesses 800.
Paul?
I'm gonna need about 350.
How is Paul as a drunk?
I'm gonna say 801.
801.
All right.
There are 1214 jets.
Which means Jacob would be closest, so Matt gets the point.
I thought it was gonna be like seven something or six something.
I love it.
It's already the much better version of Price is Right.
I love this.
I gotta fix this because I just realized there was one little error in my equations.
You're cooking, buddy.
All right.
How many pounds of ice cream?
We're starting with Paul this time.
Zoned in.
How many pounds of ice cream were used for the world's largest ice cream sundae
made in 1988 by Palm Dairy?
10 pounds.
10 pounds of ice cream is the world's largest ice cream sundae.
All right, Jacob?
Wait, go this way?
Beat it.
Beat that, all right?
Good luck.
Good luck being better than second best on that.
I'm gonna say...
How much?
More than 30.
Oh, really?
More than 30?
I only said 10.
Oh, I don't know what you said.
I said 10.
800 pounds.
Oh my god, that's insane.
And Matt?
11.
11?
You sneaky fuck.
The correct answer is 44,687.
Jacob would have been closest, but due to math,
Matt is second now there.
I played it right.
He gamesmanshiped it properly there by knowing that Paul was so far off
that you could be one better than him and be correct.
I was close.
This might give an even bigger advantage to the person who goes third.
That's true.
Well, I mean, it depends on genuine answer or not.
Right, right.
All right, next up.
That's a genuine answer.
This one we are starting with Jacob.
We're back to the top.
As of May 19th, 2025.
Ask something about ghosts.
How many episodes of The Simpsons have aired?
Something about ghosts.
I asked for a ghost question.
Oh, Simpsons episodes?
How many have been?
As of when?
As of May 19th, the most recent airing of their most recent episode.
So there have been 532 episodes.
532.
Matt, what episode?
Five hundred and thirty.
All right.
There have been 790 episodes.
Yes.
No.
Locked in.
What did I say?
You said five thirty two.
I got it.
Paul said five thirty.
So he's second.
Oh, in my mind, I said five twenty two.
I don't even know what I said anymore.
All right.
Starting going in the middle is really tricky.
It really is.
Just say ten.
How many minutes is the combined run?
Where's my ghost?
Of all 21 official studio albums by Bruce Springsteen.
Oh, wait, what about ghost?
How many minutes?
It's spooky season.
Is the runtime of all of 21 of Bruce Springsteen's studio albums?
Wow.
One thousand eight hundred.
Paul.
It's hard to game this one.
Yeah, one thousand eight hundred and one.
Oh, Jacob.
It'll be weird when Paul gets it on the nose.
Which way is wrong?
Right, right.
So this is the thing, right?
So now you have to figure out what your right answer is.
Right.
In your mind.
That's it.
And then figure out where you want to be.
I have a 50/50 chance.
Well, if Matt is closer to the answer than you are right now.
Not possible.
If Matt is closer to the answer than you are, then you get a point.
If you're closer to the answer than Matt is, then Matt gets a point.
Wait, no, but you have to guess and that'll change it all.
Right.
But you said right now.
I was answering the question that you asked.
Oh, I guess you're right.
Something about ghosts, please.
There's not a lot of ghost math.
Sorry, man.
What were the two answers?
Eighteen hundred.
Eighteen hundred for Matt and eighteen oh one from Paul.
Eighteen oh two.
All right.
The call was between eighteen oh two and seventeen seventy nine or seventeen ninety nine.
Right.
I'm getting this one locked in.
The correct answer is one thousand one hundred and seventy eight minutes.
Shit.
Paul gets the point.
Oh, yeah.
Closest.
Yeah.
Matt was closest with eighteen hundred.
Paul was second with eighteen oh one.
So by sandwiching Paul.
I meant through the other.
But you couldn't have sandwiched yourself in between us.
Right.
OK, this is fascinating.
But you couldn't.
But I couldn't that time.
Right.
That's right.
Oh, that is a different because I'm using ghost math.
In September.
OK, I like this.
OK, OK, OK.
I think we found a new tactic.
I like this.
That's true.
We definitely found a new tactic.
How many distilleries are currently operating in the United States of America?
Do they count Guam and Taiwan?
Matt, we are starting with Paul.
Of course not.
Now, distillery means makes rum, makes alcohol, makes alcohol.
Distilleries.
Although it just makes.
So St. Croix counts with Cruz and rum.
So I'm going to guess there's probably.
Oh, probably.
I'm going to rough guess.
Let's say a hundred.
No, probably two hundred per state.
Per per state per state.
Oh, so you want to maybe this is my.
You want us to just tell you now that's wrong and showing.
Not all states are like Kentucky.
Thank the fuck God.
And the fuck God is my favorite.
Yes, he's the good one.
Hello, God of fuck.
I am the God of fuck.
Wait, are you done?
Two hundred states.
Two hundred per state is not right.
So using ghost man.
If this is your first episode of listening to Matt Madley's ice cream social, I would.
I'm sorry.
Just stop now.
This bail.
I really thought he was just relying on me to do the math.
Like two hundred per state.
Go for it.
Whatever you think that might be.
No, no, no, no, no.
You got the number in front of you.
Just put me close to it.
Yeah, no.
OK, well, let's do.
Is this the first guest on this question?
Five thousand five thousand.
OK, Jacob.
Four thousand nine hundred ninety nine.
OK, now we're playing for shit.
No, so I get the gamesmanship, right?
Because then if I go somewhere more realistic.
If you if you go realistic.
Yeah, then you give me the point that I give you to go unrealistic.
You give Paul the point.
No, yes.
You went forward and you know, no, no.
I went one under you even one.
So Matt can't get between us, right?
But you either has to go under or over.
If he goes over, then that's going to be point to me.
That's what I just said.
And you followed that up and say no and then said the same thing here.
Basically, I'm in a position to either give Jacob or you a point.
That's the only thing I can do exactly yet.
So the question is, do you think the number or less than their number?
Or you could get it exactly right and give us two points.
That is true.
That is an opportunity.
Matt, get it exactly right.
All right. For the sake of getting exactly right.
Here we go.
Daddy's rolling the dice.
Thirteen hundred twenty one.
Ghost math.
All right. The correct answer is two thousand two hundred and thirty,
meaning Jacob is second closest.
So Paul was closest.
Yes.
Have you gone over?
No, no, I was close.
Matt was closest.
I was way over.
Oh, you both are way over.
There's only two thousand places making booze.
Yeah. Can you imagine?
That's why there's such a shortage.
That's why you can't find booze anywhere.
I'm realizing right now.
I'm like, holy shit, why can't I remember any of these answers?
It's because I never have to.
I usually have the computer screen in front of me.
Next up, we've got a fun one.
This is one of my favorite ones.
This is about ghosts.
Are you keeping track of the points?
Yeah, I got it.
It is currently a three way tie at two points a piece.
Who has the second most points?
Me. I am currently winning with the second most points in this game.
How many more questions do you have?
I have four plus a couple of backups.
So a lot of questions.
I got two more.
Two more sounds great.
Then we'll keep going if we want to keep going.
How many college football teams are currently playing football in the Big Ten?
We are starting with Jacob on this.
The Big Ten.
For you non-sportsball fans, this is actually a very good question.
I think like.
Four.
Four is Jacob's guess.
Matt, how many teams are currently playing in the Big Ten?
Ten.
Solid guess.
Paul?
Five.
So you're thinking of the Pac-12, which has two teams.
And not the Big 12, which has 16 teams.
Because, you know, math.
The Big Ten obviously has 18 football teams.
Which makes Matt the closest guess and Paul the second closest guess with five.
I thought Paul went below me.
No, he didn't go below you.
He went ten, he went five.
I'm using ghost math.
So currently, ghost math is winning the game.
Come at me.
Casper is running this thing.
How many days, how many days were there between the groundbreaking
and the grand opening of the Fountain Blue Las Vegas?
Oh, Jesus.
Holy shit.
That was a boondoggle.
How many days?
With ghosts.
Who goes first?
This one starts with.
I think I went first last time.
Matt, you start first.
Oh yeah, because I said four on the last one.
Fourteen hundred.
Fourteen hundred days.
Paul, how many days between the groundbreaking to the grand opening?
Fourteen hundred and one.
Eat that.
Fourteen hundred, fourteen hundred, fourteen, no one.
Fuck.
So again, like I just decide, I decide who to use.
No, who you want to give two points to going for this.
Let's see.
Three hundred sixty five times.
Seventeen.
Oh, you think they did it on the actual anniversary?
No, no, but like.
Oh, but you're just doing that.
It was roughly 17 years.
Was it?
Yeah, 17.
It was a fuck ton of time.
Seventeen years.
So let's see if I go high, Matt gets a point.
If I go low, Paul gets a point.
Right.
Not 17 years.
Paul has the lead.
Matt has fourteen hundred guests.
Paul has fourteen oh one.
Ah, OK.
So if you go high, I get a point.
Right.
You go high and I get a point.
Wait, wait, you say the Fountain Blue?
Yes.
Oh, one day.
One day.
Yeah, one day.
That's right.
It was one day.
All right. Well, Jacob was close.
It was I couldn't find the official day of the groundbreaking,
but I found an article on February 2nd of 2007.
OK.
And it opened December 13th, 2023.
Yeah.
So six thousand one hundred and fifty eight days.
That was a lot of time.
Five ownership groups, I believe,
and multiple other things that happened in that time.
I think a couple of court orders to tear down what had already been constructed.
So that means I get the point, right?
Yes.
It does.
Which means right now, Matt and Paul are tied at three,
which means Jacob has the second most points.
And when Matt and Paul are tied in Jack vs.
Nerd, second most points win the game.
Yeah, we could do that if we really want to.
It's really funny.
Second most points wins the game.
You can say that adds a whole other layer of strategy.
It's so much more confusing.
It does.
I have three.
I have four more questions.
We can play for second second second if we want.
No, let's wrap it up.
No, that's good.
One more, but this is all right.
This is this is one last one.
He doesn't have any about ghosts.
Well, not with that attitude.
All right.
Oh, we're going to go with this one.
I have two that I'm trying to between.
What is the current cost to join the Las Vegas a season
ticket holder priority list in American dollars?
You're probably going to say you're pride, but that doesn't.
Starting with Jacob.
Oh, shit.
God damn it.
Why does it start with me?
Four hundred seventy two dollars.
Matt, this is just to get on the list.
This is the this is the down payment to put your secure your spot
for the A's season tickets.
What did you say?
Four hundred seventy two.
Four hundred seventy three dollars.
All right, Paul.
It is definitely more than that.
Shit.
But I think four hundred and seventy.
What did you say, Jacob?
Two.
That's a four seventy two.
Four seventy two fifty.
This is actually the only time you can technically get in there
with a middle number.
It's terrible.
Oh, it gets even better, guys.
The current price to join the season ticket list is 19 dollars
and one cent.
Oh, shit.
I got that right.
I still won.
No, I knew you got the point.
Yeah, I thought it was like a hundred bucks.
Yeah.
So here's the thing.
Paul got the point, which now gives Paul four points,
which means Matt wins the game because he has three points.
Jacob loses with two.
We did it, guys.
Well, that made me the first runner up.
I like it.
Excellent new game, Missoula.
Hope Jack have fun programming that one.
Yeah, holy shit.
Well, here's the thing.
If you were to host a live again,
I think the way to do it would be for all of us to.
You could write your answer down and then show it.
So that way you can't do it this way.
So you can't do gamesmanship.
So even if we did on Zoom, we could private message you.
Yeah.
Our guesses without you.
Right.
That's something that we can or we could just write it down.
Or just write it down and hold it.
We can figure it out.
Yeah, we could write down a piece of paper, hold it to the camera.
Normally, I'm like the lowest tech guy.
I can't even come up with a lower tech solution.
What are you talking about?
Matt's like, just make all the answers below 10
and we can just use our fingers.
You know what?
That's actually better.
For one of them is not a bad idea.
This is this game is all just all within 10 to 1 to 10.
Feel free to sign your answers to me at any time.
I want to thank Penn Jillett for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Penn.
We don't have anyone else to thank right now
because we are in the back and I've done a bad job at prepping for this show.
That's we're going to do a lot.
We got a lot going on.
We got a lot of thanking.
We got a lot of jiggering with our Patreon.
I want to thank Mitzi for stopping by with a brand new game.
Of course.
Thanks for having me, gentlemen.
Or an updated or an old version of the game.
A fun, a fun version.
Yes, a fun old version.
Yeah, and thank you to everybody who supports us over on Patreon.
You are the reason that we're able to do this show.
You are the reason that we are able to do things like ScoopFest this week,
which is the reason that you're getting an insane show right now.
So there are a lot of reasons and they're all for you.
Congratulations.
Yeah, for anybody who has left a bunch of money
by their unraptured neighbors, you can send that our way.
Yep.
At preachingfun.com.
Slash Rapture.
I was all ready for it.
I expect to be thanking Terry Fader next week.
It is so weird.
It is so weird hearing these sound clips not at one and a half feet.
And if you want more questions about ghosts, go to fartsinabag.biz.
Bring it.
Next second closest, just ghosts, oops, all ghosts.
That's fartsinabag.biz along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you to our Patreon page.
We're for as little as three dollars a month.
You can upkeep this show on the air.
Like I said, the Patreons are the reason that we are able to do this show
twice a week each and every week, no matter what is going on in life like this week.
Exactly.
So here you go.
Enjoy.
Take care.
Thanks, everybody.
I was going to ask Paul, did you like the video I made for the bucket show this week
with their pop up guys?
Yes.
I really thought they were going to kiss at the end.
I was disappointed they didn't kiss.
There's a lot of sexual tension between those two dolls.
It was really heavy.
Thanks a lot for this, everybody.
Take care of yourselves out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
I did like it.
I liked it.
It's funny, though.
It's just somewhere in the middle, that's all.
There's a bunch of Christians who aren't Christian at all right now.
There's a bunch of other Christians who are diving way too in on this rapture stuff.
But that's me in the middle.
Those aren't Christians either.
That's not what Christian Christianity is not about going up into space.
Wait, whose rapture is that Christian?
It's not it.
It is a weird small sect thing that came up in like the 20s.
It's not truly Christian.
It's evangelical at best.
There's not a way to buy yourself out of it.
So it's definitely not from the Catholic Church.
Exactly.
It's right to who?
If it's if it can't be cured with a plenary indulgence, I don't want to hear about it.
See you tomorrow.
You've heard me talk about Samaritan.
And today I get to tell you about an additional sharing option called Redeem HealthShare.
It's everything we love about Samaritan, like the freedom to choose your providers
and be in control of your health care, but with more program options to fit your budget
and health care needs in a modern digital platform.
There's an add on feature to allow for a wider range of medical bills to be shared,
including preventative, dental, vision, and routine care.
Join the hundreds of thousands of fellow Christians and check out RedeemHealthShare.org today!