Oh, hello there. I am so glad that you're here. I want to take this opportunity to thank
you the ice cream truck drivers. Thank your ice cream truck drivers. Right now. Sorry.
I got confused because I fucked something else up. It doesn't matter. Right now. I'd
like to.
This is a message from sponsor Intuit Turbo Tax. You've sent so many emails to your tax
pro and nothing. It feels like you're chasing updates, but now your taxes are done for you
by a TurboTax expert. So you actually know what's happening. You can match with an expert
and just hand off all your tax stuff to them right in the app. So instead of guessing,
you can feel confident your TurboTax experts on it. Now this is taxes. Intuit TurboTax.
Visit TurboTax.com to learn more. Only available with TurboTax experts. Real time updates only
in iOS mobile app.
Thank Dr. Scoop Little, Elton Magic Scoop, Fifi, Frankie Sticky Scoop, Galactic President
Scooper Star McScoops-A-Lot, Ice Blue Scoop, I wanna Scoop Baby, Jacob Dickeliger, and
Jake Schneider.
Race to savings now at Menards. We carry the largest in stock selection of Energizer batteries
ready for your next project. Power up your devices with Energizer batteries. Nothing
outlasts the long lasting power of Energizer ultimate lithium batteries. Right now get
a four pack of lithium batteries for $9.99 through February 14th. Plus view our weekly
flyer on Menards.com and race to savings on all your battery needs at Menards.
Save big money at Menards.
If you wanna be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows,
the life you save may be your own. That's right. I forgot to hit record on the zoom
in case we have zoom people talk. So now I'm gonna hit record on the zoom. Now we're recording
on zoom. Woo! Here we go!
Hey Johnny, do you wanna go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Oh yeah! Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social! Coming to ya! From three different locations
around the globe! It's time for Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social! Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's
Paul Mattingly! Sitting in Los Angeles, that's Matt Donnelly! Sitting in Las Vegas, it's
me, Jacob the Audio Guy. We're PreachingFun! Hey guys!
Very exciting, very exciting stuff guys.
Yeah!
What happened?
Um, I'm being sarcastic, but uh, no, I'm in LA doing a little run at the Magic Castle.
Nice!
Have you already started that or is that coming up soon?
No, I started it. We did it on Wednesday night and Thursday night so far.
What room are you in?
The Peller Theatre, which is funny because it's a theatre that features duos, so people
think Peller is a combination of Penn and Teller, but it's not true. Just by coincidence,
the guy who pwned it up the cash to make it happen was a guy named Albert Peller, got
the theatre named after him. And uh, yeah, it's-
But you know the interesting thing about Albert, right?
Go ahead.
Did you know Albert?
No.
I don't know if you knew Albert or not, but he actually changed his name to represent
Penn and Teller. He was such a big fan of Penn and Teller that he changed his name to
celebrate Penn and Teller, and then by coincidence, that theatre was named after him.
Originally, his last name was Angel Field, but then he found more magic people to change
his name to, so-
His name used to be Shithouse!
He changed it in the third century.
But yeah, and so I'm playing with my buddy Nick Paul, a very funny guy, and one bit we
always do in the show is we say we have an improv background, and so we do improv during
a magic trick where I basically just try to mess with him while he does a magic trick.
I love- I still haven't seen this idea live. I love this idea.
It's really fun. It's really fun. Last night, I was messing with him and I actually messed
up the trick.
Good!
You got into it so you're playing the bit too hard.
Exactly.
I'm honestly not interested in you fucking with him during the set if you've never fully
messed up a trick while fucking with him.
No, and I did this bit during my magic live show, so when I messed up and he really had
to reset, I go, "Don't worry. I can handle this. I'm an improv guy, a master of crowdwork.
Sure, I mostly work cruise ships, but crowdwork is universal. Hands up, who's celebrating
their 50th wedding anniversary?"
Crowdwork is the same no matter where you go. Quick!
Who's celebrating their 50th wedding anniversary?
Where are my people who are turning 100 right now? Hey, there they are. There's always a
group of them no matter where I go. There's always a group of people turning 100.
Look at that. There's the man himself, Arthur Peller, at 110. There he is.
How old is he? He dead?
Little is known about him. Little is known about him. He's an enigma.
No one knows. No one knows.
Is that right? No.
It depends on how wide you want the scope to go.
No one on this show knows. Yeah, no one playing the Peller Theater this
week knows. That's what I know. Yeah, but we're doing a show. I have a new bit. I put
a new bit in the show with Ray Applethorne's fine craftsmanship again, but I'm not going
to give too much away because I'm going to perform it at ScoopFest. We'll talk about
it after. I'm sure we'll be talking about it after ScoopFest, so there you go.
Look at us. We're talking about it now. It's super fun. It's a super fun bit. Yeah, it's
been a great run so far. It's always fun to be back out here.
Nice. Yeah. Nice, nice, nice.
I've had a comic booky week. You got exposed to radiation and now you can turn green at
will. Well, I told you guys I saw Thunderbolts, yeah?
Oh yeah. Yeah, you needed that.
Didn't really like it. I just saw Superman.
Any better? What did you get, the soup or the man?
I stuck with the soup and I don't regret it. Waiter, there's a man in my soup. That's
Superman. Has that been done before? That's a good one.
I know. My brain went to the same exact thing. That's a good joke.
That's just a simple turn. That has to be done before, but it's really nice.
That has to have been done before by somebody. Yeah, that's Superman. Oh, okay.
It's all right. It's okay. It's fine. I'm a Marvel guy, not a DC guy.
I was going to say, some people are finding it very emotional seeing that movie.
Really? Yeah.
The last couple minutes, the old James Gunn heart string machine fires up.
Oh, that's right. It is a James Gunn one, isn't it?
It fires up on full cylinders in the last couple moments.
At some point in the movie, there's a baby raccoon that they're torturing and he's crying.
He throws babies, dogs, squirrels, everything. He throws everything at the fucking screen.
He hates automatically his emotions. No, no, no, it's fine.
Waiter, scoop and chat with a bold opinion that this man was a lot better than the Snyder
Man. Wow. Wow. Whoa. The famously bad Snyder Superman.
I was going to say, so is everything. Yeah.
So is me just telling you about Superman. Jesus. So bad. But yeah, it's all right.
But I don't know. I don't see how they're going to build the franchise off all this,
but we'll see. Now, we'll see. Yeah, I don't care about that, though.
But that's the whole thing. No, no, no, no, no. James Gunn's in charge
of making new DC films. Fact. This, this supposed, you know, the Superman has to be responsible
for every single movie that's going to come out after this. I think it's just not something
that has to happen. Okay. All right.
I think the DC is fucking up timing wise bigger than bigger than just will they be able to
do a sequel or universe around this? I think everybody is ready to take a break from superhero
movies. I think that I think yes, the majority of people around are ready to be done with
superhero movies for a little while. I know, which, which I know leads me to why DC is
such a terrible company. The best movie they've made recently is just too little too late.
Yeah, it is. Like a good superhero movie. Everybody's
tired of watching superhero movies. Shit. And it really is a matter of timing. Like
you say, Jacob, and I think it's more to the point of at least for me, my personal self,
not only am I a little bit done with the whole onslaught of superheroes, but I think more,
more for me, I feel like I can't even, I can't even believe in this shit at all at this point
because no one's stepping up to do shit. When did you believe in the end? The Superman?
Oh, I, I don't believe in the Superman. I believe in the spider-man. Ah, there it is.
But just leave sticky webs everywhere, everywhere that you go. But I don't know. It's just,
it's just hard to, to, to get your gumption up for that, uh, you know, truth and justice
stuff when truth and justice is under such direct attack in a lot of places, name one
place that it's not going the way you think. The fucking Smithsonian? Uh, no, uh, yeah.
I mean, it's, it's preposterous. That's the thing. And I just kinda like, well, all right.
Listen to this podcast though, that I was trying for a while to have a no sarcasm rule,
uh, when I was talking about things and it's just too overwhelming. I can't. Agreed. I
can't. Agreed. 100% agreed. I can't. I can't be genuine all the time, people. You don't
want to hear us speaking earnestly about this. And I don't want to, I don't want to speak
earnestly about it at this point, but I want to, I want to make my opinion known to a point,
but I mean, I, yeah, hold on. I'm going to take a moment and just speak earnestly about
it. You know, Vern, I'm really tired of the Smithsonian getting changed around to show
what other people are. That's right, Vern. I'm super tired of it. I'm going to say Christmas
and go to jail. Vern. I went to the convenience food Mart the other day and they done changed
it up. They called the Super Gulp the big sipper. Damn it, Vern. And they're racing
our history, Vern. Anyone young listening to our podcasts, uh, sorry. That means under
40. Yeah, just did a, a very good Jim Varney, a pull there. Uh, Jacob, I like that. Yes.
Ernest goes to camp was a thing. Yeah. And then Ernest does anything became a thing.
And Ernest goes to jail where he got electrical superpowers. Ernest goes to camp crocodile.
That's the new one. Uh, I remember actually, I remember watching this movie. I remember
watching Ernest goes to camp. Uh, we would have different, uh, different, different families
would step up sometimes, take care of, uh, take care of us, you know, uh, give my dad
a break when he was just raising us as a single dad. And, uh, I remember being at the Chadwicks,
uh, they were lovely family that would take care of my, my little brother and I for weekend.
And um, uh, they had, uh, a daughter who was like eight years older than us. Yeah. Oh man.
She was, she was gorgeous in taste of like, uh, you know, whatever. And so you were all
in love with her. Yeah, exactly. And everybody was in love with the daughter and we're sitting
there at, uh, you know, 11 and 12 being like, you want to want to hang. And I remember,
I remember torturing her, um, as, uh, uh, me loving and pointing out every single joke
I loved. And Ernest goes to camp to her. Like she was trying to like, just for minutes on
him and be like, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. She was
trying to like leave the room and I was like, no, no, the golf cart came back. That's the
same ghost golf cart from the beginning. Amazing. That's amazing. That daughter name was Sarah
Lowe. His name was Saint Mother Teresa. I mean like all she's thinking is like these
poor kids with their dead mom, I guess I can sit here and listen to the fucking breakdown
of Ernest goes to camp. Is this what dead moms do to kids brains? I can turn them onto
this Jim Varney shit. Jesus Christ. He got mushed out in the head real quick. I either
volunteered as a boy soup kitchen, or I guess listen to this drivel for an hour. Let's just
do that. Oh damn it. Well, Saturday, uh, keeping on my comic book theme, my local guy, he's
moving soon and he's having a, he's having a big sale on a bunch of his, uh, dollar books
and what, what have you. And, uh, so he's got his cheap bins and then, uh, he, he made
them all his dollar books. He sold them for a dime a piece for this one day sale. Yeah.
That's less than a dollar. I got 160 some books for like 16 bucks. It was amazing. That's
awesome. Uh, so yeah, I, I, I had a real good sweep there. Got a bunch of X men and X force
and a bunch of little Nicky nacks, all kinds of weird stuff. Uh, some, somebody swooped
in before me and got all the Spider-Man, but that's all right. Uh, I've got a lot enough
Spider-Man, but, uh, yeah. So it's been very, uh, very comic book heavy week for me here,
which is nice. Um, and then I went to, and let me go to another comic book shop. We went
together out at the Pittsburgh mills, the Pittsburgh mills. Have I told you guys about
the fucking Pittsburgh mills? No baseball team. So the Pittsburgh mills is an almost
abandoned mall. Okay. They've got, it's a dead mall, but it's got like three stores
still left in it. And currently it has a spirit Halloween, a Macy's and a giant comic book
shop. And that's about what it's good. Then I say giant comic book shop. I mean, giant
comic book shop. It is huge. Takes up like five storefronts, ginormous anyway. Uh, when
because there's also a lot of eateries right there around the Pittsburgh mills mall. That's
where we go to Chili's sometimes. So we were going to go, if you do a Google search for
the Pittsburgh mills mall, the first thing that comes up is why did the Pittsburgh mills
mall close? Yeah. And it's, and it, exactly. This mall is closed. Go ahead and look up
Pittsburgh mills mall potholes. Because as soon as I suggested, let's drive out to the
mills and Anne agreed, I said, I'll drive if you're not going to give me guff about
the potholes. And she's like, I'll drive because there are God sized cracks in the earth that
await await your vehicle. And Anne just can't, she's like, ah, anytime I hit one the wrong
way, it's like, forget it. She will drive around the whole parking lot. So the, the,
the place closed quote unquote, the mills closed and everything's in this weird litigation
space, right? And it comes down to the stores that are renting their quick timeout aren't
just clear. You said I'll go if you don't complain about the potholes. And her answer
was I'll drive. Yes. So yes. And was like, no, no, I'm going to complain about the potholes.
So I guess I should drive. That's it. Like, yeah, she's like, I'll just, I'll just drive.
She's like, here's the other thing. She's like, I'm going to complain about them. That's
a non-starter. You know, you can't put that on the table. I wouldn't, I'm going to veto
that right away. That was done. If the only way that my husband can drive me is if I don't
complain about the potholes, I suppose I'll do the drive. That's what she said. And I'm
like, okay, fine. Now I heard that conversation happen. I accepted it and I moved on because
I have been a part of that conversation word for word. Absolutely. And to, to her credit,
she's been having to go from store to store all around this district, right? Yeah. So
she goes, there's a cup, there's a store out by the mills that she goes to. So she knows
these streets. So she knows where the killer potholes are. So she has some sense of the
navigation of the streets and I don't knows the streets. Don't ever question it. Don't
ever question it. Anne McPheeters knows the street. It was like, uh, I think it's called
like a Harbor pilot or whatever, but basically, um, when you bring big ships into, to ports,
they, they, they, they take a small boat. They shepherd out a guy who knows how to navigate.
Yeah. Yeah. The tugboat to get you away from the rock. Yeah. I like that. And they could
fucking use that out there. And as the Harbor pilot of potholes getting to this thing, like,
no, no, we're going to, we're going to go sideways here for about 25 feet. We're going
to drift for a while. Look up the fucking potholes. I'm crazy. The Pittsburgh mills
mall is currently experiencing a significant pothole problem with a recent lawsuits filed
by the mall's owners, uh, and even by neighbor, uh, neighboring businesses due to the poor
condition of the roads on the private property. Yes, it is terrible. We, we finally got and
went long ways around to go to the chilies. And then when we finally got out of the chilies,
we, we, we had our dinner and then we're heading out of the chilies. She waited for traffic
to stop to be done. They were still in the mall complex. She pulled out into the wrong
side of the street, drove down the wrong side of the road for about 90 feet. I know these,
I know these streets like the back of my hand. She's just like, she's like, we're not even,
I'm not even playing that game today. She's like, I'm not even doing it. Oh, and the dance
we have to do all around. It's insane. You know, like, uh, it was like the, they'll tell
like, uh, some of, you know, if someone's as late with their, their pregnancy, like,
like, like they're nine months and it's just so, oh no, they'll tell you to go get on a
rough road to go on a wagon ride. I'm saying we should, we should monetize this on the
rough road. They say going like a hay wagon ride. You're right. The Pittsburgh mills pregnancy
popper, the labor maker, labor maker, the labor maker tour, the baby bringer, the Pittsburgh
mills pothole baby bringer tour, the baby popper router. Come on over. My God. I can
only imagine driving around, riding in a wagon, being pulled in that parking lot. You would,
you would injure your spine. You would not come out of that without serious injuries.
Yeah. You know, who else is willing to rattle babies out of mothers? And that is the following
sponsor today's show. Man Manley's ice cream social is brought to you by Roald Dahl's guide
to writing about abnormally large objects. That's right. That's from boson scoop pronounced
a boson scoop in a 20, 23. That's when he gave it to us. This is Roald Dahl's guide
to writing about abnormally large objects. Hello. It is I famed children's author and
raconteur Roald Dahl. You may remember me from such wonderful child's tales as James
and the giant peach. Well, that was my final draft after I experimented with several other
large objects before I landed on James and the giant peach, there was Kevin and the gargantuan
grapes. And there was also Stephen and the abnormally rotund orange. I also wrote one
called Bethany and the big old snowball. Catherine finds a fucking huge quarter. That last one
turned out to just be a silver dollar. Silver dollar the dumb lady. She was just a dumb
person. He was a dumb person. I went on to write more dumb stories later. But finally,
of course, I landed on James and the giant peach. Yes. Now, if you want to come up with
your own person and the large thing story, I encourage you to do so. But don't you dare
use the name James? Don't you dare use the adjective giant? Don't you dare use peaches?
Those are my intellectual properties. Hi, I'm Jimmy the large nectarine. And I would like
to tell you guys a sort of tale. Go ahead, Jim. Jimmy the large nectarine. Yes, that's
right. I feel you may be dangerously encroaching upon my IP. In what way? In what way? Rolled?
How do I say your name? Say it how you want, you philanderer. I'll see you in court. Listen,
what you've done is you've gone around my idea of having an individual involved with
a large object. Yeah, no, I am the large object. And you yourself have become the personification
of the object. Yeah. So you have anthropomorphized. That would be like me having a book called
James the giant peach. I'm just hearing dollar signs. That's all I'm hearing. That's absurd.
And you are your Jimmy the giant nectarine. That's right. Originally, it was me and the
giant nectarine. But the book, not to spoil it, is about us finding a device that combined
us into the giant object you see before you now. Like the fly. Yes. Like the modern adaptation
of the fly. So you're Brendal, Jimmy. Yeah. Yes. Oh, I like this. Say, would you like
to come to my writing cottage that I have out in the back of my house? Sure. But just,
you know, there's a lot of odd things to being a giant nectarine that maybe your house is
not prepared for. What do you mean? Every time I sit down, I squeeze juice everywhere.
Oh, yeah. Do go on. Oh, that seems like a feature of the book to you, Ralt. Oh, we're
about to have some sweet, sweet times, I think, you and I, James. Mr. Jim. Mind if I dip a
finger in that peach pit of yours? My gosh. My gosh. Sure. Enter a scoops of checkout.
And if I put a finger in your navel orange? That's just upsetting. Yeah. Just upsetting.
Nectarines. I went to a music gig the other night and there was a fan there. There was
a woman who is a fan of this music group and I guess follows them around from different
gigs and had made them all baked goods, had made the entire band baked goods. The fan
cakes as the fan cakes. Tiff likes to say. But I mean, brought them a veritable buffet
of baked desserts. It was so much. It was so many cookies. There was a cake. It was
all this stuff. And yeah, I was like, I am a little jealous of this right now. There's
a fan of this band who brought in enough baked goods for at least 10 people. Oh, wow. Dedication.
Yeah. Well, what were the things? Did you eat it? What's going on? Oh, I ate some of
it for sure. I definitely ate some of the fan cakes. You know me. I eat the fan cakes.
You know I eat the fan cakes. So then you can't be jealous. There were cookies. There
were brownies. I can be jealous. I can be jealous of what I want to be jealous of, Paul.
Don't tell me what I can be jealous of. You got the benefit. That's true. That is true.
I did get the benefit. It was like lemon bars. It was really good. Oh yeah. Real good lemon
bar. Oh yeah. Real good lemon bar can be great. We got the Wagner's market right up the street
from us, right? On an unrelated note, my stomach is completely pregnant now. Oh no. Swallowing
so much sperm. I got a I got only fan cakes. Wait a minute. Clumsy. Oh God. Only fan cakes.
Well you know what we got to do, Jacob? We got to get you on a wagon. We got to get you
on a wagon in the Pittsburgh Mills parking lot real quick. Rattle something loose. Get
that get that cake baby out of you. Time to rattle it loose. Do it. Do it. Do it. Oh man.
That same night I discovered that several of the Fremont Street performers are now trying
you know when they when they shut all the lights down on Fremont Street and they do
the shows on the canopy. They do like the video shows on the canopy above there. Right.
So I guess several of the street performers have now instead of taking a break while the
canopy does its thing, they try to dance along to it. Okay. Because I guess they're not allowed
to do their act while the canopy is playing, but they can just dance along to the canopy.
And so they stop doing several people stop doing whatever act they're doing on Fremont
Street and just start awkwardly dancing along with whatever is happening on the big Fremont
Street canopy. And they expect people to continue tipping them and or stay at their location
to watch the show restart after the canopy stops doing its thing. That's like y'all
have the wrong idea on what to do with this situation. I appreciate y'all trying something.
This isn't it. My heart goes out to those poor motherfuckers. Oh my god. That is the
worst gig on planet Earth. I think I did stop yesterday and watch a street magician though
on my on my stroll of the strip yesterday. There was a street magician in front of Bellagio.
And so I saw that guy. Oh, maybe he Yeah, he made my faith in humanity disappear. He
wasn't that bad. No, no, no, no, no. I'm just saying in the general that the poor performers
have to be out there. Oh, Huskin and buskin. Oh, man. Oh, Jeff Loomis points out that the
top five Fremont Street performers pull in some bank. There is sure there is a real cottage
industry that happens in Las Vegas with the street performers, especially down at Fremont
Street. Yeah, we don't know whether the guy used to get paid 20 bucks to get kicked in
the balls. We don't know whether he stopped that for medical reasons or whether he's now
retired to a lavish island. We don't know. Yeah, I think or because he died. They did
some kind of ordinance on it. I think they actually I think that guy that Matt's talking
about died. Oh, really? Oh, the nut kicking guy. I think he did from a nut kick. I someone
kicked his nuts into outer space, just fucking Thanos did just. The legend of moon nuts.
Your testicles are like planets. Boom. No, I think I don't I don't I don't know. I don't
remember anything about him dying, but I did think that I think they stopped him doing
that. Yeah. Oh, you think they probably died because he had because he stopped. That was
the only thing keeping his balls from growing out of control over his body. Secretly restarted
his heart every time. It was the it was the only way he could keep his balls from becoming
so big that they would keep him in his house. They found him in his house stuck. He woke
up one morning like Kafka and he couldn't get him like he's like Gregor Samsa. And he's
like, Oh shit, it happened. The balls got too big. I can't get out the door. And I left
my phone in the kitchen. Like, what would you do if your balls were too big to get through
the door? Yeah. And you left your phone in the kitchen. You're dead. Yeah. Yeah. You're
dead. Because you're not over. You're not gonna What are you gonna pull your balls off,
make them? No, no, you're right. I'm dead. It's the only option. Chaotic. But Chad says,
Sure. But if I make a living kicking men in the nuts, I'm a sex worker, quote unquote.
Right? Well, someone was a savior for that man to keep his balls in check. Because otherwise,
they were gonna just keep going. Yeah. Oh, according to chat GPT, the the guy on Fremont
Street who got kicked in the balls has indeed passed away. Wow. Oh, no. Yeah. But we don't
know what from what? I don't know what from. Yeah. I particular torsion. That's it. I passed
away after hospitalization, according to a social media claim. No mainstream, blah, blah,
blah. Not allergy. This is a good time to mention the zoom chat. If you are a patreon
supporter of this show, you are eligible to come join us in the zoom chat for this show.
You can be in here with us. People have the chat going all the whole time. And people
have something to say, they can say something in the chat, and we'll bring them on to the
show. And they'll say it. Those people are all patriots. They support us over at preaching
fun.com and you can too. Oh my god. That's all it takes. Jacob cloud on a brothel on
the chat is pointing this out. Now I can't let's see it either. He was really thrown
because your Las Vegas hat. If you look at it differently, that logo, the LV can look
like a four seven. And he thought you were wearing a Donald Trump. Oh, yeah, totally.
It totally can look like a 47. It really does. I don't see it at all. So look with the L
and the V connect that can be the four and then the that's a four outer crop of the V
cover up be a seven up the far side of your of your set of your V. Okay, cover the far
side of your V. There you go. You see the four? Okay. Oh, yeah. Yeah. See the four.
Okay. And then he said if you let that go, you see that one's got the little thing of
it. So it looks like a seven. Oh, and that looks like a seven. It kind of does look like
a 47. Another reason to be in the zoom chat. Preaching fun.com. I can't unsee it now.
That's really fun. Who said that first cloud on a brothel? Who is the person that I'm angry
at for ruining that? Man, I like this. All you got to do is black out that little dot
at the top of the V. All I've got to do is put a piece of tape over the hat and not wear
it ever again. That's all I've got to do. Set this cap on fire. Easy peasy living squeezy.
Nothing that kerosene in a match can't fix. No problem. Oh, shit. You know who else is
going to show up and ruin things that I previously liked? And that's the following sponsor. Today's
show, Matt Madley's Ice Cream Social is brought to you by Corey the Camel's Bail Bonds from
James T. Scoop in 2021. That's Corey the Camel's Jail Bonds. Hey everybody, it's Corey the
Camel. Hey, hey girls. Hey guys. Hey everyone. So I know a lot of you are going to jail now
because you're doing stupid stuff like not being born here or, you know, doing other
dumb things like saying no to people in authority. Well, okay, fine. Do it. Do what you want
to do. I don't care. It's fine. It's free country, sorta. So anyway, all you got to
do is pay me money and I'll get you out of jail. That's right. Corey's Bail Bonds is
here to help. Are you in a pinch? Are you serving time in the old clink, huh? You in
the old four bar hospital, the old, what are the other nicknames for the jail? The slammer?
Yes. What else they call it? The crossbar motel, huh? The stinky place where you go
when you're in jail. What's the other nicknames for the jail? Dr. Hassan Pfeffer's Fart Box?
You know, those classic, classic nicknames. Oh, I am going to Dr. Hassan Pfeffer's Fart
Box. Oh, well then you're in need of my services. I am. If you end up in Dr. Hassan Pfeffer's
Fart Box, all you got to do is call me and I'll get you out lickety split. Oh, I don't
want to get out. I've been waiting for months to go in there. You've been trying to get
into Dr. Hassan Pfeffer's Fart Box for a while. I love the smell. Yeah. Not a lot of people
do. It's the hottest club in town. I can vouch for, I can vouch for the bail bondsman, Corey
here. Thank you. I was, true story, wrapped up in a Las Vegas sexting rig and as an Israeli
citizen, I got bailed out and then just got on a plane and flew the country. All right.
And that was shortly before he became president of Israel. Another success story, everybody.
This happened last week in Las Vegas. Wait a minute, what happened? All right, commercial
over. Hey, he's good to check out. Matt, go ahead. Oh, also Dr. Hassan Pfeffer's Fart
Box. That's a great costume idea. Oh, yeah, yeah. Because that's open to interpretation.
There has to be a Dutch oven costume on Amazon. No, there was a child sex ring arrest. They
arrested like eight people in connection with a child sex ring here in Las Vegas. There's
a big- Eight children? Eight people, eight- They didn't arrest them fucking kids. They
arrested those children. It wasn't ICE. Those kids are still running the streets. It wasn't
ICE. It wasn't ICE. They weren't arresting- These are actual police. Okay. These are the
police that don't arrest children. Yeah. But yeah, so one of them was an Israeli citizen
and they put his bond at like, I don't know. I don't know the amount, but it was a low
amount. So he just paid it. He just paid it and went to the airport, got on a plane and
just left the country. Okay. You know, he probably didn't realize that he wasn't technically
allowed to do it. So there's a bit of a dust-up over, you know, with all the people involved.
Be like, how the hell did you let that happen? It's a big controversial story here in local
Los Angeles. Oh, Leon Kassab is saying this was not just an Israeli citizen, but a government
official. Ah. So that makes it a little more sticky. And I don't guess we have any kind
of extradition deal there. Oh, you know, if anything Israel does, it's played by the rules.
So- Right. Holy, an Israel government official was arrested in Las Vegas earlier this month
on charges of luring a child for sex. Yeah. Like full on. Yeah. Like with a straight up
fishing pole. Yeah. Candy bar. There was a bobber and everything. Wow. You know what
I mean, Vern? Yeah. If we're going to make bobber jokes, I might as well go back and
make earnest jokes too. It was Lake Mead. A lot of people stock their ponds with fresh
fish. We stock Lake Mead with children, hungry children. Let's see. Oh, he had a $10,000
bail. He had a $10,000 bail. He posted that, uh, that standard amount for the charge. Didn't
appear before the judge was not required to surrender his passport and returned to Israel
two days later on a pre-scheduled flight. They could have just looked at flights he
already had scheduled. The chat is filling in the mad details here. Winter scoop says,
we do have an extradition treaty with Israel. They're claiming he wasn't the right guy.
They're claiming and then Newman comes in and says, this is an earnest Lexington, Kentucky
native. Wow. This guy was from Kentucky. Oh, this is really government official, but he's
from Kentucky. He's originally from Kentucky. Apparently. Well, that's what Newman's saying.
Yeah. Right. Well, I trust Newman. I, you know, if it comes, if it's, if it's a Kentucky
history thing, Newman knows it. That's what we know. That is true. Well, I mean, we know
how to fish for children. Right.
Speaking of children, this is a good segue, right? Um, so I was recently, uh, haunted
with, uh, what, what, you know, nature versus nurture genetics versus whatever as, uh, one
of my children, one of my children has started wearing a gold chain around his neck. Oh,
you took the kids out of Jersey, but you can't take the Jersey out of the kids. I like to,
I, I was, I bit my tongue because I wanted to be like, Oh my God, you look so Jersey
right now. You fucking T neck reject, get that shit off of you. Have you seen the South
Park where one of the boys finds out he's originally from New Jersey and, uh, and the
mother goes full New Jersey for him. Oh my God. I was doing a show last night and I brought
up San Antonio and the crowd all cheered for San Antonio. And I said, are you all from
San Antonio? And they go, no, or whatever. Like they're just for cheering or whatever.
It's just a nice place. Next girl gets up. She says she's from Jersey and no one applauds
at all. Not, not a single clap. One boo from the back. I was like, wow, we just love hearing
the word San Antonio that we burst into applause. But you know, Jersey just kills it. Kills
the mood. I get it. I get it. There are rules. And then, uh, my other child, this is really
daunting. Wait, wait, younger, younger, worse than a, you're still in a gold chain. Olders
were in the gold chain. Great. What else is, is there anything on the gold chain? No, that's,
that's what makes it simple and elegant. Yeah. Slow your roll. I got questions. I got questions.
Am I going to start giving gold chains to Matt's oldest son? Yes, I am. Has he been
watching the A team? Uh, no, he's just been watching, uh, I rock Z for furbishing videos
on YouTube. Okay. Well he's coming by it natural. You know, this one has the tee tops on it.
A lot of people don't like the tee tops on it. I tell those people, go fuck yourself.
That's what I tell people. If they tell me they don't like the rock with the tee top
on it, you can fuck yourself right now. Come down to the shore and say, you don't like
the tee top. Oh shit. No. Okay. So if that channel doesn't already exist, somebody hates
money. Oh, I'm sure it does. If fucking is this situation from Jersey shore is not doing
I rock Z restore videos on YouTube, then the situation hates money. Let's go down. Let's
take a drive out here to the dump. Okay. Let's go to the dump and let's see what we can get
on our I rock mission. Hey, look at this piece of shit over here. It looks like a flattened
piece of garbage. Looks like your mom's boy. I got to, but what do you know? It's an old
Iraq that's been through the crusher, but we can dig some gold out of these here Hills.
Look here, friend. Look at that. Oh, we got ourselves a volume knob. That's a legit factory
Iraq volume knob. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Weren't you on the Jersey shore? Was I ever, I am
the fucking Jersey shore. Yeah. I wrote, I wrote shampooed on Snooki. How about that?
How about that? I still got the other name. I couldn't think of all I can think of the
other. I still got basically a shroud of Turin on my belly from where that lady went to town
on me. I got the Snooki shroud of Turin on my Fupa. I got the Snooki shroud of Turin
blazing on my Fupa forever from a fake tan juice and her hay scoops at checkout. Oh,
that is upsetting. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Matt. Yes. Is this the beginning? Is this, is this
the end? Is this, is this it? Or is it now I gotta get a bracelet. Now I gotta get a
hearing. Now is this just, are we testing the waters? What's happening? His ears pierced.
He wants, he wants two sleeve tattoos. Wait, on one arm. Is this for real? He wants two
sleeve tattoos, but on the same arm. No, no, no. Uh, no. What, what do you, has he asked
for a tattoo? No, I wouldn't put it past him, but no. He has asked for a lot of tanning
lotion though. What do you, damn, I need a bunch of self tanning lotion. Latter day scoop
found the fucking shroud of, shroud of Snooki. Oh, no. Oh, that's, that's as upsetting as
the story. That's exactly what it looked like. Do, do you think, what do you think his tattoo
request might be? Um, he would probably get a Spider-Man tattoo or, uh, uh, uh, something
with, with the band or something like that. He's really into music. All right. Drumming.
The Spider-Man is the way to go. That's eternal. Yeah. All right. The naked lady, uh, mud flaps,
uh, the, the, the silhouette naked lady on the mud flaps. He did say he wanted, uh, three
different tribal symbols on his lower back for peace, tranquility and, uh, and money.
But from different, but from different tribes, three different tribes. The mud flap tattoo.
That eliminated the, that, that area of the tattoo, right? Like you don't get tattoos
in your lower back anymore, right? Like that, calling it tramp stamp eliminated. I think
the tramp stamp is out. Yeah. Yeah. The cleave sleeve is what's coming through now. The cleave
sleeve is in for sure. I see a lot of cleave sleeves, but I don't see a lot of tramp stamps.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I've also started seeing a lot of, uh, a lot of ladies here
in Las Vegas walking around in the, in the very short dresses with the, uh, with the
leg tattoos, like the leg sleeve. Oh, leg sleeves. What do you, what do you call the
leg sleeve tattoo? Is there a name for that? Somebody in the chat tell me if there's a
name for that. But it's where they do the whole leg, just like you do like the sleeve
of the arm. Hot? The gam glam. Where the scoop just says milk leg. I'm sorry, that's scooper
Nova girl. That's the milk leg. Pant leg. The ink leg. Ink leg. Ink leg. Ink leg. Or
just leggings. Gam glam. Actually the unconsolidated. Gam glam. That's it. Gam glam. It's a gam
glam. Glam, gam, gam, glam. Yeah. Yeah. A mistake. The mistake. Yes. That's pretty handy. Uh,
and my youngest son, we have like, uh, this is, you know, this is going to sound a little
bougie guys, but we have, we have, we have toaster tongs. Do you have toaster tongs? Toaster
tongs. Yeah. They're like basically like wooden. To take your thing out of your toaster? Yeah,
like wooden, like little wooden tongs. They're smaller than like classic tongs. They're wooden.
Yeah. They're almost like, like, uh, people who can't use chopsticks, you know, use fake
chopsticks. Oh, I got you. I got you. But why would they go with wood for a hot thing?
It doesn't conduct electricity. Yeah. So if you jam it. You can stick that all the way
down the toaster and not kill yourself. Yeah. I see. Yeah. Okay. And, um, uh, there's two
because I one time used it to get food out of, uh, some other object and my wife got
angry that I use the, the toaster tongs on another food object on the improper thing.
So I was never in the toaster and a bit of like, you know, 20% rage, 50% sarcasm bought
a second pair of toaster tongs. Good. Okay. To be like, I'll use these however I please.
And, um, uh, my son spontaneously grabbed both toaster tongs and started moving around
my kitchen like a crab. Oh, no. And I was like, it was like, I saw a ghost. I was like,
wha, what are you? Have you, you've never done that for, right? He does not know my,
my, that I was the crab at Starbucks. I was, when I worked at Starbucks, I used to move
around the whole store and cower into a corner with the two pastry tops. Nurture versus nature.
That memory straight up came out of your ballsack. That's just, there's just nothing else to
that. Yeah, it's science. Your tongue. Yeah, it is science. It is science. Well, you know,
they're finding out more and more of that crazy shit about just how much, yeah, how
much DNA memory there is and how much, and I mean, you know, cause like, like with, with
women, uh, they're born with, uh, easy now we're going to be in a Sarah Hester Ross clip
right now. We're three guys talking about women. Right, right, right, right. Uh, how
about, uh, female presenting individuals? Okay, go for it. Okay. Okay. Male presenting
individuals are, are, are born with the microphone that that, you know, that's from there, you
know, they have them in the womb. All right. I mean, yeah. Like as the, as the zygote develops.
Yeah. Yeah. No zygotes develop into babies, into a fetus. Yeah. Like early on you've got
that genetic material that's going to make the next generation and they're discovering
more and more that events that occur during pregnancy to the mother can translate genetic
information habits, different stuff. Like, uh, like they did a study on like, uh, groups
of people who are experiencing famine and how their progeny were affected by that. And
not even that first generation, that second generation sometimes too. I don't know. It's
interesting. It is interesting. I mean, I'm always blown away by animals learning behavior,
right? Or like all of a sudden all these animals, like, no, like crows in a certain region all
know how to like navigate traffic lights and things like that. Right. Or like, yeah, things
with it. And, and the light fly over them. That, but by the way, that's how they navigate
the traffic lights. Yeah. Yeah. They've, they've, yeah. Whereas crows in the past would just
fly right into them. Right, right. They've, they've evolved, but, uh, uh, they're learning.
Did you, did you see not, they are evolving now, Jacob, did you hear about that? I'm being
stupid, but I know what's actually happening too. No, no, no, no, no. Did you, did you
read this article, uh, Matt, about the crows that have all gone mute? No. Yeah. So there's
this whole region, uh, of crows that have gone completely mute and the scientists are
looking for the cause, the cause, the cause, the cause. Oh, it's over. Oh, I killed Jacob.
I killed Jacob, everyone. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. There's just sad emojis coming in on the chat
now. Just depression. Uh, let's just go live feedback in the chat. You got some LOL, some
laughing faces, you got, but you didn't get one side. Andy said I murdered that one. So
thank you. You have three sad faces. This is looking like a 60% hit of a joke. We've
got it. We've got to see you at the cone. Hey man, I'll take 60% any day. That joke
is for the birds. Yes. I'm raving about it to my wife. Leon. See, now we're rolling.
Now we got it going. Oh, Mr. Head Scoop thought that it was a real fact coming through. Yeah,
Mr. Head Scoop, that is your fault. That's just on you. I, I hate to blame the victim
on this, but that is your fault. Brogan says 60% of the time I'm funny every time. Yeah,
that's generous. Thank you Brogan. That's generous. I don't give a flock. Boo. At any
rate, I will submit my youngest son for genetic studies for comedy transference. Good. Oh
my God. That's so crazy. I've never been a prouder dad. I've never been a prouder dad.
That's pretty amazing. That's pretty amazing. Yeah. Has all of the strife about you getting
the wrong thing out of the, with the toaster tongs, has all of that been settled or is
there still tension in the house? I don't know. I never see my wife. I don't know. I
don't know. Oh, I saw her yesterday. She was angry. She was mad about something. I couldn't
tell what, but she was hot about something. But yeah, yeah, yeah. You should do Cisco's
the tong song. Oh, tong to tong tong tong. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, someone already memed you Paul slaking
fool. It's not a murder of crows unless there's probable cause. There you go. Oh, slaking
classic. Now I'm mad at you too. Now I'm mad at you. So, uh, one of my kids is now in middle
school. Uh huh. They start middle school at seven a.m. Because they hate you. That's it.
Wait a minute. They say, they say cause the bus schedule. So like grade school starts
at nine a.m. And middle school starts at seven a.m. And they say it's now busing. This is,
this is something where I legit have beef with the way they do it because there are
tons of studies that say this is terribly detrimental. And it's especially detrimental
to children in that age range. I know what beef is. I have had beef experience. I know
adolescents need more sleep. They've proven that man. It's fucked up. Oh, I, I agree.
Uh, it's, it's, it's a real, I know you do. I know it's not on you. It's a real game changer.
Uh, I would be so awkward if this is where Paul found out that Matt was the one who set
that rule up. I was like, look, it's the buses guys. You the one? You son of a bitch. I'll
never forgive you. This podcast is finished. Uh, it was even worse. What's up with them
not looking out for kids is, uh, middle school, they had signups for cross country. And so
Mike signed up for cross country and it is 105 degrees out right now. Yeah. And so I
figured they can't be, they must have them inside of the gym or they must like, you know,
take it easy or do something different. And I go to pick up my kid from after cross country
and his face is just bright red, like a tomato, like absolutely. Oh no. Your son is a, uh,
a fair skin young man. Yes. Also anyway. Yeah. He is porcelain, uh, skin. Yeah. And, uh,
it was a bright red tomato. And I was like, I said, is that sunburn or from exhaustion
of running? And he says, I combo. He says, I don't know that I don't, I honestly don't
know. Probably is the answer. Probably. Oh, this was like, I don't know why I look like
I'm a tomato right now. That's horrible. I said, why are they having you run when it's
above a hundred and, uh, five degrees. And he said, Oh, cause you know, we're, we're
part of the national program. And so we have to, we have to compare what we're doing to
all the other schools who are doing it. And most schools don't, uh, aren't in a hot area
like ours. And so it's like a false sport on the national. Oh, I got you. I said, that's
not a good enough answer for me. Just so you're just so we're clear. I don't care. I don't
care how you fare nationally. My child. I don't care. I don't care. I don't care how
you fare nationally in this thing that I already don't care about. I don't care about children's
cross country running. So why would I care about how you line up against other kids from
Milwaukee? Yeah. I just, I was like, what are we doing? And even, uh, my youngest son
was like, uh, we did recess indoors. Cause the principal said we won't, we won't go do
recess outdoors if it's, uh, if it's a 102 or above. And I said, somebody at the school
has figured it out, but I said a hundred and two, who gave that two degree variance to
like, I was thinking a hundred degrees. That's the official number, Matt. That's the number
that you want to pay attention to is the one oh two. That's really crazy. Amateurs pay
attention to a hundred professionals pay attention to one Oh two. It's a, it's 101 boys roll
out the soccer balls. Let's go. We got an iron thermometer. If it, if it takes up to
one Oh three, we're heading inside and it's madness. I mean, they're, uh, the soccer practices
start next week. And I'm like, it is still August. Why are we pretending like it's not
August in Las Vegas? Why are we like, why are we doing this cargo cult of education?
It's still October. It can still be October in Las Vegas and be that hot. Um, Oh my God,
that's awful. It is, it is ridiculous. That, that is why when I joined the cross country
bear jamboree, I didn't fuck around. I just, I just did the animatronic jug band. I was,
I was an animatronic jug band, a fat bear that sat down. I was like, Oh, can I just
sign up for cross country bear jamboree? Paul ran cross country a couple of times in the
suit. It didn't end well. No, that was awful. Yeah. I have an update for some of the scoops
who told me, uh, basically there's a, there's a, a K-pop Disney show where they do K-pop
versions of different Disney songs and stuff, because my kids have ever since they went
to that concert have not stopped listening, just cannot stop listening to the soundtrack
to zombies and descendants movies. Oh, so you're trying to switch it up on them. And
so they said some people said the music from the K-pop one's actually pretty good. And
uh, so I try to turn my kids onto that and they saw it coming a mile away and they were
like, no, no, no, thanks. Have you tried black pink? I was like, Hey, I heard there's like
a K-pop show on Disney. Maybe we should watch that tonight. And they were like, no, fuck
you old man. Did you try black? Nice try. Nark. Do some like black pink concert footage
on YouTube and stuff. I bet they'll like that. All right. Yes. I think keelers of the age
where I think black pink will turn his head. Okay. Yeah. Black pink is good. He'll be like,
and they are, and they are legit good music too. Yeah. Yeah. You'll like they are. They're
really, all right. I'll, I'll, I'll do my best. I'll do anything to stop listening to
throw on black pink and throw on some fucking baby metal, dude. Like some baby metal concert
footage is awesome. As you know, uh, early in the summer, you know, we took them to MJ
the musical. So Michael Jackson was pretty prominent and the thing now we have mixed
emotions about Michael Jackson's legacy, but separating artists. I don't mind some Michael
Jackson music in my car. Um, his propofall from Michael Jackson, uh, Michael Jackson
no longer played at all. Alive, uh, no longer alive, but also no longer played in my car.
And I guess I can't complain. It'd be like, I, what happened? I want my kids listening
to Michael Jackson. I can't really, can't really, can't really pound that. No. Chaotic
clumsy. If Jacob could wear a 47 hat, you can listen to Michael Jackson. What has this
podcast? So man, that does just look like a four. God damn it. God fucking damn it.
Jacob, are you like now retroactively looking back at a couple of weird thumbs up you've
gotten walking to Caesar's, you know, walking about a lot of people just yelling things
about, uh, like January 6th to me. Peaceful protest. Am I right? High five. Yeah. Oh shit.
Uh, let the protesters out of jail. A lot of people say that to me. Fuck the Smithsonian.
Huh? Yeah. Yeah. That's, that's come up a lot. Man, it all makes sense now. Wait, like,
okay, here's what that's like. Seriously. We've lost the plot. We can not, we can not care
about a Cracker Barrel logo. We just can't. No, you just can't. We can't. We can't. By
the way, how weird was it that I called this weeks ago when I was in Mesa, Arizona, I made
a joke that it was going to be just called barrel after. Yeah. And, uh, and I, I, I predicted
a dust up with, with manga and, uh, and Cracker Barrel. Of course. Just, just like the Simpsons,
we predict everything. That's right. They're looking, they're looking for anything to distract
from a certain dead pedophile. What? Uh huh. Uh huh. But Maxwell died? Like it wasn't even
like they changed the name to something like, you know, like General Mills and like Antrimima
and all other stuff. Like they changed, they changed stuff. They just took off the weird
guy that you couldn't really see that kind of looked like a shotgun, but kind of looked
like a person leaning against barrel. So here's the thing. It just says Cracker Barrel now.
With that logo, as a kid, I always thought that that was a big strapping man, man spreading.
You thought he was straddling a barrel. I thought he was straddling, side straddling
a barrel. Yeah. Only in my later years, I really looked at it. He's got, it's, it's
not, it's not one leg. It's both his legs and they're withered. See, I look like, it
looks like he's straddling a barrel. You're right. I always saw him as a straddler. Yeah,
yeah. No, he's, he's, he's an old grandpa. He's a withery old grandpa with both his legs
on one side. And so taking, taking away the weird old white dude that you can't quite
see, just going with the actual name of the company, created chaos. I mean, the, the loss
as it should, the company lost hundreds of millions of dollars. Shit. Really? Yeah. So
dumb. Yeah. And people are just mad that they changed the logo. But you know what? Also,
that shit is just fucking straight up stock manipulation. Yeah. Yeah. When you get right
down to it, all this shit is just, they're just playing these games. I, okay. I work
for a certain company that has several concentric circles around it. Uh, that the head of that
company just, uh, stepped down. Yeah. Oh, right. This, the CEO just stepped out. That's right.
Yeah. But, but he didn't leave the company. He's in a pole works for the Olympics. Several
concentric circles. Yeah. He works for, he works. He still works there. He's just in
a different role. So it's all just optics and games, man. Ain't nobody losing nothing
except for us. Exactly. I got over that woman was like, we, uh, the viral clip of the woman
saying, look, you got a lot more in common with these immigrants being picked up off
the street than you do with the billionaires causing this mess. Oh, yeah. Hey baby. That's
the goddamn, there was, but I'm stepping down. You won't hear me anymore. I'm going to be
right over there. That's why guys. So you cannot talk to me. I'm going to be look. Yeah.
Uh, I've been doing this role shittily for 11 years. I'll take my golden parachute now.
Thank you very much and continue to work here. Perfect. That's, that's trying to make what
two bucks off of, uh, Brogan. That's it. Yeah. Five. Yeah. Thank you. We get, I do. I get
the PayPal emails. You play spawn and Brogan Paypal's us and then the spot tax. I get the,
I get the, uh, the emails. Um, anyway. All right, let's get into some scoop mail or something.
Let's do it. Let's do a little scoop mail. Oh, we don't have any physical scoop mail.
We just have regular scoop mail from Valerie. Good morrow churned denizens. I haven't written
in a while as life has gotten in the way. The last thing I wrote was about the lady
wanting a CSI team to investigate the mysterious shit in her shed toilet. I'm a little behind
in on episode 1234. Uh, there was a proposal to add, see you at the cone as a sign off.
This reminded me that I hadn't actually written in to propose an alternative use of cone.
My partner's work life doesn't allow him to be a scoop. However, he's very supportive
enjoys the bits and stories from ICS that I curate for him. And he knows a few of the
running gags. What do you mean? Your partner's work life? Does it allow him to be a? Wait
a minute. What's going on? What's the conflict of interest? We present, we pose your partners.
Does it allow your partner to listen to podcasts? Well, I don't know. There must be something
going on there. Uh, he also enjoys meeting scoops. Everyone will be known for, uh, known
or met thus far has been amazing, kind and fun as my partner supportive and scoop adjacent.
I have taken to referring to him as my cone in a few of the scoop gatherings that we have
been a part of. I would like to propose the cone be used for a non-scoop supportive partner
and that the new sign off be one of the following. See you in the parlor, wink and tap on nose
optional or see you at the soda fountain jerk, optional handshake like pulling a soda. That's
the fountain jerk. I like to see at the set of fountain jerk is good. Yeah. I like that.
I think there's room for all of these things and I love that you've got, I've already gone
ahead and just started calling your supportive partner, your cone. I do like that. Let's
hope they don't waffle. Just coming through. Ka-ching. Brogan's the best. Oh, we got one
from Andy. Hi churn. It's just a short one today. I wanted to write to ask for a trophy
or statuette or merit badge or whatever it is that you give out to improvisers for a
chanting outstanding achievement in improvisation. Here's the scenario. My wife and I had been
married for a little while now and we have been meaning to update our wheels. I came
home one day, Kevin carrying heavy grocery shopping bags and walked straight past her
into the kitchen to dump them on the table. My wife followed me into the kitchen and from
behind said in a bright and proud voice, Hey honey, I got my new will signed off and finished.
So now you will get everything. Before she could even finish her sentence, I turned on
her and used a piece of produce to pretend to stab my wife directly in the heart. Somehow
she didn't see the funny side of this and I was sleeping on the couch. That's Andy.
Oh no. Andy? Good bit. That was a good bit. Good timing. It sounds like you were fast
too. I think she was mad that you were fast. Yeah. Well, was it a banana? Ooh. Was it a
cucumber? Was it celery? Could have been the type of produce. The type of produce. A piece
of raw chicken. Just poultry. No. Salmonella. A piece of raw chicken. A flappy old chicken
breast. I challenge you to a duel and you smack them with chicken breast. Ow. That really
hurt. I just saw that episode of the Simpsons the other day where Homer goes around slapping
people and challenging them to a duel and gets in a gunfight. Well, that's what we used
to do on this show. Now we just do Jock vs. Nerd. Oh yeah. Ladies and gentlemen, it is
time for Jock vs. Nerd. Explosion. Explosion. Of chicken breast that will slap you. Whoa.
Oh, we got a Price of Skrite today. Let's see. Matt, the Magnum Scoopus wrote this Price
of Skrite for us, said that they know that Matt really hated all of the Jock vs. Nerds
where there were the infinite wrong answers. So we made the Price of Skrites. Apparently
Magnum Scoopus made this Price of Skrites specifically so that Matt would hate Price
of Skrite by the end of this game as well. Wow. So let's see what happens. This is some
fucking saw shit right here. Yeah. What number is the fourth law of thermodynamics? Hint,
it isn't four. What are you? I'm first. I don't even know what this question means.
What number is the fourth law of thermodynamics? Hint, it isn't four. Yeah. I don't even know
what that means. Means it's not number four. It's got to be number five, right? Yeah, I'm
going to guess number five. Paul, what's your guess? I'll guess number three. All right.
Matt? Four. Let's try it. Zero. Oh, well shit. Huh. All right. Oh, we were all over. At
what temperature in Kelvin does all motion stop? I mean, absolutely stop. Paul, you're
first. Absolute zero. Absolute zero. Matt? Negative one. Oh, that might win. I'll say
one. It's zero. Paul got two points. Hey. A blank day is a vulnerability in software
or hardware that is typically unknown to the vendor and for which no patch or other fix
is available. Matt, you're up first. Zero. Zero. A zero day. Oh, a zero day. That's pretty
good. Right. I think you're right. That's a Jack Reciter. I'm going one. Paul, what
are you going? Not two. Matt, do you hate this yet? It's zero. Matt got two points.
It's all zero. That's the bit. Oh, yeah. Yeah, we got it too. Okay. This year predates the
birth of Jesus, which is one AD or one CT, et cetera, and is used for astronomical calculations.
I'm first. I'm going to guess zero. Paul? I'll guess. Well, no. Oh, what was it? No.
What was the BC? What did it go up to? I don't know. I know what you're talking about, but
I don't know. I'll guess 230. 230. Chinese dentists, please. One. One. Good guess. Good
guess. Jacob was exactly right. Zero. Two points. All right. Jacob, what's the scores
now? We're all tied at two. And here is the fifth question. Paul is first on this one.
This numerical nickname was given to school-aged Samuel Joel M. Well before his Tony award-winning
performances. Oh, zero. Mustel, right? Great. Zero. Zero. Matt's going to guess one. The
M stands for Mustel. Paul was exactly right. P-31, P-38, B-17, B-29, Spitfire, Mosquito.
These are all well-known WW2 aircraft of the Allies. But what is the most famous Japanese
aircraft, Matt? Zero. That's the zero. I'm going to guess one. Paul's going to guess
two. And Matt was exactly right. In Pulp Fiction, the rapey pawn shop guy had a chopper with
his name on the key chain. His name can sometimes mean a number in British English. What was
his name if it was a number? Hilarious. That's the best question in this Price is Right right
there. His name was Zed, which is zero. Paul's going to guess one. Matt's going to guess
two. And Jacob was right. It's time for the bonus round. We all have four points each.
It's me first. I'm going to wager all four. I'm going to do a high-powered spin. If you
can hear my dogs barking, it's because the yard guys are here. Oh, yard guys. The yard
guys. Oh, yard guys. And I lost the wager. Oh my God, Jacob, what a catastrophe. I'm
down to zero points. Paul, what are you betting? I'll wager it all, Bill. Wager? No, it's Jacob.
My name is Jacob. All right. Let's go. Mid. Mid spin. Oh, Paul is a medium-paced kind
of spinner. We all know that. You know me. And Paul, I almost lost his wager, but he
got two times the wager. Oh, shoot. Two times my wager. Look the fuck out. Paul's got eight
points. Matt. I wager all my points. Betting it all. Low, please. A low pace. A nice lack
of daisical spin. A lazy spin. And Matt gets four points. You know what that means. Matt
and Paul are tied. Eight points apiece. Jacob wins. Oh no. Cats game. Jacob wins. Oh, traditional
Scoopity rules. That was a Price is Skryte sent in by Magnum Scoop. If you want to send
in a Price is Skryte or a Jock vs. Nerd of any kind, head over to HeyScoops.com. HeyScoops.com
right there on the homepage. Send us in a Jock vs. Nerd. Send us in some... Oh my God.
Matt is just roving right here on screen. What is happening? I lost my shirt in Price
is Skryte. Do all the things over there at HeyScoops.com. Also buy yourself some tickets
to ScoopFest. Do yourself a favor. Come visit us here in September in beautiful Las Vegas,
Nevada. Head over there, HeyScoops.com, or you can just go to ScoopFest.com and hey,
you can get a discount to your tickets at ScoopFest by being a Patreon. You go over,
you sign up on the lowest tier, $3 a month. Sign up to be a Patreon. You get a discount
for ScoopFest that is more than $3 a month. It's more than $3. You can make us look silly.
Go to Patreon.com/HeyScoops. No, no, no. That's too complicated. Go over there to PreachingFun.com.
I'm stretching this out because I can't remember where the button is. There it is. That's it.
I'm good at this. And if you want to go, I don't know, slap people with chicken breasts,
go to fartsinabag.biz. It's a lot of fun. That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com
takes you to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this
show on the air. That's right. Not only does it get you tickets to ScoopFest or cheaper
tickets to ScoopFest, it gets you the knowledge that you personally are keeping this show
rolling. That's right. All of that crow humor from earlier wouldn't be possible without
you. Yeah. All right. I want to thank the following people who all carry on distinct
memories from their parents sperm. That'd be Scoop Lindsey, Scoop Jesus, Scoop J'adore,
Scoop Real Good, Scoop Emily, Scoop Dave Ill, Scoop Chang the Beijing Bugle, Scoop Bucky,
Scoop Brady, Scabby the Rat Scoop, Sax Guy Jimmy D, Sarah Boyle, Sonja Petrovich, Sam
Reid, Saltlick Scoop, Sackett Mengel, Ryar Appledorn, Ryan Hayward, Rose, Ron Heck and
Roger Edge. Big thanks to these people who may not be from Jersey but do love to rock
a gold chain. Pick it up, pick it up, pick it up. Philip Guyton, Phil Tomlinson, Phil
Friendly, Petty Officer Scoop, Peter Sanzone, Peter McDougal, Peter Hines, Peter Buford,
Pete Bougie, Pete Romano, Peaback Scoop, P.E. Scoop, Polygon, Paula, Paul's brother, Paul
Hoser Scoop, Luxton, One Fell Scoop, Okie Scoop, Nicky Benoit, Nicole Levin, Nicole
Bursonback and Nicholas Petty. And I want to thank the following people who all recently
got a pothole named after them in Pittsburgh. That'd be Rodimus Scoop, Robots Ahoy, Robert
Paulson, Richard Hill, Richard Graffiti, Richard Fastnot, Richard Dunn, Reverend Nick Dingman
of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster, Scoop Getty, whoa that's a long one, Reverend
Nick Dingman of the Church of the Flying Scoop Getty Monster, Remember the Alamode, Refrigerator
Perry Scoop, Randy Glenn, Randy, Ralph Barrett, Raggedy Girl, Radioactive Scoop, Quiet Quiet
Scoop and Pyro Plus, Proto Scoop and Proper Scoop.
Big thanks to these folks who get paid for getting kicked in the nuts and may or may
not have died because of it. Nesticle Scoop, Neil Fleish, Neapolitan, Neck pubes, Nathan
Hootin, Nathan Clay, Miss Johnny Australia, Mr. Head Scoop, Motor City Schmitty, Monica
Day, Monodnock Scoop, Mohan Nair, Mitzula, Mississippi churning scoop, Mississippi churning
scoop, Milkleg Scoop, Mike Wins and Mike Six, thank you.
And the following scoops are just like me and really scared one of their gardeners just
now just by sitting in their chair and the gardener just walked past the glass door to
my office, looked inside and looked very frightened to see me. Those are Mike Federley, Mike Michelle
Yaser, Michael Shaw, Michael Martin, Michael Calder, Michael, Melissa Archiga, Malia,
McTits, Max the Ginger Scoop, Max McKenzie, Matt Galacki, Matt aka Stormageddon, Matt
Scoop-A-Fail, Matcha Ice Cream Sunday, Mary Norbury Glazer, Mark Wilson, Mark Madsen,
Mark Gates, Mark Cohen, Mario Rosa, Mark Sadowiski, Marble Tulip Scooby Tree, Maple Raisin Scoop,
Mama Ninja Scoop, Macho Scoop, Randy Sprinkles, M. Hertz, Luke Mellon, Lauren Grincey, Linda
Brandmere, Lil Red, Leon Kassab, Leon Cox, Lee Forrest, Lee Drummond, Laurie Ellsroth,
Latter Day Scoop, Larry Goodale, Lance Amon, L.A.J. and Mack Schnoor, thank you so much
everybody.
Thank you all so much. By the way, I just checked our email. Zero PayPal tips for me
taking off my shirt, just to be clear.
In other words, the amount that we expected.
So far, so far.
Yes, thank you all for tuning in. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon.
We do love you guys.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the call.
[Music]
We're Brick 'N Puff!
We sure are. See ya!