(upbeat music)
- Oh, hello there, I am so glad you are here.
This is my favorite part of the show.
This is the part of the show where we get to thank you,
the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Who are the Ice Cream Truck Drivers?
Why, those are the folks that deliver
that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now, I'd like to thank Beard and Scoop,
Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Christine Elsesser,
Kristi Salinas, Coach Rat Bastard,
Darren Cunningham, and Darth Scooper.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver,
just like these fine folks, and I hope you do,
PreachingFun.com, PreachingFun.com
is where you can go to sign up
to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
- Otherwise, I'll see you at the cone.
(laughs)
- There it is.
- 'Cause you're dead.
- Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Great, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- So, I bought, like, sunglasses for, like, my larger head.
- Okay.
- And I got them polarized, and it comes with a swatch
that says polarization test.
You can put 'em on and see, like, a secret word
in a little swatch, and the word was Israel.
- It's time for Matt and Maddly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting over there, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting over there, it's Paul Maddly.
Over here, it's Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
- Very polarizing sunglasses.
- Very polarizing.
- Extremely polarizing sunglasses.
- I'm not even sure if that's a real story
or just a dad joke.
- It's a real story up until the Israel part.
It just said their brand name in the little swatch,
but I laughed at polarization test really hard.
(laughs)
- Yeah.
Oh, that's so good.
- That was really funny.
So, I was making burgers for my kids last night
using the Smasher that Jacob sent me a link for
last time we brought up making burgers.
I was can't smashing some burgers for my kids.
And my youngest likes himself a pretzel bun,
so I get, like, a fancy, I get, like, nice pretzel buns
from a supermarket.
And then--
- Your youngest has excellent taste.
- So then I get, like, a nice, kind of like brioche style bun
for my other kid who doesn't like pretzel buns.
He normally just takes a regular hamburger bun,
but he's the only one eating it,
so I'll buy, like, a roll, you know?
And he's eating it, and I said,
you don't like the fancy bun, do you?
And he goes, "Dad, I'm an American."
(laughs)
- There it is.
I want no fucking brioche bun.
(laughs)
I demand that my bread have a clown on it.
- Wonder has to be in the title somewhere.
- It has to be just the most bleached, white, flour.
- I need it to be so preserved.
- Yes.
- Like, mold cannot grow on it under any circumstances.
- I want my hamburger bun to have been made in 1987.
(laughs)
I want it to have been sitting in a warehouse.
- That's when they were still good.
Oh, they were good then.
- Preserved under salt.
- They were so good then.
It's like those McDonald's buns
with that exact same weird white spot
on the bottom of all of 'em.
- Oh.
- Classic, classic consistency.
Out, are you, get out of my house.
- I don't know how many decades
it's been since I had a McDonald's hamburger bun.
- Clearly, it's been a minute.
- Yeah.
- Jacob, I know, you've long not been a fan
of the Southwest general seating procedures.
We've documented--
- No, I have not been.
And it seems like I might be finally getting my way.
- You might be.
But in the meantime, you know, as someone,
I don't mind it.
I don't, I like it.
- Yep.
- I love it.
- I find myself with a lot.
- Even though they started charging for bags,
it's still cheaper to check bags on Southwest
than the other airline.
And so I still--
- Yep.
- Fly Southwest 'cause it's still like 35 bucks for two bags.
- I just had a long conversation last week about airlines
'cause we were talking about like airline credit cards
for her band and for all of her gigs and everything
and all the travel that she does.
- Yeah.
- And we ended up, 'cause we'd been using Southwest
and we were like, let's look at these other airlines.
Let's look at the other cards and everything.
And nope, Southwest, that's just where we stayed.
- Man, I'm telling you,
you've got the major hub there in Vegas.
And that was what I got weaned on.
Having to go out to Jersey,
I had to not fly Southwest from here.
There was no Southwest from here to Jersey.
- No, there's not.
- It was very disturbing.
- The closest you can get is Baltimore.
It's the closest.
- I think I went on United.
I went United both ways and I was just like,
oh, I don't like this.
(laughing)
I do not care for this.
I do not care for this United stuff at all.
- I am getting online in Chicago,
fly back home here after doing my corporate gig.
And it is tight quarters in O'Hare.
And I'm blanking because I should side note,
I drove like hell to the wrong airport.
I went to Midway.
- Oh, that's the worst.
- And the only thing that was good was that
I had to rent a car.
But since I do have checked bags,
what I like to do is I like to pull up the curbside,
rush up the curbside check-in.
- Ooh, I like this move.
- Yes.
- Check my bags, then return my rental car
and I'm not lugging all of my bags through the airport.
- Yes.
- Just taking my carry-on.
- Because there's a secret that most airports
don't want you to know
and that's that they can't tow your car instantly.
(laughing)
- They can threaten it.
They can threaten to find it.
- They can yell about it a lot.
They can do that.
They can't tow it instantly.
- So they were like trying to check my bags at Midway
and the woman is making a very confused face
and I'm panicking 'cause as she takes longer,
I'm looking to see,
making sure I'm not getting eyed for a fine
with my rental car.
And she goes,
I don't know what's going on.
I've never gotten this message before.
I brought this guy over.
Brought this guy over.
He hasn't gotten this message before.
I think you have to go inside.
And my brain went, no, I don't.
I have to go to a different airport.
My brain is like, wait.
And so I was like, somehow did I book a ticket home
from a different airport?
And then I realized I landed at a different airport
and didn't realize it.
I had just been to Chicago three weeks ago
for Chicago Magic Lounge.
And so my brain was just confusing the two airports.
So I luckily left with a lot of time.
So I arrived at the proper airport with very little time.
So I was still rushing,
but I wasn't gonna miss my flight or anything.
I was like, oh God, but I drove like hell
between those two airports.
Anyhow, so I'm in there.
I'm in Southwest and it is tight at O'Hare.
It is like, you know, 'cause Southwest makes you line up.
They usually make you line up along the thing.
The line they have here is like a very stunted little--
- They don't have the square footage.
- No, they don't have square footage.
- In the airport there.
- So you gotta like basically move towards the thing.
- They've got the square footage at Midway,
but they're not at O'Hare.
- And there was a young man, well-coiffed man from India,
I believe, with his tall, very tall sister or girlfriend.
I don't know.
- Yep.
- And he is--
- Either way they were making out.
- He is beaming uncomfortable anger already.
Like he is holding his bags and he is like elbows out
and we're in tight quarters and you gotta do the thing.
We're like, hey, what number are you?
I'm this number, I'm this number.
This is what I'm okay with and Jacob hates.
And I'm trying to figure out, you know,
where to stand or whatever.
And, you know, they said--
- But it's within increments of five.
- It's within increments of five.
And I honestly, I do have my own pet peeves with it.
We're like, some people kind of go,
like if I'm seven and they're nine
and they're in front of me and I go, I'm seven,
they go, some as a Southwest person will confidently go like,
yeah, like meaning like you don't have to get in front of me.
We're both in the same vicinity.
And I kind of go like--
- Close enough.
- And I kind of get like, no,
that's the whole fucking point is numbers.
- That's some bullshit.
- Seven is lower than nine.
- Ass.
- So this guy has got his elbows out
and I'm saying, I'm a seven.
I'm saying it, you know, and I'm saying it out loud.
And I get a couple of a communicate me,
him and his sister wife are not communicating.
And he is like stewing.
I can feel him stewing from his back.
You know, when someone's so angry--
- Oh, it's the worst.
- For stewing, right?
- Oh my goodness.
- And so finally, some guy comes up
like a little late to the party and is like,
excuse me, A1, A1, A1, excuse me, A1.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And I was like, oh, this guy's coming through
like Lipitor through a vein here.
And he is there and the guy goes, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And he goes, yes, I'm A1.
And he goes, no, we're all A1, which confused us all.
I was like, I was like, I am Spartacus.
Today we are all A1.
- No, buddy. (laughing)
- Matt never got off the plane.
I don't know who Paul's been talking to this entire time.
- We live here.
And so I was laughing.
He goes, no, I've done this before.
I know how this works.
I'm A1, excuse me.
- I'm definitely up there.
- And he shouts like, no.
Like he starts like to open his arms
and like clear everyone back.
Like no one move kind of body language, right?
- I feel so bad for this guy.
That's just the worst as he's having a terrible day.
- And he's like, and so the guy with A1 is like waving
like anyone from South was like, get over here.
Please get over here or whatever.
And he says that the Indian guy says, no, no, no.
You announced that it is open seating.
- Oh boy.
- And the flight attendants like, no, yeah.
When you get on the plane, it is open seating.
He goes, no, you announced open seating.
So it is now open seating, meaning that like.
- No, no, no.
Like whatever you want is wherever you want to go.
No son, no, no, no, no.
- Once you announced open seating, so now anarchy.
- You know what this means?
- I was like, listen, our podcast is a similar rule
about dibs.
So I understand what you're saying.
- Yeah.
- Dibs has been called is what you were saying.
You're saying once anyone with South us
utters open seating, the numbers on our tickets
become useless.
They're right out.
- Out the window.
- Disqualified.
- Nope.
Don't even look at them again.
They're not worth the paper that they were printed on.
Open seating motherfuckers.
- So I take this opportunity to turn to person with a nine
and I'm actually with someone with a four and a three
who don't want to go past this angry person.
So we're all, we're all like our little clutter.
We're all like little clutter space together
right behind them.
So I decided to announce it, interpret what is happening.
I was like, this guy thinks because the words open seating
were uttered in any capacity, our tickets don't matter now.
(laughing)
- Oh boy.
I make a point of getting up.
- Nothing else matters.
- You gotta get up super early or stay up super late.
- Yeah.
- And you get on that app and you wait for the moment
that thing flips over and you hit your button
to get your good seat availability.
- I'm telling you right now, Mr. A1 and myself,
we are, you know, we both fly Southwest enough
when you get A-list, they check in for you.
You're going to get your A.
- Yeah and A1 is, that's a $50 ticket.
- Also A1 is I know 'cause like they make sure
that like Penn gets it whenever he flies
'cause he can get that one seat that has the six, seven.
So there's that one seat you have more leg room.
- Yep, but that's an extra expense.
- Yes and it's, and oftentimes it's a privilege.
Like it's oftentimes like it's like anyone traveling often
is A1 is like someone who travels like every day.
Like it's just a, it's just a huge thing or whatever.
But I, but yeah.
I was laughing so hard and angry
and he continued to be a show.
- You sat open seating.
- They got the front row with the extra seats
so they could feel like they were in first class.
You know, I think that's all they were anxious about
was getting that first row,
which means you have to put all your shit behind you,
which I hate so I never sit in that row.
I fucking hate that, right?
And then guys, I have to tell you something.
I was haphazardly, stick with me, I was a good person.
So I, since I already checked bags,
I would say if it's a full flight,
I will gate check my one carry-on bag
and only have my book bag.
- Oh, okay.
- And so I get on the plane,
but I put my book bag up in the carry-on,
which they, that's not okay.
- Frown upon that.
- Right. - Yeah, yeah.
- But here's the thing. - I do the same thing.
I do the same thing though, and I'm ready.
- And I'm ready, exactly.
So I put it up there and I go,
if they call me on it, I'll bring my book bag down.
If they don't call me on it,
I bet the person who's got the center, middle seat
is gonna have their bags and they're gonna be pissed
that they have to put their shit all the way behind them
and I will offer that row.
So I waited till the whole thing was on.
The person was like, can I sit in the middle seat?
Like, I'm fucked.
I said, yes, and not only that, here.
And I took my book bag out, put it at my feet,
and then I put their carry-on into the space
and then the carry-on right above their head.
Not all heroes wear capes, guys.
- Champion of the flight.
- Not all heroes wear capes,
but this one carried a book bag.
- I was waiting for, tears is maybe strong,
but a thank you, they didn't give a shit
that I did a good thing for, they didn't care at all.
- Oh, wow, what do you know?
- I mean, they still gave you the thank you hand, Jay,
during the flight, right?
- I mean, that person is an American.
(laughing)
- I was like, do you realize what I just did for you?
Like, do you understand?
- Yeah.
- They did not.
- You owe me, you.
- I said, that's it, open seating.
And then I hit a music cue
and everybody had to switch seats until the music stopped.
- Did the guy end up getting on the plane where he was?
Was he not stopped?
They didn't put him back anywhere?
- No, they let him on and he was just,
I mean, he got up like probably like seven times
to get something out of one bag or another.
And then they were--
- Yeah, he's one of those.
- They were doing, it was just like--
- He was having a terrible day.
I see these people at airports and on flights
where I'm just like,
you are being horrible to everyone around you
and I hate you so much.
- Are these people--
- That being said, I recognize that you are having
just the worst day that a human being can have
and I'm sorry for you.
- Do you think it was because he didn't want to fly?
Do you think he was a nervous flyer
and these people, they can't handle the loss of control
that flying he is and so--
- I mean, I think it factors a lot.
I think we have folks here who work in the airline business,
including myself.
I think I'm much more anxious on a plane
and I get much more fucking pissed about little shit that--
- Sure.
- But I find that--
- As someone who is with you often,
both in and out of airports.
- Yeah, yeah.
No, Matt, you're definitely much more anxious flying.
(Matt laughing)
I can just, you don't have to wonder, buddy.
- Hey, I said nothing to that woman that shook my seat.
(both laughing)
- I didn't say you're not a hero, sir.
I just said you're more anxious.
- Right, and so I tell myself,
you're not gonna care about this in like 20 minutes, right?
Like that's what I tell myself when I start to get--
- Future Matt does not give a shit about this.
- Not give a shit about this.
So, yeah. - That's the trick.
- But it is, it is, yeah.
I think everyone gets fucking pissed about going on planes.
- No, it's not a fun experience for anyone.
- So speaking of good deeds, guys,
well, I'm patting my own back here.
- Okay, other arm.
- So there was an attack on Verizon,
either a cyber attack on Verizon or just a big fucking
fuck up at Verizon.
But all Verizon went down like two days ago.
- Oh shit.
- I was giving like crappy service across the country.
And at the same time, there was an Apple update
that night before on my phone.
And then I got up and my phone was not working.
And then I was like, oh shit,
maybe the update messed something up or maybe whatever.
- Right.
- And then all of a sudden I'm talking to other people
and they had their phones down too.
Man, going around without cell service
for more than 24 hours is crazy.
Like, I know it's so dumb, but I was like,
man, the word would fall apart
if this happened for like four days.
- Oh yeah.
- It will fall apart, Matt.
- Yeah, it will fall apart.
Because I was looking forward to it.
- The amount of time to just hop to my car
is like all a GPS from the car.
And also I was just going like, shit, no, I won't.
I have to figure out.
- Incorrect.
- I have to figure out where I'm going.
- Wow.
- And so, but I'm getting this thing on my phone
that's a SIM card failure.
- Okay, hold on, I got it.
- Goren knows what I'm talking about.
- Yeah.
- And everyone else I'm talking to who has Verizon phones
didn't get that message.
- Right.
- Oh.
- But I went into a Verizon store to be like,
hey, my phone says SIM card failure
and they literally there's three of them.
And they all went, yeah, no, the network is down.
And it's down like across the country or whatever.
And I said, oh, but mine said SIM card failure.
And he goes, they're all saying different things
to different people if you look or whatever.
- So they were like, ignore all the other things.
It's the network.
The network is just wreaking havoc.
- Yeah.
Now I'm getting some people in the chat saying
they have Verizon and nothing went wrong with them.
Well, good for fucking you, okay?
If you Google the news stories, say Verizon outage,
you will see news stories on it.
- I'm looking at it right now.
The weird thing is it doesn't seem like Verizon
has said still what caused it.
- They have not said what caused it.
I'm thinking I ran, but I don't know.
But why not guess I ran too much.
- I think I ran too hard and the rest of my phone.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So I said, I said, I said, I said, I said, oh, I go,
oh, so you've been dealing with this all day.
And they go, yeah.
And I go, oh, that can't be fun.
They go, one woman literally pointed us and said,
it's your fault and you're not doing anything.
I was like, really?
The retail person working for Verizon storefront
is in charge of the network?
They're like, I like to sell your phone
and keep this entire network going across the world.
- Wow.
Now, Matt, it sounds like you made a bit of an assumption
there when this retail store employee just told you
this story, you then assumed that they did not indeed
control the Verizon network.
- Oh my God, I'm a fool.
- I didn't even ask you, buddy.
- It's right there.
But do you, right?
I could have, but do you?
I could have just said that.
- And then it'd be like, as a matter of fact,
you caught me on the undercover boss day.
- Yeah, I run this thing.
- I'm Tom Verizon.
- I decided to get a little taste of that old 14.75 an hour.
See how that treats me.
Take a little taste of how the other half lives.
- Watch this.
And then he takes off his glasses and shakes down
his long hair and he's a beautiful girl.
The whole time.
- Amazing.
- I'll tell you who else was a beautiful girl
the entire time, you didn't even realize it.
And that is the following sponsor.
- There's more to the story, but today's show
is brought to you by the bearded liberal truck driving school.
School for the bearded liberal truck driver,
trucker, trucker, the bearded liberal trucker driving school.
One of the most polarizing characters.
Some people don't like when we do this character.
- Oh, I love that character.
- Yeah, but yeah.
So that's from 2022, sex guy, Jimmy Deescoop.
And it's the bearded liberal trucker driving school.
- All right, you pansy sons of bitches.
Strap on your rainbow hats and let's get going.
All right.
Get in the goddamn truck and follow me.
It's a truck driving school.
You're gonna learn how to parallel park this son of a bitch.
That's right.
You're gonna be able to aim this thing, slide it right in.
Getting right in between the Marxist ideology
and Jungian theology.
You're gonna just zip it right in there tight as a cord.
Yeah, you're gonna love it.
Yeah.
You're gonna be able to maneuver on the highways
and byways of this great country
better than a woman's right to vote.
(laughing)
- I'm sorry, do we learn how to drive trucks
while we're here at all?
I was hoping to learn how to drive a truck.
- Eventually, Mr. Yamby Pamby.
- Boy, oh boy, you sure like to mouth off a lot.
You know, you might want to think about
taking some meditation classes.
Fucking shit.
- No, I was just, I thought this was a truck driving school
and so I was just here to--
- Oh, it most assuredly is.
It most assuredly is.
But I can't help but notice
you got some pretty fancy shoes on there.
- They're Nikes, yeah.
- Any ideas where those were made
and by which infant's hands?
Boy, oh boy.
- No, no, I don't.
I just bought the shoes.
Pay less, I think.
- Hey, let me ask you a quick question.
What's your favorite war?
- I'm sorry, war? - Wrong answer.
There is no war but class war.
Get in the fucking truck.
(laughing)
- Enter Hayscoops at checkout.
- Well, so I leave the Verizon store with no service.
I decide to wait out the outage
and I go next door to the Smiths and I get cupcakes
and I bring all the workers cupcakes.
- That was very sweet.
- I say, sorry you haven't--
- And then they fixed your phone for you.
- That's really nice.
They're like, here you go, here you go, sir.
Boop, boop, boop, boop.
- Let me turn your phone back on.
- There you go, there you go, sir.
(laughing)
- Well, I wake up the next day,
I do a little research at night, you know, research.
I asked Chad GPT how to fix my phone.
- Good, I said, you're fucked, buddy.
- And then I go on YouTube and watch some videos.
- Oh, you did do some research.
- And I'm trying to do all this shit to my phone.
- Did you figure it out pretty quick?
YouTube's like, hey, everybody's screwed.
- No, no, I meant that like, oh, sorry, I skipped a step.
So basically I started talking to all my--
- Yeah, you did.
- I started talking to all my other Verizon friends
and they got their bars back and I didn't
by the end of the night.
- Oh.
- Ah, okay.
- So at midnight, you know, everything's closed,
but at midnight, I'm realizing that like everyone else,
I'm the only one still with no service in my phone.
- Have you tried turning it off and turning it on again?
- Right, I did.
- Did you put it in rice?
- I shoved it in rice.
I tried to rub its thigh and then whisper in its ear
to turn it on.
- Whisper in its tear.
- In its tear duct.
(laughing)
And then it tells you like,
you can take out your SIM card thing.
Have you ever taken out the SIM card of your own phone?
- It's a pain.
- It's scary.
You gotta get like a little paper clippy thing
and you gotta like push real hard,
like harder than you would on like a delicate object.
And then like it goes bunk and then it comes out.
And I laughed because I was following the directions
on the YouTube thing, but of course you're playing,
pausing, playing, pausing.
And it says, do not blow into the empty slot like a Nintendo.
And I was like, oh, that's exactly what I did.
I had too late.
You need to put that before.
You need to tell me that before.
- I did that immediately.
- That's a go-to.
- Have you guys seen all the videos
where people pour molten glue into their phone holes
and pull it out as a cleaning method?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, oh, no.
- Yeah, I've seen those.
- I don't know that that's advisable.
- I don't think so.
- I haven't done it.
I've seen the videos.
I haven't then tried to replicate it.
- I don't think you'd go to the Apple store
and they'd be like, have you done molten glue at home?
I don't think that's ever gonna be the jack.
- I think it would fuck you up.
I think you could maybe do slime, maybe.
- No, I'm not putting any goo in my phone.
(laughing)
- Yeah, they use the hot glue.
Yeah, I don't know.
- Like if I get a little fuzz
in the charging port of my phone,
I get a little Q-tip and just pop the fuzz out.
- Wait, you pop out fuzz with a Q-tip with more fuzz?
- That seems ridiculous.
- Fight fuzz with fuzz.
Fight fuzz with fuzz.
- Well, you know, now that I'm saying it--
- No, now that you're saying it,
as an old time video game collector,
when I'd buy all those used copies and movies too,
they got stickers all over them, of course.
The best way to get that sticker residue off
is with another adhesive sticker.
- There you go.
- So fight fuzz with fuzz.
- Fight fuzz with fuzz.
- Mike Nielsen--
- Matt, have you gotten the $20 account credit?
- I haven't gotten that.
- I can show up on your next bill.
- You're owed, well, I think you have to get it.
I think you have to call them and--
- Oh, we say hey, motherfucker.
You better get on that horn.
- According to the New York Post,
there is a call for this to be done automatically now.
- Yeah, imagine selling it.
- It's like a $20 account credit,
which is being slammed for being inadequate.
Do you feel like $20 is adequate or inadequate
for your pain and suffering?
I mean, so a day without cell service
is worth more than $20?
- Oh, yeah.
- But it's definitely more than 1/30 of your bill.
- Well, I think it's a breach of their contract,
and I think it probably isn't,
given all the legalese they've been in there.
- I'm sure it's not.
- But at the same time, I think that--
- But I'll go to the Verizon store and tell them that, though.
- But in certain cases, it's a life or death situation.
I think they could really become here, not heroes.
They could make some good positive news
if they waived the monthly fee for everybody.
- Yeah.
- I think, I mean-- - Oh, sure.
- If they said--
- Oh, scoopernova girl, Matt, wants to know
how much the cupcakes were.
Were you, even with the $20 credit,
are you still in hock to Verizon here?
- I got $60 cupcakes each.
(Matt laughs)
- Whoa.
- Basically.
- I got the nicest cupcakes I've ever seen.
- But Jules and actual Jules.
- Gordon Ramsay's corner cupcakes.
- No, I got, you know, seven bucks?
- Yeah, nice cupcakes.
- So even with the 20, you're coming out a little ahead.
Even with the cupcakes on the 20,
you're coming out a little ahead.
- I'm probably not gonna go for the $20 credit.
I'm just gonna let you guys know right now.
- You're not gonna call it Verizon
and get the $20 credit. - I'm gonna let you know
right now. - You're not?
- Those are things where you value your time at zero.
I don't value my time at zero.
- Are you kidding me?
Time at zero? - Okay, Matt, here's,
to just call them up and say,
"Hey, give me $20," and they go, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
- There's the word, there's the word.
What do I do, Paul? - Right.
- Just, just call them.
Just, it's so easy.
The word just makes it so easy.
- Oh, boy.
- I won't be on the phone for an hour on hold
with all the other schlubs trying to get
a $20 fucking refund.
- Okay, maybe you don't do it today,
but in no way, no way they're gonna let people
stay on hold for an hour for their $20 thing.
That's fucking crazy.
Oh, so you just click a link.
There you go.
I'm sure you can do it.
You should absolutely do it.
I just got $20 back from my oil change.
I'd spent, but I spent 20 minutes doing it,
but that's worth it to me.
That's a dollar an hour for me.
- You're really distracted by the $20.
This is not where this story's going.
- I'll tell you why, because this is the $20.
That's what this is to me.
You're speaking in terms of action figures.
That's a Craven the Hunter.
Are you crazy?
You don't want a Craven the Hunter?
Are you insane?
- Not really.
I don't want a Craven the Hunter.
- Well, you don't want a Craven the Hunter.
You're not a Spider-Man fanatic.
He killed Spider-Man.
You know how hard that is to do?
This guy figured it out.
- Very few people have done it.
- Yeah, I think he's the only one.
- Call the cops.
That's a crime.
- That is murder.
- He ended up dying over it.
- No, he didn't actually kill Spider-Man.
That's the twist.
(laughing)
- Look, this is all adding up to,
is on the day there was a software update,
on the day there was some kind of weird cyber attack
or not that took down a lot of Verizon's network.
- Yes.
- By total coincidence, on the same day
my SIM card crapped up.
- Just a total, total coincidence.
- It couldn't have been coincidence.
It was some kind of--
- I think it was.
- No.
- Or the update did it.
- What do you think, Jacob?
What do you think?
- I tend to, I do tend to lean towards Paul's way
of thinking on these with the electronic stuff is,
if one thing happens,
I don't think that it's usually coincidence.
I think it's usually somehow tied together.
- It was corrupted by something, yeah.
- Maybe not in the way that,
maybe not in the way that we're thinking about,
but like, I bet it's tied together somehow.
- Look, I have an older phone.
I have a 12, right?
- Okay.
- So I think, what, the 17 is out now, I think.
- Did someone give your phone a comic book
with boobs in it?
'Cause that's the ultimate corruption.
(laughing)
- Circles on circles.
- Circles in circles.
- I showed, I showed my SIM card,
the entertainment landscape in Las Vegas,
and it just gave up and crapped out.
(laughing)
- It went goo.
- I'm like, yikes, beer.
- You made it research the boring company.
It was like, corruption, corruption.
(laughing)
Corruption, Joe Lombardo, corruption, corruption.
File corrupted.
- Well, I--
- Joe Lombardo was the Nevada governor.
- So somehow--
- Yeah, somehow, somehow he's the Nevada fucking governor.
Oh boy, we got out of that place.
- I wasn't telling you, I was telling the people listening.
- I'm telling you,
I got out of there by the skin of my teeth
before that place started to blow.
(laughing)
- Dude, compared to some other,
look, I don't like Joe Lombardo
and I'm not voting for him ever.
But I mean, compared to what other states have
for politicians--
- I guess you're right.
- I count my blessings that we only have Joe Lombardo.
- He's an old school intelligence scumbag,
not just a blatant YouTube lying scumbag.
- Right.
- I suppose.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, there are some things that he says when he's like,
yeah, I was just over there and that I walked over here.
I'm like, oh, he just said something
that was demonstrably true.
Okay, that's okay, good.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Laurie in the chat like,
hello, Indiana over here.
Could be a lot worse.
- Yeah, no, I count my blessings with Lombardo.
- You know, hey, throw a dart at the old US of A.
You're gonna find some horrible shit right now.
- I'll tell you who disagrees with Paul
about that completely.
And that is Matt Son, who is an American.
- That's right.
- Also the following sponsor.
- This show and this Verizon story
was not supposed to carry over two commercial breaks,
but this show is brought to you by Sales Ship Salesale.
Yep, that's Sales Ship Salesale from Night Scoops in 2021.
Sales, sorry, Sales Ship Salesale.
You get it? - Right.
I get it.
- Okay.
Hey, I'm Sal
I sell ship sales
And today I'm having a sale on my ship sales
Would you like to save
When you buy a ship sale from Sal
Today's the day of the sale
So set sale for savings with Sal's Ship Sales Sale
Sailing
Takes me to sales where I can buy sales
For my ship
Oh yeah.
That's right, I'm Sal with the pipes.
Sailing
It's a discount that you'll apply at the register
- Me her.
- Oh God.
- Open seating, open seating.
Wherever you sit on the boat, it's yours.
- No, you don't understand.
- I'm gonna sit here.
This is where I'm sitting now.
- No, you don't understand.
- I own this boat now, I'm sitting on it.
- No.
- My boat.
I'm having a sale for ships.
Oh my God.
- And her hay scoops at checkout.
- I'm losing everything.
- Boy, that did not go well for that retail.
- I lost everything.
- Oh boy.
- I lost all my ship sales.
- Buyer beware.
I realized this week, I was having a conversation
with a friend of mine this week and I realized
that there is something that happens to me
with some regularity that I don't think happens
to other people, I think in most cases ever in their lives.
- Happy beginnings.
- Okay.
- Just 'cause. - What is it?
- Just hold on, just 'cause,
'cause I'm just gonna push through it.
I went back in the Verizon the next day
'cause I was the only one who didn't have a phone working.
I said, "Is there such thing as an eSIM card?"
They said, "Yes."
They sat there, took a half hour to repair my phone,
and I said, "How much do I owe you?"
They said, "You gave me cupcakes yesterday,
"don't worry about it."
And so whatever they're gonna charge me,
didn't matter, they got cupcakes.
It's the whole fucking story I was trying to get to,
and that's why I don't give a shit about the $12 credit.
Okay, go ahead.
- That's a win right there.
- No, I'm sorry, we're out of time, Matt.
That story carried us over all three parts of the show here.
Sorry, everybody, we're actually out of time.
We can't do any more episodes.
We used all of our time for all future episodes
of that story, so I'll see you later, everybody.
I can't even play the outro music, I'm sorry, I would,
but I'll just, everybody turn off your podcast
listening devices.
- We're constrained by our pretend constraints.
What is your, what's going on, Jacob?
What happens to you that doesn't happen to other people?
- I get accused, probably weakly,
of giving someone a false name.
- Whoa! - Oh!
- My name is so common. - Yeah.
- Jacob Smith, I get accused almost weakly
of giving a false name to people.
- I have never been accused of that.
- So people go like, "No, no, no, what's your real name?"
- Yes!
- Like in what environments?
- Like if I have to give a name for anything.
- Like Starbucks? - So like a valet,
yeah, like a valet parking, Starbucks, anything,
anything like that.
If I have to give a name, and they go--
- It's like going up for a reservation,
"Party of two for Alan Smithy, please."
And they're like, "What?"
Yeah, well, it does read, it reads pretend.
I mean, I'm not convinced it's your name.
- You shouldn't.
- Wait, we just learned this lesson,
so we get to put it in action right away.
Is it your real name?
All right, breaking news, breaking news.
- Who can say?
But yeah, like I'll drop a car off at the valet
and then they'll be like,
"Oh, we need a last name for the ticket, Smith."
And they will just stand there and look at me
and not move their pen at all to write my name down.
- Yeah.
- They're like, "Ha-ha, we've heard it all, Dickhead.
"What's your name?"
- Yeah, and they will like,
I'll often get like an eye roll or anything.
And I'll be like, it's common
because a lot of us are named Smith.
I don't know what to tell you.
- Okay, Jacob, so now you need to take on
like a Bob Dylan, Jack Frost type vibe here.
You need a day-to-day events like that
where you're getting reservations
or valets, you need a pseudonym
or a nom de plume, if you will,
that will somehow at least ring less false
than Jacob Smith.
- Okay, okay.
Sir Antoine.
- No, no, they're gonna go with sir.
A lot of people know they're Knights.
- Don't go putting a hat on the hat here.
Don't make this into too flowery.
- All right.
- No, no, no, I've been Jacob Smith my whole life.
- You're going flowery.
- Let's go to the chat here, actually.
Just the first name, what does Jacob look like?
You see a guy who looks like Jacob approaching.
Give us some first name.
- A latter day scoop is already saying Hiram.
- Okay, Hiram?
- I like that.
- Are you getting a Gary and a Peter?
Alex?
- We got an Alex.
- Okay, so far I think Hiram Twattberger is winning,
but let's see.
- Hiram Twattberger.
Oh, Sebastian.
Thank you, Canadian Scoop.
I do like saying, my name is Sebastian.
- George Jetson.
You should go by Paul Mattingly.
That's a good one.
(laughing)
- I mean--
- Name, Mattingly, Paul Mattingly.
- Solid choice.
- Oh, Andy Cheek is right.
You should go by Murray.
- Murray. - Murray.
- Of course, that's what I should do.
Murray, Murray, Murray.
- Here's my second suggestion.
Your last name should be a name really known in town.
So it should either be like Wynn or Greenspun or whatever.
- You wanna really try just winking, nodding.
- Like, yeah, parking cars, sure, no problem.
Murray Wynn.
And they gotta go like, wait, is he a fucking Wynn Wynn?
Is he like-- - Who knows?
- And you gotta put everyone on their toes.
You gotta make sure everyone--
- Murray Riviera.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I don't know if Newton's strong enough for Wayne Newton,
so I think you have to go straight Wayne Newton the third.
You have to go Wayne Newton the third.
- Wayne Newton Jr.
(laughing)
- Who are the ones who used to own the Palms and all that?
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Oh, the Maloof's.
- Maloof. - That's it.
- Oh, Murray Maloof. - Murray Maloof.
- Murray Maloof. - Murray Maloof.
(laughing)
- That is, that will get you,
that might get you some stuff.
- That might.
I'll get a license plate that just says Third Maloof.
- Third Loof.
(laughing)
- Maloof Three.
- Murray Maloof.
Holy shit. - Murray Maloof is great.
- Nobody's gonna bat an eye at Murray Maloof
in Las Vegas. - Nope, nope.
I won't get a single look with Murray Maloof.
- And in the early 90s comedy movie of this, of course,
you end up being kidnapped and thrown in the trunk
because you're Murray Maloof.
- No, I get held for ransom as Murray Maloof.
(laughing)
- Oh, Murray Maloof.
- That's it.
- And there's a hilarious stream of hijinks
that gets me out of it.
- How hard is it to get a player's card
with Murray Maloof on it?
- Hard, you need a fucking ID.
- I think, for me, impossible.
- How hard is it to get an ID that says Murray Maloof on it?
(laughing)
- If only we knew anyone that could put together an ID
for me with pictures they already have of me.
(laughing)
- Murray circus, circus.
Murray Excalibur. - Murray circus, circus.
Murray circus.
- I was thinking about just Goodwin.
My name is Jacob Goodwin.
- You know-- - Murray Goodwin.
- I used to get accused of dying my beard
when I had a red beard.
Now I do die my beard and no one brings it up.
(laughing)
But how do you react?
'Cause I used to really,
the first few times it happened,
I was really like, what are you talking to me about?
Does it really throw you?
- I am always ready for it now.
- Okay. - I'm ready for it.
So literally, I see the interaction coming.
We live in Vegas, we valet our cars more
than people in a lot of other places do.
So I keep going back to valets, that's why.
We're around valets a lot.
And so I'll see, oh, this is a valet that I don't know
in a place that I may be a regular at or whatever.
And I'll see the kind of eye roll or the kind of look
and I'll just, in an effort to keep it moving.
I'm ready to just keep the process going.
Like, no, no, write it down, it's Smith.
I promise, that's the real name, let's go.
- Really, okay.
Do you have your license handy?
Are you ready to fling your license at them or something?
- I'm not that, no, I'm not that far.
All right.
- How about Candy Venom?
Candy Venom as your new hip street name.
- And then test yourself, see if you can keep
your same energy where you're like, I know, I know,
write it down, like Candy Venom, write it down.
- Yeah, I know it's common.
You have like eight Candy Venoms in the lot right now.
I get it.
It's common for a reason.
A lot of us are named Candy Venom.
I don't know what to tell you.
- Candy was the most popular name
when I was born a boy in Nevada.
Every boy was named Candy for a week.
It was the Candy Crush game was all the rage.
- Oh sure, everybody was.
- And then Venom of course,
America's number one favorite Spider-Man villain.
- That's why he is Matt Son's favorite villain.
American.
- Oh man.
- American.
- America.
- So I want you guys to think about,
just be aware of it,
keep in the back of your mind over the next few weeks.
I want reports of things that happened to you
that you don't think happened to other people.
- That's a good one.
- Oh.
- Preferably mundane, this is a good scoop mail thing too.
- That is a good one.
- 'Cause I have already just, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're not talking to me, you're talking to our listeners.
- Yeah, I'm talking to you too.
- Yeah, but like we already know
all stuff about each other.
Like I, our neighbor, Chris, who we all know as Chris Lash,
he just moved into my neighborhood.
- Oh nice.
- And I haven't talked to him yet.
I want to keep, I forget if I came to tell him,
like, hey, you and I are first and last name people.
We are always introduced as first and last name.
We've talked about us.
- I think Chris Lash and SJ are friends
from before Chris moved to Vegas.
- Oh wow.
- Yeah, I think SJ, I think Chris is the one,
I think SJ and Chris did a gig together,
like shortly before he moved out to Vegas
and then he moved here and just blew up.
- Yeah, yeah, he works like crazy here in town.
- Oh yeah, he's, we should say Chris Lash
is a wonderful musician here in Vegas.
- Yes, not.
- Who we should probably have on the show at some point.
- Yeah, well I'll tell you what, and this is very early.
They literally just had like one meeting.
But you know, for fun, for one of the quiz shows,
they decided to do a version of Weekend at Bernie's,
the musical, where they did like a 10 minute version
of the musical.
And now it was so fun to work on that they want
to actually work on Weekend at Bernie's, the musical.
- Oh, good, good, good.
- They've only had one meeting, but I can't wait.
It's Casey, Sarah and Chris.
And so it's going to be hysterical.
- I just had a fucking realization last night.
This is just a personal thing.
It doesn't help our podcast at all.
But I just had a personal realization last night
that made me so happy.
And that is Casey Wilson and I are on the same schedule
at Absinthe these days.
- Oh, nice.
- And that means that the next time they do a quiz show,
it'll be on one of my off nights and I'll be able to go.
- Go play. - Oh, very nice.
There you go.
- I really just thought about this last night.
I was so happy to realize that.
- Well, I guess you're working,
I didn't get to see you that night at Sarah Saras's show.
I got to do the show with your wife.
- That's right. - Yeah.
- I heard about it, I heard it went well.
I saw a little bit of video from it.
- It was super fun.
- And your set went very well.
- It did, it went very well.
I was so happy after doing like three corporates in a row
that I was like-- - Oh, I bet.
- Just letting loose, it was really, really funny.
It was super fun.
I also had like awesome people hop up.
So you know, for "Straight As Jacket Escape,"
I had a gay guy and a woman burlesque dancer
raise their hands for-- - Perfect.
- Who are the straightest guys in the room.
And they came up-- - Yes.
- And they were just hysterical.
You know, like when artists try to be funny
and they aren't, it sucks.
If they're funny, it's not-- - Great.
- I laid out and she just took over.
At one point-- - Smooth sailing.
- You know, I come up, I got the shackles
stuck between my legs.
And a guy in the back just goes, "Oh balls."
Like that, like that.
And I was like, that's funny, right?
Like, this is funny.
And I go, and I let it go, I would tip my cap to you, sir.
But obviously, you know, and I just show
that my hands are stuck between my legs.
And the girl just walks over and just doffs
an invisible cap over my head.
Just tips my cap for me.
- Hilarious. - Well done.
- I was like, this is great.
- Is this a burlesque performer that you know?
- No, I just met her that night.
- Oh, that's great. - Shea was her name.
Yeah, yeah, she was great.
- Who was she? - Nice.
- Shea. - Shea.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- She's named after a stadium.
- Oh, you should give that a name.
- Oh shit, I was gonna say, I should have asked
if that was a real name.
She gave me a fucking valet name.
She gave me a fucking fake valet name.
Yes, I'm Shea Stadium of the Connecticut Stadiums.
- You know, we have all that stadium money.
We have all that stadium money.
- How much stadium money do you have?
(laughing)
- But yeah, do we have two knitting scoops?
We do, we have two knitting, this is good.
- I love it.
- It's a higher compliment than when we're told
that people like to, people tell me like straight confidently,
like I fall asleep to you all the time.
And I don't know how to take that as a compliment.
- You should take it as a compliment.
- They need it as a compliment.
- I said that to Joel Hodgson,
he did not take it as a compliment on Twitter.
But that's because he couldn't hear the nuance
and love in my voice.
- That's right.
- I live by those movies.
- But knowing, I think knowing that people knit to us
is maybe, that is the highest compliment, I think.
- It's a pretty high compliment.
- I can see multiple knitters.
- It is very relaxing.
- David Sorenson, what do you do with your hands, buddy?
Get to knitting, get to knitting, go.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- All right, there he goes.
- He's doing it, he's doing it.
(laughing)
- Mattingly, what are you doing with your hands?
- You know what?
- Losing at Jock Versus Nerd.
- Boo!
Boo!
- You wanna do a little Jock Versus Nerd action?
- Oh, am I?
- Fuck yeah.
- I'm on the hunt for balls.
(upbeat music)
On the hunt for balls.
- Oh!
- All right, real quick, two things.
First of all, it's colder than a witch's tit out here
in fuckin' Pittsburgh.
It's so--
- Paul Mattingly's favorite saying, everybody drink.
- But you love your governor, so lucky you.
(laughing)
- We do have a pretty good governor.
It's so cold out here.
That's why I'm literally wearing a jacket,
because we have heater on in the house.
It's just, it's cold.
It's so, so cold.
It's been bitterly cold for days,
and the cold is just seeping
into the bones of the home at this point.
- Uh-huh, the bones!
We have stopped the show.
Paul is cold.
- I don't know if you saw,
but the final reveal has been made.
The Pokemon-- - On The Masked Singer?
- The Pokemon crossover with LEGO.
The first three sets have been revealed.
- Oh!
- Did you see? - Pokemon LEGO?
- Yes.
- Pokemon LEGO?
I have not seen-- - So, Mega Bloks,
which is the company owned by Mattel,
which is one of their rivals,
they had the license for a while,
and they were making Pokemon LEGOs.
So now the Pokemon company is working in tandem with LEGO.
Can you put a guess out there
as to what the biggest set of the,
it's Charizard, Venusaur, and Blastoise in a big diorama.
What is your price tag you think might be
on that three-piece big display set?
- Oh, I thought you were going to have us
guess what they were, but you named the characters,
'cause I was all ready to guess.
- There's two other sets I can have you guess.
- Okay. - Paul wouldn't have been able
to name any of the characters anyway.
- Well, what do you think-- - I was gonna guess
either Ryachu, Pinky Rat, Foxfire, or Hermey.
I'm reading 'em off my phone.
- No. - Okay.
- Pikachu, of course.
Ryachu is an evolution of Pikachu.
You could make a Ryachu out of that Pikachu.
- Yeah, Ryachu's an evolution of Pikachu.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Okay, price tag for all three of 'em is a,
Lego built-- - It's a one-piece.
It's the three big bads from the original game
in a large display base.
Big, it's big, big.
- And like, it's pretty big, so a lot of pieces--
- It's big, it's a big set.
What is your price tag guess for this big Pokemon Lego set?
- $20. - I mean, it's gonna be--
- 20 bucks. - All right, all right.
Good guess, good guess.
I'm seeing $3.50, I'm seeing $4.95 in the scoop here,
in the chat. - $1,000 is guessed by Andy.
- $4.95, I think it'd be more than that.
- Dave Sorenson is-- - Is it limited?
Is it, are they only making blank amounts?
- No, it's not limited, no.
- Okay. - No.
- Oh, that is a great hat, Yarn and Sticks.
That is a great hat you just made.
That is a nice looking hat. - That's really cool.
That's really cool.
- I would pay-- - How much is it?
- I just, two birds for no reason.
I would pay three, oh, the whole hat is middle fingers.
It's a bunch of hat middle fingers.
- See, it fools you.
- Oh, that's a nice cozy hat to wear to a protest
at Minnesota right now.
Yeah, yeah, that's exactly it.
Okay, so I'm gonna guess that I would do
five Yarn and Sticks hats for that Pikachu.
- I mean, that's a good trade. - Oh, easy.
- I don't know what the little sets are going for.
No, the big set is actually priced to move at $650.
- God damn it. - Ooh.
- I know, and this is the thing, right?
Like, Pokemon is very much a kid-oriented brand,
or it was for a time. - Right, right.
- And Lego also kid-oriented brand for a time,
but this is a specific product based at adult collectors.
And so they even asked in like an AMA,
and people were like, "Is this a Lego set for kids?"
And they're like, "Nope, this is for adults."
Okay, so they acknowledged it at least.
- Adult collectors, yeah.
- No yucking, anyone's yum, no kink shaming, no whatever,
but if you bring a possible lover back to your house,
and they're gonna touch the thing,
you go, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, that was $650."
Like, I feel like the date is over.
- No, I think the date might be over if that's the reaction.
If you don't care that they touch your $650 Charizard,
I think that makes you cool.
- Oh, that was like, 'cause I have a Lego,
I have a Lego Batmobile on my bar at the house.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you're always going, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!"
- But like a friend, we had people over one day,
and one of our friends was over,
and they had one of their kids,
or they had their son here with them,
and their son was, of course, super polite kid, great kid,
young kid goes, "Can I play with the Batmobile on the bar?"
Of course, yeah, take it down, hand it to him,
put it on the floor, walk away.
I just got like some little moving parts and stuff on it,
and I come back over there a few minutes later,
and the kiddo and his dad are both there,
and the dad is holding the Batmobile,
and he goes, "He was twisting a thing in here,
and now it won't work to twist it anymore.
I think he might've broken it, so sorry."
I was like, "Please!"
I was like, "Oh, I freaked the fuck out."
I was like, "No, no, I'm not!
I'm very happy that your kid is playing with the Batmobile,
and I don't care if it's a Lego, it goes right together."
- Come here, kid, you broke my toy.
You broke my fucking toy.
- Okay, please, please do not think
that I'm doing the no, no, no thing on you.
Keep playing with it, I don't care, it's fine.
- It's fine, it's fine.
Here's a bill, you can pay in installments.
(laughing)
- I'll send you a Venmo request, it's not a big deal.
I mean, they're canceled, you can't get the new ones anymore,
but I think they still have some on eBay.
You know, it's big money, but you know, you can,
you can switch, you're gonna be all right.
- You're gonna be out like $1,200, something like that.
Well, that is the other thing, too, is, Matt,
you make the point, you know, of someone sees that
in a possible partner's living space.
- Yeah, yeah, a social situation.
- And what's their reaction?
But you have to also know that Lego, as an investment,
have appreciated at a rate greater than even gold,
and that is true.
The evaluation of Lego is greater even than gold in the last,
- I'll tell you what else is true.
- In the last like 15 to 20 years.
- And that is that this is at least the 20th time
Paul has told us this.
- No, no, maybe, maybe twice I've told you that.
(laughing)
- Let's do a little Jock vs. Nerd.
Who got a Jock vs. Nerd today from, oh shit, I can't see it.
- From Reisenberg, yeah.
- And it's all about 2025.
This is a scooperty in look back to the year 2025.
- I just want you to know,
before you get the cars, I want you to know that every time
Sarah and I take a call from a financial planner,
I always say, you have Lego in the portfolio?
And if they say no, I fucking hang up the phone every time.
- Hang right up, hang right up.
- I reiterate, I say, no, physical Lego.
I want you to buy sets and vault them for me, please.
(laughing)
Because that's where the fucking money is.
I don't care about their stock.
I want to be able to resell Animal Crossing Lego sets
in 25 years for 10 times their purchase price, thank you.
(laughing)
- The categories are sports, movies and TV, music, culture.
Matt, you're up first, what you want?
- I'll do sports for 200, please.
- This team won the WNBA Championship
for the third time in four years.
- That would be our own Las Vegas Aces.
- The Las Vegas Aces, of course.
(horn honking)
- Take that, Lombardo.
I don't know what that means.
- Stay down.
- Matt, I think he's happy about it, honestly.
- Oh yeah, good point.
- Seems like it's something he'd be happy about.
Paul.
- I'll try movies and TV, please.
- For 200, on February 16th, NBC aired a three-hour
live broadcast to celebrate this show's 50th anniversary.
(groaning)
- Oh, SNL.
- I was like, what are you doing?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, it's Saturday Night Live.
Saturday Night Live is the correct answer.
- I was trying to remember, I was like,
did they do a special on Good Morning America or some shit?
(laughing)
- The Simpsons.
- Yeah, well, the Simpsons is almost--
- I'll try culture for 200.
This numeric pair was Dictionary.com's Word of the Year.
- Really?
- I guess six, seven? - That's a Word of the Year?
It's gotta be.
- Yeah. - That's a Word of the Year?
- Yeah, six, seven.
I guess that's the Word of the Year.
- Man, in these strange times where 69 jokes
don't even get kids to raise an eyebrow anymore.
- Nope. - Nope, not a bit.
Not a bit. - Well, I mean,
it's all over the internet.
A 69 joke, that's just innuendo.
You go online, it's right there.
Ain't no jokes anymore.
- Ain't no jokes. - It's true.
- It's not, it's not. - Ain't no jokes.
- No, like, back in our day, it was like,
when you started to think about that,
you'd be like, "Oh, oh my God, the possibilities."
But if you're eight years old now,
you've seen every iteration possible.
- You're just, if somebody mentions 69 to you,
you're just thinking of the last porno
that you watched, were they 69?
- Exactly.
Exactly.
Exactly. - Matt, you're up.
- Sorry, I was just picturing my kids watching porn.
- Circles and circles. - Me too.
- Circles and circles.
They're just doing Illustrator and just drawing it.
(laughing)
- Can you imagine that powerful?
- Photoshop away from them.
- If we could actually just draw something
that we would get off on, that'd be pretty great.
- You can't?
You can't do that?
- No.
- Oh. - No.
- Sorry, you guys don't have that superpower.
- That's why Paul's Christmas book is so sticky.
- Every woman I draw just looks at me like I'm ugly
and I lower myself as two.
(laughing)
- Oh.
- I'll take sports 400, please.
- This man won the third annual Las Vegas Grand Prix,
winning the race for the second time.
- Third annual.
- Gros. - Joe Lombardo.
- This is Nevada's own Joe Lombardo.
This is Max Verstappen.
- Verstappen!
- That's right.
- Max Verstappen.
- Paul.
- Max Verstappen up.
Movies and TV, please.
- For 400, this Canadian sports romance television series
is the surprise hit of the 2025 holiday season.
- Oh.
Oh.
- Canadian sports romance television series
is in quotes, by the way.
- Yeah.
Heated rivalry.
- Oh.
- I was about to say-- - Heated rivalry.
- I was about to say hot on the ice,
but I knew that wasn't it.
- It wasn't hot on the ice.
- I was--
- Hot ice equals water.
- Icy hot, icy hot.
- Icy hot.
- Broke back goons.
Holy shit. - Broke back goonin'.
- Broke back goonin'.
That has a double meaning. - Oh, that broke Paul's camera.
- That has a double meaning.
- Sorry, I just drew something I found very alluring.
- Oh, sure, you gotta take care of that.
- I have to tend to this raging boner
that I just induced with the cartoon I made.
- I'll do movies and TV for 600.
This movie took home five Oscars,
including best picture at the 2025 Academy Awards.
- Oh, man.
- Fuck. - I'm laughing, I know.
It's like we just don't give a shit about the Oscars anymore.
- Fuck.
I have no idea.
Not even a little bit of an idea.
I will pass.
Matt. - Man, I'm mad.
I even listen to like a Showbiz podcast
when they go over this stuff.
I know I'll know it when I hear it.
- I work in show business.
- I know show business.
I know Oscar.
- I'm Murray Maloof.
I should know this. - Oscar Goodman.
- I probably produced it.
Fuck, pass. - I'm here to kidnap you.
- Well, damn it.
Pass, I'm gonna kick myself, but pass.
- Paul. - Five Oscars this thing won.
- Including best picture.
- Well, what even came out last year?
- I don't know, man. - I just go,
I only see movies that my kids wanna see.
- It's just Citizen Kane over and over again.
- "Titanic Reboots" is Leon Kasov.
- I don't even, like, it wasn't--
- "Avatar 3."
- I mean--
- Oh, I know it now, but I can't remember the name.
- Do you?
I'm trying to think if there was even any--
- So you don't know it.
- Any prestige type movies.
- No, it wasn't prestige.
- It wasn't?
- That's a different movie.
It's about magic.
- Oh, was it? - Oh, was it?
- It's the stripper, the Russian stripper,
the stripping Russian mafia movie.
- Oh, I don't even know what that is.
- Me either. - Pass.
- Let's see what it is.
What is it, Matt?
- I'm trying to remember the name of it,
but I know the first name of the actor,
Enora, that's it, yeah, yeah. - Enora.
Enora.
- Ignora.
- This Enora is what I did to that movie.
- I did.
- Matt!
How the fuck does that,
I didn't even know that movie existed.
- Here's the thing.
Not only is it an Oscar,
it's about a stripper who gets wrapped up
with the Russian mob.
It checks all of my boxes,
and I still haven't watched it.
I still haven't--
(laughing)
- An Oscar-winning movie about a Russian stripper
and the mob.
- It checks all of your boxes-- - Where have I been?
- It checks all of your boxes,
or it rushes all of your boxes.
(laughing)
- It Ukraine's all of his boxes.
You crane your neck to see an Enora.
- It two-knuckles all of my boxes.
- Oh, two-knuckle!
Oh, the country of two-knuckle.
(laughing)
- Matt, you're up.
- Sorry I hurt your Lego sculpture,
in two-knuckle we'd be aggressively pet sculptures.
- That's where Balky's cousins come from.
He's from two-knuckle.
I am from two-knuckle.
- Sports for 600, please.
- This basketball star was named Time Magazine's
2025 Athlete of the Year.
- Tiger, tiger, tiger woods, y'all.
- Barani James.
- Barani James?
Dio?
- Barani James.
- Oh, Barani James.
- And Roddy James Dio, of course.
- Both are--
- Roddy James Dio.
- Both are as good at playing basketball.
(laughing)
- Stay down, Roddy James Dio.
- He will.
- You're not good at basketball.
- He will stay down.
He is dead as Dillinger.
- I am debating, you know, it could be Luca.
It could be--
- Uh-huh, she lived on the second floor.
- Yeah, second floor, Luca.
- She lived upstairs from you.
- It should be, she killed Luca Alexander,
but will Time, like do you know what I mean?
Like, Time doesn't, like, if it was a true sports magazine--
- Was it Kobe?
- That's GA.
- Did they go Kobe?
Did they go like, salute your shorts?
- If they went to any card collection convention,
then it's still Kobe.
Kobe still rules at--
- Kobe's the hot card collectible now, huh?
- Yeah, always.
- Hotter than Jordan.
- I'm gonna go with Jake Eldridge to Alexander.
No, wait, no, wait, no, wait.
- Okay, but--
- It's Caitlin Clark.
- There it is.
Ah, Aja Wilson of the Las Vegas Aces.
- Oh, well, good, that's actually well-deserved.
She's a three-time MVP.
I actually--
- Apologies to Aja for not knowing that.
- I actually forgot to ask, I wanted a jersey of hers
for Christmas, and I should have asked for it.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, you don't get what you don't ask for, Matt.
- That's true, that's true.
- I just looked online, it's $650.
(laughing)
- That is pricey.
- VIP.
- You get at least one Lego set for that.
Paul!
- Almost.
Movies and TV closing it out.
- This movie generated the highest domestic gross
of any film released in 2025,
taking in $423,949,195.
- What was the big wiener?
- Anora.
- No, I guess it's gotta been,
the Oz movie, right?
Wicked 4 Good?
- Wait, careful with your subtitles.
- Wicked 4 Good is the new one.
- Yeah.
- As the other one was still going on in 2025?
Was that both?
- No, I think the other one was released in '24.
I think the first Oz movie was '24.
- Yeah, I'll pass, 'cause I really don't know for sure, so.
- Oh, shit, that goes to me.
I thought it was the new Avatar movie.
- You might be right.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think that's the one it is.
- Ash and Fire and Ash?
- Yeah, the new Avatar, Fire and Ash.
- Did that come out last year?
Or was that just--
- It came out in December.
- Did it, okay.
- Yeah.
I'll guess that one.
Avatar 3.
No, we're all wrong.
It's a Minecraft movie.
- Oh, we all forgot about the Chicken Jockey fiasco.
- Yep.
- Fiasco?
- Yeah, whenever Chicken Jockey showed up on the screen,
everybody would lose their shit and trash the theater.
- Yeah, that sounds like a wonderful artistic event.
- I mean, it sounds a bit like Rocky Horror Picture Show,
so I can't, I don't hate it.
- Right.
- Oh, it's me, I'll do sports for 800.
This player won the 2025 Heisman Trophy.
If this is Paul, name any active college football player.
(laughing)
- I would still not be able to do it.
I would not be able to do it.
I have cut football out of my brain.
- And this is college football.
- I know, and that's an even less thing.
- Yeah.
He just won the Heisman.
He plays for Indiana.
He's probably gonna play for the Raiders next year.
Do I have to give his first name?
Can I just give his last name?
- I'll give you points for his last name.
- All right, Mendoza.
- Mendoza.
- Yeah, Fernando Mendoza.
- You forgot Fernando.
- I forgot Fernando.
- That's the enemy of McBain.
- Look, we should all get to know that name.
He's going to be playing here.
So we need to--
- Yeah, he's gonna be in the silver and black next year.
- Mendoza.
- Matt, you're up.
- I need to make up some points here, yeah?
- Oh yeah, score check.
Well, we're all pretty close.
Paul's got 600, I've got 200, Matt has zero.
There's still two daily doubles left out there
and seven questions.
Anybody's game.
- Well, you know me and culture.
Let's do culture. - It's true.
- How can there be any answers in 2025?
There was no culture in 2025.
- This power couple announced their engagement
with the tagline, your English teacher
and your gym teacher are getting married.
- This is Travis Kelsey and Paula Abdul.
- Ah, yes.
- Travis Kelsey and Taylor Swift.
- That's right.
I did not know that.
I didn't hear that quote.
Paul.
- It was dumb then, it's dumb now.
- Yep, music for 200, please.
- All right, daily double.
- Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
- Gonna give Paul some distance.
- This performer was Spotify's most streamed artist
of 2025, dethroning Taylor Swift.
- Ooh.
- YouTubers CG5.
- Who beat Taylor Swift for streams?
Oh my goodness.
- I find out that The Weeknd just snuck in there
and had so many streaming listens
that we just didn't know about.
I mean, no, that wouldn't, no.
- I would think maybe Charli XCX,
but that was 2024 when she was rocking up on it.
And I don't think she ever dethroned Taylor Swift.
- There are two prominent guesses in the chat
since this is a daily double and you have to guess.
Some people are saying Sarah Carpenter
because of the popularity of Stranger Things,
and other people are saying Bad Bunny.
- Oh, it's Bad Bunny.
- That's my guess.
- It's Bad Bunny.
- My guess is Bad Bunny.
- Yeah, he's big, big, big.
Bad Bunny.
- Yeah, yeah, you going Bad Bunny?
- I am.
- Let's see.
It is Bad Bunny.
- Yeah, what up, Doc?
- Yeah, I was like, I bet that the whole Super Bowl
controversy really got him a lot of listeners.
- Apparently he's really, really good, so.
- Oh no, he's fantastic, of course.
- Might have also exposed some racism in this nation.
- Oh, what?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- Look, let's just eat regular hamburger buns
and talk about it.
- When you say this nation, you mean this one?
- This nation?
Where in my own citizenship might be in jeopardy?
What are you talking about?
- I'm just going to ignore Matt
and whatever craziness he's talking about
and just move on to culture for 600.
- God damn it.
- Andy Byron and Kristin Cabot are best known
for the role they played in this 2025 event.
Andy Byron?
Shit, I don't know.
Pass, Matt.
- Andy Byron and Kristin Cabot?
- I said Cabot, but I don't know.
C-A-B-O-T.
- This is culture.
- The role they played in this event.
- New Year's Eve?
- I know, that's what I'm like.
- The West Virginia State House elections.
- Pass.
- Paul.
- A pass.
- Let's see.
Coldplay kiss cam couple.
- Oh, yes.
- Infamous, infamous Coldplay kiss cam couple.
Matt.
- Infamous.
- Culture 800, please.
- Let's see.
After thieves stole $102 million in jewels
from the Louvre in Paris, France,
it was reported the password
for the museum surveillance system was blank.
- Damn it.
I knew all the factors that laid out in the question.
And then I knew it was jewels the amount in the Louvre,
but the password. - I think that's it, Matt.
- Oh, password?
- No. - It was password?
- No.
- The jewels?
- Well, it might be password.
It's either password or Louvre, I think.
- Ah.
- That's it.
That's it as the password.
- No, I think it's Louvre.
Or password, it's one or the other.
- I'll pass, you can take them all the money.
- Paul.
- No, I don't want to try and guess, I don't know.
I think it's the Louvre, but I'm not 100% now.
Now you got me guessing.
I think it was Louvre.
- It was sticky.
You're going Louvre?
- It was sticky cheese because the I was a one
and the E's and the cheese were three.
- Let's see, it's Louvre.
- I heard it was the Louvre.
That's why I gave you, I told Matt it was the Louvre.
- Paul, you got music for four, six, or 800.
One of them's a daily double and that one could fuck you up.
- It could fuck me up.
I guess I might as well go out big with 800, please.
- Music for 800.
In May 2025, the song "Wasted Love"
performed by JJ and written by him
along with Todora Spierich and Thomas Turner
won the Eurovision Song Contest for which country?
- Oh, that's, oh, shoot.
Who won the Eurovision, I don't pass, I don't know.
- Oh, that passes to me.
There was a large amount of conversation this year
about Eurovision at work with all of the Europeans
and everybody that I worked with.
- Was there really?
- There was a ton of conversation about this event.
I didn't listen to any of it.
Pats, Matt.
- I also did not follow the story at all.
Birdie, birdie, bird, bird, bird is my final answer.
Pass. - Good.
Austria, that's right, I do remember that.
- Austrian went yodeling.
- That's right.
It's me, I got music for 400 or 600.
Matt has 400, I have 200.
Paul has 2000, so I'm probably not gonna catch Paul.
Let's see, I'll try to get some points on Matt here
and get second place.
Music for 600.
Name any of the eight artists that were nominated
for best new artist at the 2025 Grammy Awards.
Shit.
Is my answer to that question.
- Ice Spice.
- I don't think that's even this year.
- Um, jeesh.
Yeah, I don't know.
Pass, Matt.
- I don't know.
- Paul.
- Pass.
- Chappell Rhone was this year?
Oh, motherfucker.
Benson Boone, Sabrina Carpenter.
Oh, this is all, I would have thought
that several of those--
- Well, that's 'cause the Grammys
are behind the fucking time.
- I was gonna say,
Sabrina Carpenter's been around for a minute.
- Yeah, that's--
- Dochey's been around for a minute.
- I feel better about not getting this question right now.
- Yeah, you do.
- At least most of the--
- Teddy Swims, yeah, he, oh no.
- We're back from our technical problem.
Oh yeah, none of us guessed on that one.
Paul or Matt, closing out the category end of the game.
Paul is definitely winning
and Matt is gonna probably get second place.
It's a daily double.
- We'll have to get this so I get third place.
So there's stakes here.
- Oh, that's true.
Yeah, we got stakes.
This song began 2025 at number one
on the Billboard Hot 100 and fun fact,
it is also the number one song
on the day I am writing this scooperty, 12/10/25.
- That's not a helpful hint at all.
- Well, it means it was number one
for either a long time or twice.
- Billboard Hot 100.
- Oh, I know it.
- Is this a Sabrina Carpenter song?
- I don't think so.
I think this is a song that comes around in December.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Amy Winehouse's, no.
(laughing)
- Amy Winehouse's.
They try to make me go to rehab
And I say Merry Christmas
- Oh God.
- I can go to rehab.
I gotta wrap presents and no, no, no.
(laughing)
Mariah Carey's "All I Want for Christmas".
- "All I Want for Christmas" is you, Matt Donnelly.
- I'm so proud of you.
- That's right.
And that is the game.
Paul wins with 2,000 points.
Matt's insane with 800.
I'm in third with 200.
That's from Rum Raisenberg
and that was 2025 in retrospective.
- That's a great scooperty.
Good job.
- Nicely done, Rum Raisenberg.
- How much we don't remember.
But you know, like, you know, maybe.
- I'm a little embarrassed that I've never heard
of the best picture winner.
- That's, you know.
- I hadn't heard of it either.
That's disheartening.
- Although I'm not as embarrassed as they should be.
- Well, "20/20 After" was famously,
and this is why I listen to my showbiz podcast,
is that like, was famously hampered by the,
this is still the echoes of the writer's strike,
or the actor's strike.
- Oh, right.
- So they couldn't get enough stuff into production.
So movie theaters were pissed
about how little product was coming to the pipeline in 2025.
It was a bad year for TV too.
It just like, everything was so delayed
from all the strikes.
- Great year for Keeler though.
Pluribus is just taking off.
He's doing great.
- I see Paul Chamberlain up there.
I don't know if I gave Paul a full proper shout out,
but I had a corporate gig in South Bend,
and he basically lives, he lives in South Bend.
Not basically, he lives in South Bend.
But he basically stepped up as my advance man.
He helped get stuff to the venue that needed to be.
He was there at the venue before I got there.
He introduced himself to the person running the venue,
and like, he had me all set up.
I like walked in, and everything was like set up for me,
because Paul did everything, and it was really great.
It was awesome, and just--
- Oh, awesome.
- Further proof that just our podcast audiences are amazing.
So there you go.
- Yeah, we have the best listeners.
- He'd been in the turn with his son before,
so that was very nice to see him again.
- Yeah.
Speaking of our listeners,
that scooperty was from a listener.
If you wanna make a scooperty
or any kind of other jock versus nerd
that we do on this show,
heyscoops.com is where you can go.
Head over to heyscoops.com.
You could also send us some scoop mail from that page.
Do all the things over there at heyscoops.com.
Do it now! - Please!
- And I wanna thank the following people
who support us over on our Patreon page.
- Let's do it.
- I wanna thank the following-- - Yes!
- These people all bought Lego back
when you just buy a pair of socks for Lego,
and now can't believe how much it's worth today.
That's Aaron Boyd, Aaron Abe Sloan, Adam Goff, Adam Ribzik.
Yep, you nailed it.
And then Adam Stickney, Alex Moorhead,
Anarko Scoopo, Andrea Anderson, Andrew Langmead,
Andrew Ossichuk, Andy Hayworth, Angela Chan, Anne Smith,
Anton Jernberg, Amaris, nope, Aramis.
That's it, Aramis Saar, Barry Rowe, Bart Vonk,
BJ Joyer, and Ben Gao.
Thank you so much.
- These people have a SIM card corruption error.
Ben Sherman, big load of scoop. - I don't know.
- Big sexy butters, Bill Newton,
Black People Escape, Bo Campbell, Bobby Becerra,
Brendan Light, Brendan Allen, Brian Emrah,
Brian Galuta, Brian Lehman, Brian Richard, Brian T. Wolf,
Brian Gregsten, Brian Traves, Bullscoop, Cali Ghost,
Carmen Perry, Carolyn Albert, and Carson Lomas.
- And the following scoops are Americans,
and that's why they like their bread white.
- That's Cavan O'Hara, Chaotic Clumsy, Charles Eaton,
Charles Ullman, Charlie Thompson, Chris DiPero,
Chris Ellis, Chris Hofzetter, Chris Jackson, Chris Roberts,
Chris the Microscoop, Christine Phillips,
Christopher Hayworth, Christopher Scalinda, I think,
CJ Magnata, Coffee Bean Scoop, Corey Owens,
Corey Anichimora, Court Myers, Crock-a-Dunk Scoop,
and Daniel Lozer, thank you so much.
- That's it, Jacob, it's a little,
Dexfield a little shy over here, are we sure?
We have a lot of people to thank.
- I was about to say, we have new list stuff going on,
we have new stuff going on from Patreon.
I am looking into it.
This list feels light.
- Oh yeah, bud.
- Yeah, it's light.
No, I was looking at it yesterday, and yeah, yeah.
But yeah, we're gonna figure all this out.
- We'll get there.
- If you're new, or if you haven't been around
for an episode or two, Annie is no longer with us.
Our longtime Patreon-- - She's alive, she's alive.
She's alive. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's not with us, she's with us, capital U.
She's not with us, lowercase U.
(laughing)
Yeah, yeah, no, but she's been with us for years and years.
We love Annie, but she has moved on.
And yeah, so we are figuring out new lists
and all of that stuff on our own now
with Slaking Fool's help as well.
So yeah.
- Yeah, so we'll keep--
- But yeah, we're gonna get it all figured out,
and yeah, it'll all be there.
It'll all get put together.
- If you wanna be part of the exclusive technical error
thank you lists for this month,
then you wanna get over to preachingfund.com.
It's like the tier that fits your budget today.
(upbeat music)
Come visit preachingfund.com
It's better than hanging with your mom at a deep end
- Or if you, like Matt Donnelly,
are buying eight different types of hamburger buns
to feed his family, go to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts
Farts in a bag.biz
- That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfund.com,
it does take you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as $3 a month
you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon subscribers.
So please, if you think this show is worth more than $0,
preachingfund.com, fartsinabag.biz,
that's where you can go.
I'm just still, it's just rattling around in my head.
Like how many different types of hamburger buns
does Matt have right now?
- It really throws people for a loop, right?
Where I go, I'm making barbecue burgers.
What kind of bun do you want?
How do you take your bun?
How do you take your bun? - Bun?
- Yeah. - How do you take your bun?
- How do I take my bun?
- It's gonna be just beef and cheese.
- Now beyond that, is there preparation to the bun?
Do you offer grilling or toasting?
- I toast the bun on the grill.
- Yeah, that's the best. - Shay Donnelly
has a great many amenities.
- I was gonna grill the bun.
I've grilled the buns in the past,
but I realized I'm like, I don't wanna get my kids
in the habit of having extra butter and cholesterol
on their already cheesy burger, so.
- Do you stir or steam the buns?
- Toast the buns is enough.
- What are you talking about?
Don't get them in the habit of having delicious food.
You don't wanna ruin their palates.
Is that it?
You wanna keep them American?
- He don't wanna shovel butter and salt
into their mouth all the time,
which does make him less American.
- It does, it does.
But to quote Jeff Goldblum, "Butter finds a way."
- Butter does find a way.
- All right, thanks folks, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
- Yes. - We'll see you soon.
(upbeat music)
- See you at the cone.
- Hickey Buns Donnelly.
- That's what we're gonna call the kids today.
- I'm not seeing them.
- Say, "What's up, Hickey Buns?"
(laughing)
- Start calling Hilly Hickey Buns, see what he does.
- I hear you like a specific type of hamburger bun,
young Donnelly.
- It is blatantly, egotistically,
I'm trying to compete with like In-N-Out
and like other fast food.
- Have you bested those other fast food places
thus far?
- I want them to say, I'm gonna say,
"Hey, why don't I make burgers tonight?"
And I want the kids to go, "Oh, awesome."
You know what I mean?
Like that's the goal.
- Instead of, "Why don't we go out for burgers?"
- That's it, I'm trying to go like,
"Or we go to In-N-Out," is the other thing
that can pop up, right?
So that's what I don't want.
- Well, so far, you've got him to say,
"I demand pretzel or don't serve me that French shit."
So you're halfway there.
(laughing)
- Progress.
- I'm gonna do basically a bun flight next time.
We'll just do-
- A bun flight!
(laughing)
Here are sir's choices for the evening.
Please make your selection
and I will go back to the kitchen.
(laughing)
And do what I find.
- This one is awfully yeasty.
- Yeah, I know, yeah.
- You've got a costume to these buns here.
Don't jump right into this yeasty mess.
- This is real yeasty.
This one's real yeasty, careful.
Careful, Hill, too much yeast.
This is-
- Now this one is whole grain over here.
- This one-
- You don't wanna jump straight to whole grain either.
- This is from an artisanal sourdough starter
that began in 1874.
You believe that?
- Which is almost as old as your mom.
- You are tasting revolutionary bread, basically.
(laughing)
- Bye.