Oh
Hello there, I didn't see you there, but I'm so happy you're here
I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers
I'm recording this episode in the past, so I don't have a new list yet
But thank you to each and every ice cream truck driver out there who knows by the time this goes out
I might have added the ice cream truck driver names in
Knows anything anymore. I think we should maybe do that for these day. Yeah, we're gonna try and do that
We're never gonna try and do that if you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I hope you do preaching fun dot coms
We can go preaching fun.com head over there sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows the life you save
Maybe your own
Here's a program hey Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah? I'd love to great
Let's go appear guys, and I'm sweaty. I'm fresh for my kids Christmas
70s out there is it oh, it's it's obviously too warm
It's time for that Maddly's ice cream social sitting over there a sweaty pool of his own mess
That's Matt Donnelly singing Pittsburgh. It's automatically in Vegas. It's me Jacob the audio guy. We're preaching fun
Yeah, this is week
Three for me where we've had snow and I can't go out
It's fucking freezing cold, and I can't go out and clean up the backyard from the dog poop and with four dogs
Pooping all the time. It's a lot of dog poop
And so when I go out to do anything in the yard like change up bird seed or anything that Anne needs me to do
So I try to stay the hell out of the backyard when there's nothing but dog poop, and it's freezing
I have to come back in and spend another ten minutes cleaning my shoes off from all the skank that gets on my shoes
I'm trying super careful. I try to dodge it like landmines. I can't miss it
If you have there's an amount of dog poop in your backyard that it is impossible for you to walk around it
It's close because they like that area that leads right up to always one spot. It's kind of makes more kind of a zone
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay. No the entirety of my backyard is not filled with dog shit
I'm like, holy Jesus man. How often are you cleaning? I'm cleaning every week, but this is two weeks in a row
I haven't been able to so right. It's a lot. It's a backup, but it's also frozen
So what are you gonna do? I got to invest in some new fucking boots
But yeah here I am start a business of frozen dog poop pickup for other people's houses
Gross. Yeah. No, thanks. Did I tell you guys actually had a couple kids come by?
Back when we got our first like three inch hit and they just rang the doorbell. Hey, can we clean your driveway off?
Yeah, I'll give you a three inch hit right now. They said can we clean your driveway off for a little bit of money?
I said hey house 20 bucks. They're like, let's get it. Let's do it and they did it and it saved my fucking hole
It's like this is amazing. This is the
America I'm telling you this is what it's all about. But here I am
Freezing my took us off and then I read Vegas is having record high temperatures. Oh record highs
Yes, so while you're in the middle of a triple volt
polar vortex yes is
Which is a very rare event, but it's caused all of the Arctic atmosphere to moot descend upon your your town
Descend upon rural, Pennsylvania. We are slowly building an El Nino over here
Which is creating warming temperatures and bringing them over here to create one of the most warm and dry
Decembers in Vegas history. Yeah, it's the combo you want. Yeah
So this this Saturday love it dry El Nino or El Nino. I forget which one creates it warm El Nino
Versus the polar vortex the battle for the century
Let's go
Warm and dry was actually the original name of Matt Mattingly and it is the primary designation for the kind of sex robot
You want that is, you know, the first and foremost is it warm and dry?
just torso and
Torso warm and dry torso by Matt. I
Just I just got back from my kids Christmas concert, and I say concert because basically say my air quotes
yes, because this is a music program and
a couple things one is that this year out of nowhere someone started a
Cheerleading program at the school to teach kids how to cheer. I
Thought you're gonna during the showcase. There was some kind of weird
We're sitting there. Go music. Go music go music. I don't know
So that's it. So they never have had a cheerleading program before no, no, no, but it's important to teach
Coeds first through fifth grade. I believe it was all girls in it. I did not see a boy in it
They were gonna they were gonna make it coed, but they decided that Matt's son would be too good
Another thing as soon as they say they didn't want to well Keillor's the kid cheer captain now, right? I mean that's that's cool
He was going up on you Paul Keillor's growing up on you, buddy
He's not in that school anymore. Keillor's gonna come back and be the coach. He's in a different school
Yeah, oh no, baby's baby's getting old I got it wrong as that yeah La Nina not El Nino
Yeah, is that a
Directional wind declination. What's the difference? I'll give you a directional wind
Is a Madonna title, right? Yeah, it's like El Nino. Yeah
and so before
Before the concert was to begin we had to do 15 minutes of just watching them do cheers for cheering sake
Do cheering was it at least Christmas theme cheers? Nope
You just watched children just go like yo be aggressive be
Aggressive. Yes
Like just watch that for 15 minutes. I would categorize this as like a sneak attack, right? Like the parents are gathered
Yeah, no one knows about this truly program of audience
This is a violation of the Geneva Convention and then I'm like, but I got you guys all hyped up right? I mean
Sweaty right I said I spent walk 25 minutes home. I was so pumped. I
Think this thing is working
Yeah, no, you're right. You're right. Cuz basically once once that bumped the concert time. I was like, well now
I'm not gonna make ice cream social on time
I was like basically I waited the one part that I knew my kid had
Watched it and was like snuck out the back and then great was like I'm gonna walk home so that my wife can see
The whole thing. Uh-huh
It took me a really long time to figure out that your text said that you were that you had to ditch your wife
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it didn't say you had to ditch your wife. It said he had to I know I
Know that was it. That's yeah
That's why I'm so happy for your wife. And that's why I put exclamation points because he said you had to dick Sarah
Oh my goodness
Sorry, I'm running late getting back the concert ran long I had dick Sarah we understand me right there
Context clues, but it's still very funny
Yeah, I even put a capital D on there look at that
You put a capital D on that all the marriage is anything like mine when that happens it's capital D that kind of day I
Mean we're getting close to the holidays so we're due, but we'll see
Is your birthday that's fucking great. Yes, so
Who am I kidding everyone goes over the holidays we can't but
But
So then they go to this this music program right where they they sing some songs, but then they also do this thing
This is like some innovation. They had a few years ago and what happens is they do like a creative writing
storytelling time you
So then they select like three or four, I guess I don't know ten just it felt like it felt like a million
But I stayed for four
These stories that the kids have written together
There are Christmas themed stories and all the instruments on stage instead of creating songs for the Christmas concert
creates sound effects for the
Oh, that's the worst
Terrible, I'm watching some avant-garde children's foley exercise. Do they intentionally add lots of sound effects to the stories?
See I did this as a little kid I think I've told you guys this before my dad wrote a program on our Atari 400
That was sound effects
Okay, and you can play all kinds of different sound effects through the program
Yeah, and so I recorded myself a story about mr. T and Lee majors going to space
Yes, and I used all those sound effects as a young aspiring radio guy and Foley artist myself
Well, don't get me wrong. I loved doing Foley stuff too, and I liked doing it with friends as well
I don't think it should be done for
200 parrots
But I'm sure the comedy and timing of it was just spot-on
And I don't know if maybe seven demos is worth the idea of showing off this Foley expertise
Down to one or two of the best ones and then present those seven different stories
Yeah, well, they did more how long a story I did I did they're like five minutes six minutes
What yes, that's not no you do a story by cheer a story that a cheer a story than a cheer break it up
Figure it out. Nope
Three Christmas songs and seven stories. That's what you get here Christmas songs. What were the Christmas songs negotiation went worse than Ukraine in Russia
Well, it's okay Israel's gonna pay for it. That's right, huh?
Yeah, what were the Christmas? Oh, well first like Oh Christmas tree
Okay, Christmas tree wasn't owned honing ball. I have issues with Oh Hanukkah Oh Hanukkah
Let's light the menorah that song wait at what they do a version of Christmas tree. That's Oh Hanukkah
There's another song called like Oh Hanukkah Hanukkah. We'd like the menorah
Hanukkah you guys don't even know the song I'm talking about. No, no, okay
I think this is a children's school song that has that has come up to
Include everybody it's abominable. I
mean like the snowman it is like it seems like it was in inspired by someone like
fever fever chopping wood
It was like the melody they came up with for it was like chop chop chop chop chop chop chop. No
And and I guess it's like the first songs that was like a first included but like everyone Christian schools
Like I guess we have to sing Hanukkah songs
And they've included this about it. Leanne can stop and chat. Yes. This is about Israel
Listen you can't say that the Jewish people run show business and then also put out that terrible song. You can't have it both ways
Either you're in charge of everyone's beautiful music career. You can come up with a better melody then
Than that there there are there are other beautiful Hanukkah. They just don't want Mariah Carey running away with all the publishing rights
But yeah, so
It's it's it's it's a terrible song and they sing it or I guess yell it or shout it
It doesn't there's no way to unshout it. It's just shouting
It's and do they play instruments to where the kids just sing it they play instruments, too
Okay, that makes it worse. It does make it worse and yeah
And and like it might as well like be done to like like the Ramones like they might as well have like a punk drummer
just driving they don't do like klezmer and and
Juice harp and all that kind of thing. They have every instrument out there Paul. I don't know if they're all done in a way
That makes it satisfying to the year
Authentically Jewish in nature of these there's marimbas and chimes and wood instruments and all kinds of stuff out there. It's a couple laptops
Try to get all Beastie Boys on it
Laptops going on
They're running tape. He got straight-up DJs DJs on the wheels of steel the ones and twos. Yep
but I
Was like what kind of avant-garde artsy shit am I watching?
There is nothing that makes me want to have kids less than than children's musical events. Oh, I
Know it's the worst dance concerts concert concerts all of it. It's just terrible
Oh, this is and this is just this is just for the parents people who don't have kids won't get this but
Going to see different productions kids productions is torture enough
But if you kind of don't plan it correctly and you don't realize it, but you go in the last one. Oh
It's a huge mistake
What do you mean at the end of the last one? They're gonna get up and start thanking all the people that helped out and put in
So you stay for an extra half hour 45 minutes of terrible? Thank you speeches that mean absolutely nothing to you. Yeah
it is just
It is it is not
But a huge thank you to dr. Stevens dr. Stevens, which are you here? Are you here? Dr. Stevens?
Ladies and gentlemen, dr. Stevens came to the children
Three times a week for the last five weeks to help them prepare this side, right? Yeah, let's hear it for dr. Stevens
When I asked dr. Stevens originally, could you help us learn how to sing this song? He said yes
He did his hey, baby aggressive dr. Stevens be
Team go go go. Hey, where's my let's bring out my instrument people. Let's do our dr. Stevens medley that we came up with
Dr. Stevens
You help us learn that song is frightening my cat through my headphones
Because it was so good. Yeah. Oh
Look at that scared cat is scaredy cat
Which one is that speech or smokes? It's the smokes the dirty smokes the dirty dukes
I'll tell you who else is gonna rub that dirty cat in Matt's lap
And that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by
the fine people purveyors cat butthole in my face
Yep, there's just a cat but we can just see the tail sticking up. There's just clearly a cat butthole in your face
It's really throwing this is why you should join us the bucket show
This is
Bizarro worlds ice cream social today shows brought to you by Bizarro worlds ICS
Hello me I'm Jacob me like me like Paul jokes
Yeah
Me have more Paul jokes
Lined up and ready here more Paul jokes now
Me agree with Paul, yep. Oh
Paul always right Paul always right in Bizarro ICS
One percent totally one percent
Paul love Elon Musk
Oh
Huge Tesla guy. Oh
Those things are terrifying is terrifying all this shit is terrifying
Cars are coming to kill us all. Oh
That's probably fine. No, I don't think it is. Well, I got sick
Yesterday I went into work. I I got up and I wasn't I wasn't feeling good in the evening
and then I wasn't feeling good in the morning and I pushed myself to go on and head to work and
I drove to the end of our
Neighborhood and I paused for like 20 seconds and I almost just turned the car around because I was feeling so crappy and I was
Like no just go to work. Just do it
And I did it and then I was there for about 45 minutes and I started really feeling terrible
Like I was gonna pass out getting like cold sweats. I don't know. What was the food poisoning or something? I don't know
But I went I told him I gotta I gotta get out of here so I
Left yesterday and today
I stayed home today just to make sure I could get some rest and feel better and I do feel better
So no, it wasn't an Aldi hot dog this time Mike. So anyway yet
Yeah, I was like all the hot dogs chase any germs away. I was just beat and I needed a break
I've been doing just a lot. It's been busy
But Jeff Loomis in the chat is saying that you do look tired. I and and yeah, Jeff is right
Paul honestly looks like shit. He's sitting there and he just looks terrible
You should have seen me yesterday. I really did look I looked the site
I'm feeling a little bit better now, which is good. So it's got a two more days and then I can take a little break
I didn't want to say Haggard, but now that you brought it up
Call me Merle cuz I'm Haggard
That's a joke that everybody gets and dead Lazlo says I'm just sick of work I could sympathize and it's true
I am fucking sick of work
Work is awful
Especially worst time right here. You're in the height. You're in the height of it's it's crazy right now. Yeah, it's really crazy. But
Yeah, I just needed a fucking break. Oh, I need to go to the sweat house. That's right Leon. Well last night I
Was invited to City Cast Las Vegas is just a social
Community gathering nice. Oh, how nice and so they invited us out to a place called the crush pad
It's a gathering of podcasters. Just podcast listeners. Just just members. Oh members sponsoring members
And and so we were out of the crush pad and
The wine bar the wine bar and it was a delightful little wine bar met the owners
they had a tastings of
Four wines that were exquisite
Okay, and then I was laughing because I
also ordered a little a little prosciutto appetizer and then I went ahead and got myself a
Glass of their they have a chilled red house
wine
Nice and I was like, yeah, let's do that
And then the person in front of me ordered two glasses of wine and I got two raffle tickets
And then the person told me gave me their what gave me my wine and then walked away and I said
The fuck yeah, I said, excuse me. Do I get a raffle ticket and she did even like oh
You ordered the house
Wine so no. Oh
and I
Laughed what do you have to order to get a raffle to I have to really?
Was like I saved a few bucks by going with the house and then it's like when I give you a fucking tote bag
Don't you feel stupid after four bucks next time you cheapskate, huh? Yeah, it's Christmas season. Don't be a Scrooge get some good wine
Yeah
Then I laughed and then the person who ordered the wine said I didn't know
The rule so I didn't mean to walk you into that trap
So I said, okay and then out of guilt she's like never mind you can have but you can have a raffle
And she gave me the raffle ticket
And I'm talking to my friend there is
You know, we're so we're the social addicts. So the guy who walked me into that trap we joked and we
Set down with them. We had a little wine him and his wife two doctors in town and
And I said if I win this raffle, I I obviously will will refuse to take it
I will I will I'll yield it back to the story. I didn't qualify properly for it. I
Can't I can't possibly everyone know like any cheapskate can win one of those
What is that a coffee mug give me that give me that outrageous this is for people who won a good
Good cabernet. I'm sorry, sir. This is for customers not freeloaders
But I did I met the I also had another awkward interaction there I was there and I looked at this woman
Well, that's awkward and I looked at her name tag and I was like I said you'd look familiar and she goes shit
She got me like a weird look. She's like
What like what and I was like, I don't know. I was like basically like do you want to help me out here?
Kind of like do I familiar to you?
There's the regular dance of do I look familiar do it and she goes you're probably gonna say I look like a singer
I go. Oh, well, okay
I work in town, you know showbiz maybe maybe maybe she's cross paths and she goes yeah
No, I'm not that singer
And then like went away like half annoyed
And I
What a weirdy and I said like she went away is half of a Domino's advertisement from the 80s
The person next to me. I was like I didn't even bring up the singer part. She did
I only said yes to the singing part because I thought we were trying to figure out how we knew each other
I thought you were helping me out
He's like no, you just think every black woman's a singer go fuck yourself. You racist is basically what happened there
That's what it was. Yeah, so we did not hit it off. That was I
One strike on the socializing for the for the for the city cast Vegas outing there. Oh
That's and that is too bad because that is the person that we brought in today to interview for this. Hello. Hello miss
So you you met Matt Donnelly last night. Did you? Oh, no
Yes
And and you did not care for your interaction with Matt Donnelly
Hey, are we actually recording on this? Oh, we're recording right now, buddy
Okay, let's do this. I'm here. Am I sounding okay on this?
Beaming that's Rob. We're doing it. We're in the middle of a bit, but Rob Rob is here. Hey
Rob, I was just talking about being a city cast Las Vegas social gathering last night. We're already rolling
I know I could sense the excitement in your voice
Recalls the big event. That's what that was. I
Will say I'm gonna burn you guys right now
You guys handed out conversation starters last night to people as they walked in
We sure did and I am laughing because I have inside information on your company that you guys are allowed to be a little
Political, but you're not supposed to be like a politically leaning podcast organization, right?
We get feedback every now and then from upper management as well as the audience
What I like to say is city cast is for everyone if you love Las Vegas or love to trash Las Vegas either way
We have a home for you. Great officially. Welcome Rob from city cast Las Vegas. Thank you
And hey Las Vegas newsletter editor and I appear occasionally on the podcast
Yeah, just to clarify absolutely great job on both your newsletter is outstanding. I think you did an amazing newsletter
I think some of my favorite things that you guys make the Nevada Independent and the Las Vegas Review Journal look like
You might as well just light dog poop on fire and ring their doorbells. You're embarrassing them. You are embarrassing them
Well, we link to them sometimes. Yeah, we got we got a tip ahead to them
you know, we just kind of like to collect what everyone's talking about add a little bit of our own stew to the mix and
or mix to the stew your way, but it's we slide into your inbox at 6 a.m
every morning and give you a quick look at what's going on in Vegas. So here is the
Everyone loves Las Vegas icebreaker. You guys hated me when I came with a party last night. Okay, great
What's should we should we have the conversation based on this card now?
This card says what's your ethical responsibility as a citizen when you believe your country is acting immorally. That's your casual
Icebreaker for me to just talk to any citizen of Las Vegas
That is a little few people
That's a literal icebreaker
Has to switch out today. Ah
Some did yes, I don't want to talk about nature Rob. This doesn't have to be a God chosen journalism moment, but this has David Figgler written
All over it. This is Figgler all over it. I
Think it was more like we have what we call a membership team
Helps us organize these events because it was for city cast neighbors. That's our membership group. That's right
And you know, we were kind of worried, you know, cuz some of these people, you know, they want to get out and about they want
To meet new people so we don't want it to be, you know awkward
So sometimes, you know, we had a couple games out like you know and stuff
But nobody even had to open them because everyone was naturally organically making conversation and mingling
so it's true the icebreaker card was part of that and I think a few people used it but not everybody did but it's a
Good way just to welcome people and get them thinking about something straight off the bat. It was it was a
It was a landmine and the people that I met but yeah, we moved on anyway
So you did get some Intel and asked the question to it. I did I did I did fitting off with the with two doctors
Let's let Daniel and Christine. I think
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah, they're doctors and
I'll vouch for them. Yeah. Yeah, and they did it
There I just say yes, I mean if we're not for your newsletter Rob
I wouldn't know things like the Taco Bell ultra run which is coming up in a couple of weeks here
Actually, it's coming up Saturday Saturday. Oh, it's the Saturday. All right
Where people run from Summerlin to Henderson and stop by seven Taco Bells and have to eat a Taco Bell menu item at each
One of the things we do at City Cast Vegas is we do events we compile events and it's kind of like a guide to
The week and I was coming across this thing called the Taco Bell ultra marathon
I'm like that looks boring some another marathon sponsored by some
Corporate entity and then I looked at it and this isn't sponsored by anybody at all. This isn't
Roots thing that a person came up with who was in an organization here locally called
I believe the Las Vegas slow runners. So, you know, there are people who want to be out and about but it's kind of like all skills and
Let all skill levels welcome and the whole idea is you start at a Taco Bell in
Summerlin you end up at a Taco Bell in Henderson and you stop at five others along the way
This is more than 30 miles. This is why I didn't feel this was a real event
I'm like, yeah like this is a joke for people who don't know
Henderson and Summerlin are on opposite sides of the city of Las Vegas
They are they are two just neighborhoods basically on the east and west sides of the city
It's not even easy to run between the two takes a while. Yes. Oh
Driving between the two is a nightmare running between the two full of Taco Bell seems like a hellscape
Right. So there's there's some guide guidelines and even experienced runners. I did talk to someone involved
So I knew this was legit and they're like, you know, I'm a runner myself
This will probably take me like eight hours some people may be five some people may be longer
But also I think some of the participants might just do like two or three Taco Bells
I think the real serious ones are the ones who are like doing the whole thing
I'm a Taco Bell 5k guy. I'm not a Taco Bell
I can I think run from one to the other and then call it a day
But you have to eat something different at each Taco Bell
Wow can't repeat and then you have to eat the whole menu item
Yes, and you can't run with it. You have to finish it and then go
You can't just eat like a bite of a taco and then head out. You got to eat the whole taco
Exactly. And I'm also there's a 15-minute penalty added to your time if you throw up
This is a real rule. That's fine. There is a 15-minute in this race
There is a 15-minute penalty for that in life. There is a much bigger penalty for it if you don't throw up though
If it wants to come out let it come out
And again just to let you guys know city cast is legit
I reached out to the slow runners and the person's person's personal
Instagram page trying to get them on today's podcast and could not reach them
But you got you got the interview you got that you got the facts there
Yeah, so I ended up talking to someone who's actually making the official t-shirts
So if you go on their website, they have an official t-shirt for this unofficial Taco Bell event. Holy smokes
One of the Taco Bells is right on the corner from my house
You should just go and hang I know I was like
One of those tables like cups of water maybe there was water
That'd be a bucket ready for anyone who's ready to you wouldn't bring water 15 minutes. I have 15 minute penalty buckets waiting for them
Little cups of Baja Blast. That's what you got to have
Last bonus you can there's two bonuses
One is you can add Diablo sauce to everything and do a Diablo sauce shooter at the end
Oh, I think it's just drinking a packet fine
Fine, and the second one is you have to commit to drinking at least two liters of Baja Blast. Oh
over the seven locations
So what's that equate to like four larges or something like that? It's about two liters. It's about half a dozen
Vomits six. Oh, this was invented by someone who loves Taco Bell and hates running. There's no no, you know, this actually
Happened in a couple other cities. Apparently this is an annual tradition in Denver
I think they're the first ones to come up with it and just a few weeks ago. There was one in the DC area
Yeah, just by coincidence the CEO of CityCast David Plotz
He saw my story sent me a note and said his son ran in the DC version
And complete it October. I
believe it was late November
Okay. Okay, great. Maybe Denver was October. Maybe I don't know the website I found it says
50 kilometers nine Taco Bell meals across DC. Well, yeah, it's insane even worse than the
Yeah
Seven miles while stopping at nine Taco Bells
That makes me want to do that and
The idea is you wear costumes and kind of have fun with it. Sure. And it's all a trust system, right? Yeah
And you went over and taco at the end if you're first. Oh, oh
Come on
Burying the league being a golden taco winner is pretty great
Yeah, great
That goes right on the intro to everything I do after that, you know
No matter what I'm doing
That should be on front page in the RJ golden taco winner is
All right, and I don't know what it is I asked my contact who is part of this
Who's making the shirts and I said, what is the golden taco? And she said I don't know
So it's a little bit of a surprise for whoever gets it. All right
Rob I gave you I gave you 12 hours
I gave you 12 hours notice on the spot to do a year and hours of sleep
Yeah, exactly
And he does last night. I challenged you to come on here and I wanted the top three
underreported Vegas stories for 2025
Yes, now when I asked you that just pop in your head right away or did you was it hard to come up with?
No, cuz you also gave me the option for the five overall news stories of the year
Yes, and I said well three sounds easier than five
And I think my first option will make you grow and you'll be like you didn't put much into this
But I want us to think about I want I want us to think about the the year
So far looking back. It's been a it's one of those years. It kind of feels like two years
It doesn't really feel like all this was one year lots been going on
But what do we remember as the first do you guys remember what the first big news story of the year is from?
January of 2025
Yes
No, no, I don't remember what the first news story of December I guess this election shit
Are we talking just Vegas maybe somewhat indirectly just Vegas, right?
Just Vegas. Yes. Yeah, I'm thinking from now. I'm on the outside in PA now getting still
I still have lots of feeds coming up. My first thought goes to the boring company increasing their
presence
They Elon Musk tunnel company. Yeah
Okay, any any other?
Guesses I guess there was a bunch of protests stage in January, right?
And we we have a bad we have a bad record with how we handle protests. Are we there?
There's always a protest about something every day this story. I'm gonna give you a hint. Okay, so was explosive
Explosive explosive news story. Oh was this the the the Tesla truck that blew up at Trump's tower
That's right happened. People forget this it happened on January 1st. Oh my god five New Year's Day
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, this was the Tesla cyber truck that the guy blew up like in the valet parking area of the of the Trump Tower
We're in Vegas and he was in it, right?
Yeah
he
Blew up along with the Tesla. Yeah, he drove to be clear. He wasn't he didn't blow it up by accident
He meant to blow it up. Yes. Yeah, this was an act of terrorism. This was an attack. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, it wasn't like, you know the accelerator like right, you know
I don't think they have those in Tesla's anyway, but yeah, so this guy drove from Colorado Springs rented the Tesla and
You know, he came pulled up. I'm learning right now that it was a rental
This is what you get from CityCast that's right details, yeah, I mean you're not gonna blow up your own
You know replacing the batteries
So if you do survive, you know, you want to yeah that explains why somebody else's car
My my rates at budget and hurts went up last year that explains it. I think this had something to do with it
Yes, he used Turo. You know what Turo? Oh, yes
You are oh, it's sort of like I don't know. It's kind of like almost we thought about getting into this when it was brand new
It's the uber of rentals. I think yeah
Yeah, you can like sort of like your car, right? Yeah, it's a car sharing that actually does make it more fucked up because everyone running
A Turo usually owns like one or two cars for Turo
You know, it's basically like how we all can run our own rental car company
So that means if people used to do this with the condos
Yeah, so this means that person really did blow up someone else's like really that was a really expensive hundred thousand dollar
Tesla Cybertruck, it's kind of it's kind of like an extra fu, you know
I'm gonna ruin this guy's car
But yeah pulled up to the Portico share the valet and you know what?
I think is kind of under reported about this story is yeah got a lot of attention at the time
But you know when the person responsible dies, you know, you don't really get to follow up on motives
You don't really get to follow up on you know, what was behind this right and you know, there was sort of I mean the guy
had a history in the Special Forces with the US Army and
You know, there were sort of like questions over his political leanings
And if that had something to do with it or if he's just having
You know a bad time in life and is coping with this and maybe had some mental health issues
Sure, but the fact that you know, this is happening at the Trump Tower
which
you know coming right after a very contentious election and
The Trump presidency was there some drama around that I miss that yeah, you may have heard
This president again, so I have not been following the news closely. Yeah, so
You know, but it's also makes you think about how easily it is for kind of what could be considered an act of terrorism to take place
At a Las Vegas landmark, right? I mean pull up into a valet. So you kind of wonder about okay
What's happening since then to account for this kind of stuff to catch people before they take this kind of action and how do you increase security?
Remember there was that crash that happened in front of Planet Hollywood a few years back
Yeah, and and now because of that because they ran into tourists walking on the sidewalk now you have the you know
The pillars the ballasts, I believe yeah
They're concrete ballasts that are along along the sidewalk blocking off the the sidewalks from the road now
Because then the crash referred to is over. Yeah. Oh, yeah, they're everywhere now and they and they came up quick
They grew out of the sidewalks
Right, we gave birth and planted the seed and a screw. That's the company. I should have started the ballast company
I would have made a fortune. Yeah, I think especially in this town
So I mean Vegas is always looking at ways to improve security
Chat is yelling at us bollards. Yeah bollards not ballast ballast at the bottom of a boat bollards are the things on the side of the road
Yeah, it's not like my business is words or anything
We'll edit this in post right these microphones are decorative. Yeah
So I thought that's a somewhat under-reported story mainly because it's been forgotten. Yeah, you're right
I totally haven't thought about that forever and it happened in my own backyard and
I didn't connect it to all of the bollards that are around
Here or ballasts or ballasts or ballads for the people's standing in front of building singing to make sure you don't crash
Your car they just sing slow songs
She's not that singer I don't know
No, I have so I have a second story that the second story kind of follows a similar theme
we're gonna kind of go and flow between one story and another but
Have you noticed anything about Metro police this year? I
Mean, they're super nice and polite and don't give out a bunch of fuck you tickets. Oh
Wait, no, I'm wrong
They've handled I think they've handled the arrest of some of our friends very well
You know people have you had to bail out people? No, we're good friends with Jimmy Sonina who had that terrible
There you have protest. Yeah, you got arrested for some nonsense. Yeah, right
So, you know the one thing I've noticed about Metro this year, which has gotten some attention
I think it needs to get a little more attention. Okay, the way this fleet is expanding
Just the technology they're using
I think you may have seen the hoopla over their big
Cybertruck speaking of which cyber truck patrol fleet. Yeah, some guy gave him a bunch of cyber trucks
Yeah, and how much do you think those fleet of cyber trucks cost? Oh
Oh gosh, I I bet with the retrofitting and stuff that they're doing to the cyber trucks
They've got to be $200,000 a piece where they got to have bulletproof
stuff in them and all that kind of 200,000
Elon Musk tried to
Speaking of things that we forgot about remember when Elon Musk debuted the cyber trucks and threw a big steel
Ball-bearing at the back windows to show off the bulletproof glass and it wasn't bulletproof glass
So he just broke them on stage at the unveiling. I do remember that they just went. Oh well
Yeah, they're like oops and they did it again on a different window. That one also wasn't bulletproof
Ten of those. Yeah, that's the ones for us. So some guy bought a bunch of Tesla cyber trucks for Las Vegas Metro Police
Ten or fifteen of them. This was nearly three million dollar donation from a tech investor
Ben Horowitz who is
with a venture capital firm
Anderson Horowitz, so good guy and yeah, but this isn't the first time he's donated to Metro
do you
Do you remember the other forgotten story this year of remember the guy who set Tesla cars on fire?
Yes at the dealership
Yes, yes, which was like a protest
Right and he was caught but Metro said, you know, we wouldn't have caught him without some of this new technology
We have specifically license plate readers that are now throughout the city
And there's a back there's about a hundred and eighty of them
Oh, it's at least at the time that we did the story and those cost about six million
And who do you think paid for those this guy Horowitz?
Yeah, Wow, so this is not get a lot of speeding tickets
Mr. Horowitz person well now correct me if I'm wrong Rob, but are not the very legality of those devices still in contention
You I mean you can definitely make from a privacy privacy violation
I mean, do you want to be tracked? You know your whereabouts going because that's how they were I'll answer. No
Okay, that's the question interesting interesting. Yeah, but the way they sort of get around this is I believe they make the donation to
Sort of like a third-party like fraternal order of police type of thing and then it kind of goes through that way
You know if this guy was really in some kind of legal trouble
What would happen right you're donating millions and millions to make?
You know Metro police
in theory more successful more like a an army unit, but
You know what happens if you commit some major felony commit? I'm not saying this guy's a bad guy at all
Maybe he's a great guy. No, but you know there it works in some protection. It is weird. You know makes you it makes you pause
Yeah, is there any other?
Motive like in other words like just just just spitballing. I mean I like I like why would a guy spend over 10 million dollars to
Quote-unquote make the city safer, but basically to give Tesla trucks and surveillance equipment to one city
Like what what's it? I don't understand any time. There's a side for him anytime. There's a data collection element
That can be monetized, so he's not doing this out of the goodness of his heart
There is money to be made with that license plate data. That's what I'm asking right. I don't know exactly
I don't know exactly what or is it even probably you could probably know you can probably figure out a way to measure like cars
Mileage and all that kind of thing there their MPH or MPG, you know ratings and things like that
What is the ascent of your armpits have to do with anything Paul?
I don't know I always have something to do with it balance for a man, but made for a lady
No, it's all it's all crazy. I saw a tick-tock recently where someone was talking about this very thing
And it's not about the billionaires accumulating all this wealth at the end of the day
Yes, that's kind of a sickness and a weird symptom of it all but the accumulation of the wealth is
Secondary to their end goal, which is becoming above the rules of normal society
Right and how better to become above the rules of normal society than by purchasing the people who enforce the rules of normal society
I mean this literally is like like Batman comic-villain level. It is right frightening where you're like
Oh, I just did a Google search on this guy. Apparently he's opening a new nightclub in Las Vegas. It's called Horowitz Island
And apparently the police are just not paying any attention to it at all. Okay good
The big the big the big innovation of the nightclub is that you don't get carted at the door. That's right
Technology that allows you to not be carted at the door. Basically a teen club
The teens seem awfully old to be hanging out there
Allegedly
I'm sure is a great guy, but it's not just cyber trucks. It's not just the license plate readers
There's also a fleet of drones now. Oh, no that mr. Horowitz says the drones kill me
Well, the the one day maybe yeah. Yeah, it's true. That that's such a weird thing. Oh
And if you look at it, you know, if you just kind of who's our governor right now Joe Lombardo
Yeah, and what did he used to be? So, I mean chief of police getting your influence
Where you can you know, it could be very valuable depending where people end up in public office. Yeah. Yeah, I
But that you're right. This is next level bizarreness
I had no idea it was just one person footing the bill in a donation role to create this kind of
militaristic
approach to policing is
The are the cops at least flexing on safety. Are they flexing on any kind of statistics to back up any of this?
Cause I'd be more afraid they're flexing on people he'd or if it's the
Right. Well the sheriff right now is
You know running for reelection he's saying murders are down I believe but these are all stats you can count them how you like
but you know what happens if there's a greater for example ice presence in Las Vegas and
We are experiencing right now
Right and but it could get really bad in theory like some other cities and what happens when the governor gets involved or the sheriff gets
Involved and now you start mixing politics with influence
and how
Much to resist this kind of stuff or get involved in it. It just raises a lot of questions and hypotheticals. It's not great
It's not it's not a good look. It's it's the what's what's the the thing?
You want you we want to avoid the the appearance of impropriety and this this certainly does not avoid that appearance
That's what I'm trying whether there is that's what there is any impropriety or not. This looks shady as fuck
That's what I'm poking at Jacob is like, of course hearing this you make you go like yikes, right?
but like our what is the counter and that's I mean, that's what's actually I've been fascinated by a
lot of these terrible things that are happening in the country is that that doesn't even even seem to be a
Quote-unquote company line that people are hiding under anymore. People just say like, yep. It's terrible. We love it. We love terrible shit
Like I don't I don't if you're not doing anything wrong you shouldn't be worried about it
So, yeah this guy is someone in chat saying that he invests in in in in
Flock safety the I guess that's the company that tracks license. Yes, that's the license plate gotcha
so the racer slash reader slash so he is he's getting data to
sell
This that's it. Yeah, he's like we get we get to be his demo city. Although in Vegas
We're so many cars without a license plate. You're gonna lose a chunk of data
We just stepped up the thing about to call people out on that
Rob is the one who reported that let me know that was working there. The tattletale line is working. Mm-hmm
Have you ever you weren't working working? I don't know. It's generating more tax revenue for the state
Gary Rob, that's what I want city cast to crack
I want you to do either an article or a podcast with just tattletailers what they get out of it why they're doing it
Have you have you encountered anyone who's called in anyone on the line like like a guide on how to narc
Yeah, like no. No, I want to hear from the narcs. I want to hear from the well
My favorite narc is that you can report on people who have smog issues with their car
There's an actual program Matt what's your license plate up
Corolla smog out of this well
Can't tell me those guys working in the smog shacks aren't just as soon as somebody fails and heads off on their day
They're not jumping on the horn and oh, yeah, I got a tip
I don't think they get like a cash reward. Oh, well, then maybe they're not doing
Your neighbor it was like aluminum cans like you get ten cents. It's like it's a really nominal fee
golden taco
So, I guess we're just at the beginning of what this means Rob, right?
We don't know what this actually is going to entail. We haven't seen police drones in action yet. Have we?
I think they're more of like a glorified delivery service right now where they are at different stations
And then they can kind of go and maybe scope out an area before the actual officers arrive
Oh, well, it's kind of a monitoring thing. All right
The I I just picture I believe three four of them coming up to me while I'm on my walk at night
Just shooting lasers at me is what I'm picturing. Yeah. Well, it's coming next
To be unveiled at CES and truly if you're making
Drones for metro services the way you're gonna sell more of those drones is to have the predator style three laser
Dots that you can project on people while they're on their late-night walks
Yes, the sign of you will you will sell a fuck ton of those drones to all of these police departments
If you just put those three lasers on it. Yeah
Was that all three was that was that -
That was - I know they kind of run together and probably feel like one big story
But let's go with what we all want to talk about Elon Musk Tesla Tunnels boring company
We've talked about it a lot at CityCast in some way
It's kind of our lane, but we've teamed up with ProPublica twice now
Wow, and I'll tell you ProPublica ProPublica does not mess around that
They are very serious and diligent about what they do a big shout out to David Figgler our host
Yes, and lawyer not our lawyer but a lawyer who really is curious about this stuff really digs deep into it and finds the
Things that not a lot of other people find out about so you are right. This is definitely under reported
I don't think people are talking about this at all on a national level and
This company is running a muck like a bad
Like action TV show where someone has no regard for the law and just keeps ignoring. Oh, it's fine
It's really like yeah commit violations now deal with it later
They've had warnings. They've had
But in the latest, I mean we reported I believe it was like over a thousand since they started and then
Or excuse me over a hundred thousand dollars in fines from Nevada OSHA for some safety violations
And that was last year
This year we were reporting that
Kind of think of what it well it did illegal dumping was one of them they were yes, they were yeah, so kind of by where
Historic commercial center is I was put historic in front of that's a very kind way to
Branding I spent so many years in that spot in historic commercial center. Yes. Yes in the historic onyx theater
The historic
Hawks syringe syringe is historic
Green door
For me
History is made at Hawks gym
But you can have that to be your new slogan by the way you'd have that for free history is made at Hawks gym
I mean it is historic and how many clothing optional all-male 24-hour gyms are there in this country?
But I'm sorry, let's stay focused here Rob
Let's stay let's stay underground with these tests
so now we reported there was
almost 800 environmental regulations over the last two years alone and these were sort of for like
Digging without approval and releasing untreated water into like city streets which go back into our water system, right?
And there was a case where would you mean like untreated waste water from their machines and things like that?
Like right water water that they've been using not just water that they found underground somewhere and they're dumping it like
It's not like they just found a pocket of water like they're bringing all this water in
Diluting chemicals and yeah, they're doing all this stuff within the just dump it in the street, right?
And you do go underground you come across water and that kind of thing
but you know, there's also waste from just use right and
You know, they just seem to be drilling full speed ahead and worrying about
the repercussions later
There's some questions about transparency
We had a congresswoman Dina Titus on our podcast at City Cast and she said she wants to see
Governor Lombardo just open up the transparency of the meetings that are taking place with state officials and the boring company
Because they're sort of allegations that they're kind of getting some preferential treatment as far as you know
Covering this stuff up and not being so transparent about it and kind of giving them some more chances than another company might get
But you know, there's been agreements
There's been allegations of the agreements being broken and just fines left and right
But this is a company that has a lot of money at their disposal
Elon Musk is on pace if not already to become the world's first trillionaire. He has money to burn and
couldn't have a nicer guy
This all is for something that
I know your insider Intel said we shouldn't be as
Impinionated but I think the boring company the boring tunnel and the boring company and what they're doing under Vegas is an incredibly stupid
Public transportation. Yes. Yes. The end goal is not
It doesn't justify the means at all
Like who cares taking traffic above ground and putting it underground the same exact tunnels
Could have been a subway or some kind of large-scale people mover
why
In the name of technology, we're just putting taxis underground putting Disneyland style conveyor belts underground
Where people could just walk down there and then stand on the conveyor belt would have made more sense than this
I would have taken that over this. Yes, you know just by the way, I'll still take that over this
If somebody has the conveyor belt technology that they want to put in those tunnels today. I'm fine with
I just sold that company to make bollards
If somebody could really
Short what's there with the monorail system?
If only they could expand on the monorail system
But that monomaniac it's gonna get completely demolished at a certain point Monterey right because there's no
You don't have the replacement parts for the monorail. So now it's outdated
So once it does bite the dust, we were we're stuck with it and can't fix it. Yeah, so maybe we'll have like Tesla's driving themselves
Tesla does have like a subway car train type of thing that operates in Europe somewhere. I believe I saw this story
I'm like wait, they actually can do this too. Why aren't they doing that here in Vegas?
And now their latest idea is well, what if we take the Tesla's?
Underground put them above ground and now they can go to the airport for five bucks and we're like, okay
That sounds great. That sounds like a taxi with a super discount price. Mm-hmm. That's not new tech
Yeah, Tesla operates a battery-powered shuttle train the giga train in Germany for its gigafactory in Berlin
Yeah, providing where's our train? Yeah, that's just like this just makes a lot of sense. Yeah
I said exactly that was exactly what uber did bitch. Where's my giga train is where I'm pumping it out. We are
Uber came in with a problem with saying no. Yeah, and sometimes we should say no and say hey
How about what you're doing in Germany? Let's do that. Yeah for sure
Was there any?
Understanding of what that big green goopy pile of gunk was there was that weird mystery lake that they yes speaking of
Discharged water. Yeah
Yeah there I mean
It's funny because I think so much of the attention was how security handled that story
So at their new station that they're building at the old firefly song if you remember that place on paradise
I so their latest arm top is heading out. It's heading out towards
UNLV so, you know, it's kind of gonna give some accessibility to like the sphere area and all that but there's
construction happening and there's a little kind of pool of greenish water out there and
When a local station, I believe that was the CBS
KLAS affiliate here try to take some video of it what you're allowed to do from the sidewalk. They
Security shooed them away tried to cover it up. So, you know, if there's nothing wrong with that you would think well
Why are you trying to do that? I'm not gonna totally jump to conclusions and just go with the headline
Yes, it's a little weird and suspect but you know, it's up to them to explain what this is
And from what I've seen so far, they really haven't
Green pool of sludge in the middle of the city is I heard on that video that they made them delete was
Four turtles eating pizza and fighting each other get out of here
Right out of the they were using taekwondo. I think taekwondo turtles
All this in the name of having 12 cars drive you from one hotel to another underground
I know I would like Metro to take their drones and fly above this pool of green water. Yes, exactly
Let's go Lombardo fire them up. I'm a little visit. Yeah, the giga train in Germany carries 500 people per trip
Just saying it's a lot more than four. Jesus. Yeah, that sounds convenient. Doesn't it? Yeah, it really does
Mm-hmm. If only somebody had come up with the idea to put a train car underground like a a sub
Train way. Tell me they couldn't refit the monorail. They could refit the monorail make it work
Yeah, that's my vote. No glory in it. No ego in it Paul. There's no ego in it
Look at the giga train on the monorail tracks and expand it. Yeah, just bring it done
Yeah, bring it to where it needs to go Rob
Thank you so much for giving us an awesome top 300 reported stories of 2025
We really appreciate it all connected to Tesla interestingly
Yeah, funny and CityCast Las Vegas you can read about all that stuff there. So we're here. Where do people go to subscribe?
We have a so the the website is Las Vegas dot CityCast FM
I just tell people Google CityCast Las Vegas, right? It'll come up but free newsletter free podcast daily
Yes, and they do a great job with both your newsletters incredible Rob. Thanks for coming. Thank you so much
And we got to get you back on I'm around. I'm around. I'm available talk about
Media friendly as they say
just friendly
Not if you're not media. Oh if you're not media is not friendly. I need I need some I need eyeballs or ear balls
I don't know. That's it. Otherwise and thanks for coming to the holiday party. Yeah
Extra shout out again the crush pad on Saharan Buffalo. So good. Yeah. Yeah, they did a great job
And you know what? They gave us good wines. It's not like they just put out stuff. They put out the good stuff
It really was a special order the cheap stuff. And if you did you didn't get a raffle ticket. Yeah
All right, and we did give away four bottles. There was a raffle. There you go
I left for it though. The raffle was up. I couldn't in good conscience win the raffle. So, you know, no, no
Yeah, I think that's the number that went unanswered. You might have missed your chance. Oh
All right, well, uh, we're gonna move on to our trivia portion of our show Rob
So you have to torture yourself for that if you want to go back, okay, I got I have to go write a newsletter
This was a lot of fun. Thanks for having me on and good luck at the
Taco Bell Ultramarathon. I will thank you. Thank you. Thank you man. I did all the luck I can get. Thank you
So everybody have a good one
Rob from City Cast everybody. Good job Taco Bell
Ultramarathon the only place where you get the runs
Runs get you the runs get you
Holy shit. I can't wait for Matt's reporting from that Taco Bell by his house
I
Will be I'm just picturing like a bunch of young Matt Donnelly's with the with the horse heads on
The whole thing it does it reeks of the idiot around that I did when I was younger for sure. Yeah
It's gonna be great you guys want to a little Jack vs. Nerd. Yes. Yeah, let's do it
I'm on the hunt for balls
The hunt for balls
We're gonna scoop it today from Eric Dittleman friend of the show. Hey Jacob, you're gonna want to read these category descriptions
The first one is
A-n-a-p-o-d-o-t-o-n-s, which Eric sent a
Pronunciation guide here and
Paddittons and a paddittons
These are idioms where the second half is often unsaid or assumed. I will give you the second half
You say the first half. Oh
Not a magician. These are people who sound like they could be a famous magician
animal camouflage for each given phrase an animal is hidden within it and
Boston is questions about Boston
Self-explanatory great. Thank you for running in Dittleman
Come see Dittleman and I with two other amazing magicians in Lesley, Kentucky, Cincinnati, Ohio
Bloomington, Indiana Green Bay, Wisconsin, Madison, Wisconsin Milwaukee
Wisconsin Wabash, Indiana
All those tickets are available to you in the new year at jokers of magic comm that's the jokers of magic tour
Yeah, it's gonna be very exciting. Do it awesome. Come see that show. It's gonna be so fun
so the categories are and
Paddittons and a bad and a puttittons
Not a magician animal camouflage and Boston Matt. You're up and I puttittons, please for 200
Do is the Romans do dot dot dot do is the Romans do?
So I'm supposed to give the first part of that
What is the first part of that phrase, okay
Well when it went in Rome, right there right when in Rome
Yeah, when in Rome and then the second part is usually implied
So he's giving us the the part that's usually implied and then we have to get the first part. It's me. I'll try
Not a magician 200
Not the headliner of magic reinvented nightly at the link
This celebrity is married to Alison Brie and appears in now you see me franchise where he merely portrays a magician
What oh I got yeah, I don't even understand this question I'm passing Paul
I
Is it Jesse Eisenberg, I mean that's
That's why I have to pass. I'm not sure Matt Dave Franco
Franco Dave Franco is not Matt Franco and he's married to Alison Brie. There you go. There we go
But he's now the only Franco brother allowed to have a movie career
And a pot of tins
for 400
Make lemonade when life gives you lemons when life gives you lemons
Matt and a pathos isn't there for 600 wear it
Dot-dot-dot wear it if the suit fits if the suit or if the shoe fits damn it
If the shoe fits not if the suit fits, I'm gonna I guess I'm putting clothes on my feet
Hey, you've got to
That's me. I'll close that in a pot of tins for 800 and he shall appear
That's the uh and and the suit fits it's you try on a suit and then he shall appear
The devil made the cut of your suit devil's cut devil made this suit. It's the devil's cut angel share suit and he shall appear
Speak of the devil
Yeah
Nice ball
I'll try animal camouflage for 200 if we go at dawn. We'll get there on time
Hmm if we go at dawn we'll get there on time was there explainer in the category
There was hold on go pull it back up now for each phrase an animal is hidden within it goat
It's a goat I'll go at dawn. Yeah goat. I see gotcha. Yeah
Literally hidden in it Matt. Oh, I like this animal camouflage, please for 400
E-sharp major is an uncommon key signature
Hmm
Huh
Oh
Everybody in the in the chat right now is just looking with very concentrated expressions. Yes, I've got it
E-sharp major is an uncommon key signature
Arp Arpma Sharpa a
Sharpa a Sharpa
Answer if you shirt your pants wear it the devil appears
It's happening. All right, damn it. I can't see it path
Passes to me. I'm not I'm not doing any better pass Paul. What is it monkey?
Monkey. Oh
There it is monkey. Oh
Monkey yeah, there is a monkey in there monkey is in the middle the monkeys in the middle. It's me. I'll try
Animal camouflage 600 how loud was the alarm?
How loud was the alarm?
Was the alarm I don't know why I picked this category I haven't been good at any of the other two
Why did I pick the third question?
Um
Down oh
I'm just I'm looking at the letters trying to see if any of them make sense together. Yeah
I have this one, but I think you passed the Paul, right? It does pass the Paul. Yeah, Paul's on fire with these
This is a good podcast Paul you're up I will close out animal camouflage, please for 800
Here we go. Let's do it now. It's for a thousand. Oh boy
Did you save room for cake?
No, Paul, I'm not asking you a question. Did you save room for cake?
Yeah, Paul if you stall Myra's been typing it in the chat each time. Yeah, okay
Well, I don't cheat on the chat
Did you save room for cake
You the answer is you you have to you have to respell y-o-u to e-w but it's you
Ver
Saver
Did you savor um for cake? Ah, the I'm 4k. The I'm 4k is there. Ah
the I'm 4k
What do you think Paul? I'm still trying to find it
But do but do but do but do but do but boo boo boo
This is everybody's favorite part of the show. It's where Paul thinks about things. Oh, it's a daily double
So I can't even it is a daily double. Yeah
Save save room saver saver s-a-v-e-r saver
Boom right
I'll go Rue. Oh, that's okay. Oh like a baby kangaroo. All right
For cake o-r-c-a orca orca. Yeah, Oh
Matt
animal camouflage, please
Is gone? It is to camouflage make one up
Let's see
I'll do not a magician for 800, please
Are you ready not the mind freak who has a question this Olympian turned attic attitude-era wrestler
Often chugged milk to wholesomely mock stone cult Steve Austin. It's true. It's true. Oh
Shoot wrestling
wrestling
attitude-era oh
It's that guy. It's it's the the Olympian guy. Mm-hmm
So you guys both I think you know this one. I think you know this one. Yeah
Ain't what seems angel
close
Angelo Chris Angelo
Turn it 90 degrees. That's it
Turn that angel on its side turn it 90 degrees. Oh Kurt Angle Kurt Angle
That's it
It's me I'll try
Not a magician 400
Not the most famous magician and escape artists still remembered even to this day this animated chef should try escaping from the rat
He has controlling him while he cooks
What do I have to say the name of the of the chef in the movie or could I just say ratatouille
Is ratatouille, I'm just gonna say ratatouille oh
It's lean lean weenie oh
So it's not okay fine. Okay fine fine. Bye. Have it your way Diddleman
I'll try Boston for 200
Despite Paul's belief that the Liberty Bell is in Boston is actually in this city
Philadelphia
It is Philadelphia. Well done Paul. Hey you're learning stuff man me
Not a magician 600
Daily double
Now it's for six. Oh, it's for six hundred now. It's six that yeah
Not the retired Vegas magician who performed over 15,000 shows at the Monte Carlo this actor and Star Trek legend
Was the original host of reading rainbow?
Levar Levar Burton Wow Levar Burton that was a lot of fog in that brain. Yeah
Like you know both of these
Yeah, you know all the Burton's score check we got three questions left Matt is now in the lead with 1200
I'm in second with 1000 Paul is in third with 200 no more daily doubles
Just a four hundred six hundred eight hundred dollar question left. It's all Boston
I guess I'll try to maybe try to win the game. I'll do Boston for 800
Paul Revere's instruction to hang lanterns in the Old North Church to signal the movements of the British is
Immortalized by this phrase in Longfellow's Paul Revere's ride poem
Wow, I
Mean, I think it's just one if by land two if by sea. That's it
And then the devil appears and then the devil appears
The Candyman can yeah
Paul you got Boston for 400 or 600 what doesn't really matter. It does not to you. It doesn't
That's right, I'll go 400 Oh give it math the opening. Thank you
These are the three professional sports teams that are from Boston Boston is in the official team name
the Boston Red Sox
Okay, the Boston Bruins. Oh got it good and the
Boston
The Bruins are the one I thought you wouldn't get Bruins again
also Bruins
The Red Sox to Bruins and the Boston. Oh, geez
Think green, baby. Oh
The Philadelphia
Philadelphia Boston Eagles, that's right crack like the Liberty Bell, uh
But oh the Boston Celtics, oh that's it
Red Sox Celtics and Bruins. That is it
And everybody lost money on whether Paul would get that question right or not
It's and Matt closing out the category and the game. It is Boston for 600 and for the tie
Named for name for colleges or universities in Boston or the immediate surrounding areas. No final answer
No, I choose not to go fuck yourself you
Who is go fuck yourself Boston College, okay Boston University
Holy Cross, okay
MIT
Great. Let's try them
Harvard MIT Boston University Boston College. There's three of them that you said and what's the other one you said? Did you say it?
What's it on here? Holy Cross?
It's Holy Cross on there. Oh and more. Yes and more
Game Matt and I are tied with
1,800 for the win Paul is in second and third place. I suppose with 600 that's from Eric Dittleman
Thank you Dittleman. If you want to send us a scooper II just like Dittleman or
Price is right jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd head over to preaching fun com preaching fun commas
We can go to sign up for all those things and make another. Sorry. I'm jumping around. Hey scoops comm
That's where you can go to do that. My wife just walked in and distracted me
Make a scooper II. I was feeling really proud of having those four colleges until I saw the list of like a thousand
There are a lot of colleges in that area
As soon as it said general surrounding area, I was like, oh my yeah
But good job Dittleman. That was a really well-written scooper II. That was excellent. Yeah, I'm surprised it was as good as it was
I want to thank Bob from the city cast from popping on here
Yes, thank you so much. Yeah, check out city cast check out the the podcast check out the newsletter
It's all kinds of really great things over there and they host parties around the holidays
It always fills me with a certain
Respect and dread when actual other real podcasters join us on the show
People get callbacks from the talk people that run the Taco Bell
I feel like I feel like oh we've made it we're part of the club and also we don't belong here
Well, then you hear Matt talk about how he reached out to multiple other people to get different angles on the story and nobody got
Back to everybody got back to me
Ice cream social does not move the needle
But yeah, I just want to thank all the people who join us here on zoom today and
This is also the part we want to thank the show that people support us over on patreon
Absolutely
Normally here's where we put in a list of people probably by the time this episode airs. This will be a list of people
Thank you so much for joining us. I'm saying that only because the Jacob wants to mark the time and
And then you can also support us keep this podcast going as we head into 2026
By picking a tier that fits your budget at preaching fun.com
Or if you think you have a better idea than shuttling people four at a time through an underground tunnel go over to farts in a
bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun.com
It does take you over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month
You can help keep this show on the air. This show is reliant on our patreon supporters
So if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars farts in a bag dot biz preaching fun calm
Those are your new favorite websites head on over there check them out. It's really cool stuff
Paul's doing a big game night on on video this this week with our patreon supporters
Hopefully Matt and I are gonna be able to pop in there for a little bits as well. It's it's really great
We have we have such a nice community. We have such a fun community. It is wonderful everybody supporting everyone
It's just really great and it's nice to see it this time around the holidays
I I see scoops on on social media and online
Helping each other out as the holidays hit and the holidays are tough
And so seeing our community rallying around other people in the community and really helping each other out
Just because they are listeners to the same stupid podcast out there. That's how they met and
Now they're really doing hard work for each other and making the world a better place. And so good job scoops
I guess good job us, but we didn't really do anything but start talking into microphone catalyst at best
That's it on a good day. We're catalyst. Yeah
Yeah, thanks for everybody. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
See ya!