Oh hello there, I am so glad you're here. I would like to thank the ice cream truck
drivers. Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. It's a new month, I don't have a
new list yet, but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver by name before this
episode starts. Not this episode, a later episode of this show. You know what I mean.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, PreachingFun.com, that's where you can go.
Go sign up, be an ice cream truck driver, deliver this freaking ice cream straight to
people's freaking ear holes, and who knows, the life you save may be your own. My voice
just cracked there a little bit and I realized that I set my water down in a different room
and forgot to bring it in here. So I've got that going for me. Hey Johnny, do you want
to go to an ice cream social? Oh I will, but now we have to start a show. Yeah, I'd love
to. Great, let's go. You have this whole fan part for each day whatever you want to go
with your life. That's true. That's true, I could have gone right now, I could be back
by now, with warm, hydrated, but alas. It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting at C, it's Matt Donnelly. Sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, that's Paul Mattingly.
In Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy. We're preaching fun. We're preaching fun.
We are. Hey everybody. What's up everyone? We have a guest in Zoom today. Yes. As I almost
said in churn, we have a guest in Zoom. I love the new studio, it feels just like home
to me. Isn't it nice? We just wanted to really make you feel right at home. Celestia, how
are you? I'm doing good. I've recovered from ScoopFest, I hope everybody else has too.
Oh, that makes one of us. Paul, how are you? You were hurting yesterday, right? I have
had a week, gentlemen. So, I don't know what's going on. I don't know what's happening. I
was tired from ScoopFest, got in Monday early, had a day to recuperate, did laundry and such
shit. I say a day to recuperate, it was hardly a day to recuperate. Tuesday night, I'm teaching
my free improv class. Wednesday morning, 4 a.m., I'm at Target. So, small window of sleep there.
Right. I get home on Wednesday, I do a Zoom meeting about a show on Friday, our podcast,
and then I hit the hay because I'm already sleep deprived. I work on Thursday. I'm still
very sleep deprived. Get up on Thursday, Thursday is lawn mowing day. Come back home, take a
two hour nap, mow the lawn, then crash out again. Is every Thursday lawn mowing day?
This Thursday was. Okay, okay. It's also pick up poop and trash day. So, those were my big
things for Thursday. It's good to have a list. After I did my 4 a.m. work till 10. Then Friday,
finally, this is going to be the start of recuperation time. I'm going to go to work
on Friday in the morning, and then Friday, well, Friday is going to be busy, but Friday
we were going to go to the optometrist, me and Ann for our annual, and then we were going
to hang out all day, drive around, have some snacks, and then, because she was off off,
which meant she couldn't get pulled in, which is what usually happens when we make plans,
and then I was going to go and do a show at skit with the teachers in the evening, and
then I'd be free and done. And then today was going to just be off. I was going to sleep
in, catch up on sleep, maybe go to the comic book store, whatever. Well. And yet. And yet.
So we go for our annual optometrist visit, and everything's going smooth, everything's
fine. And then the optometrist says, uh, you need to go to the emergency optical place.
I'm like, what the fuck? So apparently I have hemorrhaging happening in my left eye and
only my left eye. Uh, there's an emergency optical place. Yeah, there is. Yep. Uh, Pittsburgh
healthcare is way above what you got in Vegas. That's for sure. And it's just optical only
optical only. Yep. Wow. Yeah. I've never heard of such a thing. I know it was pretty wild.
So, but here's the, well, I'll say, I'll get to it. But so I'm like, okay, shit. Anyway,
it's not both eyes. So that kind of negates diabetic stuff, which I've never had. I don't
have hypertension. My blood pressure is not perfect, but it's not terrible. Right. So,
you know, that's not it. It's not bleed out of your eyes. Bad. It's not bleed out of my
eyes. Bad. My optic nerve is unaffected. My coronial area is not affected. I haven't had
any vision problems. I wouldn't have known anything if I hadn't gone in for my annual,
right? Yeah. So you can see, you couldn't, uh, like in the mirror, could you see blood
or anything? No, no, no. The only thing that's happening are literal pin, pin prick points
of blood in my eyeball at the ends of veins at the ends of veins that you can't, you can't
see with the naked eye. You can only see it with the, with the optics of a microscope
looking in my eyeball, right? Okay. Like these things are pin sized splotches of blood. It's
not like my, my eye, aqueous humorous full blood or anything. How'd you know the name
of my eye was little hemorrhage, little tiny hemorrhages, little tiny hemorrhages. We go
to the optical specialist and, um, we get some more pictures done and the nurse there
is like, I don't know what this is. I'm not an expert. I don't know what this is. I mean,
you are an expert. She says, I don't know what this is. So they don't know what it is.
And then it would be really terrible if you went to a doctor and they explained to you
how they're not an expert. Right. Well, then the doctor comes in, the actual expert doctor
comes in. This is my first day, buddy. Really? Sorry, I don't know what this is. And I've
been in this fucking thing. I read a whole book and this was not in it. I've had my eyeballs
dilate over here. Well, it's because it's not in tandem that's throwing them. Right.
Gotcha. And I think it's probably a vascular thing. Like something's just not. Did you
tell them about your fight club? Right. That was the thing. I don't know. Did I experience
head trauma? That's the other thing. Like that's the other thing they asked me about
head trauma. And I'm like, did I experience head trauma? Well, that's it. Good head trauma.
You're not going to remember, right? Did you tell them? That's right. That someone told
you that you had dust mites in your eyelids and you took a vacuum cleaner to one of your
eyes? Did you tell them? I told them that. They said, no, that shouldn't affect anything.
But I did. I did. I had, you know, I had a lot of travel. I had a lot of work, extra
stuff, extra stress. You know, we were, we're busy. Sure. Sure. I've been doing shows. I've
been, I've been busy as fuck. One legged man and asking contest. You heard my, my week
when it got scoops. He thinks it was your, uh, your character changes during Pollywood
squares. It's possible. Too much pressure on your, on your eyeball. Any of it's possible.
So the other thing is what made this an emergency? I mean, what would happen if it was not treated?
Because I don't know. Only one real podcaster in the zoom right now and it's Celestia Ward.
Yeah. Because the, the optometrist believed that it could be a, a vascular issue. Oh Chris,
thanks for putting us on with soccer, buddy. Poor Chris. I hope his back is feeling better.
So, um, no, we're running into medical elements left and right. Everybody's old. Uh, so I,
she said it could have been a vascular issue. So she was worried it could be something indicative
of, uh, you know, stroke or whatever. I shouldn't say that exactly, but that's kinda, you know,
it could be something Lindsay might be right in the chat. She says you got fucked in the
face too much at scoop. I mean, that's true. Well, here's the thing. So villain meant to
put tiny nanite robots into your bloodstream, but it was supposed to be for like the governor,
but somehow it could be, it could be the Borg. You had identical lungages at, at the airport
and like, and they thought they're going to get nanites into the governor's Russian spies.
Who the fuck knows? Paul does have nice luggage. So I mean, it could be, yeah. You know, the,
the Irish band did a lot of Johnny cash songs. Did they in fact, damn your eyes.
Oh, good question. Good question. But I can see through this burning ring of fire. So
I don't know. It doesn't hurt. There's no symptoms. That's the thing. So it's no symptoms.
So I'm in the stirrup after having my eyes redialated, rejiggered, fucked with forever.
Wait, the stirrup? Yeah. Your chin stirrup. Yeah. You put your head in the chin, chin
stirrup and you press your face against thing and they're looking at you through a microscope.
Oh, you don't know what it's like to be in stirrup at the doctor. Okay. Not that kind
of stirrup. Thank you. That's what I was going. It's a, it's not a new fetish, a chin rest,
new fetish unlocked, chin rest, chin stirrup. I don't know. I only want to be in stirrups
now at the eye doctor. That would have been some shit. Put me in the stirrups doc. It
might come to that. So he's looking at me and he's asking me all these questions. Do
you have all these, you know, health things? No, no, no, no. All this other stuff. Uh,
you vape? No. Uh, do you use, um, uh, what was the wording? He said, um, Oh, he said,
do you use IV drugs? And I go, IV drugs? Anne was in the room with me. She starts laughing.
She's like, no, no, he doesn't do any kind of stuff. But I mean, it was just such a foreign
concept to me. I'm like, IV, what are you talking? What do you mean? IV drug? Am I getting
a slow drip of morphine somewhere? No. Do you vape? Do you use Tik Tok? Have you lost
all hope for owning property or retiring? All right. We can knock millennial off. He's
not doing millennial. I, I didn't know what the fuck was going on. So anyway, I was like,
no, no, no, no, no, no to all of it. And they're basically stumped. So they, they set
up a battery of tests. Uh, so I went and got blood work today. So I'm getting blood work
today. Um, which they're checking for like syphilis, AIDS, all this other shit. I'm like,
God damn it. I had to put in my, I had to put in my social security for an AIDS check.
I don't know. Anyway, so we're going through all these tests. It's a fucking mess. I don't
know what they don't know. They don't know. That's the thing. I get, I get to be a medical
oddity. This was yesterday. And then today was the text we get from Paul yesterday is,
oh, it's a good thing we didn't record today. Cause we're recording a day late this week.
A good thing we didn't record today because apparently my eye is hemorrhaging. Yeah. I
wouldn't have been able to record anyway because I was busy with medical shit all day, but
I was supposed to go and perform at seven 30 over at skit for, with the teachers. And
I did it and was kind enough to tag along with me. Still. We were already out there
in the city. So we went ahead and I performed. I didn't stay for the jam, but I performed
with the four. You drove with one eye. She drove with the other. You guys, I drove with
both eyes, but let me tell you, every fucking tail light was a spectacle. Oh yeah. Christmas
lights and my eyes were still fully dilated. Even I had shades on and it was still really
crazy and I was looking, my eyes were like saucers. So I did that. I felt, you know,
I felt pretty good about making that responsibility and coming through on that. How was your show?
Yeah. Yeah. And so, um, then, uh, we looked fine to pull. We had a show. Um, so, uh, let's
get mine. The lights went off. Yeah, that was, yeah, there was lights and there were
games played. So anyway, I think there were people, I couldn't say there were, there were
like 18 or 20. So, um, that's what you were told. You couldn't see. Yeah. I, uh, I will
say this. Uh, I love improvising with Matt Donnelly. Um, yeah, I really love it. It's,
it's a special, wonderful thing that I have in my life and there's really no substitute.
Um, so, uh, I will say also, uh, yeah, then, uh, today, like I said today had to go get
up early. So I didn't get to sleep in again. I'm like, eh, I got to work tomorrow. They
said no restrictions on anything, but I still feel kind of weird. I don't know, but it's
all good. Again, no pain, no, no, I'm not seeing things different. I don't know what
the fuck is going on. It's just frustrating as hell because it is a, a medical mystery.
But today, even though I had to get up early and get my blood drawn and I would just, and
has been my rock beside me the whole time. Really incredible. Uh, she's the sweetest
thing ever. She's terribly, terribly worried for me. She doesn't talk like that at all.
She's way more worried than I am. I'm more angry than worried. I'm just like this when
I talk, I don't sound like this when I sing. I got to follow up on Tuesday, but aside from
my eye hemorrhaging and having to get blood drawn today, today might just be my perfect
day. It might just be my perfect day. So other than that, Mrs. Lincoln, how was the play?
We get the blood drawn, we get the blood drawn. The costumes were immaculate. Ann is feeling,
you know, feeling the security at the booth could have been better. She's feeling very
sorry for me. And she's proud of how brave I've been through all this. And so we go right
after the, the eye thing, right? Or right after the blood draw, we go, we're out on
McKnight road, which is all the stores and fancy malls and stuff like that. Um, it's
the busiest, one of the busiest streets out there. Everybody calls it McKnight mayor road
because people drive crazy. It's big city, dah, dah, dah. Anyway, so we're driving along
and I'm thinking to myself, the places I've been on McKnight road, we don't go out very
much to McKnight. And I was like, Oh, did special boy get a special day? Did I ever
get a special day? I'm like, Oh, Ann, can we go to the ice cream? Can we go to the exchange,
which is a Zia records type place, right? Oh, nice. Nice. I love Zia records where it's
all like a good, a good record, used music, used video games, used toys. I'm in hog heaven.
I go and I see, and I've been, I've been itching to get a new rock band guitar because I, that's
one of the things I let go during my move. I foolishly let go of all my plastic instruments
and you can't get one for all of the video game rock band for under a hundred bucks.
And I need one for my three 60 because it's gotta be, so it's gotta be old. It's gotta
be retro. And when you start getting into that old three 60 models, a lot of people
didn't treat them great. So I don't, I didn't want to risk buying one online because then
I'm out like 130, 150 bucks. And I don't even know if it's going to be covered in rat feces.
So which is one of the songs, which is one of the songs you have to play on rock band
rat feces. But really, as soon as I walked in the door, I'm thinking, you know what?
I should go and look about a rock band guitar. Cause that's really the only thing video game
related I need right now. So I look up and they've got a box, a full box of the whole
kit and caboodle. Oh, the kit and the caboodle, 250 bucks. And I'm like, ah, shit for everything.
But I don't really want the drums anymore. Don't need the microphone right now. But then
I look over at the other wall and I see, and I asked the lady, I said, do you have, do
you have just like a single guitar hero guitar for three 60? And she goes, why? Yes, we do.
And she goes, we don't get these in very often, but this one just came in. And then I look
up and it's really clean and it's really nice. And I'm like, oh shit. And so this is where
the nanites got the Paul. This is where the nanites came in. This is it. It was a hundred
bucks. So it's a splurge, but I've been trying to get one for a couple of years now, four
years since I moved out here. Cause I really want to play Beatles rock band again, because
that game is just so pretty. You've ever played Beatles rock band, Jacob? No, I didn't know
there was a Beatles rock band. It's gorgeous. You should do yourself a favor of what I'm
doing tonight though. I'll tell you what I'm doing tonight here in just a minute. Well,
just look up Beatles rock band at some point on YouTube, whatnot. The visuals are glorious.
Oh, really pretty cartoon animation. And it's just, by the way, Celestia got tired of this
conversation just left. Yeah. No, she's there. She's there. She's still here. She's not.
Oh, no, she left. She's back in. Great. Um, unfortunately we're still talking about the
same thing, Celestia. You can leave again. I'm sorry. I'm just, I'm just Paul's special
day. Yeah. Just explaining my, my favorite day. So we do that. So number one, I'm already
ahead of the game. Got my rock band guitar. I come out grinning like a fish and looks
at me like I'm a crazy. I'll just say for a fact that if not for Celestia, a frequent
guest and friend of the show, I'd be really embarrassed that we're taking this long to
get to our guests. But no, no, no. Celeste, Celestia, I appreciate you indulging me because
I know you, you will allow me to say this dumb shit for a minute. I just have one question.
How much did you pay your optometrist to say you had a medical mystery to give myself a
special day? Yes. Uh, there's nothing I hate more than medical bullshit going on and having
to get involved in the show. Sure. Sure. Sure. It makes me insane. Uh, yeah, I just, I lucked
out and I lucked out doubly because Anne actually really cares about the whole medical wellbeing
of me. And, uh, married men live longer. That's exactly right. It's true. I would not have
gone to do any of this already. I would have been done as soon as she said, that's not
how it's going down with Jacob and ice marriage. I'll tell you that much right now. Nope. Well,
every time I tell Lester, I feel a little bad. She just hits me. Our next stop is the
Ross Park mall, the Ross Park mall where gunshots rang out just the other night. Yeah. Oh, big
drama in, in, in, uh, outside Pennsylvania or outside Pittsburgh. Oh man. So there was
apparently some gang bullshit went down. Anyway, whatever. But, but by the same token, we drive
in, there's a big line all around the mall. We're like, what the hell is this? And we
park in and sure enough, it's a pop-up Sanrio shop. It's a Hello Kitty cafe van selling a
special Hello Kitty merchandise. And there's just a line around the block for hello. So
you got in line. I did not, I skipped the line and went right for the Lego store. Thank
you very much. He put on, he put on his sunglasses from the optometrist and carrying a cane and
they let them, if they had been selling, if they had been selling bots, Maru merchandise,
possibly. And I mean, I don't say no to some cool Hello Kitty stuff. That shirt of mine
is one of my favorites. Bots. What's bots Maru bots Maru is the angry little penguin
with the spiked hair. That's what I say when I finished laying out my, my plan of like how,
how we're going to pull off a heist. And then I finished with like, and bots Maru and I
finished and then we, we go on with my bots. Maru is the secret code word. Turn off the
laser. That's going to cut James Bond in half. So Celeste, you're running skeptic camp. Oh,
sorry. No, no, no. Anyway, no, I bought Legos as Anne bought me Legos, which even better.
I got treated to Legos and then we went to the whiskey store. Who's a big boy. Get your
Lego and got some whiskey. Then she drove me to the comic book shop, which is in its
new location. I got to go to the comic book store and now I'm back home and we stopped
at Panda Express on the way home. So I mean, perfect. Perfect. So the perfect day. There
was somebody that commented in the, in the comment section that this is what happens
to a dog the day, like right before they get put down. Hey, don't think Anne's not thinking
about maybe this is it. I better get him some Legos before he kicks the bucket. It's possible.
Anything's possible. Get him some Legos up the life insurance policy. We've got to understand
the poor woman's been traumatized. She came out here and four months later, her father
passes and not even four months, like three months. It's just like, you know, so, uh,
yeah, she's a good point. She deserves to take you out and get you everything you want.
She's earned. Look, look, it's not that she just, she just, it's not not that she just
really loves me. I love her too. Like crazy. It's, it's, I, I couldn't do anything without
her at this point. So anyway, uh, yeah, it's all good. So I'm having a pretty good day
except for, uh, exploding eye for whatever that, uh, you know, who else is having a pretty
good day all except their eyeball popping out. That's the following sponsor. Oh, today's
show is God damn it. I hit the wrong window. No things opening up. Oh, I've got it. Hold
on. Uh, today's show is brought to you by Johnny Australia's commercial undersea navigation
and telemet, uh, telemetry. There you go. T L L C Johnny Australia's commercial undersea
navigation and telemetry. That's C U N T L L C. Good. Hi everyone. I'm now you're looking
to go down under really down under down under the sea. Well, if you need to go under the
sea, just look to me, Johnny Australia with his C U N T. It'll take you everywhere you
need to go and places you shouldn't. That's right. My telemetry operations will get you
navigating the wonderful world of Jacques Cousteau. Yeah, but mind you don't run any of those
manta rays. They'll take you out in a second. They don't play around. They got a vengeance
for us Aussies. They like to stab us in the heart with their spear for tails with that.
And that's it. That's all she wrote. So get a C U N T and go swimming. Why don't you?
Huh? Yeah. And her head scoops a check out. Yeah. Get a C U N T by my C U N T. Okay.
Celestia Ward is here. She's helping create and run a new skeptic convention. Paul, what
Legos did you buy? So I got the Gameboy. I'm sorry, everyone. We are out of time. Celestia.
I'm so sorry. Apologies. We're gonna have to bump you. Well, no, I like that. You've
completely overstated what it is. So I should just leave it at that. No, I know. Celestia
is starting her convention. It's gonna be cool. What is the thing? Tell us about it.
It's not a whole convention. It's what's called a skeptic camp. Oh, okay. Skeptic camp. And
they've been doing these all over the country. And Las Vegas is kind of like, well, we should
probably do one because you know, Vegas has got kind of a skeptical history. We had the
amazing shorty here. We had years of the amazing meeting put on by him by the J ref the James
Randy educational foundation. And then I missed the amazing meeting happening here. I liked
seeing those people running around. They were they were a fun group to have around. Cool.
And then Randy went ahead and died. What the hell? I know. Did you get to selfish and donut
party? One time? Yep. My wife was in the band. So yeah, I was at I was at every bacon and
donut party. That's right. Yeah. Yeah. I even got to the one at the old. What's the country
bar that used to be down like all the way down by the south point that's a town square
now. Not smokies, but something like that. But I remember. Yeah, they had it. They had
like the full band down there and everything. And yeah, it was all it was all great. Yeah,
yeah. Yeah, I I have fond memories of all that stuff. What don't you think we're this
country's chock full of skepticism right now? Don't we have enough skepticism? Oh, yeah,
everybody. Everybody from top to bottom is full on critical thinking. That's what we're
celebrating. We're celebrating like the country is going great. It's a victory. There's there's
no misinformation whatsoever coming at it anywhere. Good. Well, actually, you bring
up it's just a big pat on the it's a big pat on the back for the community. Just job well
done, everyone. Gold stars all around. It's just on a deck of a battleship. You're all
going to be in flight suits. There's going to be a big mission accomplished banner behind
you. It's going to be a whole thing. There's nothing political. That's that's actually
one of the saving braces of something like a skeptic camp. It's a place where we can
talk about weird stuff like we're going to be talking about UFOs and gambling legends
and how to quote unquote beat the house. And we're going to have good there. And we're
going to be talking about like, you know, Area 51. And I'm going to be talking about
creativity and drawing and skepticism. And it's not going to be political. So hopefully
people won't have their tribal masks up. And if you can teach somebody critical thinking
by talking about like Bigfoot, then they can apply those skills to other things in their
lives that might be a bit more weighty might perhaps hold the future of democracy in their
hands. Now that I think that is a great theory. Do you are how optimistic are you that that
theory is going to work in practice? Are you very optimistic? Because I'm a little skeptical
of that theory. It will never work 100%. Nothing ever works 100%. Sure. It does make a difference.
I mean, the most recent example is the RFK Jr. came out and said, Hey, Tylenol causes
autism, blah, blah, blah. What? I didn't hear about that. All right. So is that an example
of where we should exert skepticism? I don't know what your feeds looked like after that.
But mine was completely chock-a-block full of social media doctors who are who have made
a social media presence for themselves. Every magical every major medical organization,
you know, the College of Obstetrics and Gynecology, pediatrics, you know, every branch came out
and said, No, here's how you actually read the studies. No, please don't pay attention
to what just happened on TV. Here's what doctors actually figure out. And here's, you know,
the whole history of it. So that's, you know, public education. Skepticism has always been
the intersection of science, education, and consumer protection. We don't want people
to get ripped off. We don't want people to take wrong medical advice from charlatans,
no matter what position of authority they might be in. And we want people to understand
how the world works because it's pretty freaking cool. You know? Yeah. Right. We want to know
what the fuck is wrong with Paul's eye. Right, right, right, right. Absolutely. Yeah. And
we don't want conspiracy theorists on the internet to answer first. Oh, they will anyway.
I mean, they will answer first and loudest. What will take place at the camp? At the camp?
Well, we've got a number of speakers. We have a magician, Joan Ducour. Do you know her?
Oh, I love Joan. I asked you. I asked you and you're like, Oh, I'm going to be gone.
So I forget what you've got going on in the 25th. But this is happening. I would have
declined anyway, because if you want people to speak towards research and education, I'm
maybe not the best example. No, no, we just wanted magic. We just wanted somebody to perform
magic. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I mean, as a palate cleanser. Exactly. Now here is a fish. Does
anyone have a guess as to where this came from? Or was it actually magic? I would love
to turn your act into a TED talk. It's a full on TED talk. We've got to do that. We've got
to come up with all these different topics that your act could lend itself to. I'm skeptical
about whether those are his baseball cards from when he was a child and if they are baseball
cards. Well, every magician you ever watch should be watched with skepticism. You should
not be assuming they have miraculous powers. But that's why skeptic magicians get along.
But actually, that is the absolute truth. It's not like if we were allowed to actually
making people think we were magical, that would be a really weird profession. And that
is how some magicians pursued their paths over the years, especially historically. But
no, it's exactly like the more skeptical the audience is, the more the magic tricks really
get reactions. Right. So that's what you're trying to do. So you are relying on an audience
for being intelligent. Well, many magicians do. Some magicians don't. Have you had the
experience in your career as a magician? Have you had the experience other magicians have
kind of awkwardly felt really weird about where somebody comes up to you after and they're
like, oh, you really have these amazing powers. Hey, my sister has cancer. You know, where
they have not honestly think you have miracle powers and then they immediately hit you with
some kind of big life request. Long term listeners will remember that someone wanted to become
my apprentice at the end of one of my shows. Some guy thought I was actually doing magic
and then he was writing things down creepily on a piece of paper throughout my entire show.
And they came up to show me the things he was writing down and wanted to let me know
that he was on the path to figuring these things out, too, and wanted to become my apprentice.
And I could not get him to leave me alone for hours. This was in Elkton, Maryland. And
I am still here, though. I would still like to be your apprentice.
Jacob's not that wrong on the voice. And it was a really strange situation in which I
was conceding like, no, you know, get out of here. The most embarrassing story of that
is that I was doing pre show for Piff the Magic Dragon when I was dressed up as a giant
like knight king person. All right. And I would just work on some card tricks before
Piff and the dog came up for the VIP experience. So I did what's called a lie detector test
where I have, you know, give people cards and say, I want you to say yes, no matter
what to every question I asked, you know, is it a heart? Is it a spade? Is it red? Is
it black? Is it the number card? Is it a face card? And I have them repeat the answers over
and over again. They say yes every time. And then I go up, you know, three of hearts and
they're like, oh, you nailed it. And a guy was like, hey, I teach psychology at my high
school. Could you maybe go over some of the principles you used for that? And I could
maybe use it in my school. And I was like, oh, buddy, the guy dressed like a knight doing
pre show for a dog is not someone who was mastered body language.
Well, that's that's that actually hits back to some pseudoscience. I mean, that they
I don't know if you remember that show lie to me. It was based loosely on Paul Ekman's
work where he honestly believed you could detect lies just by seeing micro expressions
and everything. And yes, yeah. The Secret Service has claimed to be able to do that
for years. The Secret Service claims that they teach micro expression reading to their
agents and they they claimed their agents are the best at seeing seeing lies happen
of all of the whatever agencies around the world. It always sounds like bullshit. Anytime
I hear somebody talk about it, it just sounds like total bullshit.
Well, everyone has a version of a bullshit or lie detector in themselves, right? We all
know or think when somebody's fucking with us or lying with us or whatever. So it makes
sense that someone in a government agency would suddenly exert a lot of ego and energy
into that element of things. But yeah, I mean, it's all you know, and that's why like even
like lately there was even like a government threat about polygraphing people for trying
to control. I was about to say Kristi Noem has decided to polygraph like a ton of people
looking for whoever's leaking stuff and it is now widely known. Like I think it's widely
known that polygraphs do not work. Yes, but not widely enough. It is the subject of television
shows, books, all the like it's it is as widely known, I think, as anything can be. But it's
not widely known that it doesn't work. I think it is though. I was once hooked up to a polygraph
by a police officer. Uh huh. I have been too. Yeah. In a real situation? I was applying
for a job with the police department. This was like 20 years ago. Mine was not a real
situation at all. I got to the finals. Like, you know, it was like me and like five other
people for the position and they hooked me up and and I'm like, this probably lost me
the job. I was like, you guys know these don't work, right? And he's like, well, it depends
on who's giving it. And if the person who's giving it knows how to read it, blah, blah,
blah. I believe you can be better than other people at it. But it's not it's not it doesn't
just work. Yeah. It's a tool to leverage people to make them. Yeah, it's it's a thing. Yeah.
It can be used as a tool, but it's not it's not Wonder Woman's magic lasso. No. Which
policy just paid $250 for a kitten caboodle at a magic shop on a special day. Yeah. Absolutely.
Wonder Woman has three magic lasso. So one is the lasso of truth. One is the lasso of
faith and the other's chastity. Yeah, that's the truth. Faith and chastity. I can't remember
because absolute Wonder Woman is from hell now. It's awesome. Oh, that's great. Raised
by Circe in hell. It's it's you have roughly 20 minutes of talking material that you can
do on on Wonder Woman now. Look, I'm not going back into another Celestia layout. Let Paul
cook. Let's go. Look, hey, that's just here. No, Celestia. What a winner scoop in the chat
while Paul's thinking of his question says that they failed a polygraph that they had
100% told the truth on and they have a stress disorder. Yeah. So false false negative on
that one. Yeah, that's that's an interesting one that I had not heard of. I think what's
the most important question to ask when you're starting to approach a topic from a skeptical
or critical thinking point of view? What do you think is like the most important way to
start a position of intellectual humility? Because you could always be your own. You're
right. I like that. Skepticism is is really about learning that your brain is broken in
any number of ways. Everybody else's are too. But your own biases are so powerful. That
is the secret between like atheists and the very religious, right? Like religious people
can't believe how know it all atheists are and atheists can't believe that people of
faith have such faith. Right. And so they both use the other being an arrogant know
it all all the time. But but if you truly are coming at stuff from a scientific perspective,
I mean, even just as an improviser, I've been doing it for a long time. I still don't know
everything there is to know about how to do it best. I still don't know the best techniques.
And when you learn more about theater and performance, you know that you don't know.
Well, you're describing Dunning Kruger. I mean, the fact that people who are experts
get pretty humble about like how much else there is to learn in that. Right. That's it.
He sees a 20 minute video on YouTube and they're like, I know the doctors are lying to us,
you know. Yeah, but that's where I live is in Dunning Kruger play. Not that side of it.
But Paul, you know, Freddy Krueger, you live in Freddy Krueger. I do every night. You're
mine, bitch. Yeah, it's scary, scary. Freddy Dunning. Freddy. Freddy Dunning Krueger is
a whole nother. Somebody has to have done. What do you think? What do you think? Is reality
formed by dream or is dream part of reality? Ha, bitch. Yeah. Freddy Dunning Krueger is
the name of a two thousand twenty four rock music single by the Manchester based band
ether. Of course, it has good job. Manchester based band either. I'm surprised it took until
twenty twenty four. I'm going to have to look that up. We're going to have to play that
at the skeptic camp. That sounds funny. Yeah. If it's right. Yeah. It's October 25th, Saturday.
We're starting at nine a.m. We're going all the way through to seven p.m. We're going
to have a game show. We're going to have talks. We're going to have activities. We're going
to have free lunch. You do have to register. Go to LVSOS dot com to register. That stands
for the Las Vegas Society of Skeptics dot com LVSOS dot com. Just a quick Google form.
You'd say if you're going, if you have any minor kids you're bringing with you, blah,
blah, blah. And we will hopefully be able to have enough food for everybody if everybody
registers on time. And we've got a lovely venue down over on the east side of Las Vegas.
It is actually at the Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Las Vegas on Lake Mead. And
I was a little hesitant that, you know, one of one of our organizers is a member there
and she's a total atheist. And there's a lot of atheists in the Universalist Congregation.
And I'm like, a church, really? And she's like, as a member, I can get us the venue
for free. And I'm like, OK. And I went over membership. Now you're talking. It's perfect.
There's like a big lecture hall area. There's break rooms. There's like it's absolutely
a wonderful place to hold an event. Oh, yeah. That's good. Best guys have it all figured
out. Yeah. And no, no taxes. Hey, so Celestia, I have to say, I'm a little bit skeptical.
I've heard there's no such thing as a free lunch. I'm skeptical that it's going to start
promptly at 9 a.m. to be skeptical about the lunch is not free. Organizers are shelling
out some some money to help. Actually, we are also asking people to bring some non-perishables
because they run a food bank for the community. Oh, nice. So it's sort of in exchange for
all these lectures from cool people. We've got Brian Dunning of Skeptoid.com is coming
out. Oh, great. Susan Gerbic of she's known as the Wikipedia attrition. She's like the
organizer of Gorilla Skeptics on Wikipedia. She's coming out and giving a talk. Kyle Polish
of Data Skeptic. He's going to be talking about gambling math and everything. So nerds
will have a really good time at this and bring some canned food or non-perishables for the
food pantry. And hopefully you'll get a sandwich from the catered sandwiches we're going to
be bringing it. Nice. Yeah. And there'll be a taco truck for dinner. Oh, you need a whole
truck? Yes. The first person to finish the truck will win a taco. But is it taco? Come,
come, come, come, come. That was my is it cake joke about a taco truck? All right. Oh,
is it cake? Oh, no, it read, it read. No, no, no, it's better. It's funny when I explain
it. That was just as funny. Celestia, you stopped by ScoopFest and you did filthy caricatures.
I did. And I was so mad I couldn't do it last ScoopFest. Andy Taylor had to cover for me
because I had pneumonia. Oh, and he wasn't nearly as good. No, he was tame. He was tame.
He said he said it was more stress. If I'm remembering correctly, he said it was a bit
more stress than he thought it would be. Because really, your brain cells are going like in
all different directions for weeks before. They're lined up for you. Yeah. I was trying
to think of like dirty things I could draw in five minutes. And, you know, I'm actually
very relieved to not have to think about these things anymore because it was one of those
like intrusive thoughts. I just have these images going around my head all the time.
Okay, okay, I can do somebody like that. Oh, I can draw somebody doing that too. And if
I have two people, if I have three people, blah, blah, blah. Yeah. Did you did you have
any ideas that you weren't able to use? Yeah, I had quite a few that I wasn't able to use
because a lot of more more than I expected. People sat down and it just sort of happened.
Like stuff I didn't even think about beforehand, like the two guys in a banana suit. I mean
of Yeah, that was I have never drawn two guys in a banana suits, having sex so vigorously
that the Chiquita sticker pops off. But that was fun to draw. Right. When you didn't draw,
that's what they were doing. But what did you draw while they were doing that? Oh, I
drew them sipping Cosmopolitans. Oh, that's nice. That's nice. They were fucking each
other raw. So everybody, people I've showed some of these pictures off. I didn't put them
on Facebook, but I showed them to some, you know, private friends and everything. They're
like, What was this thing you drew? It was like a swingers party. And I'm like, No, no,
not at all. These. This is not a sex camp, you know, thing. These are just not officially
sex camp is October 25th in the basement of the sex camp sex camp. Yeah. But I honestly,
I think a swingers party would be way less fun because I mean, y'all are just a loving
community of open minded humorous people. And I think I was talking to Brian Brushwood
afterwards and he said, it's like the horseshoe. It's like the horseshoe theory. He's like,
we've got a lot of really smart people here, but at the end of the horseshoe, there's also
a lot of really dumb people. So we've got like the smartest dumb people and the dumbest
smart people all gathered to do fun things. I'm in the dumbest quality area. Yeah. I rely
on the scoops brain power. Oh yeah. I'll tell you how dumb I am in the dumber smart category.
I'm so dumb. I've got my old Apple computer here that has all my music on and everything.
And I've locked myself out and I can't remember my password and I've just fucked. I just,
I've just got to sit here for days to try and get the password on this damn computer.
And if I don't get it, I'm going to lose thousands of dollars of music. It's going to, it's going
to make me so sad. So somebody popped up on on socials the other day. It was some, uh,
some sporting person, I think had lost the password to their Bitcoin wallet. They had,
they had a bunch of Bitcoin and in this wallet for back when it was very cheap and somebody
had given them like 40 Bitcoin or 400 Bitcoin or something. And they don't know the password
and it's, it's a few million dollars in there. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well there
was, wasn't it, wasn't it somebody on here that told us the story of how they had paid
an ex-girlfriend for pizza in Bitcoin. Right. Uh, but it was, it was the only Bitcoin that
ex-girlfriend had ever gotten. So he wasn't sure if she even knew that she had some Bitcoins
that were worth like one point something million dollars. Yes. And he had not talked to that
ex-girlfriend in a while. I don't remember who that was. I think it was, that was some
story from the, from the way back past. It's a scoop mail, wasn't it? I think it was a
scoop mail. It might have been a scoop mail or a guest or something. Yeah. Somebody, somebody
will tell us over the next, uh, over the next week or two. I'm sure somebody will, somebody
will remember that bit. I am not an economic expert at all, but Bitcoin skeeves me out.
I, I don't. Yeah. It's like, it's math and it's, I agree with that. And I've always
thought that it made it so much math. So gross. Math all over me. No, I love math. I just,
I just don't know if I'm comfortable with using math as currency. I don't, I don't
know if I'm comfortable with math. I am not. Well, I don't know what you're talking about
Felicity, because it makes sense to everybody else. The rest of us are all on board with
it. I stand corrected. I'll go invest. Um, I saw it like you were, uh, you get hired
to do these like crazy gigs all the time. Um, I saw, when were you doing caricatures
on mugs and calling them mug shots? I thought that was pretty neat. I was. Yes. Yeah. Uh,
is this what's, what is, is the, is it, I've never, I guess I don't know how to ask this.
Is the, is the character world evolving? Like what's happening? Yeah. The industry is going
through some stuff and I, I always feel like this kind of indicates times of economic uncertainty
when party planners call you and instead of just, Hey, come do the regular thing you've
done for years and years. They're like, we want you to do your thing, but we've got this
weird idea and we want to try and, you know, capitalize on your talents by doing this other
thing and so they fit you into all these, yeah, they try to judge it up. And so the
latest thing has been drawing on napkins has gotten really big. Like, Oh, like you pretend
you're Pablo Picasso and you're drawing on napkins for people at the night. You're going
by yourself, a college education. Yeah. Go and take your child to Madrid. Yes. Go and
buy a vacation home, Pablo, Pablo by UA house. None of my napkin scribbles will get anybody
a college education right now, but once you're dead and appreciated, look the fuck out. That's
what it happens. Unless you're Pablo. Who else, who else got that ride? Got that ride
like Pablo Picasso. Who else came, came up with it and still, yeah. Like, I mean, who
else was John Michelle Basquiat? Okay. I was gonna say Basquiat Warhol. See Paul's relying
on the scoops for intelligence, but Basquiat passed away very young. He didn't get to ride
it for long. That's right. He didn't, he didn't write it for long, but he wrote it in flight
a bit. Uh, I mean, he would, he would, he would go into groceries for gas stations with
no money to buy a pack of cigarettes and then just doodle on a receipt and you know, just
that, but that was his life for a while. Okay. So he did. Okay. Cool. That is a, that's cool.
Let's try that today. I know many artists who have gotten free drinks from it and they're
not Basquiat or, or anybody famous, but you know, it's been a long time way to get free
drinks, but what, what the agents are now having artists do, you know, caricature artists
in Las Vegas, working trade shows and parties and corporate events is there. And I, I'm
feeling a connection here, Matt, to what you do. And I'm finally understanding the draw
of it here. Nope. No pun intended. They're having me do stealth caricatures, which means
I hang out in a corner. I stand up against the wall. I draw on a little clipboard and
then I slide it to the unsuspecting model who has no idea I've been drawing them. Whoa.
And the male artists, I know the male caricature artists hate to do this. They're like, I feel
creepy. I'm sliding. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Handing them. It's like, it's like watching binoculars
don't help. That makes that makes it more creepy. But I got to tell you, I was born
to do this. Celestia uses opera glasses. I just, oh, that would be lovely. I'm going
to have to do that now. The glasses actually help because it makes it harder for people
to see that I'm staring at them from like 20 feet away. Oh yeah. Yeah. And, and I've
got progressive lenses so I can look far or near or far or near. And, well, that's what
I always tell the ladies that I'm staring at. I'm like, Hey, these are progressive. Yeah.
I'm as progressive as they come. Farther than near. I'm staring at you progressive. From
near and far. I'd like to break off a piece of that action. Come on now.
I'm Paul Mattingly. How are you doing? I have never been a magician. I have never been a
stealthy person, but I am an overweight middle aged white woman. You put me in a trade show
room with a clipboard and I am a ninja. Nobody sees me. I blend into the wallpaper. I look
like every other. The bartenders think I'm keeping tabs on how much they're pouring.
They get a little nervous. Oh. Near. It's one of the higher nups. Neat rocks. But when
you, when you slide the drawing, I'll just say, where do you, how do you, when and how
do you deliver the finished product? That's the magic part. Plenty of times I just handed
to them and say, this is for you. But a lot of times I can slide it right next to them
on, if they're at the bar, if they're sitting at a table, kind of, if they're at a cocktail
table, I've even been able to put it into one guy's pocket without him realizing it.
And they, they don't notice. Not only do they not notice sometimes only one person out of
the group will notice it or nobody will notice it. And I just skulk off and I like, you can
count one, two, three, four, five. And then they're like, Oh my God, what the heck, you
know, and explosion of like, somebody has drawn my picture. And how did this, where
did they go? And sometimes they're looking for me in a panic for like the next 20 minutes.
I bet people chase me down by the end of the night going, how did you even do this? I didn't
see you. And it's people are so unobservant. Oh my God. If I was evil, I could have, I
could have ripped off every single one of them, taken all of their purses and wallets.
But
I just remember my password. So I'm on cloud nine right now. I just unlocked thousands of
dollars of music for myself. Everything's coming up. This is going to be the best day of my
life before we're done here. Also, I'm enjoying the hell out of this episode. I'm glad to
see Celestia. We've got we've had more people in the room than we've ever had guys. We keep
going up. We had we had 42, which is our max now that we've had so far. Everything's
happening. Everything. Things keep going up. Exactly. So things keep going up. This is
great. This is great. This is great. I'm loving it. Yeah, you scoops are here for my best
day ever. You want to tell me when your password so that you have it as a backup? I sure
don't. I sure do not. I sure do not. Winner scoops suggest that you write it down. Yes.
I am going to write it down 1000 times. Yes. Celestia, has there once has there been any
requests you've had to say no to the people trying to make your your profession into
something maybe more difficult? Yeah, I had somebody recently asked if I could draw on
golf balls. Oh, god damn, that sounds awful. And I you know, I was a little snarky. I was
like, um, I've drawn on coffee mugs and napkins and other stuff. Golf, you know, unless the
people have a lot of dimples, I'm not going to draw them on a golf ball. Who's golf? Yeah,
who's golf? Oh, hey, sure thing. But is he okay? Welcome to my golf party. I'm Joe golf.
You're going to draw my balls tonight. I haven't had to draw on people. I that's you've never
drawn. That's it. That's what you've never drawn on skin. Well, I have, but I haven't been paid
to do it. Okay. Have you was like a look for a tat? Was this for a tattoo possibly? Or? No,
no. That's the reason why I would never be a tattoo artist. Everybody always asks, Oh,
you should get into tattoos and blah, blah, blah. Number one, the tattoo market is flooded.
Everybody and their mother might be the tattoo artist in the 90s. But I don't like the idea of
something I draw. You know, if you don't like it, I want you to be able to throw it away.
So drawing on napkins and cups, maybe drawing on garbage is for me, I guess.
I have never been able to get rid of that tattoo. Oh, God. There's a question for Briar.
You ever had someone ask you if they could get one of your works tattooed?
I have. I haven't. I've had somebody send me a photographs of it.
Gosh, it's been a while. I've had somebody, you know, because occasionally people like have their
loved ones caricatured and then plaster their wife and kid on them from the caricature.
And that's happened to me a couple of times. And then I had this one guy, the only time I've
actually been like, yeah, cool. All right. He said, I'd like you to draw my tattoo design.
And I'm like, well, it was really slow. I was at a caricature. I was at the caricature stand.
Logos or tattoos. When you go to a caricature artist and you're like, hey, can you invest five
minutes in something? I want to make permanent for my business or my body. You're already dealing
with somebody who cuts corners. It's not a great idea, but he wanted to, he wanted to have a tattoo
that would win him bar bets. And so he explained he wanted a, a rooster in a noose. Like the new,
the rooster was being, you know, hung, tangled. Yes. And he said this was going to win him bar
bets. And I'm like, okay, I could draw a rooster in a noose. Tell me how it's going to win you a
bar bet. And he said, well, he's betting people that he has a tattoo of a rooster with a noose
on it. And they say, I bet you don't have that. And he says, ha ha, I won. I'm, I'm waiting for
one of you to guess, but if you don't guess, I'll tell you. There's a chicken, chicken, chicken,
choking. I'll show my cock in this bar. Well-hung cock. I'll choke my chicken in his bar. He was,
he was going to tattoo it right below his knee. And he was going to bet people that he has a,
that his cock hanging below his knee. He's got a cock hanging below his knee. Oh, that's funny for,
yeah. So the person doesn't want to blow you anymore. That's pretty,
we know these jokes. Well, we know these jokes. We all know these jokes very well.
These are jokes that are better in theory. There are a lot of physical bits that are just better
in theory. I know you go to that, what are the nursing home argument, which is like the moment
the nurse is like coming in there and you're like, Oh God, this is a low hanging chicken joke. Fuck
you. Eat your apple sauce. Oh, the nurse at the retirement home. Hey, hey sweetie. I bet you I got
a cock hanging below my knee. You have dementia. That's right. Yeah, yeah. You told me yesterday
the same joke every day, Taryn. Did you blow me? I did yesterday. I blew you buddy. Oh, I bet that
was great. It was. Thanks pal. Oh, good. You want to blow me again? I don't have your applesauce.
Oh, I do like applesauce. You know who else likes applesauce from old men who have pictures of cocks
on their knees? That's the following sponsor. From the gorilla dentist from that Bjork video,
from the makers of hemp burlap boxer shorts, it's permanently wet socks.
Hey, how's it going everybody? I'm a creepy Best Buy guy. I just want you to know that
sales are way, way down. We've got like three stores left and decided to expand our inventory.
Unfortunately, we rented a warehouse and all we had was socks. The warehouse got compromised.
Somebody put a bunch of milk in it. I don't know who would put a bunch of milk on socks.
Milk socks, gross. They did. So we got an abundance of damp old milk socks.
And if you're looking to buy some, I can get them for you real, real cheap.
But what if I'm not looking to buy some? Then I'm going to put them on you while you're tied up.
And I'm going to slowly leech the milk out with my mouth. I'm going to suck the
rancid milk out of your socks while I leave your socks on. Yeah.
You know, the best thing about having rancid milk socks is just a couple of weeks of wearing them.
And you've basically made yourself a whole vat of cottage cheese in your shoes. It's really nice.
On the one hand, I was going to tell Jacob it was too loud to hear Paul. And then I was like,
I'm fine with that. That's fine. That was a little extra disgusting, Paul.
But that's what I do. That's what I'm paid for.
This is the trick. Paul's having a day. No, no, no, no. No, no, no. Thanks to my,
let's get it straight. Thanks to my exploding eye and my beloved wife Anne McFeeters,
I am on the brink of having the best day of my life. The best day of my life.
And that includes all of you being here. You are party to the best day of my life so far.
So far. It's going to keep getting better. It is a commercial that Anne's going to fast forward,
just so we're clear. She is. You know what? Also, I would say that our, like ScoopFest for me was
one of the highlights of my life. This last ScoopFest was really, really good. Not, you know,
but easily top 10 things that I've done in my life. And I would say, Matt, you and I,
our bucket shows were easily top three performances of my life. These bucket shows were just off the
hook for some reason. I'm so glad it's all of my life. Paul was ready to retire from stage
performance after this bucket show. I loved those bucket shows so much. They were really good.
Yeah, go ahead. Both shows found like a really great button. And when we were like, when my
improv group were like maniacs, when we were all like eight equally dedicated maniacs about long
form improv, you would find those buttons in our shows. And it was like so satisfying where you
actually bring a kind of wave of callbacks and like something dovetails that changes a character
into something that suddenly fits the puzzle. It's so hard to describe, but when it happens,
and so, and basically Mark Roberts did it twice. That's what I was going to say. I was going to
say big thanks to Mark and Brenna both for bringing an amazing energy to it too. It wasn't just us
this time. No. And it felt retro. Like we called the shows on the buttons and I was like, man,
I haven't felt like this in a long time. Absolutely. I will never forget. A lot of long form teams,
including our other bucket shows, you can ape it, right? You can kind of like push it the way
that the audience feels like it's cute and it's enough and it's close enough. And yeah, we get it.
Or even just end on a laugh. Yeah. But these, you're absolutely right. There was a symmetry
and a actual connectivity to it all. It paid the fuck off. Both of them had payoffs.
And it's interesting because yeah, when I teach improv, I said there's a difference in a callback
and a connection. Yes. And it was really hard to illustrate it and both ended with really strong
connections and not just callbacks. Yes. It was really nice. Can I ask you guys as improvisers?
Because I have this recent fear as a caricature artist, because I've watched many caricature
artists before me kind of, you get, you know, your twenties, you're kind of sucking, you get better,
you learn more, you get more experienced, you get quicker, you get, suddenly you're in the mentor
position. And I turned 50 recently and you guys are kind of around the same age where you feel
like you're in your prime. You're like, I am bringing all this experience to bear. I'm faster
than I've ever been. I'm doing well. And then you're like, how long until I'm one of the old
people who loses my edge? Because you also see that. Are you guys like trying to milk every,
no pun intended, you're trying to milk sock every moment. You're prime here. Are you worried that
like in another 10 years, this could all just be like, you know, you're not hitting it anymore.
That's a great question. Can I answer first, Matt, and let you say next what you think?
You're already faster than me, right? So somebody's showing you how slow I'm getting with age. Yes.
So here's my thing. And I think about when I was real, I was, I've had a couple of really cooking
times in my career. And the one was when I was part-time track full-time second city
and going back and forth between shows. Well, I was understudying. What were you tracking?
Motherfucker. Anyway, there were days when I would do seven hours of Klingon,
get a shower at the, at the Hilton, take the monorail to the Flamingo and do two shows at night.
I was firing on all fucking cylinders. I was a young man doing it. I didn't know at the time
that that was a prime time of my physical and mental performance time. We never do.
Aha. But this is the difference, Jacob. I think with age, we do sometimes know,
like I am very conscious of the fact that that last, that that last scoop fest was great.
And those, uh, bucket show performances were very high bar. So I think Celestia,
as long as you know you're doing well, you won't become the old daughter. You won't become the butt
of the joke because, uh, unless your mental faculties completely fail you, there may or
may not come a point where you go, you know what? Time to hang up the gloves. But I think, uh,
self, self-awareness is the key. I think, well, and I think that's the key, but it's also,
just like we were talking about with skepticism and the Dunning-Kruger and all that kind of thing,
you know, you know how good you are right now, but you also still, still know, like, is it fair to
say you still find yourself improving and growing and learning new techniques even to this day?
Oh, absolutely. I tell people the day that I stopped learning how to draw is when I'm going
to stop drawing. That's it. So I think, I think the other side of it too is with the age comes
the awareness of, Hey, I am really doing really well right now. I've had 50 years of this shit.
I remember when things go to hell. This is not one of those times things are going pretty good.
Yeah. Yeah. Um, it does. So a certain perspective for sure. And I, and perspective is,
is the big word there. So long as you have, have the perspective on it all. Uh, I don't think you're
going to lose it. Uh, again, time, physicality, mental things, uh, your eyes, hemorrhaging,
those are stuff outside of your control. That's the only way I can see, uh, something coming up
to where you're like, where you become the person that shouldn't be there anymore. That's my thought.
What did you think, man? Um, just the same. Uh, I, I know I actually, I actually know I peeked. Uh,
I'm not as good of an improviser as I used to be. Um, what are you talking about? No, no, no, no,
no way. I'm going to speak here. Yeah. Okay. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, you know, this isn't like a,
what was me thing. I think I've gotten very like, uh, someone told me once, and this might be
totally wrong, but Krav Maga was supposedly this like martial arts form where you boil down every
other martial arts form to it's like simple, most lethal moves where you just do the most direct,
different things. And I think as I've gotten older, I simply have developed a Krav Maga style of
improv where like I'm still intellectually. Those are the Gracies, right? Um, what's that?
No, no, that's Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu. Krav Maga is, uh, Israeli, I believe it was developed for the
Israeli military. Yeah. My bad. Like I used to play a lot more different characters,
do a lot more different voices, do a lot more different things than I'm, I'm very much now
just kind of a very much different versions of myself and almost all of my scenes. I just
have lost that ability. Like I talked about this, like I used to, you know, for my freaking movement
final in my, in my BFA acting class, I walked around, uh, like a polar bear for, for an hour
and a half. Right. And like behaved. And that was like a fight. And like, there's no way I could do
that now. You know, like there's no imagine if somebody asks you to, and there are artists,
right? There are clowns and stuff that we know that can simply just commit to energy and do that
kind of stuff. Absolutely. Yeah. I used to, you know, be able to make up songs so well that I
would go to coffee houses and just have a, a, a grab a, grab a guitar player or a keyboard player
and just sit in and do three funny songs for the audience and kill and just like go around.
I did it like I spontaneously took over like a, uh, like a coffee house one time when you put on
like an improvised concert, like, like I used to like destroy with song stuff. And Paul has held
onto his song construction abilities for improv so much better than I have. I can go for like one or
two versus a best. It's the weed, Matt. It's the, yeah, I, I, I did a lot. I did a lot. I did a lot.
I did my fair share of smoking. I did my fair share of drinking. Uh, I also then. Oh, I thought
Paul was saying he was high all the time. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm stoned when I'm coming up. No,
no, no. No, I swore off long. I swore off short form as a long form zealot for over a decade.
Right. Uh, thank practice those skills. Right. And it was only moving to Vegas that I was like,
oh, I actually was skilled at this. It wasn't, it wasn't easy and fun for everybody. It was
something I was good at, you know? And so, uh, I stopped rapping. So that was offensive for,
for, for college white dudes to rap. Um, and so I stopped rapping. Uh, you may not have been
completely wrong about that part. Right. And so, uh, those skills deteriorated. And so,
but I still understand improv. I think at a high level, right? Yes. I think, I think I still see
the performance piece for what it is better. You used to get, you used to get a little prickly
about this and I wonder if you still do. Uh, people would comment every now and then that you were
a really, this years ago, people would comment every now and then that you were a really good
improv show runner from on stage. Yes. You used to get a little prickly about that. Do you still or,
or no? It's, it's, it's, it's a hard thing, right? Because like, basically like, am I actually doing
what I'm supposed to be doing, which is ego-less improv, right? Like that's actually, it's kind of
like, uh, uh, when you get into long form, there's kind of like a Zen approach where you're just
trying to make the pieces happen and unfold and you're really not supposed to be that egotistical
about it. And so yes, I'd have people be like, you know, I didn't, I thought you were just okay. And
then I saw you multiple shows and realized how much you were doing that kind of stuff, that kind of
copy would come up all the time. But, uh, and Paul, but what Paul was referencing earlier is that I,
I see the pieces, right? So I go like, Oh, this is starting off great, but it's running in this
direction. And if we don't counter and do a different kind of scene over here and do something
differently over here, this piece is going to implode in 15 minutes. You're, you're always
thinking big picture on stage. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. This is why we work well together. Yeah. Because
I get lost in the sauce. Right. That's what I tell people working with you, Paul is I go, Paul,
if I wanted to make a scene, simply take a half hour and two pieces, I would just come out and
start a scene with Paul and Paul would play that character unflinchingly for a half hour. He
wouldn't give me a smoke. He wouldn't give me a wink. He would not look up. And other performers
I perform with would, would kind of give me a look at, are we really doing this kind of thing?
Paul does not Paul Paul buckles in and goes. And so, yes, I think my biggest compliment to Paul is
that I can create, make sure we create different worlds, make sure we're not imploding, make sure
we're peppering different people into different universes and making sure that while I have
elements of those thoughts, yeah, you're thinking in a very, uh, very elegant structural way about
what does the show need? Yes. Then when you make an initiation that, um, that will facilitate that,
I have the, the luck and the, uh, the, um, that gives me the opportunity to then shovel in something
that also wedges with that. Yeah. You know, but like on my own, I wouldn't necessarily make as
good a choice. That's what I always tell my students. There are no wrong choices in improvisation.
There are better choices. Right. And what Matt helps me do is he sets me up with better choices.
He aims me towards the better choices. And that's why Paul encourages his students to go to Matt and
ask to be his apprentice. Cause on my own, I will be a crazed goofball. And while it may be entertaining,
it won't necessarily hold together the way it does when we work together. Yeah. I mean, Paul and I
taught workshops together and Paul will teach these crazy character workshops where it teaches
people just to buckle in, make choices, double down, go harder, you know, take it to a, take
it to a 10, you know, that kind of stuff, be unflinching. Um, and I will teach pattern play
and rule threes and all kinds of stuff, just to that, that all those things that kind of pepper
a thing. So like an example for everyone listening is we're getting so in the weeds on this.
It sounds like good cop, bad cop. No, no, no. It's not completely
disrelated from that. We have totally different education. Paul and I have a totally different
improv background. Our teachers and our schools of thinking are completely different from one another.
Um, and, uh, like if you watch a show and there's multiple people, there's a thing called a tag out
where someone from the back line will come in, touch the form on the shoulder and the person
staying on stage remains the same character. And that person becomes another person in that person's
universe. And you can change locations wherever you are. You just go to another spot and that
person and that character's life. And the biggest thing I do is an example of what Paul's talking
about. As I say, that is a challenge to everyone else on the back line. Can we make this a rule of
threes? Whatever this person does with that character, can you all follow that lead and make
it two and three? And then when you do that, you look brilliant to an audience that you, that you
all can play that way, you know, and stuff like that. And so that's an example of like, that's
just a technique thing and creating triggers in people's brains that make their forms better.
But all right, let's change the subject. I think you're going to have to charge a
tuition. This is like a workshop. Well, but, but, but that's more like a camp to Celestia's point,
Matt, given that, that whole, uh, talk there. Yeah. What do you think keeps you and what do you
think will keep Celestia from falling into the obsolescence category? I remember going out to
Improv Olympic when I was, uh, you know, 20 something years old. I think, I think maybe
just even 20. Um, you know, my whole improv group, we went out to Chicago and just stayed on the
couches of Mission Improvable, uh, for a week. And we took workshops every day. Chicago went to shows
every night at Improv Olympic. And that was when I realized I really liked long form more than short
form is because I saw, um, older guys killing it on stage, like doing really great, funny scenes.
And I was like, Oh, good. Because I'm becoming that that's it. I was like, that gives me hope,
right? Cause I felt like when I watched, and this might be wrong and I'm sorry for any listeners who
this fits, but like, I felt like when I saw older people doing short form, it looked kind of cheese
ball to me when I was young, right? I don't know if that would look to me that way now, but it did
look that way then. And so I was so excited that you could still be characters. You could still do
whatever. And it was, and it was, uh, it was still like, okay. So that was pretty cool. And so, uh,
I think as long as you are, when you're doing something more theatrical, I think you have so
much more freedom to age. I'm more, yeah. And I am more, uh, worried about it for my magic career
specifically, uh, because once you become an old guy, magician, it totally changes the lanes you
have to pursue gigs. Like it is just a different world when you're an old guy. There've been so
many amazing old guy magicians though. I mean, but it takes some like curating, right? Like people
have to kind of like you in the community. They have to kind of put you on a pedestal. You have
to kind of be people's first recommendation. Well, maybe if you get in good with, uh, some, uh,
classic magicians, maybe you can find some, some guys who have made it, made their bones
and become friends with them. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe you could, maybe you could
actually deeply befriend one of the greatest magicians to ever live in the history of the
planet that might set you up for success. I'm not guaranteeing it. I'm not. I think I've had
Hondros Insta. All right. Well, let's go. Let's talk. Okay. So let's get Hondo on, on the foreign and see
if we can get you in the pocket with him. Good. Cause that might, uh, make things a little bit
smoother. Like my, my, my, my joke is that my, my magic career has been that of a foreign star.
I've gone from babysitter to milf like instantly. And uh, and, and it's, and it's, and it's, and it's,
and it's difficult, you know, uh, uh, like the geek that haven't, it is difficult to go to milf.
That's true. If I were probably don't never go ask the milf. If I was, if I was fine,
if I was five or maybe 10 years older than I am right now, I would not be on the gig. I'm doing
right now. I'm telling you that right now I would not be hired for what I'm doing. You, you, you,
you would not be on the gig because they wouldn't hire you. Not because you wouldn't do it is what
you said. Correct. But Matt, now that you are and you're gaining the experience of it and you're
getting into that system, somewhat, do you feel with some degree of confidence in 10 years,
should things be where they are, you could then book that gig because of the experience you're
getting now. I said like a really good example of someone's doing something that I would probably
love doing is this guy named Sean Farquhar out of Vancouver. Uh, Sean was the first, one of the,
uh, the, uh, one of the first people to fool Penn and Teller on, um, fool us. Uh, he would forever
was a cruise ship war horse and just in private gig guy and just did everything all over the world.
He's won all these awards for being master magician and that kind of stuff like that is it.
He's one of one of the most respected magicians out there. He's very funny, very funny. Um, and
he now runs his own magic theater in Vancouver that has like 40 seats. It's in like a speakeasy.
You have to like find it in this like old antique shop. That's where I've heard that name before.
Yeah. Yeah. His speakeasy there is a big deal. Yeah. And so he, he got off the road and now he
runs the shows every Friday and Saturday and he just, and he sells out, he adds another show
and he does, so he does like sometimes two, sometimes four, sometimes six shows a weekend.
And, uh, and the math just makes sense for what people pay to go see him do his thing,
but he has enough of a reputation as a, as like, as like a fantastic magician to do that. And so
that is definitely like a trajectory and he's older, uh, not, not that much older,
but he's a little older. And, and, and so like that to me is an example of like a trajectory.
I could try to follow or ape or whatever. Yeah. Cool. Uh, the chat is going crazy right now.
They're just doing different, uh, MILF, uh, things and making magician the, um, and there's just all
kinds of different things coming up in the chat right now. It's, it's really fun. My favorite so
far is from Rich Milb magician. I'd like to book that old Milb, chaotic clumsy magician. I'd like
to feed reasonable plan. Cause I, I, I don't know if you've heard, but, uh, speakeasies might become
a thing in Vegas, Matt. Well, that's a, you want to talk about side effects of changing times.
Yeah. I mean, uh, the entertainment industry as we know it, the mainstream entertainment
industries, we know it is dying. Uh, and so that is, that is a, uh, that, but here's the thing.
That's exactly like, that's the only way I could work in Vegas right now. Like my dream is to work
at Vegas and be home with my children more, maybe even like coach a soccer or basketball team or
something like that. Uh, and I, and I can't, right. And I'll never gain the notoriety it takes to
launch a show on the strip. And that because launching a show on the strip means millions of
dollars, no matter what. So even if someone would give me a million dollars a day, I couldn't in
good faith be like, yeah, we can figure it out, you know? Um, but if there is a venue, like a
speakeasy that hires multiple entertainers and the reputation for the speakeasy is like, you got to
come here and have an awesome time. And I just happen to be someone who's part of that awesome
time. Like that's the way I could work in Vegas. And if that happened tomorrow, I would do it
tomorrow. Yeah. Well, I think there's hope for that. And I think, uh, Celestia too, uh, you've
probably been on the end of this too. I know for myself, I've had to invent and create spaces to
perform throughout my life. It's just, you know, from, from the, the shows I'm running over at, uh,
pod duty, just because I went into that space was like, this is a, this is a place to do improv.
Like this is going to work and it's working, you know, free, free classes and whatnot, but it's
still, it's, it's working really well in that little thing. And like, I, I, I started a coffee
house so I could do improv, uh, you know, and, uh, that I think that's the hard part about getting
older. When we were younger, we would create all of our performance situations because we could create
a social scene around them. And that's the way it goes away. When you get older is that you can't
create a place because everybody's busy. Yes. And yeah. And tired. Yeah. Well, this is the net.
This is my busy and tired. This is my big dream too is future name of Matt and Mattingly busy
and tired somehow. And I think like you're talking about like, you know, with incorporating stuff,
but like, I want like a coffee house, tea house, comic book shop, small theater kind of environment,
but it's all about just trying to, trying to grow community, but it just takes a long time
to grow community. It just really takes a long time. And I, I, I see myself at the bottom of
the bottom rung of that ladder again with what I am entering into right now.
And I see, I see that fucking ladder and I'm like, God damn it. Don't want to climb this
shit again. And I do, I do, and I'm going to do it. And, uh, and I think
magically some other magical shit will happen. That's always, that's always the hardest part
about improv is you can't take your resume with you. You always have to start.
Yes. It's all starting fresh. That makes sense. Yeah. It's all starting fresh.
You got to prove it. Cause even like still city improv is rolling out the red carpet for you.
Right. Right. Yes. Even still like their audience doesn't know who you are yet. Right. So you still
have to like get that going. Absolutely. It's all new, baby. It's all new. Now it's moving in the
right direction. I've got my class sold out. I've got a waiting list now. Awesome. But the first,
but the first class didn't sell enough timing wise. So it ain't like, you know, but it's coming.
It's coming. It's not, it's not instant. It's not. But yeah, we're building a building, a building.
Straight up. I'm just, I'm just excited for the artists in Pittsburgh. Like it's crazy,
like the embarrassment of riches you got with Paul. And so the fact that like people are finally
catching on makes me so happy because we're going to get there. We're going to get there. We're
going to make some magic happen with all this shit and with my love of comic books. And I was
going to say, but what I, oh, that the point I wanted to make was that it is in no small part
because of this podcast and the wonderful community that I can continue to do this stuff
with the degree of enthusiasm that I do coming off of scoop fast and coming here to just
start stuff again and to really lock down and teach a free class on this kind of stuff.
I am enthused because of what we can create and what this community means to me and how I want to
show up for them in the future by continuing to build stuff here too. So just, I can't thank
scoops enough for what they provide for me every day. It's a, yeah, can't do it without you guys.
Yep. I'll tell you what else you can't do. You can't win Jack versus third, but we're going to
try anyway. Fuck you. Let me get the budget. Hey, I'll tell you what in a basement.
So Celestia, will you be our go-to lifeline? Sure. I'll hang out and be a lifeline. Yeah.
Fantastic. Thank you. And Celestia toss out all that information for the,
for the skeptic camp one more time. It will be Saturday, October 25th,
9 a.m. to 7 p.m. We're going to have lunch and snacks and even some limited child care. If you
sign up, you must sign up, register today at lvsos.com. And yeah, it's free. You just have
to register. There you go. So go sign up and we've got a scooperty coming at us today for rum,
rum raisinberg. Hey you face fuckers. Here's a scooperty all about the fun stuff to do
in Las Vegas this weekend instead of attending scoop fest. I kid. Uh, it now occurs to me that
this scooperty is being sent very close to the start of scoop fest and it probably won't happen
before the event takes place. Oh, well, fucking with the face rum raisinberg. You are correct in
all of those things. The categories are shows, sports, food and activities. I'm up first. I'll
just go top left. Shows for 200. You could see this multi-species magic act at the Flamingo Hotel
and Casino. Ex Burlesque. Ever since, ever since ex Burlesque added that chimera, it's shot tickets.
I believe it is piff the magic dragon. Yes, of course. Oh, see now I was going to go with,
uh, what's, what's the, uh, Popovich Gregory Popovich. Yeah, instead of going piff the magic
dragon, you were going to go Greg Popovich. Look, he's the only one that I know of that has the
multiple species and more. He's at planet Hollywood. More live pussy on stage than expert less.
But how much dead should be? His catchphrase by the way. It's his cat's face. It's his cat's phrase.
Ozzy Robb says RuPaul's dog race. I'd watch that show too. We missed you, uh, at the scoop
fest Ozzy Robb. Good to hear from you, pal. Absolutely. A year from late April, early May,
20, 27. Yeah. That's when we're doing the next scoop fest. Yes. Um, sports please for 200.
You can see the Las Vegas Raiders play host to this salmon eating,
shitting in the woods, NFC North team. Wouldn't it be great if every professional, uh, sports team
had to live their life like the mascots. I didn't know, uh, I didn't know a paleo CrossFit gym had
a football team. That would be the Vikings. The Vikings is incorrect. It's the bears.
Well, there's a Viking shit in the woods. I mean, I think so. I think all those things also apply
to vice. We just, we just had fat bear week. Did you guys see that fat bear week? I did see that.
Yeah. Because bears are getting fat for the winter. You get to vote on them. They've already crowned
the winner. The fattest shit that these, I just, I did see that a lot of, uh, a lot of uptick in
bears going for people's trash cans to get, uh, you know, loaded up for loaded for bear. Uh, they
were all just getting ready for hibernation. And so like there were a lot more bears in residential
areas just this last week. Yes. This has been your bear report from ice cream social. Just the bear
facts. I will try activities for 600. Oh yeah. Here we go. You could attend the zombie rumble
at area 51 highlighted by live music and a blank show. I wonder if I bet this was supposed to be
area 15. Maybe, maybe not. I think maybe the numbers are transposed. I don't know. Uh, I
will say, I will guess burlesque. Oh, and the burlesque show. Oh no, I'm sorry, Paul. It's a
classic car show. I mean, that's close, right? The burlesque of the auto world. Get to see what's
under the hood. Yeah. Tassels on it. I'll stick with shows for 400. This here's the concert,
a tribute to blank at the Orleans hotel and casino. This is terrible. I was texting with
someone about this show two days ago. Do you have a clue? I live by the south point or no,
actually no Orleans. I'm confusing myself point with my Orleans here. Yeah. I mixed up a biking
and a bear, so don't feel bad. I, is it John Williams? I don't know. A tribute to John
Williams. It's not a tribute to John Williams. Uh, shit, I got to pass Matt. I don't know.
Is it the band? Is it the concert attribute to the band? Oh, the band, the band. I haven't
been to the Orleans in years. Officially there last week. Oh, well, I still don't know. I will,
I will have to pass. Wait, I know for a fact that we walked past advertisements for it.
I have an answer. The Viking. Oh, go ahead. The Viking. Here we go. Let's try the Vikings.
Oh, it's Abba. Abba. Now I remember Ozzy Robb coming through with it. The worst part about that
is I had a long conversation with one of the owners of the show downstairs during a scoop
fest. Oh shit. And you forgot that. We ran at each other in front of the, in front of the theater.
I invited them to come up to scoop fest. I don't think they did. Oh, that's too bad. I was like,
oh yeah, bring the cast, but preferably stay in the ABBA costumes. Come on up. Yeah. Yeah.
My mind is fucked. Matt, you're up. Uh, sports 400 please.
You can catch the Destructathon, which features battles between blank combatants from around the
globe. Is it robots? Between robot combatants from around the globe. I mean, that would work.
I think that's right. What's robots? All right. Let's try robots. Battle bots, fighting robots.
That is like my favorite show in Las Vegas. I I've seen it three times. I still haven't seen
battle bots live, but I really want to. It's amazing. It's the only show in Vegas where they
have like a disclaimer on the, the, the marketing that says normally shows run, you know, 90 minutes,
but occasionally the robots catch fire and that could cause a delay.
It happens. I'll try activities for 800. Get some points back on the board. Daily double.
Perfect. I'm dead. You could dance the night away at this nightclub,
which won best nightclub and Las Vegas is weekly, uh, 2025 best of Las Vegas. Oh God. Uh,
is it, is it Drays? Jacob's whiskey pit.
Is it Drays? Yeah, Jacob's whiskey pit. The real winner. Nice one, Jordan. We know what the real
winner was. There's Drays. There's, uh, do you have any ideas Celestia? What, what other nightclubs
you're out there? It's not Drays. They just closed. Okay. Well that saves me. I'm thinking
Tao or Omni. Oh, Oh, right. Ooh. Omni. I think, I think it's Tao. I think Tao is coming back
with a vengeance. I'll go with Tao. Okay. I'll try Tao. It's Zook. Those are like the driverless
taxi cabs. Uh, yeah, it was kind of like that. What the hell is Zook? I think that's the club
at resorts world. Oh, for fuck's sake. Oh, and doesn't Josh Gad run that? It's called Gad Zooks.
That makes sense. That makes sense. That's probably it. Zooks. McMullin's. Yeah. I'll go
back to shows for 600. You could go see Magic Mike live at this Las Vegas casino.
Well, it used to be at the Hard Rock Hotel and Casino, which is now the Virgin. It is currently
at the Sahara. Used to be SLS and now Sahara. Yeah. It was, it was Sahara. Then it was SLS.
Now it's Sahara again. I don't know why. Matt, you're up. Uh, show is 800.
You can see this Grammy award nominated artist known for doing backflips at T-Mobile Arena.
Who's known for doing backflips? You saw the show, Matt. I think. At T-Mobile?
I don't, I think this might've been a, oh, like a one night only concert type thing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, really? I don't think this was a repeating show. Is it? Oh, Celestia knows.
Oh, I'll go to Celestia. Is that Benson kid? Somebody Benson. He's like, don't you beautiful,
beautiful thing. Okay. I'm terrible at singing it, but you'll know the song when you hear it.
And he is Robbie Benson. Robbie, no, Benson. His his last name is Benson.
And that's all you need for Jeopardy. Who is Benson? I thought it was just Benson.
Can we just say Benson? Benson Honeydew from the Muppets. Try it. Is Benson enough as the Arbiter?
Me, me, me. Benson Booth. Oh, shoot. It was his first name, not his last name. Oh, shoot. That's
all right. Benson Booth. Paul. Paul, be the Arbiter. Yes or no? Yes, because we got Benson.
All right. Got Benson. Also, we would have also accepted Rene Aubergean-Wall.
Who was on Benson? Yes. That's precisely why we would have accepted it.
Paul, you're up. I will go. Matt, great job on that question, buddy.
I'll go food for 800. Let's get some points back on the board. According to BoydGaming.com,
these are the two open 24 hour dining options available to ScoopFest attendees at the Orleans
Hotel and Casino. What are the two 24 hour options at the old Orleans? I'll tell you,
it ain't fucking Ballywick. I'll tell you that much right now. Right. Ballywick is open for roughly
42 minutes a day. Mike and Laurie's suite. That's it. That's it. That's pretty much the only option.
Fuck, man. I had to pass. I've never been to the Alsroth suite.
Nor have I. Isn't that funny? It's just Jacob. That makes sense that it's just Jacob.
It's just Jacob. And I don't hang out. I just go in and have a drink.
I mean, I think the diner that I ate at in New Orleans. Chaotic Road ice cream and Dale Jizz.
One of those things does last. Jizz, mate. Jizz, mate. Jizz, mate.
I think the diner is open 24 hours, but I don't know what the diner is called.
I'll accept diner if you can get the other one.
Oh, OK. Then I think TGI Fridays. 24/7 TGI Fridays? I kind of think it is. I'll say the diner and TGI
Fridays. Nope. Sbarro and Fuddruckers. Holy shit. I ate a piece of Sbarro pizza while I was there.
That could have been sitting there for 24 hours. It could have been.
Those are the two funniest names for any food establishments. It is true. Fuddruckers is hard
to beat. Yeah. Yeah. Is Fuddruckers the one where they make fun of you? No. Which one is the one
where they make fun of you? Dick's. That's Dick's last resort. Oh, that's right. Yeah.
Jacob, also, that Friday's is closed. It was not even there during Scoot Fest.
Was it gone? Oh, yeah. I mean, there was a facade still there, right? But man, is it closed 24/7?
That's that's what could have confused me. It is indeed closed 24/7.
It's not open 24/7. Oh, it's closed 24/7. OK. Now I see Rob says both of those phrases are
Mormon swear words. Right. Oh, Fuddruckers. Well, Sbarro. Score check. Matt is winning with a
thousand points. I'm in second with zero points. Paul's in third with negative 14 points. We got
one daily double left on the board. Let's see. I'll try food for. No, fuck it. I'm going sports
for 800. You can see all of the high flying action of this small independent wrestling federation
at the nerd bar. Oh, shit. I know this one because I've been trying to get people to go with me to
see this for weeks on the on the rare occasions that I'm actually available to go to it. It is
called Micromania. Micromania midget wrestling, their words, not mine. Wow. OK.
Matt, you're up. I'll do food for 200. You guys remember Micro Machines? Now I'm just thinking
about my. Oh, yeah. I love my Micro Machines. It's like I could talk really really fast.
Well, you can combine the wrestling with the battle bots. You've got micro bots.
Oh. Take it. It's just it's Chick-fil-A. We can just move on. You get a chicken sandwich
from this chain in Caesar's Palace Forum Food Hall. Not just are just not on Sunday.
You what? Just click and say it doesn't open on Sunday. Yeah. The part of that that's confusing
to me is I don't know where Chick-fil-A is in the Caesar's Palace Forum Food Hall. Neither do I. I
just said not on Sunday and no Chick-fil-A. That's it. Church on Sunday. Fuck you. I work in Caesar's
Palace. I didn't know there was a Chick-fil-A. Paul, you're up. I will take food for 600,
please. By the way, I'm fine with that. I don't need Chick-fil-A. Let's get some points on the
board. Here we go. You could stuff your face at this buffet, which won the best buffet on
Las Vegas's weekly Las Vegas Weekly's 2025 Best of Las Vegas. The Caesars World Buffet? What's it
called? Oh, it's Becca Buncher. Becca Buncher, meet yourself. The Forum Buffet? The Forum? No.
What's it called? You want me to tag in? That is the entire question. I can tell you. I can tell you.
Oh, yes, please. Celestia, help him. It is the Bacchanal Buffet at Caesars. That's it. And it's
either that one or the Wicked Spoon at Cosmo. But it's always a battle between those two.
Oh, Celestia throwing shade at the Wynn Buffet. Which do you think was the winner this last time,
Celestia? Well, I think it's going to be Caesars. Right. Telling Bellagio's buffet to fuck right
off, Celestia Ward. I know, my fucking buffets. Have you met me? I love the Bacchanal. Yeah,
the Bacchanal is fucking good. The Bacchanal is amazing. The Bellagio Buffet is endless water
from their fountains. That's right. Oh, God. And they've got the chocolate fountain there too,
but you're not allowed to touch it. Did you see they put a boat in the fountain this morning?
There's now a boat. That looks so weird. It's so stupid. It makes the fountains look less impressive
to stick this big fairy. Do you realize that it's not that big? Yes. Do they put people on it? Is
that what it is? I guess. I don't know what they're doing with it. They literally just put it in the
water this morning. Is it sort of F1 stunt? Is it just for F1 or are we going to have to live with
that all the time? I think it's there as part of the new Carbone restaurant that just opened there.
I think it's a stunt from them. Really? I think it's there going forward. I bet they will have
people you can pay to go out into the middle of the fountain. They had some captain on the front
of the boat like he was steering this ship. He looked embarrassed. It's a living. Is there
law of the sea? Yeah. International waters. International waters, baby. Law of the sea.
International gray water. Also gross. If you're in that fucking place getting squirted on
by old laundry detergent, right? That is true. Yeah. No thanks. I don't know if I want to get
on that boat. What's it called? You talked me out of it. The maiden of the mist. This would be the
maiden of the pissed. Oh, they are not going to be happy with us. Paul, which buffet won Las Vegas?
We went with the Bacchanal. Bacchanal is your answer. Okay. Let's see. I'm sorry. It is the
Wynn Buffet. Get the fuck out of here. The Wynn Buffet. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Jacob tried to help
you. That's all right. Jacob tried to help you. All I've heard about the Wynn Buffet is that it's
overpriced. It's good though. Yes, I do. That's why I tried to help you. Well, thank you. Thank
you for trying. Chris Angel invented the buffet. That's right. I staffed it with all homeless
people. They had nothing. When I met them, they had nothing. They didn't even know how to cook.
I taught them how to cook. I taught them how to be there. Now, thank God. Who here
likes food? Let's hear it for food. Everybody stand up. Let's hear it for food. Everybody stand
up. Thank you. That's my show. Thank you. Let's hear it again for me. I'm not going to sit back down
before I leave. I guess I'll just stay standing. That's right. Stay standing. I have a Chris Angel
little person dwarf story that I forgot to tell. Wait a minute. I'll have to tell it to you next
time. Okay. That's a teaser. I'm going sports for $600. You can watch the Las Vegas Aces compete
against this team in the semifinals of the 2025 WNBA Playoffs. You would have to watch it on TV
as the game is in a different city. I think that's the Mystics. I think they were playing the Mystics.
I'll go Mystics. Now it's the Fever. Indiana Fever. You give me fever, Indiana. I think they're playing the Mystics in the
next round. Fever in the corn at night. Fever. Indiana. Food 400. What an awful place to live.
You get to eat at this iconic 24-hour American restaurant known for its large portions and neon
retro interior found in 1972 on the northern end of the Las Vegas Strip. Oh shoot. You know this one.
Yeah, it's a wonderful place. Go ahead, Celestia. Help me out. It is the Pepper Mill. Oh, right.
I was thinking about the other place that had the tractor and the thing and the--
Oh, the-- Old Red? Hash House of Go-Go? Hash House of Go-Go. Hasn't even been around since '72.
Yeah, the Hash House of Go-Go. I know. That's why I was hesitating and asked for Celestia's help, Paul.
Good move. Paul, you got activities for 200 or 400. You are, let's see, 3600 points behind Matt,
1800 points behind me. Let's take 400. Get some points on the board. There you go. Get
some points on the board, baby. You can catch Tomorrowland's event Unity at this iconic Las
Vegas venue. Oh. Oh. Unity. Hmm. It's got to be Sphere. Maybe. Let's try it. It's the Sphere.
Oh, so they're-- That's interesting. So Disney is using some of their ride stuff in this-- Like,
did you guys ever go on Spaceship Earth-- Not Spaceship Earth. What was the alien encounter?
What was the one-- You remember that Disney ride where you sat on-- It was like you were in a
rocket ship and you went up into space? Do you remember that? It was a giant theater that turned
into a rocket ship, basically. Oh, I don't remember. I don't remember. Captain EO?
Fucking no. It's not Captain EO. Chat, anybody know what I'm talking about?
Not Small World. No, you got in the-- Mission Earth, maybe? Yeah, I guess it was at Epcot.
It's not Spaceship Earth. Was it the thing where they spun you around and it felt like you were on
the Gravitron? No, but there was a shake to the seats when it took off. I'm closing out the
category as the game activities for 200. I don't fucking remember. You can celebrate the 40th
anniversary of this time-traveling '80s movie at the Composer's Room. It might have been Mission
to Mars. Was it Captain EO? Yeah, it's Captain EO, yep. It's Space Mountain, Space Mountain
final answer. Back to the Future. Yes, I know it's Back to the Future. I'm still naming Disney things.
Oh, okay. Okay, Dark Cauldron. Dark Cauldron. That is the game. Black Cauldron. That wins with
1600 points. I'm in second place with 400 points. Close game today. Paul is in third with negative
1600 points. Oh, shit. And that's the scooper day for today. It's from Rum Raisenberg. Thank you,
Rum Raisenberg. If you want to send us a scooper day or a Price is Skryte jock versus nerd or an
obelisk jock versus nerd, head over to HayScoops.com right there on the homepage. You can do all those
things. You can also send us some scoop mail. Do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
Sure can. Oh, Matt is so distraught over losing. He's going to jump off the edge of a boat. Don't
do it, Matt. No, he is. He won. He won. I'm so distraught over winning. I'm going to jump over
the edge of this boat. Either way, he's not used to it. Don't do it, Matt. You won. I just want to
show Ryre how he said, should I piss off my balcony? I want to show him what would happen
if I pissed off my balcony. Just ride onto a lifeboat. Go right back into your face.
On someone's head. You are like, what deck are you on? You're pretty low. You're pretty close to
the water level. I am. Yeah, I asked to be just underwater so I could really crack the door.
Give everybody a shot of the ocean real quick. Look at that. Right down on the waterline.
Somewhere over there is Canada. Law of the Sea. How glorious. Matt is just standing there,
not restrained by any international law. Nice. Oh, he just murdered someone right on camera. It
doesn't matter. Law of the Sea. Beautiful out there. We're probably going to do another episode,
but it's my first time on Virgin Voyages and obviously this is totally... It's pretty nice.
Yeah, it's pretty swanky. I'm not having as good a day as Paul, but it's really nice.
I have to thank people, yeah? Oh, we're just thanking people in general. We don't have new
lists yet. It's a new month. I'll give some personal thanks. It's a guy who gave me an
excellent Americano. Thank you to him. Good. No, I want to thank everybody who supports us over on
Patreon. If we didn't have Patreon, this podcast would not be killing it like it's been killing it
now for almost 11. Was it 12 years? I lose track. 12? More than a decade. And that happens because
people want us to exist and we're not a podcast that relies on hot takery. We don't try to do
sizzling things to go viral. We just try to joke around and keep people's days a little more
amusing than it would be otherwise. And if you think that's a cool mission, then go ahead and
support us today over at PreachingFun.com.
That's right. Fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com. It takes you over to our Patreon
page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. If you think it's
worth more than $0, PreachingFun.com, Fartsinabag.biz, those are your destinations. Keep this show rocking
and rolling for another 12 years. We'll do it if you want us to. I guess that's about it. Yep. I
want to do this for another 12 years. I seriously do. I really, really do. Then we can go back and
listen to this episode of how we thought we'd be when we were older. And then when I leave...
And I can remember when I had a functioning left eye.
You'll be there in an eye patch and I'll be there showing my new tattoo with a chicken with a rope
around his neck. God damn. Guys, I've got this great new bit. Jesus. Huge thanks to our guest,
Celestia Ward. Thank you so much for coming on the podcast. The most patient guest we've ever had.
We will. And yes, thank you for indulging my bullshit, but this was my best day ever. I had
to share it. I was blipping out a couple of times. Zoom hated me for some reason. Paul loses an eye
all on my Patreon. Well, we got you. Oh, you're doing great. Never affected the episode,
so it's all good. We will definitely share your information for SkeptiCamp on our socials
and spread the word. And please, Scoops, help spread the word, especially if you're in Vegas,
know people in Vegas, or just know some skeptics who might go, "Hey, fuck it. I'll go get free
lunch in Vegas for a weekend. Let's do this shit." Free lunch and critical thinking. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. That's a pretty great combo. I'm so good at one of those things.
Help us help Celestia spread the word on SkeptiCamp. It's a positive thing for
the planet and America for sure. So yeah, yeah, yeah. Thank you, Celestia.
And Paul, you got to ask fact check Andy about his eye. He had a retina detachment scare.
Oh, I know. We've been through it. We talked through it. That was one of several hundreds of
things that have kept Crispapus 2 from getting done. It's almost done. It's technically done,
but that was one of the- Christmas is coming.
Huh? Christmas is coming already, yes. Christmas. Oh no, but it's, oh, Christmas is,
forget it. If we could get Crispapus 2 by Easter- Christmas 27.
Because the Easter bunny is a big part of the show, is a big part of the story.
That'd be perfect. I don't know if we're going to be able to get there. I got to see what Andy's
up to, but we're close. We're getting closer and closer. So we may need to call on you again.
Can we put no work demands on Andy's plate right now?
Exactly. Cause he's, well, no, he's working now. He's, he's doing caricatures right now,
but he's had a fucking rough year of it. And I, Andy, I love you the most, buddy. You're my,
you're my art hero. I adore you. You're my, my, my book partner. We'll get the book done when we
get it done. But Celestia, while you're here at some point, we may call upon you for your editorial
skills on old Crispapus 2 as well. My pleasure. There you go. All right. Cool. Cool. Cool.
All right. Well, thanks for listening, everybody. Thanks for being here. Thanks,
Ben for creating this podcast. We love you all and we'll see you soon.
You've heard me talk about Samaritan and today I get to tell you about an additional sharing
option called Redeem Health Share. It's everything we love about Samaritan, like the freedom to
choose your providers and be in control of your healthcare, but with more program options to fit
your budget and healthcare needs in a modern digital platform. There's an add on feature to allow
for a wider range of medical bills to be shared, including preventative, dental, vision, and routine
care. Join the hundreds of thousands of fellow Christians and check out RedeemHealthShare.org today.