Hey Sal.
Hank, what's going on?
We haven't worked a case in years.
I just bought my car at Carvana, and it was so easy.
Too easy.
Think something's up?
You tell me.
They got thousands of options.
Found a great car at a great price.
And it got delivered the next day.
It sounds like Carvana just makes it easy to buy your car, Hank.
Yeah, you're right.
Case closed.
Buy your car today on Carvana.
Delivery fees may apply.
Oh, hello there, I am so glad you are here.
I want to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Oh, those are the folks that deliver that frickin' ice cream straight to your frickin'
ear holes.
We're not getting demonetized yet.
Right.
This Valentine's Day, create a space that feels warm and welcoming with help from Menards.
Whether it's a small refresh or a big project, Menards has the tools and materials you need.
Build something together and make your home a place you both love coming back to.
Don't forget the sweets for your sweetheart.
Get a six ounce bank of Russell Stover chocolate candies for $3.99.
Now through February 14th, save big money and finish your projects together at Menards.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I hope you do, preachingfun.com is where
you can go.
Go over there, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and you will get thanked at this
part of a future episode.
I don't have a new list yet.
It's a new month, but we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver by name at this
part of the episode coming up this month.
So if you want to be an ice cream truck driver, preachingfun.com, head over there, sign up
and who knows, the life you saved may be your own.
Boom.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Ah.
Oh man.
Before we start the show today, I want to say that my wife is a beautiful and intelligent
person.
Okay.
A round of applause for my wife.
Yes.
We must have really messed up.
It's time for Matt Maddowin's ice cream social.
Sitting in Texas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Maddowin.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the audio guy.
We're preachingfun.
That's right.
I'm in San Antonio, which of course is French for the red stick.
Yes.
Very excited to be here.
I'm in the west side of Pittsburgh, which is French for Aaron Rodgers can suck my balls.
By the time this comes out, we'll know.
I'm telling you, the truth will be out.
Are you expecting a Rodgers Renaissance, Matt Donnelly?
Here's the thing.
One, he's old and the only person who's been able to play old is Tom Brady, and no one
else has been able to play old.
But, you know, Saquon Barkley came back from an Achilles injury last year for the Giants,
struggled, then got traded to the Eagles and became an MVP candidate, offensive player
of the year and Super Bowl champion.
Most people are better their second year back from an Achilles injury.
So if Rodgers is going to be healthy, last year's not a sign of what he's going to play.
Yeah.
Do you think he's got something to prove?
No.
I just think out of sheer karma, like we live in the most annoying timeline and the most
annoying timeline thing to happen would be Aaron Rodgers, Aaron Rodgers Renaissance would
absolutely be.
Oh my God, Jacob, I forgot to talk to my mic for the whole first, okay, now I have my mic
up to my thing.
That's going to sound fantastic.
I will, I will patch something together between the recording, the zoom too.
I'll patch something together between your mic and the zoom.
I'll sweeten it up, Donnelly.
There goes all the trends we were going to hit on social media.
No the most annoying thing that I agree with you completely that Aaron Rodgers having it
being the comeback player of the year this year just goes along in line perfectly.
Yeah.
I wish him no ill will, but I hope he snaps like a twig on the first play.
I mean, his other Achilles does have the opportunity to do something really funny right now.
It's true.
Come on Achilles, do it.
So I went and got, I went to get into the truck last night to go to work.
SJ had left for the, for the week, he's out of town until Sunday night.
And so I went and got in the truck last night to go to work, got in, hit the little, it
has a push button start, hit the push button start and nothing happened.
Oh no.
Nothing happened at all.
Yeah, like, uh, the, uh, like the lights didn't come on, no clicking, nothing.
Just just dead.
DED dead.
Now this is your gas vehicle.
This is the gas truck.
Yeah.
Is it all gas?
It is all gas.
No, some of its metal, I mean some breaks, some metal, some oil, gas, no breaks.
So I got in and it was dead.
So I had to Uber to work and then Uber home from work last night and then had to get up
early today because SJ's out of town.
She has the, she has the car.
Yeah.
So I can't, I can't jump the truck.
I don't have another car to jump the truck off of.
And so I, uh, I call roadside service.
I call Dodge roadside service.
They very sweetly came out, uh, this morning, uh, however, very early after getting out
of a show at midnight.
Boy, does that early morning come early.
That is tough.
Yes.
And, uh, so, uh, he gets here, he puts the, the jump back on there.
I say, I don't know what happened.
Uh, the truck's pretty new.
Uh, it shouldn't be having any battery issues, but, uh, who knows?
Let's see.
So he puts the jump back on instantly.
Everything comes on everything.
Everything turns right on.
Truck powers right up because yeah, the battery was dead, but I can't tell if it's charging
or not.
Uh, it looks like it is though.
And, uh, but he had another call to run to, so, and you said, can you, before you go,
put those on my nipples and give one more, one more go.
Yeah.
One more.
Just hit the button.
Clear.
Don't look at me.
Okay.
Look at me.
Clean up my pants.
I'm a AAA member.
I said, clean up my pants.
I need roadside assistance.
Come on.
I'm quadruple A. I have four A's.
Fourth A stands for?
You know what, the final A is in the back seat, brother.
Yes, sir.
Go ahead and find the A. Oh, you had to come out and say it.
I was trying to be all coy.
Nope.
Not me.
Anal.
A stands for anal.
What does the other A stand for?
I thought it was all supposed to be anal.
Yeah, yeah.
It is.
It's anal, anal, anal, anal, anal.
If you have four A's.
That was five A's.
What company are you working with?
Oh, shoot.
I've exposed the fifth A.
They're going to kick me out.
Only the secret fifth A?
The quintuple A!
Jacob, you have to edit this out or they'll kick me out.
Quick, don't talk into your microphone again.
It's actually, they wrote the theme song to the second level of Super Mario Brothers.
It goes, anal, anal, anal, anal, anal, anal.
Oh, my gosh.
That's the secret lyrics.
That's only the triple A.
Yeah.
Secret lyrics.
Well, Jacob, I don't want to step on your story here.
One of those pipes goes right to the five A meeting.
I don't want to step on your story here, Jacob, but I have a sneaking feeling that since the
technician had to go away quickly and wasn't sure that the battery was charging, I have
a sneaking feeling all did not go to plan.
No, no, no.
After that, everything is fine.
Everything is currently peachy keen.
Really?
Battery charged up.
I took it down to AutoZone and they put the tester on it and checked it over real good
and they said it was all good.
Getting the zone.
The weird thing though, AutoZone, anal, anal, anal, AutoZone.
Hey, remember when AutoZone used to be called AutoShack and RadioShack sued them?
Yes.
No.
It made them change the name to AutoZone.
Who's laughing now?
Who's laughing now, RadioShack?
Exactly.
They were called AutoShack, huh?
Yeah.
When you were a kid, it was AutoShack.
When we were kids, it was AutoShack.
I guess we didn't have any AutoShacks in Kentucky.
Getting the shack.
AutoShack.
The difference.
The weird thing though was when he put the jump pack on the truck, everything turned
on.
I watched nobody in the Zoom laughed but Paul on that one, which is fine by me, but the
fact that I got Paul is good.
I had just taken a drink too.
It was dangerous.
No, the weird thing was everything though was turned off.
So like the radio was turned all the way down and turned off.
All of the climate control systems, all the air conditioners and everything was all turned
off and the doors were unlocked, but everything was like folded up and like the mirrors were
folded up and everything like it does when it locks.
So what we figured out was the new Dodge, and I bet other new cars have this too, has
like a power save mode.
So if it is getting down to almost dead, it'll start turning off auxiliary systems to try
to save the battery.
So it turns down the radio, turns off the radio, turns off the climate systems, unlocks
the doors just so you don't get locked in or locked out or whatever.
It's like a Starfleet starship that diverts all power to life support.
That's it, just bare life support.
And so what we figured out was right before she left town, SJ had unloaded a whole bunch
of stuff from the truck and she had, when she went to turn off the truck, we think she
might have double clicked the button or something and just turned all the auxiliary stuff back
on after turning the motor off and just left it running.
Wait, is it a keyless car?
Yes.
Got it.
And so I think she turned the auxiliary stuff on, left everything running.
It looks like it ran for about nine hours.
Yeah.
Wow.
The battery held out for a really long time.
That's pretty good.
Can that be good for your battery to run dry like that?
If you just woke up early, Jacob, you'd be fine.
You know, if you just woke up a little earlier.
Oh, motherfucker, I did today.
Usually I'm up for like 45 minutes before we start recording.
I've been up for three and a half hours today.
Oh, buddy.
I feel you.
In San Antonio every day.
And I just walk like a different direction, see if I can discover, basically I'm going
to discover a place for coffee and a place for breakfast tacos.
I just have to go whichever direction I'm pleased to find a new place.
Right.
And I saw the sign for coffee and I went inside and it's actually like this lush lobby of
a hotel on this beautiful coffee station that was there.
And then on the menu is clearly like put together by like a true coffee enthusiast, all kinds
of different drinks and syrups and that I don't normally see.
Dirty sodas.
Basically, a lot for dirty sodas and the really nice espresso cappuccino machine, you know,
those real real deal machines, a lot of Starbucks push button one.
And asked the lady if I could have, you know, an Americano and a point of one of the syrups
and she goes, I, yeah, yeah, you want like a big cup, I was like, yep, that size is good.
And then I was like, pastries here, what are these, what are these things in the middle?
She's like, I, I think they're danishes.
Okay.
Was this like her first hour on shift?
I go, I, I didn't want to say it, but I go, I also think they're danishes.
I just don't know what kind, like, oh, you and I both recognize the circular shape, but
I was curious to the contain what they contain.
I concur, doctor.
Those are danishes.
She's a cheese.
I think cream cheese danish, I think stepped on cheese danish.
That's super, that's a classic, that's okay.
Let's give one of those a whirl then, you know, and, uh, so to see that up, she's making
my drink.
She's pouring espresso over ice into my little thing.
And then I see her like almost look over her shoulder at me and then she just pulls out
like a bottle of water and pours a bottle of water into my thing for the water, for
the espresso.
I'm fine with using bottled water for my water, for my, uh, but, uh, curious that this very
fine station doesn't have working plumbing, um, and so, and she goes, it's, it's, it's
bottled water.
She was like, it's, it's good water.
I was like, no, no, it's good.
Go, go help yourself.
Go for it.
I'm happy.
Everything's fine.
And then I said brown sugar, cinnamon brown sugar was the name of one syrup.
I was like, yes, let's do a couple of pumps of that.
Two pumps, please.
And uh, she's looking around and she's like turning around every bottle and she's like,
I found a sugar free one.
I was like, don't, don't worry about it.
Just I bet.
Yeah.
I bet you have vanilla.
Give me two pumps of vanilla.
I bet you know right where that one is, right?
She goes, are you sure?
Cause I have the sugar free brown sugar cinnamon here.
No, no, no, no.
Um, uh, did you find out if this was like somebody's kid or something?
Was it, was it take your kid to work day?
What's that?
She actually was using, uh, the kidnapped hand gesture and I missed it.
She kept asking you if you wanted an angel shot.
It's quite possible.
There was a robber underneath the counter with a gun pointed to her the whole time.
You just weren't being nice.
You want sugar free, I think I have some more pumping syrup with the brown sugar under the
counter.
If you just look under the counter, if you take these out without paying for them, they
sometimes trigger a silent alarm at gun point that I have to come out now.
I'm sorry.
Everybody.
I have a gun.
That makes a lot more sense.
The only thing I said, the only thing I told this young lady was please don't tell this
guy that I'm under here and that's the one thing you did.
Did I say it?
I didn't mean to.
I tell you what.
You strongly implied it.
I couldn't, I just couldn't take it.
Mr. Robber, Mr. Robber, I believe in second chances.
I have to go record a podcast anyway.
I'm going to leave and then you guys just start from one, you know, start from scratch.
No, no, no.
You, you go ahead.
I don't even want to rob this place anymore.
I'm, this is really just taking all this steam out of my sails.
The reformed Robber from San Antonio presented to you PBS through selective partners like
the Helena Rubinstein Foundation.
It's such a good feeling to know you're alive because I left you living, though I was robbing
you inside and I said, you know, not today.
I will not shoot you then run away.
It's a good feeling, a very good feeling, a feeling you know that I'll be back to get
my fucking money, bitch, and if you don't have it, this trigger is going to itch and
it's going to go off and blow your head away.
I promise you, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Mr. Robber's neighborhood.
We're happy to see him.
He's just changed out of his sneaky clothes.
Wherever he goes, near or far, I still don't know what danishes are.
What did you eat?
A pastry?
So she goes to get the French vanilla syrup, right?
Oh, yeah.
Here's the thing, baristas, you sheer up things, you got to wipe or what if you have like the
removable spouts, you wash the spouts, right?
Right.
If it's the pumps, you still have to at least take like a warm cloth at the end of the shift
or the beginning of the shift to make sure you wipe those puppies down.
Right.
Yeah.
Wipe them puppies.
Mm hmm.
No.
Hadn't been done.
She goes to squirt the vanilla syrup.
Oh, God.
You saw the glomp?
Just jizzes right in her own face.
Oh.
Just absolutely explodes in her own face.
Oh, shoot.
Like a joke.
Oh, she's having a terrible day.
Like a joke at a naked gun, she just assaults her own face with vanilla syrup.
Oh.
Oh, sweetie.
I feel so bad for this sweet girl.
She goes, I hate these things.
I'm trying to make you a coffee, man.
She just wants you to have some coffee in a day.
Can I have some flavoring?
You're like.
Yes.
He tells me he loves me.
Just and like literally was like, oh, I hate these like literally with like syrup across
her face goes like, I hate these things.
She just turns around, looks at you, Mondays, am I right?
And I was like, been there, girlfriend.
How do you think I got how do you think I started interning for Penn and Teller?
I made them coffee.
Can I tell you how I got these claw clackers?
Let me tell you, I used to pick up pastries with my bare hands when I was first working
here.
Bear hands out of this.
That was just a little too grotesque of a thing to do.
So I I went ahead and got myself some tongs.
And I use those to pick up the bear claws and the pastries and the Danish.
And I was a fiend for the day, even though I didn't know what was in the Danish.
That was part of the fun picking up the Danish that I couldn't tell what was inside.
But I went ahead and ate it anyway.
And then I rigged all your fucking things to explode your God damn it.
I was wondering where the story was going.
But now it was worth the monologue.
It was worth the pain.
They say he's a super criminal and I know the whole time I was like, this doesn't sound
terribly criminal at all to me.
But the ending, though, it took a turn.
It's all about the way I hide the syrup sheepishly showed me this container of cinnamon.
She's like, this is like cinnamon.
And I go, it is cinnamon.
It's like cinnamon.
Yeah.
She said it's like cinnamon.
And I was like, like cinnamon.
I was like, that'll be great.
You go ahead and you go and clean your face.
I'll throw some cinnamon in here myself.
I got it.
I got this.
I don't believe that I can in good conscience ask you to do anything else for me.
I'm going to see myself out.
Please have a better day.
I don't want to leave this establishment with you having 10 drink additives splattered all
over you because of my order.
I can't take that on my conscience.
No, this is just outrageous.
Then she leapt onto the wall and stuck to it.
Just boop.
You know who else thinks the walls when they jump at them?
The following sponsor.
Today's show, Mad and Mally's Ice Cream Social.
First of all, shout out to Froyo who wrote why is so syrupy in the chat.
Today's show is brought to you by Vacation Packages for Nerds.
That's from Big Ben in 2021.
That's Vacation Packages for Nerds.
Hello there.
I know you're all dying to go on some kind of a trip or a journey or a jaunt of some
sort and maybe go onto a balloon or a flying device.
What I'm offering is a trip that you can take with your loved one or your sibling or what
have you.
You can go to a place where they will love you and take you and embrace you.
This is Nerd Vacations brought to you by nerds who know the way to do it.
Of course, Nerd Vacations are all at home.
That's exactly what we're doing.
We're going to be at home and we're going to play Magic the Gathering.
That's it.
Magic the Gathering, of course, everyone knows is a vacation unto itself, taking you to the
many varied lands all across Innistrad and Phyrexia and all places in between.
You can only imagine the kinds of locales you will find yourself in when you are mid-battle
with your cardboard warriors.
Go ahead and place them onto the forefront and see how much mana you can deal damage
to your opponent with.
While you're there, just imagine yourself in the fields of Ravnica, floating away on
an island on all your own.
That's my idea of a really great vacation, or hey, how about this for a nerd vacation?
Why don't we plug in the old game system and let's go to a place we all know and love,
Vice City.
Yes, let's all go to Vice City for a vacation where the toots are plentiful and they can
be beaten for the money you give them after you do it.
This sounds like a trap.
This is definitely a trap.
I'm not saying that Grand Theft Auto, the video game, is any kind of secret government
sci-op, but I'm certainly not implying that the new Grand Theft Auto 6 is going to actually
literally entrap people into the virtual game world where they will be unable to escape,
where they will be actually shackled to the game for many, many hours of their day, playing
it to earn real-world money only to just spend that on food and water delivered to their
home because they can't leave because they have to keep playing the game because they're
going to be the game.
Oh, so it's not going to be that?
You say it's not going to be that, though?
No way.
No way are we going to be utilizing actual in-live players replacing NPCs.
That would be uncatchable.
No way.
Good.
As long as you're not going to do that, I'm fine with it.
Signed off.
Don't trust it.
You tricked us, you super nerd.
You tricked us.
Good.
Ha-ha.
Take a vacation, bitch.
So I was doing-
Fair enough.
Tough but fair.
I ended up, you know, I put myself on all these different websites trying to increase
my corporate work for magic.
Oh, did we ever get resolution on your Bachelorette gig?
Did that happen?
They canceled.
I was going to do it and they canceled that.
Well, there's the resolution.
They called off the wedding.
They put up a picture like, "This is who I'm going to bring in front of us at 10 o'clock
at night in this private suite."
And they say-
Do you have a cancellation fee?
Yeah.
Nice.
So you made a little money.
Yeah, so I'm joining all of these sites to figure out my best practices, and why I went
through with this Bachelorette party was to make sure I could create a performance agreement,
Chad GBT, and basically ask my friends for best practices and just go, "Yeah, I'm sorry
I'm not going to hire an entertainment lawyer for my $300 gig for Bachelorette party."
I get you on that one, but still, the AI zombies are coming for us all.
Oh, they are.
That's true.
I'm terrified.
That is true.
I don't disagree.
So same, on a different website, I ended up just agreeing to do a birthday party in Redlands,
California, about three hours away from us.
Same thing, I was just going back and forth with the person, so I ended up agreeing to
do it.
All right.
And so I drive out last Saturday to a party in the Redlands, California, and a beautiful
backyard for someone's birthday.
And I'm doing a rope trick, right?
And I say I have a magic wand and it's a giant bowie knife, it's a 10-inch bowie knife, make
jokes about a game through TSA, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I always hand it to someone and say, "Do you believe in the power of this magic wand?"
And then I have them turn two pieces of rope back into one pieces of rope, mirror, right?
And I get up this person who's honestly, I believe, presenting mail.
So I watch my pronouns and they also seem to be with someone who also seems gender fluid
in the back.
And so I hand this person the knife and say, "Do you believe in the power of a magic wand?"
And she quietly dead eyes me and says, "I believe in the power of our Lord and Savior,
Jesus Christ."
Oh, boy.
I'll see your ridiculousness and I'll raise you.
At the throne.
That's right.
I want to say, you know, it's funny about knowing how magic tricks work.
I know how con artists work and I want to be like, you are surrounding yourself with
self-hatred.
Do you understand?
There's a place where you are free to be whoever you want and that answer is anywhere but a
church community.
Isn't that sad though, Matt?
I want to give you a hug and take you out and say, "Let's just go.
Let's just go.
Have a nice life."
Get in the car.
That's a big part of the whole religious thing.
The self-hating thing is a real deal.
It's legit.
I mean, I can't...
You and your partner, you guys help me load out and I'll take you to the gayest area of
South Las Vegas.
Yeah.
We'll go get you fixed up.
Yeah, yeah.
This is going to be the best night of all of our lives and let's fucking go.
I promise you will see Jesus in the back of the Piranha Club.
Yeah.
He dances in there.
Yeah, yeah.
His name is Jesus and he will blow your mind.
And other things.
I basically said, "Fair.
Do you feel like helping me with this little magic trick?"
Sure.
I'd love to not have that conversation right now.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Were they the celebrants?
This is my second routine.
Who were they?
I have like seven more to go.
Who were they in regards to the party?
Friends of, just friends, had to be friends of either the children of the person, or celebrating
someone's 70th birthday.
So they were an outside irritant.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got you.
And then I go further in the show and I'm doing my unarmed chop routine and I get the
person up and I go, "Who are you?"
And the man I go, "And you know everybody here?"
He goes, "I'm his daughter."
Like there's like a weird awkwardness of like, "I'm his daughter."
Okay.
And she's a nurse that gave plenty of good humor to the arm chop routine.
And then later on I get the couple, right?
The wife hired me for the 70th birthday party and so I'm going to do the wedding ring routine
with them, celebrate the birthday guy and his wife.
And I go, "How long have you guys been together?"
And they're like, "10 years."
And I was like, "Oh, now I know the awkwardness of the daughter thing."
Yeah.
Got it.
This is daddy picked up a new piece of ass here.
Yeah.
And daughter might not be incredibly thrilled about it.
This is hotter wife number two is here.
Yeah.
Or could it be the other way around?
Could it be dad is new dad?
Or did she look just like her dad?
She was not old enough to be the mom of the...
She didn't say, "I'm Amanda's mom," or anything like that.
Oh.
Yeah.
Did she have a beard that gave away like she had the same facial hair as the dad?
That's it.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's a key indicator.
I mean, I guess, Paul, since you're really holding me to the coals here, I don't know.
I don't know is the answer.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Paul.
The last time I saw a birthday magician, all he did was ask inappropriate questions about
family lineage.
That's right.
This is like...
And his name was Piff the Magic Dragon.
That is true.
If you put on a dragon suit, you can get away with more.
That's true.
One of the reason I ended up following through with it, I said, "Have you ever hired entertainers
before?"
And she said, "I have.
We hired a comedian.
It was not a good experience."
Oh, dear.
And I go like, "Oh, gosh," and making me ensnare myself into saying like, "Well, I can make
up for that guy," kind of thing.
This is before you started your show as you were meeting them?
This is the booking.
Yeah, the booking.
Oh, okay.
So this is...
Well, that's good.
But you didn't just show up at their doorstep and go, "Hey, you ever hire anybody to do
stuff like this before?"
And was it okay?
And were they wearing pants?
Because I'm not.
It was not happening here.
No.
Oh, the downtown breeze is a-blowing nice and free.
Did you find out who the comedian was?
From Jersey thrust a bowing knife at me, I think I'd believe in Jesus too.
Fair enough.
Fair.
No, I did not ask who the comedian was because there's no good...
Either I don't know them or I do.
And that's terrible.
Or you do.
Yeah.
I don't...
And then I have to...
What am I going to do?
Call that person up?
Be like...
Absolutely.
"Jason, you suck, buddy."
Yeah.
No.
No upside, I don't think, to knowing who it was.
And it's out in California.
Exactly what I wanted to know.
So I imagine it's some guy from LA is actually what I think.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So because of the reputation of a party magician, I was absolutely trying not to ask any questions.
I tried so hard to not clarify anything.
Just like, "Great.
Moving on."
So, do you have any kids?
You do.
Any that live?
All right.
Could you bring them out?
Could you leave me alone with them for a while?
I have some magic I'd like to show them.
Marry for 10.
Well, then who's her mom?
Wait a minute.
Is she here?
This doesn't track.
Get everybody up here.
Everyone who's been married to my friend, get up here.
Everybody.
All the wives.
Get them up here.
Any miscarriages in the audience?
Hands up.
That's always a good ice breaker.
Anybody have a child?
Die young?
Anybody?
Take it from this magician.
"Pregnancy is tricky."
Oh, boy.
Look in my hat.
Appropriate party magician is a pretty good bit, though.
If you look in my hat, I've got my own form of IVF.
I vanish flowers.
You can actually use that one, Matt.
Yeah, Matt, you can use that one.
Hold on.
Let me get out a pen.
A pen with invisible ink.
Don't worry.
Matt, don't worry.
We're recording this.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Just send me on our edit.
I'll add to my notes.
IVF.
I vanish flowers.
Gold.
This is under the gold column of my notes.
This is the best.
Under the "put it in tonight" column.
So funny.
Let's see.
Oh, ultrasound.
That's the noise that I associate with applause.
That's my ultrasound.
Applause.
How about you guys give me some ultrasound right now?
Oh, wait a minute.
This party has been catered, and that means just like IVF, they're going to feed us.
It's a catered party.
It's a catered party, so they're going to feed us.
Matt, timeout involves there might be a timeout later.
All right.
You don't want Paul to just keep on whispering to him.
Let's see.
Not about penises, no.
This is a long way to go here, but let's see.
Okay.
So I'm going to start my own television mystery series, and I'm going to employ a famous TV
author who's going to help.
He's written tons of screenplays, and he's going to help me with getting this new project
born.
Huh?
Oh, no.
His name is Steven J. Berthknell.
Yeah.
So what else happened?
That's a long way to go for that one.
That was a real long way to go for that one.
I actually just thought you were going to make a way worse joke, and I'm just glad you didn't.
That's all I care about.
What TV producer were you thinking of?
Roger Still?
Okay, so I don't want that to go out to people.
Claire abortion.
I'll tell you, one of the coolest things that happened out here is for the second time,
Tim Jenison has left his ranch to come out and have a meal with me.
Oh, that's so nice.
Great.
Get out of here.
Where'd you guys leave?
I'm really going to miss this podcast.
Where'd you go?
So he picked me up and he says, have you ever been to Rudy's?
And I said, no, he goes, Rudy's is a very famous barbecue place.
I'm going to take you to the original location.
And so we go about 25 minutes out of town, and it lives up to the hype.
It is attached to a gas station.
It is just built into the building.
It is all bare bones.
There's no air conditioning.
There's just fans going on.
You walk in and kind of like a cafeteria kind of lineup.
You order your sides first, then your meats second, and their plates are pieces of wax
paper.
They have just the brown paper.
The guy with the sides is handing out small samples of the creamed corn to let you know
how today's batch tastes.
Oh, wow.
And so we're eating creamed corn and we get some briskets, some ribs, those chopped brisket
and barbecue and turkey.
It was crazy.
And you all just sit at these like big picnic tables.
You get a big bucket of soda.
And I tell you, just superior to a microwave hot dog.
Just so good.
In what way?
No, I agree.
That's a fancy new location, Jacob.
The original one is literally just attached to a gas station.
Like you see gas pumps on the side.
I can send a picture too.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Let me see if I find the original.
I love me some good burn ends.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And you know when you go into those places, you just see like the plywood walls, people
putting food onto a basket with some paper on it.
You know it's going to be the best thing ever.
We did style switch the last time I was in Austin with my brother and I got their burn
ends.
And it's just really well done pork belly.
It was just I've regretted ordering the brisket.
I was like I should have just doubled up on the burn ends because it was so fucking good.
Like perfection.
Yeah.
And then in line, he's talking about how rough to get ourselves a sausage, you know, Texas
barbecue place are always known for sausage, we'll get half a link.
And I go, oh, that's good.
I can't wait to have a barbecue.
When I go, my podcast partner, he grosses me out.
He likes a microwave hot dog.
And Tim jenison says heats it up just fine.
Yes, I am in good company with super genius Tim jenison.
And then I said, he also does it with with bratwurst.
And Tim goes, Oh, no, no, no, that's terrible.
You got to grill a bratwurst.
Not an Aldi brat.
It barely counts as a bratwurst.
Agree.
You're right.
I believe Aldi brat is disqualified from the conversation.
You and I both agree there.
No problem.
Yeah.
It is bratwurst asterisks.
You know what?
I'll take I'll take half support for my preposterous dining habits.
That makes me happy.
You know who else is happy to take half support and half support only?
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Sweet Relief, 24 hour hotel and spa where you can always
come in us.
Oh, God.
Jacques Scoop toe from 2024.
That's Jacques Scoop toe 2024 for Sweet Relief, 24 hour hotel and spa.
Hello, my name is Mr. Bill Stevens.
And I run this hotel called Sweet Relief.
It was built by my father, Jerry Stevens, here in our house.
You can come to my house built by Jerry Stevens and you can have a sweet relief.
That's right.
The secret of our spa slash hotel is that every piece of art is fuckable.
All right.
We have made.
Yes.
Art.
OK.
We have waist level paintings throughout the hotel.
So you don't even take it off the wall.
No, no.
They're there, they're all of all of our paintings are equipped with glory holes.
They are all glory hole paintings and they are all themed.
Now here is the trick.
I'm sorry.
Before we.
Here we go.
We continue this negotiation.
Always with the questions.
Huh?
Are you are you French?
What do you mean?
I'm just curious about your accents.
My father's name was Jerry Stevens.
I am Bill Stevens.
Does that sound French to you?
It does not, sir.
It does not.
OK, then I would not think that that needs any more explanation.
You know, I hear you saying that.
But I I'm very curious about this accent, sir.
And listen, here's the thing about about the about where are we going?
This is the thing about my place, OK?
All of the artwork he's got is on a waist level.
And it's all got holes in it where there's mouths or butts.
And that's what you can insert your stuff in.
Now, I have not let out the ladies either.
I have not forgot about the ladies.
What?
No, I mean, I'm curious.
Huh?
I heard you.
I'm curious.
Well, how you plan to help the ladies?
Oh, the lamps.
Enter a scoops of check.
Those are choking hazards or you don't put them in your mouth.
I mean, you can.
You can.
All right.
You can do anything you want that sweet relief.
I don't care.
My whole house, because it's my house and it's filled with the calm of a thousand strangers.
I don't I can't get I can't access the back of the paintings.
They're built into the walls.
I did it.
plan ahead.
Which this is illegal to let you know that my home reeks of takeover.
My home reeks of bleach and sour apples.
It's just a bad scene.
It's I the walls weep.
You understand me?
I have to take a moist towel to most of the walls every morning to take away some of the
seepage and it doesn't stop and keep seeping.
There's a girl who works at a coffee shop who's looking to get extra work.
Do you think you can help her out?
Oh, I love a barista bring her over.
You should use socks says chaotic and too late.
I've it's in the drywall.
I really should just replace the drywall.
Look, my only good thing is that it's at waist level.
So at some point I could cut it all away and put like, you know, what do they call that
design?
What do they call the waist level beams when they go on?
You know, at this point in the bit, you're asking for architectural specifics.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think he's asking for a chair rail.
That's exactly chair rail and runner board.
Is that what it's called?
Sure.
Okay.
Great.
What funny is I want to bring up something that Tim and I talked about, but now I can't
tell them to listen to this episode.
Next episode, next episode.
Well, I want to bring up something real quick, too late.
Bad Pirate Scoop sent me an amazing, an amazing gift from Australia.
He is friends with a creator called Salt, Andrew Saltmarsh, I guess is the creator's
actual name.
And he does this art by Salt and he made these really cool stickers and sent them to me.
They're all crazy Star Trek themes.
So this is a bat left in a piece of pie.
It says a good day to pie or a good day for pie.
This is a doctor, which I believe just says, Hey, in Klingon, like hey, what is the doctor
for our audio listeners, which a doctor is a Klingon dagger.
Okay.
It's a Klingon dagger with the word Hey on it.
Yep.
This is a zombie hand giving the Vulcan salute, it says live long on it, which is cool.
You were just flipping off the camera.
Yeah.
And then this is a red shirt, what remains of a red shirt with a damaged com badge and
blood all over it.
Clearly the victim.
And then I got a couple others that are beautiful stickers.
They are.
And I've already put them on a couple of them on some notebooks I have that I'm going to
be using for the the upcoming improv classes that I'm about to start teaching this month,
which I'm really excited about.
And I just wanted to say thank you bad pirate for that gift.
And I am holding on to the letter and the envelope because it might be the last piece
of international parcel that I received for some time.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
Yeah.
Where do you where you want us to support this person?
Yes.
I would say yeah, check out art by salt, S a L T. Andrew salt marsh is that individual.
They're an Australian.
And yeah, you can go check them out.
And yeah, that's it.
Okay.
All right.
It does really great work.
So I was talking to Tim, and we're getting it, you know, he's he's he's a total
like audio nerd.
Right.
And so we were talking about like the recording of sound and basically like, all right, because
he has like the Beatles microphone and stuff like that.
Yes.
Right.
Yeah.
He's got some real, real interesting shit.
And he and basically, if we just get into it, I was like, I basically was like, I was like,
I've had many people who understand audio explain to me how we actually record physical
sound into an object, which I still don't get no matter how many times people explain
to me what happens.
And he says it's even crazier than that is that it was like a French scientist, one of
the first known people to kind of figure it out.
And he was recording sound into like, you know, like, like, like cylinders.
It wasn't it wasn't quite that was like, it was a really like loose like metal material
like similar, I guess would be like tinfoil now, but it was kind of like a very, very
weak metal pewter pewter, right.
Something like that.
Maybe I don't have to look it up.
But a soft metal.
Yeah.
And that's the song was also soft metal.
No.
But yeah.
Good.
But the person first known recording audio is by this French scientist.
We've got to get a soft metal Jacob album where he just whispers, whispers Metallica.
Jacob soft metal quieter, quieter, softer, softer.
That's better.
And but it's still just full volume music.
The music is still just blasted.
Take my hand.
So take my speech, take my hearing, take my arms, take my legs.
This is not a heavy enough of a story to carry the bit, but all it gets.
But so so he said the crazy way of figuring out how to record stuff.
I haven't gotten to the punchline yet.
We've done too many bits in between.
He was the punchline.
The punchline is he was doing it before the phonograph.
So before we had an ability to listen to what we were recording, this guy figured out that
we could record.
Yes.
I have heard about I've been told several times about how we figured out how to record
sound before we learned how to play it back.
Tim couldn't believe that I found this to be hysterical.
I was like, wait, it's like everyone's singing and playing.
And then some some nerds going like, see the wrinkles?
It's here.
It's in here.
Guys.
They go.
Oh, OK.
Can we hear it?
No.
No, you can't.
We don't have that kind of technology, you fools.
Keep playing, though.
It's making the coolest wrinkles.
How long how long between learning to record and learning to playback?
I don't even know.
I don't even like they discovered because they discovered this guy's recordings later.
They didn't know at the time he had done it.
So it was like it was like seriously centuries later where they found the recordings and
then found a way to play them.
And sure enough, you heard the voice and music of like basically a popular song at the time
in France, which is baffles me.
That baffles me so much.
Digital sound makes so much more sense to me than than analog being recorded into a
piece of metal.
I don't know.
I can I can wrap my head around analog sound a little bit better because it is, you know,
it's just it's a needle vibrating.
It's the actual vibration of of stuff.
And well, I mean, it's the vibration of the needle against the groove of the record, then
amplified through the air, which is what's the only when you get right down to it.
If we didn't have air, we wouldn't have any of this shit.
Yeah, that is true.
Take that.
You people take air for granted because it's all got to go through the air and the compression
of air.
Right.
Yes.
I mean, I think that's what that's.
Yeah.
There's all kinds of crazy shit that's that above my brain, above my brain capabilities.
Like you said, vibrating air is above your brain for it to be like centuries later for
me to take a needle to it and go, oh, there it is.
And then hear it.
It's like, what?
Sure.
I don't know.
There was about a 20 year gap between it, Scott, Scott, Scott de Martinville patented
the oh, boy, I don't even know how to say what that word is.
It looks kind of like phonograph, but it is definitely not.
Phone.
It's pronounced autograph maybe phonograph and it could transcribe sound waves as a visual
line onto a piece of paper, but it had no mechanism for playback.
Scott intended the recordings or phono autographs for visual study rather than listening to
it.
So he was trying to invent something that could record the sound so that he could visually
study it.
And then Edison invented the phonograph about 20 years later, was it called Phono, Phono
Autograms?
Yes.
Phonoautograms.
Is it phonautograms or phonoautograms?
Phonoautograph was the machine and phonautograms were the things that the machine made.
Phonoautogram is a wonderful Mr. Burns kind of line.
He would, he would, he would drop that.
Oh yes, Smithers, I recorded this onto the phonautogram.
Yeah, exactly.
I recall, I had a recording of this on phonautogram when I was a boy.
When I was but an adolescent.
Yes.
Uh, that means 20 years, that's like enough gap for the people to come back.
They're still living, right?
It's like, Hey.
Right.
We were really dicks to you back at that early recording party you had and sorry we haven't
spoken in two decades since we ridiculed you.
But it turns out you did record.
And I have a recording of you ridiculing me as well.
We just figured out how to listen to it.
The world's first DJ, the world's first DJ, the world's first record producer.
Because that's what, because we were talking about like basically like that you had to
play like such with such ferocity for the early, it had to be so loud.
It had to be so loud.
And then we figured it out later how to do it soft, like that's where, you know, you're
from from Bing Crosby to Sinatra to like that era of crooner.
Like we can't empathize with how much of a babymaker that was.
We cannot.
We can't go back in time to figure out that we used to have to have such loud things to
hear it.
And all the sound like this because we were kind of shouting, half shouting, half singing
me and my baby.
Yeah, and the very first time someone's like, you know, like the solitude, you're like,
oh my God, that's fuck right now.
Oh, hard.
I knocked my son into next Wednesday for Sassin' Off.
So hot, Bing.
So hot.
Oh yeah.
He made a wrong move at the corner of smart mouth and bullshit attitude.
So I had to correct that behavior.
I wonder if Bing is going to be in Hollywood Squares at Scoopfest.
We'll have to find out.
Who can say?
I don't know.
I can't wait to find out.
I'm really excited now.
Now, for those of you who don't know, I'm going in blind on this.
So it's going to be really, really fun.
I can't wait to just not know what impressions I'm supposed to do.
By the way, Scoopfest.com.
Go check it out.
Yeah.
End of September, end of the month, this month, come on out to Las Vegas.
It's going to be awesome.
It is.
Did you invite Tim to Scoopfest?
I didn't.
See now, Paul's dropped.
I actually sent him an email specifically.
No, no, no.
Paul, I know what you're going to say, but I did in fairness to Matt already send Tim
an email specifically telling him to stay the fuck away from Scoopfest.
All right, I guess we don't want him infringing on our zone.
We only have room for one hot dog microwave in this town.
That's right.
It was right after Matt told that story.
I just sent the email.
Fun fact, all you have to do to send Tim Jenison an email is just write Tim in the send bar
and it gets to him.
He's like Santa Claus.
Dead Lazlo might actually make it out to Scoopfest.
Do it, Dead Lazlo.
Come on.
We love last minute Scoopfest tickets.
Oh yeah, come on out.
In the meantime, we go play a little Jock vs. Nerd.
Oh, Schneikies.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock vs. Nerd.
Hey gang, long time listener, first time caller, I made a scooperty for you using questions
that I pulled directly from a grade four brain quest that I picked up at a thrift store.
For those of you who aren't old, brain quest is a long skinny bundle of paper bound together
with 1500 questions and answers grouped into categories that was used to learn things in
the pre-internet era.
Hope you enjoy.
That's Johnny.
So Johnny made us a brain quest scooperty.
Did you guys have a brain quest?
Do you guys know what that is?
It sounds familiar.
Well, it sounds like a primarily Canadian thing since it was called grade four.
Oh no, no, I don't think it was.
Yes, look, Canadian Scoop Crystal says I remember it.
First thing up in the chat.
I'm telling you, I remember it.
Oh, I'm sure they made an American version.
Yeah.
Nope, Jacob, Paul gets full credit.
You get none.
Sorry, buddy.
All right.
Tough but fair.
What are the categories are?
Before we get into the categories, I just want to say happy birthday to Didgeridoo Scoop,
one of my best friends since his birthday.
Yeah.
Happy birthday, buddy.
Happy birthday, Didgeridoo.
Early days of this show, having Didgeridoo Scoop make Didgeridoo covers of famous songs.
God damn.
The funniest shit.
It's still one of the best things this show has ever done.
That is a truly gold bit.
That is really funny shit.
Yeah.
Talk about your early recordings.
It would literally be stuff like, whoa, living on a prayer.
So good.
It is right up there with dog experts.
Thank you for that.
The categories today are science, math, geography, and grab bag.
If you insist.
Grab it, Paul.
Grab it.
Oh, thank you.
Matt, you're up first.
I will take it.
I will take math for four hundred, please.
Which is it the better buy three shirts for nine seventy eight or three thirty five per
shirt?
Oh, OK.
OK.
Let's see here.
I have to divide seventy eight by three here.
If it goes into seven, that's two times nine.
Three shirts for nine seventy eight, please.
All right.
Three shirts for nine seventy eight.
Less than that.
It would be ten o five the other way around.
There you go.
Paul, that was an example of the dramatic pricing that's going to be going on as you
shop now at Wal-Mart is going to randomly jack up everything that you buy.
I'll go with grab bag, please.
For four hundred and the song.
What color is the Rose of Texas?
That would be yellow.
Yellow.
And in reading the question, I almost reflexively said what color is the yellow Rose of Texas?
Hilarious.
It's me.
I'll try science.
That's actually what San Antonio stands for is yellow rose.
And of course, the Arapahoe legend that the flower got its color from horses peeing on
it.
That's right.
That is what puts the yellow in the yellow Rose of Texas.
The yellow Rose of Texas is colored like that because it's pay.
That's right.
That's how the song goes.
Which two planets have no moons?
I don't think Mercury Earth is one of them.
Earth.
Earth doesn't have any.
Our moon is a myth.
If you're flat, you can't have basically a spaceship.
Don't get twisted.
That's right.
Which two planets have, I think Mercury is one and let me see Venus or Venus has a moon.
My guess, Jacob, and I'm not sure, but I do recall pretty recently one of the planets
got reevaluated and basically called the moon.
So maybe that could work or not even called a moon called like a large body.
Yeah, it was like a large celestial body or right.
Yeah.
So what do you think?
I think it is Mercury and I think it's shit.
This is an old book.
I think it's Mercury and Neptune.
I don't know.
Wait, no, it's an old.
No, I see what you mean.
Yes, of course.
It's Pluto.
It's going to be Mercury and Pluto.
Mercury and Venus.
I was wrong.
So Pluto has moons.
I don't know.
Or it was already not a planet.
Yeah, or it was already not a planet by then.
Well, maybe.
Matt, you're up.
I will take math for 800, please.
The sum of 16 plus five plus eight is the same as the product of four times seven, true
or false?
Now, let's see here, 16 plus five, that's 21 plus eight is 29 and four times seven is
28.
So it's false.
False is correct.
29 is not the same as 28.
I'm literally showing my math.
Are you smarter than a fourth grader?
I will try grab bag.
If you insist, here we go.
Longfellow wrote the Song of Hiawatha.
Is it a short story or a long poem?
It is a long poem.
That's me.
I'll try math for 1200.
Very well, Hiawatha.
How much is 3/8 of 24?
Let's see, 24 divided by eight.
Nice.
We're divided by, wait, how do you do that?
Multiply three times eight, Jacob, and you get it.
Right.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
So that would be, yeah.
So 3/8 of 24, wait.
I am just so confused right now.
I gave you bad advice.
I don't know why.
You did.
Where are we?
That doesn't make any sense at all.
No, divide 24 by eight.
Yes, that's what I was doing.
But then subtract two.
4/8 would be 12, so it'd be nine.
Yes.
Well done.
Boy, it is hard to do math with Paul telling me things while I'm already confused.
Matt.
I will take math for 2000.
Holy crap.
Using pencil and paper, divide $50.40 by 14.
Matt, do you have a pencil and paper handy?
You have a calculator, because that would work too.
I know.
Am I allowed to use the calculator?
Probably not.
No.
Okay.
Let's do this.
So I'll try by multiplying 14.
So times two is 28, which means times four is 56, so somewhere between three and four.
So if I say three points something something, does that count for this?
Yeah, to get us on with the game.
Yeah.
3.6.
Okay.
There you go.
Paul.
Grab Bag, please.
For 1200.
Name the main villain in the series of Unfortunate Events books.
Uncle Olaf.
No.
Count Olaf.
Count Olaf is correct.
Saved my butt.
Is he their uncle?
I don't know.
I think he claims to be their uncle, and that's the whole thing, but yeah.
Oh, okay.
I'll try Grab Bag 2000.
What is a pistachio?
Oh, like is it a nut or a legume or a berry?
Is it a berry?
I bet it's a berry.
Or a flower?
I bet it's a berry, too, because it grows on trees, right?
Yeah.
So I think that means it's a berry, so I'm going to say berry.
Ah, it's a nut.
Boo.
Matt.
Ah, boo.
Ah, come on.
Oh, no.
Boo, guys.
Come on.
Thanks.
I'll go for 800.
Daily double.
Now for 3200.
Oh, yikes.
I was doing so well.
You were.
Which creates the fastest wind on Earth?
A hurricane, a cyclone, or a tornado?
Oh, this is tough.
Okay.
Tornadoes are tiny, but they're tinier, but I don't know if that means their winds are
less forceful or more forceful.
Well, I think technically a hurricane and a tornado are the same thing.
It's just that one forms over water.
Nope.
Cyclone and hurricane are the same thing.
A tornado and a water spout are the same thing.
Right, because a water spout is a tornado over the water.
Hurricane and cyclone are the different coasts for us, technically.
I believe so.
Right?
And it's the rotation, the way they're spinning, right?
I don't know.
Hurricanes in the Atlantic and cyclones are in the Pacific.
I think so.
That's vaguely what I know.
So if Hurricanes and Cyclones are the same thing, it has to be one thing, so I'm going
to go with tornado.
Ooh.
All right.
It is a tornado.
Look at you.
Look at you, with the big brain.
Look at the big brain on Matt.
Look at the $6,400 that Matt has now.
I may or may not be currently helping a fourth grader with homework all the time, so maybe
it gives me an advantage.
Hilarious.
Paul.
I'll try science for $1,200.
I'm the only planet that orbits the sun on its side.
Oh.
What?
What does that mean?
It means that other planets are not on its side, and one of them is.
Oh.
Uh, wait, what?
So some planets, because you have the magnetic poles, so I think that's what it's referring
to.
Is it referring to the ax, the tilting of the planet, or is it referring to what side
of the sun it rotates around?
No, because it rotates around the sun.
It doesn't just rotate on one side.
I'll have to pass.
I have no idea.
It passes to me.
I'm pretty sure it's Uranus.
It is.
Wow.
It's just like, it's tilted way over on its axis.
Interesting.
Okay.
I think it's part of why Uranus has such an odd orbit.
Also, the planet goes around the sun in a weird pattern.
Okay.
Because of its rotation and tilt on its axis.
Interesting.
Okay.
Science for $2,000.
All tropical fish live in salt water, true or false?
Oh, this is a tricky.
I don't know.
False.
It is false.
Some live in freshwater.
There you go.
Matt, you got geography that we have all avoided for four, eight, 12, and 2,000.
Geography for four, please.
Give the word for the farthest edge of a settled territory.
Over yonder.
I have no idea.
Pass.
Pass to Paul.
Border.
Oh.
Frontier.
Ass.
Nope.
Frontier.
Paul.
Uh, can I try the 2,000 just to try and win?
Yeah, you can.
I don't even know if I can win.
You can't.
What map symbol shows the location of a city that is not a capital?
Go ahead, Paul.
What map symbol?
Paul, actually, go ahead and just name a map symbol.
Dots?
Letters?
Mmm.
I mean, it's been a minute.
An arrow that says city?
It's been a minute since I used a map.
Mmm.
That is not a capital.
Oh, you remember the old bit that was in, like, every third movie where you'd have a couple
of people lost in a car somewhere and one of them would just pull out the biggest map
in the world.
Right.
It would just keep unraveling it.
It would take up the whole front seat.
Wasn't that a bit in Dumb and Dumber where they had to keep flapping open the -- or not
Dumb and Dumber.
Yeah, Dumb and Dumber.
I think it was.
I don't know.
I will have to pass because I really am at a loss.
That's to me.
I certainly don't know.
Matt?
It's not supposed to be a location of a city that is not a capital.
It's just a dot.
Microphone.
It's just a black dot, I believe.
I said dot.
You want to try a black dot?
Yeah.
All right.
A black dot.
Man, fuck me.
The fuck.
It's just a black dot.
That was the first thing I said.
Shit ass.
That's me.
I'll try Geography for 800.
Put in order from east to west, Texas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Alabama.
Alabama is the farthest east, then Mississippi, then Louisiana, then Texas.
Alabama, Mississippi, Louisiana, Texas.
Well done.
Matt?
I'll take Geography for 1200, Jacob.
Oh, I don't know why I asked.
Matt, close it out the game.
Geography for 1200.
Which is the world's largest body of freshwater, Lake Superior or Lake Victoria?
Well, I have to guess here because I've won the game.
Yes.
Yeah, you win no matter what.
I guess although if I pass, who's the pass to?
Passes to Paul.
Oh, good.
Then Paul can try to beat you for second place if I pass.
Can I?
Oh, that's true.
I think, yes, you can.
I'm 800 points ahead of you, Paul.
All right.
For games.
A $1200 question.
For gamesmanship, I pass.
Paul?
I'll go Lake Victoria.
It's Lake Superior.
Of course it is.
Lake Victoria is second largest, Paul is wrong and that is the game.
Matt wins with 8400.
I am in second with 2800.
Over Paul's best efforts, he only got 800 points.
Not my best efforts.
And that is from Johnny.
Thank you, Johnny.
Thanks, Johnny.
If you want to send us a scooperty, send us a Price of Skrite, Jock vs. Nerd, send us
an Obelisk, Jock vs. Nerd, send us all the things over at HeyScoops.com.
Go right there.
You can send us some scoop mail over there as well, right there on the homepage.
There are links for all those things.
There's also a link right there to buy some tickets for ScoopFest.
It's gonna be awesome and you should be there.
It is going to be off the chain.
Get there, please.
We are less than three weeks away.
It's happening.
ScoopFest.
Let's do it.
Let the panic attacks ensue.
Oh, in four weeks, I'm going to be so relaxed.
Yes.
In a month, I'm just going to be so relaxed.
Exactly.
We'd like to thank all the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
Did you send lists or we don't have lists yet?
We don't have lists yet.
Ah.
Well, normally we'd be going to our lists here to thank the people individually who
support us at a particular level.
So if you haven't checked it out, go over to Preaching Fun and select a level that fits
your budget today.
if you like me are a little shocked that we didn't talk at all about the new Nebraska
re-release album that Springsteen is doing, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com takes you over to our Patreon page where for
as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
If you like what you hear, if you think it's worth more than $0, head on over to PreachingFun.com.
Head on over to fartsinabag.biz, go to either one of them or go to both of them and make
two accounts.
That'd be fine with me too.
You can do all those things.
Go over there.
Keep this show running.
It gives us money to just keep the show going.
I don't know how else to put that.
It lets us do the show.
Pay for websites.
I don't know, we got bills y'all, I don't know what to tell you.
We're about to pay the Orleans a lot of money.
We are.
Matt, the Nebraska, the new gift pack of it, it comes with a Blu-ray concert that he did
at the Count Basie Theater in Red Bank.
Oh, well that's great.
Yeah.
I'm in.
You're going to go for the deluxe edition?
Jersey Pride.
That's right.
Yeah, I will go for the deluxe edition.
They've got a CD and a vinyl edition.
Both of them have the Blu-ray there.
All right.
Well, thanks everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See what the cone, see what the cone We're Bridges, final.
Babymetal I've seen in concert several times.
They're really, really good.
Thank you.
I think we should cement, by the way.
See you soon and then see you at the cone to the music on the pickup is good.
I like when we do live podcasts, people just sing along and I think that's the way to do
it.
All right.
Well, we'll see.
Yeah.