Oh hello there, I am so glad to see you. I want to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much, Richard Dunn, Roy Stansberry, Sarah Boyle, Sax Guy Jimmy D Scoop, and Slurpee
K.A. Motherfucker. If you are a what? I can't talk today. If you want be ice cream truck
driver. If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, head over to preachingfun.com. Preachingfun.com
is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows? The life you save
may be your own. Buckle up, I can't talk for the podcast. Hey Johnny, do you want to go
to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to. Great, let's go. We are here in the middle
of snowmageddon part two. I am broadcasting from the frozen tundra, where none can pass.
The white walkers are on their way, the wall is falling. It's all ice dragons from here
on out. Forget it, fuck. Well it's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social sitting
over there. It's Matt Donnelly sitting over there. It's Paul Mattingly over here. It's
Jacob the audio guy. I'm a little chilly too. We're preachingfun. Yeah, what are y'all,
60 degrees over there? I think it's closer to 70, but I do have a space heater going
right over here next to me because my feet are a little chilly. It's so crazy out here.
We got so much snow yesterday. It just did not stop. 12 consecutive hours of snowfall.
It's time for Pittsburgh, parking and weather, with the famous Paul. Yeah, so it's thick,
thick and rich up in this motherfucker. Like Gatorade. We've had to dig passageways for
the dogs to go out to poo and pee. There's a big mound of snow up on one side of our
porch that Ted keeps playing king of the mountain on it, so it's really cute and very funny.
They love it. The corgs love it. They got those double coats. They don't give a shit.
They're out there farting around in the snow, and then they come running right back as soon
as they get the littlest bit. Inconvenient, so they're like, "Well, I'm just going to
come back inside now." But they're ridiculous. Yeah, they're spoiled. We're very fortunate.
We did not lose power at all during all this, so we didn't get any kind of ice per se. We're
still digging out. We had generous, lovely neighbors come by at the height of the storm
yesterday, and one guy on his ATV with a snowplow on the front plowed most of our driveway,
and another neighbor came and snowblowed the rest of the driveway, and then it got another
six inches on top of that where they'd cleared. We had to shovel again, and I've got to shovel
again today before it's all done. And you called them back? You called them back over?
I did not call them back over. They did more than they needed to know. Where are you guys?
We got six more inches. Guys, we're at six more inches. Hello. Hello. No, they did great,
so it's going to take a little while to dig out. I was supposed to have my first new class
this evening for a new semester at Skit, but we put everything on delay because everybody
is buried in snow, and it's still pretty difficult to get around. Lots of schools are closed
for the next couple of days. The temperature is only going to go down from here. Yeah,
sexy temperature. So the tough part is going to be, as there's a little bit of snow melt
during the day, then the temperature goes way below freezing and ice, ice, ice, baby.
So we'll see. We'll see how it goes. I don't go back to work till Wednesday, thank goodness,
or until Thursday, Wednesday night, Thursday morning. So yeah, I got a little bit of time.
Ann had to go in today, but she's got that snow mode. And she said once she got onto
the main roads, it wasn't terrible, but still not great. Yeah. Unless you're a corgi. Unless
you're a corgi, then life is pretty fucking good. Yeah, they're loving it. Jacob, I wasn't
paying attention. Who'd you think the ice cream truck driver, the top of the show? Not
technical school port. You do not. No, no, he's on the next show. That's why I laughed
to myself before we started the show. Cause you said he hadn't been thanked yet. I was
like, I got him on the list. He's queued up for today. Too bad for him. We're doing a
double show today. So he's going to hear about himself on two episodes. Well, we'll thank
technical school port twice. How about that? Holy shit. A large black cat just walked past
my back door and it just scared the shit out of me. You don't have a black cat. No, I don't
own any cats. It should get the shit out of you. Large animal. He's coming for your, coming
for your puppies. Oh, it just turned into a human. It just turned into a human. Just
turned into a goth. Look at human. Well, we also found out we have a, we have a fire hydrant
in our front yard and during dirt. Cause we had about three days of real heads up on this
major storm coming through. And so, and doing her due diligence, looking up different factoids
and whatnot about preparation, et cetera. It turns out we are responsible for keeping
that fire hydrant accessible during winter storms because it is on our property. So really?
Yeah. I didn't realize that either, but funny enough, it's not really covered. It's kind
of clear. That leads me to believe that that water line has some, it's a big kind of heat.
It's a big metal fire hydrant, right? Yes. But it also, I think it has, must have some
kind of heat source in that water line to keep that all warm. You don't think it's moving
though? I guess that's it. It's just flowing. Everyone knows that hot water puts out fire
faster than cold water. It's science. It's just science. It's just a big metal fire plug.
Like that thing's going to hold heat longer than stuff around it. Nick Newman is giving
me the wave off, uh, that there is no heat under that, that, uh, fire hydrant. What are
you going to listen? You're going to listen to a fireman? I guess I'm listening to a firefighter.
I don't know why Nick gets all the fucking credit around here. I said it wasn't fucking
heated. He didn't listen to me. He sees a fire fucking fireman shows up, makes some chili
and says, it's not heated. You go, well, I guess it's not heated. I very quickly changed
my opinion on the, on the information of experts. Jacob, something, something I think more of
us could learn. I just was going to say it's 2026. Are you really going to listen to a
fireman tell you what, how a fire hydrant works? Right. What a dumb ass you listening
to the experts. You want to do your own research. Why don't you vote? Yeah. Get a glass of warm
milk, a warm, raw milk and a spit at the house. That puts it out. Did I talk, did I talk about
this? I was at, I had lunch when I was in, uh, when I was in a Burbank with my friend,
uh, Eli, uh, his wife, Erica, and then she's a doctor. Yeah. And, uh, she says all the
time now she goes, we're going to, you know, we, we think your child has, you know, blank
and we're going to, and our plan to take care of them is to do blank, blank, blank. And
they go, hold on, hold on. And they type whatever she's saying into like chat. Oh, they don't
even already have an opinion. I was already cringing. Cause I thought the parent would
already have an opinion, but they have to look, they're not that informed. Oh, that's
even worse. Yeah. They quest, they, they, they go, hold on before I tell you to proceed,
I have to look this up and figure out what this chat. GBT tells me about what you just
told me and whether or not I approve of the doctor's plans. This is why no one should
be using chat GPT. No one should be using any of this AI garbage. It is a detriment
to all of us. Absolutely. I use it all the time, but I don't use it to chat GPT. I don't
use it to question experts. I don't use it, but you're feeding the beast, baby. You're
feeding the beast. Just be careful. I just tell chat every day that Paul Mattingly loves
you. I want to get Paul's, I want to get Paul's name into that chat. GPT brain chat. GPT can
come to my house and we'll have real nice talk. Come to my house. I fed that beast a
long time ago. Uh, I remember when it first happened, I don't think I've told the story
on air, but I think it's been long enough. I can. The statute of limitations has run
out. Yeah. So I, when it first came around, it was fascinating. And, and, and, and so
I put every approved script of pen and teller, fool us into chat GPT. Yeah. And I figured
it could, maybe it could help me write more scripts. Cause one of the biggest challenges
being a writer on that show was writing 80 versions of, we'll be right back with more
magic after this. Sure. Right. Right. 80 versions of that every year. Try to put some cute jokes
in it, that kind of stuff. Yeah. So I put it in there and then one season, uh, all of
a sudden, like the producers started experiment with chat, GPT to see if it was like worth
doing it. All of a sudden I got like a note that was like, Hey, this chat, GPT stuff is,
it's pretty good. I know I gave it all of our scripts, like whatever, but I didn't make
that argument. And then they were like, uh, we, we had switched from a 14 episode season
to a 20 episode season. Yes. Right. Which means that I thought you had longer to shoot
it. So that was fine. But I got paid. It was about money. It was about whether I, how much
more am I getting my episode rate? Is there a flat rate? Like what's happening with it?
And they were dragging their heels. Uh, I was, the executive producer was not getting
back to me. And then they kept making jokes about chat GPT and replacing me with jet GPT.
So all of a sudden it was like three weeks before the season started. Yeah. And I wrote
a very, uh, uh, formal note. They hadn't hired Paul back yet. Um, and I wrote a very formal
note being like, Hey, if you don't want to fly Paul back out, uh, I happily switch from
being a writer to warm up comic for this upcoming season. Ah, because clearly you guys, I guess
don't know what's getting back to my contract. I'm hearing jokes about replacing with jet
GPT. Just make me the warmup comic and let's call it a day. Uh huh. And I wrote it to the
one is a producer wasn't getting back to me. I wrote to both executive producers and the
show runner. Good, good. This seems like a reasonable response because I was just getting
pissed. Yeah. I got the angriest voicemail I've ever gotten from the executive producer
of cursed me the fuck out. Like read me the riot act. Like I know exactly where he's coming
from because obviously when I did work, the two other producers called the, that executive
producer who's in charge of signing the contracts and what the fuck's going on. But that was
an awkward, it was awkward backstage a couple of times throughout that season. It was a
little frosty in the green room a few times, uh, that particular season of full with that
producer with his chat GPT for Halloween that year, Matt felt like it was pointed a little
bit at him. Uh, yeah, no, I mean, look, you know, yeah, it is what it is. Uh, I said that
like my current opinion with AI and chat GPT is like, we thought we were creating like
this God of all knowledge, right? That we could consult and what we created was like
a really eager, fresh out of college assistant. That's like, who's just like wants to just
supply you with everything. Sometimes they're right. Sometimes they're wrong, but like they
got your back, right? Right. They're just like, ah, here, maybe, maybe you want all
this. You're like, ah, maybe two of those things, but thank you. Yeah. You said this,
but that's not even true. What you wrote here. I don't think you researched that properly.
It's just wrong. This is entirely wrong. Yeah. Yeah. So now that's how I look at. That's
how I look at chat. GPT is, is like, it's a, it's a really, really wants the gig. It's
really going places, but right now it's just fresh out of college and it's, and it's trying
too hard. Boy, do I like using it to, uh, to sort information. I like putting a lot
of information into it. And they were like, make me a table that shows me all of that.
Yeah. Yeah. It works really well for that. That's it for the clerical and like clinical
things. It's good. You know, for knowledge and like advice, it's terrible. Oh,
advice. Forget it. And for humor, it's abominable. Yeah. Right. But for sexy dating chat,
go ahead. Let's go. They'll tell you exactly what you want to hear.
I'll tell you exactly who loves a good sexy Twitch chat, not Twitch chat, chat, GPT chat
on Twitch. And that's the following sponsor today's show, man, man, at least ice cream
social. No, no, I'm getting a boner. Stop. Absolutely. I can help you that boner if you
want. Would you like me to list seven things you can do with your boner? Seven things you
can do with your boner. Today's show is brought to you by, Oh, new sentient tampons hungry for
blood, hungry for action. New tampons from goof scoop in 2023.
Hello. It is that time of the month. I know because I looked at your calendar. Hey,
I am count absorbable. I am here to fill your vaginal cavity and suck up your blood. Yes.
Count absorbable guarantee is no leaks. A dry panty every time.
You never have to fret when count absorbable. He sees the wet. I will take it away. Slurp, slurp,
slurp away. It goes into my hungry maw. I count absorbable promise that no blood shall go wasted.
Please run to your local supermarket or big box retailer and pick up a package
of count absorbable insert upon. They are fresh and ready to be used in your vaginal cavity.
Insert upon what? I insist upon you insert upon.
Better hay scoops to check out. Why aren't they called insert upon?
It is a trademark way of saying tampon is insert upon. They should be called. I honestly think
that all of the world has kept everyone in the dark about everything for as long as they can.
Everybody just tries to obfuscate and confuse everything constantly.
Something wrong this week. Why are condoms constantly being placed on bananas in health
class? Use a fucking dildo. Use a fucking penis. What the fuck? I don't know. Everything's weird.
Everything's a fucking game. Everything's a fucking shell game. I don't know.
How you doing, buddy? It's all bullshit. I'm fine. I'm covered in fucking snow is what I am.
I don't mind it, though. We went out to a fancy dinner on Friday night, which was lovely.
Matt and Malia. How much of what you ordered was cut in half and put in a plate of molten cheese?
Oh, my God. Have you been seeing the videos of the thing? Have you seen the videos? It's exactly
what I said. And they're all just like they eat the first one and then they go for the second one
and the whole plate comes up because it's fucking glued to it. It's hilarious. Congealed. It's
hilarious. Oh, my God. We just chat GPTed Count Absorbo. Oh, my God. That is outrageous. Who did
that? Is that Laurie? My God, Laurie. That's great. Oh, no. That's really good. That's going
to be at Scoop Fest. I mean, that somebody's coming as Count Absorbo for John versus Dirt.
Can you save that for a sticker art, please? That is wonderful. My God. That's great, Laurie.
Holy shit. That's exactly what I was thinking. He likes. He's like, let's make a sticker out of it.
I know. Well, yeah. Well, I mean, we're not making stickers anymore, but you also just
ranted against using chat GPT. Now you're blown away by chat. I am. I know. I hate it. Well,
but you know, and it's terrible because I don't use chat GPT to make our stickers. We don't use
chat GPT. We have artists to make all our stuff. We don't have any of that. Stealing from other art.
That's clearly stealing from other art. It's clearly stealing from whoever makes garbage
pill kids. Oh, there's also that does look a little bit like garbage specifically.
However, it should serve as inspiration for the Jack versus Nerd costume ball. So there you go.
No, I do want people to come as Count Absorbo for John versus Dirt ball.
I am very excited about that. Nick Newman says that he is less disgusted by Count Absorbo than
he is by the cheese pool burger. I agree. The cheese pool burger is out of hand. It's so dumb.
So anyway, yeah, we went and had a fancy dinner at the little winery down the road, which was
lovely. And we also had my friend Scott and Sarah came with us too. So that was awesome. And it was
just kind of one of those nice little things. Anne was still on vacation. And this was a thing I had
planned for a long time, the six of us to go have dinner together. But Anne schedule, we'd made plans
with Matt and Malia a couple of times and Anne had to bail because she got pulled into work. So I was
like, hands off work. So I didn't invite anybody until Thursday. This is like, fuck it. Last minute
is the way to go with all this kind of stuff. And we did it. Social butterfly. It worked. It worked
out. It worked out great. And then I ran back home to get back on the, uh, the zoom and we had a real
fun scoop zoom night game night. And that was great on Friday night. Super, super fun. So yeah,
who was the one who was the big winner from the scoop hang? Oh man. Um, well, no one wins the
scoop hang. No, no, no. Um, uh, scooper star McScoop slot, general scooper star scoops lot. He won a bunch. Uh, and, uh, scoop shooter was tearing it up too. Uh, galactic president, scooper star, scoops lot. Thank you, Richard. Yes, that's, that's, and, uh, Richard, uh, did really well too. Slurpee CA came through pretty hardcore. Uh, yeah, we had a bunch of great, we had the cavernous buttholes. That was a great one, Leon. Yeah. Uh, I won one or two, but, um, yeah, it was, this is a really fun night.
We played one weird game, this murder game that we didn't understand. And, uh, it didn't, it was wasted like 20 minutes, just fire. But we were all having fun just chatting and, you know, having a good time. So it was really nice. So we'll do it again next month. We'll set it up. Uh, I'll try and aim for, I'm trying to aim for different nights of the week so that different people can play here and there weapons drawn. That was the game. It did not make any sense. Um, yeah, but thirsty won that one. I don't know. He didn't know how I want it, but.
Props to him for tearing it up. So yeah, it was fun. So we've had, we had a good week off and then we kind of buckled down for snowmageddon coming in here. And here we are. Unfortunately, Anne had to go back to work today, which sucks, but I've got a few more days to still kind of just literally chill out. And I am so, so cold.
I am, I'm looking for a, there we go. I see Matt dirty and Chad here. He sent us a breakdown of our scoop fantasy football league interview here. Oh, good. Coming down to the wire. I forgot. I know it's done. It's all over. It's all over. Yeah. It's all over. Uh, but, uh, let's see, uh, here's a wrap up of the 2025 scoop fantasy football league in the upper league. Jake Harrington team, 185 lumberjacks took the championship over.
Mike brosberg, the manable. Yeah. Uh, Otto Eisenberg, sweat house employees, uh, took third place over Matt dirty, savory, Maddie D being relegated down to the lower league is Matthew Burdick, Matt Matthew. Welcome to the lower league, buddy. I've been down here the whole time. Uh, I want to give you a welcome. We have free lemonade and I think you're gonna really like it here. It's pretty cozy. Do not drink the lemonade.
It is gone bad. I will absolutely be here waiting for you when you get down here. So no worries there. Uh, and so is a Troy Soto, uh, Troy Sato. I don't say no. How do Troy? How do we ever said your last name correctly? I don't know. I say Sato Troy Sato. Yeah, he's been, well, he's been obviously running, helping run this league for the very beginning. So he's, he's, he's welcome to lower league, buddy. Uh, and the lower league, Jacob Smith, Matt has team hassle.
Back, Matt has sold back that ass up. Uh, you won the championship in the lower league, Jacob. Oh, did I? Yes, you did. Oh, that's interesting. This is the first I'm hearing of it. Uh, you beat Paul Clayton, whose team arsonist gets all the TDS. Uh, he, he, he, you beat him, but you'll both be moving up to the upper league next season, buddy. Jacob Smith, everybody, Jacob. No, I'm in trouble next year. I'm in trouble next year.
Also, I guess I have to play next year. I guess after winning, I'm obligated to play another year. I joined, uh, 12 magicians in another league and I won that league and just want you to know how much worse magicians are than scoops at fantasy football. Just so I'm sure that tracks that definitely tracks.
Definitely tracks. Yeah. So Paul Clayton, let's see in third place game, Dave Peterson, whose team Tyreke of Alcohol beat Justin Jelenek from the Fighting Squirrels. So, yeah, that's it.
So if you want to join our league next year, this year we were better. We had like a Facebook group and the Facebook chat was a good place to interact and bust balls. So we set up some fun trash talk.
We stepped it up this year. For those that was the only thing I was missing in the other years is there was no consolidated place for me to make fun of myself. But this place was very, it was very comforting this year.
I told us, Jay, she was like, did you win your fantasy football league? I said, well, my my because she was asking about the big one that I play every year. Yeah, I said, oh, I got I got third place in that one. But I won the the scoops one.
She looked at me. She's like, you you played a fantasy football league with the listeners to your podcast and then you you won. That's precisely what happened.
She goes, did you organize this league? I said, I did not. I did not. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Thankfully, I at least did not put the thing together. I just played at least the illusion of arbitrary. Yeah. We had 22, 22 people, 22 people, 22 teams.
We have over 24. So if you want to get in touch with Matt Daugherty or Troy next year as we head into it, we'll announce it as we head into it. But they always we all pay to get in the league. And then they give a big chunk of change right back to us as a donation for our our podcast, which is very generous of them.
It's wonderful. Thank you. Oh, wait, that means I won money for this, too. Yeah, I forgot about that. Technically. Yeah. Yeah. So I took money from the scoops insult to injury over here. I if you if you look over on the chat, Leon has posted one of the winning T shirts from the T Fury battle, which is no AI. That was my illustration of a duck.
And then people put cavernous butthole under it and you can order that through TV. Great. I think the cavernous butthole ducks would be a great team to add to the football fantasy football league for next year.
My team name this year was I say horse, you say beans. So maybe go with cavernous butthole, having this butthole. The cavernous buttholes. Yeah. The fighting cavernous buttholes. Yeah. So I was 18 out of 22 players, which is pretty good. Hey, look at you holding your own pretty good.
You're regular Kansas City Chief over here. I'm 22. You're a regular Dallas Cowboy. I'm in the lower league, right? So they're automatically above. Oh, they're all just all guys. They're automatically above. Who's even in the Super Bowl? Is it happened already? Do we know it did happen?
It did happen. Paul breaking news because this airs Thursday. So yeah, the Patriots with a decisive victory over backup quarterback step up one head to seven. So they're coming into the Super Bowl with a lot of heat. That's a lot of heat.
Head to seven. Did you did you watch that game at all? I did because I'm on tour with Eric Dillman, who's in New England there. Oh, sure. Sure. And we were snowed in, right? Which I haven't got a story yet, but we were we were. I am.
I am the Snowden Hotel in Bloomington, Indiana. And so we trudged through the snow to the upstairs bar here in town, and it was packed because it's a snow day. Sure. And we watched what should have been an awesome day watching football and instead was one of the most boring.
Actually, one of the most poorly kicked games I've ever seen. Was it one of those games where was all field goals? No, it was all missed field goals. Oh, no. And all botched punts like right. And so that shows the outcome of the whole thing.
Huh? Yeah, it was. It got snowy and super windy like the game started, and it was a clear, beautiful, sunny day in Denver. Oh, and then like a blizzard rolled in. Like third quarter, it was clear and fine. By the fourth quarter, you couldn't see your hand in front of your face. Well, that was crazy. That was the weirdest thing on Thursday. I guess it was out here. Thursday was like.
Spring. It was weird. We were like, What the fuck is going on? It sunshine. Beautiful. Still snow on the ground, but just gorgeous. And then turned on a dime weather wise. Yeah.
And then, well, then the Rams in Seattle played probably the best game. I don't think the Super Bowl is going to be better than that game. No, I don't think so. I think that was that was a really good game came down to really like crazy, weird mistakes. And yeah, like it was a real battle. Yeah, it was fun. That was a great game.
I haven't seen you all see for the minute. He says go Pats. Yeah, I mean it is it's going
to be it's it's funny that like both teams will be an underdog story. If the Patriots
win it'll be crazy for a team that had four wins last year to take a second year quarterback
and win this early would be bananas. Right. And Sam Darnold has literally been shipped
off by two teams. And if he was the Seattle quarterback it'll be a crazy story for him
to win. If Sam Darnold wins as the Seattle quarterback the Jets should have to go to
the SEC because if he wins as the Seattle quarterback that means the Jets are so much
worse as an organization than we ever even thought they were. Also. No I'm reconsidering
we don't want them in the SEC. I was just gonna say I think every jet fan I know would
take that deal. Yeah. I think every jet fan. I'm thinking about what LSU is doing right
now. LSU is definitely running its team better than the New York Jets. I would. Vinnie Grasso
is a huge jet span. I was like I bet he'd be like yeah yeah let's do that for them.
Let's do that for a few years. Let's see how we can handle the Tennessee volunteers for
a while go down there. I'll tell you who else can handle a bunch of volunteers. And that's
the following sponsor. Today's show Matt Manningley's ice cream social is brought to you by Dan
Ackroyd's acronym Emporium. That's right Dan Ackroyd's acronym Emporium. Hello there my
friends how are you doing. How's it going. It's me Dan Ackroyd star of many films stage
and screen SNL alum and purveyor of the paranormal. That's right. I look into ghosts and ghost
research. I love to look up strange stuff and put vodka inside skull shaped receptacles.
That's my life. That's what I do. But my side hustle now is a new one and very intriguing.
I've decided to start coming up with acronyms. Acroids acronyms. Yes. You go ahead and give
me any kind of an organization and I will acronym the shit out of that. I will make
up an acronym for your organization sir. What organization are you with. Oh we are. I run
a car factory that makes silverware for for tables. All right. We're going to call you
spoons. Spoons S.P.O.O.N.S. And that of course stands for silverwares put on ornate shaped
silverware put on ornate new new shaped. That's it. Silverware put on ornate new shapes.
There you go. That's a classic acroid acronym. Give me another one. What's another place
of business. What are you doing. What are you selling. What are you making. Oh I work
in FedEx. You work in FedEx. All right. Let's come up with. Let's call it shipped. Shipped
will be the acronym. That stands for shit. I put in shit has has it put shit has it put
shit has it put express delivery. There we go. What do you know. She got it. I work in
Ikea. Ikea. Perfect. Let's go with Tuba. Terrible underwater breathing apparatus. Enter a scoops
and check out. Oh spelling is not the kid's forte. I misspelled weather. I went with the
wrong spelling of weather in one of my little advertisements for the class I'm teaching
on Saturday night out out in Toronto. You went with the H. Yeah. I went with the wrong
one the one that describes how the the atmosphere is doing rather than you know. Oh no I went
the wrong way. Yeah. So I still can't even get it right when you're to correcting me.
I don't even know. I just that's that's that's a that's an Achilles heel for me that one.
But also it's a blind spot. I think in the future it will be an advantage for me to have
my spelling errors riddled throughout my writings as it will be indicative of my non chat GPT
infused work. So people go oh yeah there's Manningly trying to spell again. He clearly
wrote this without any fucking help. Obviously from him is obviously him with his no no ability
to spell. You guys want to do a little scoop mail. Yes. Scoop mail. I would love it. We're
starting off with a with a heavy one today. We're starting off with one from the OG scoop.
He's in the chat with us as well. But he wrote this a while ago. Hey guys I want to reach
out and just say thanks to you guys and all the scoop community. In early October I lost
my brother at the young age of 56. Sadly he had suffered from mental illness and addiction
for most of his life and was homeless when he passed. He was in my town living in Section
8 housing for the past few years but drifted to Florida and ultimately ultimately to Las
Vegas in August. Coincidentally he was in Vegas during scoop fest because of ICS and the scoops
I consider Vegas a treasure at home away from home and the fact that he passed in that area
near scoop family gave me some peace in all of the sorrow and issues that arose concerning
his arrangements. I just want to remind you that you guys and the scoops have brought
me laughter joy and friendship and it doesn't go unnoticed. Thanks again for all the love
and support. Love you all. Even you. You know who you are. That's Andy. The OG scoop. Andy
I'm sorry pal. Yeah man. Yeah. That's tough. And then the whole scenario that you brought
up that seems really tough. I don't know how I would deal with. Yeah. With a situation
like that. That's really. And I know there was an issue. I know Andy had a you know just
all of the stuff that goes along with that. You know transporting the remains back and
doing doing all of that stuff. Right. You know it makes a lot of it makes a lot of work
and it sucks. Yeah. Yeah it's incredibly difficult. You have to almost delay your grief and put
on your professional hat. Yeah. Remember Anne having to go through a lot of that shit when
her father passed and she really had to kind of postpone her feelings for a while to get
everything else lined up properly. It's hard. It's incredibly hard to be responsible. I
can't imagine being in Las Vegas and be like my brother is unhoused somewhere around here.
That's a really weird thing to deal with. It's a hard thing to have to deal with. Yeah.
I don't think there was crossover. I don't I don't think Andy was in town while his brother
was here because Andy didn't make the most recent scoop fest but his brother was in town
during the most recent scoop fest. Gotcha. Yeah. Yeah. No it sucks. But the scoop community
of course is always fantastic. And that's part of what O.G. was was trying to say there.
And that is something that's always worth compliment rescinded. No never mind. Never
mind. I tried. I tried everybody. You heard me. You heard me try. Rejected. I will not
take it. We got one here from poutine scoop. Hello fuckers. What was your first clue that
you guys liked music as a kid. I don't mean bus dumping bands while on the island music
but the first time you knew. For me it was Alanis Morissette. I didn't get you. I didn't
get you. You ought to know. That must be what that's supposed to be. Auto correct. I had
a field day with this email. Sorry. I didn't get you ought to know as a teenager but when
hand in my pocket came out as a single I had to get my first CD and radio. What was it
for you. Poutine scoop. Poutine scoop. I know that my first CD that I bought when CDs come
out came out was AC DC's Razor's Edge. The classic AC DC album Razor's Edge. And I stand
by that purchase. I stand by that. I you know I've always been embarrassed about my musical
tastes and I've always been something else about that. Even like I shared a room with
my brother Rob and when we did homework together I would default to his taste in music. He
played the music in the room that we did homework to. Like I was still buying just like Springsteen
and Billy Joel stuff. I was going to say having watched that Springsteen documentary I think
you're I think your embarrassment is justified. Fully justified. The movie you said doc right
but the movie the movie's bad but the documentary's good. Oh I haven't seen the documentary. He
was playing like Dylan he was playing old school R.E.M. He was this weird British band
called the Levellers. I remember he was into whatever. The Levellers. He was always like
playing like cool stuff and then I was always just aping whatever my brother older brothers
were into. So yeah I would say I my first CD purchase I literally was like what's the
greatest selling CD at the time was Pink Floyd's Dark Side of the Moon. All right. I would
actually probably say is when when post island time I think like when Steve and I did reduce
and I moved to San Diego as our less interesting and less fruitful sequel. We had a roommate
Mikey there and he got me into all kinds of cool bands. I really got it. Tom Waits at
that time. Yeah it was just a bunch of cool bands came out of that and that really kind
of shaped the way of the music. I swear to God that I don't think like I'm curious how
I listen to music before I took acid once once I took acid. I heard music differently
the rest of my life and I can you describe that. Well yeah I don't. I was just a melody
person. I was into whatever the catch was. You weren't listening to lyrics. And then
all of a sudden I took acid. No. So to this day I'm still not a good lyric person but
I love arrangements instrumentation like how far where is the brass of the mix like versus
like where's the drums like where the keyboard and I get fascinated by arrangements and sounds
and quality of sounds and types of sounds. And I like all of that stuff in music now
and that did not happen until I took LSD. OK. I don't know Matt. I didn't often. You
know I mean like I can count on my hand how many times I've done it. But it changed the
way I heard music forever. I think you really need to watch how I listen to music. I think
you need to spend some time with Nine Inch Nails The Fragile. I think that album will.
I bet I would go back and really appreciate it. I think you would because that's a double
album and it is just layers and layers and layers. A lot of shit. I mean I definitely
listen to music in a very similar way. I definitely listen to it. I'm listening to like the structure
of it. I'm listening to like interesting side melodies and harmonies and all. Yeah I'm bad
about listening to lyrics as well. Yeah I remember like going to Beyonce's album and
like hearing she puts hints of her other songs and other parts of the songs and like following
those threads and stuff and the patterns. Yeah I like all that stuff now. But I'm still
self-conscious. You remember years ago when 50 Shades Closed I was an Uber driver for
two weeks. Oh yeah. And the thought of putting on my own music when someone else got into
a car stranger was like good lord. Like that was the most stressful thing to me was what
to have on the speakers when someone entered my vehicle. Yeah. My brother and I were very
lucky as kids for a little while while we were going to St. Mark's. Mom and Dad couldn't
pick us up after school. We had a babysitter for a couple months and she would come and
get us and she was a cool college student and she was jamming to the violent films.
She had that. Oh solid. In her car the whole time. And that first violent films album it
was fresh. It was brand new then. John and I listened to that a lot. That was her jam.
And so we both got to that. John even more than me. I think he's seen them in concert
a couple more times than I have. He's a big violent fems head. And then we just got into
a little more alternative stuff. He went to Pesh mode Tom Waits. I went they might be
Giants and body count. So you know we both had our things. We listened to all kind of
crazy shit. That's the thing. Both of us very diverse musical tastes. And I'm on a tour
right now and we're sharing a Sprinter van. Yeah. And we were doing a late night drive
and all of a sudden it was like we should put on some music and I was like I'm in the
front seat you know. So you have control. You couldn't do it. And I literally was like
what is everybody like. I was like I'm not going to lead the charge. I will not lead
the charge on this. I will not do it. I was too scared. I was like I don't think this
whole place is going to jam out to the Aved brothers. I don't think that's going to happen.
You never know. You just got to go for it. Southside Johnny baby. I say the other fails.
The other part of John and I's music and I think I don't know if this applies to you
or Jacob. Jacob probably you but we were in a region coming up through college and whatnot
that got a lot of bands. Tons of bands come through Ohio and Louisville. Oh yeah. There's
just a touring circuit through there with venues that are older venues that can house
you know three hundred to a thousand people for mid-level bands coming up. And at that
time you could go see a concert for fifteen twenty bucks. You know. Yeah. So got to see
all kind of shit coming up in college. I don't I don't guess that's really an option for
a lot of college students today. I don't know. I got to see this is a weird random one. I
got to see vanilla ice on one of his first concerts that he did when he switched over
to like thrash metal. Oh yeah. When he first came out of rap. All right. Yes. Like vanilla
ice ice ice baby would even still been on the charts when he was doing this and he was
doing like scream thrash metal versions of all of his rap song crazy. It was crazy. It
was at a place called the bait shack in Louisiana. And yeah it was like this is insane. I remember
going up to Ohio with John one time we went to see Alanis Morissette right before she
blew up. We saw her on her jagged little pill to her right before everything really got
huge. Like I said we probably saw her for 20 bucks. And Tyler what's his name. The Foo
Fighters drummer was with her at that point. Oh that was one of his early hits. The guy
who just passed away sadly. Yeah yeah. Tyler Hawkins thank you. Hawkins that's it. All
I could think of was Horton. Thank you Scoop Chat. So yeah and it was just you know yeah
that's cool. And I also got to see Guar at that same spot. I saw Guar twice in the same
weekend. I saw him in Louisville and then saw him again in Cincinnati. Oh by the way
Guar's cover of Pink Pony Club is so good right. It's just spectacular. If you haven't
seen Guar cover Pony Club then do yourself a favor. Pour one out for Odorous. Also there
was a really good there was a really good rock radio station in my hometown growing
up. So I could I could pull that up. They always had really good songs. They played
some really good stuff. They played some fucking bangers on there. And yeah it was like I
don't know what the number was like 106 or something like that. But yeah that was that
was probably the most that was most of my music growing up because like we had cassette
tapes and all. But like I wasn't going out and buying them. I didn't have we didn't
have cassette tape money. Not all that. I was just looking at my library to see like
what what what are my top like what. Not my top my most recent ones. F1 soundtrack I really
liked it. Springsteen Arctic Monkeys Jesse Wells Brandi Carlisle. Jesse Wells that's
good. Jesse Wells is killing it. Yeah Noah Cyrus Irish band called Seal another Irish
band called The Heistle Prophets. That was obviously inspired from Scoop Fest. Yeah yeah
more Irish music in my life. Two Skinny Jays Lena Hall Imagine Dragons Ava Brothers Brandy
Carlisle again. We got also service. Yeah. What's the skinny with Pina Plain. They still
out and about there. Now they're going out two out of three at a time and rotating between
the three of them because the cruise ship changed their policies about hosting trios
because of the amount of cabin space it takes up. Oh for fuck's sake. Yeah. Well there's
only one solution one. They have to pair up. Somebody has to pair up right. Yeah yeah yeah.
There's only one solution. They have to become one of those things like they have to attach
each other's mouths to their assholes. They have to become one of those things. They have
to become a centipede. They have to become a human centipede. So they can go on tour
together. That's the only thing that they can do. Hey guys it's Matt, Fiona and Phil.
Start fucking. Quick. Let's see what have I listened to lately. Oh yesterday I was listening
to Victory Lap Nipsey Hussle album. Oh I forget what triggered Nipsey Hussle in my head but
boy was that album fucking great. Gone too soon. And then randomly, boy talk about two
sides of a different coin here, randomly last night I was listening to One More From the
Road which is a live Lynyrd Skynyrd concert from the 70s. Wow. So that's my two most recent
Nipsey Hussle and Lynyrd Skynyrd. So I guess nobody living I suppose now that I'm thinking
about it as well. Nobody living. Nobody living. Let's see we got one here from Hey Scoop Get
Off My Lawn. Hey guys exciting news for Christmas. My wife bought us tickets for Matt's show
in Lexington next week. Oh hell yeah. I don't think it's next week anymore right. It happened.
It means I saw you. It means you came and we hung out. Yes. I kept talking about it
and she had to pretend it would be awful to see Matt for a third time just so I wouldn't
think that she didn't want to go or just so I would think she didn't want to go. Ah boy
is she right. Now the real question is will you do Battle of Dreams again? I'm convinced
and possibly wrong about how the trick works so I'll be watching carefully. The last time
you did it you kept my wife's dream and put it away for later. Still waiting to know why.
See you soon Matt. And here's an obelisk I did a while back for you guys. Enjoy Hey Scoop
Get Off My Lawn. Quickly before you get to that game. Yes. No Battle of Dreams was cut
from this show. That was a foolers run and the jokers they did not want it in the show.
I don't do that trick as often as I used to just because I haven't ever been performing
in an environment where I have I try to do it on cruise ships and what happened was I
found that the staff would not get all the papers out to everybody but they would get
out to like 20 or 30 people and it made it feel more exclusive than inclusive with people
in the audience there. People were upset that they didn't get to do it. Yeah and it's also
part of the prover that anybody can do it. That's it. Anybody can participate. Yeah.
So sometimes people don't even have the papers like what the hell do I care. Yeah. I actually
want to change the so right now Penn and Teller are doing it in their show and they have made
it much more sophisticated. Is it going well? And it's going very well and Penn has really
made it his own. And Hondro who invented the trick and performed the trick saw the latest
version of Penn and Tellers and said I'm not going to do it anymore. You guys are doing
such a better job. Oh wow. I did. And so he said I'm going to stop performing it. Are
they back at it? You should have started by saying that. You should have started by being
like I'm not doing it in my show anymore because Penn and Teller are doing it so well. So Hondro
and I have decided not to for now. Penn really liked that we were all doing it and like we
would all three of us would kind of like talk about different things we've learned from
different versions of doing it kind of thing. That part was awesome you know to feel like
I'm included in the group with Hondro and Penn. And I actually want to change the trick
for myself now because of doing crowd work of people's dreams. It's like I basically
I'm trying to like figure out a trick that could I could cut into more social media friendly
things right and put it earlier in the show not make it like a finale piece. I think about
asking people for fun facts about them or someone in their family as a go to ask instead
of asking people to come up with a crazy dream. I think I want to get like hardcore some kind
of fun fact. Oh yeah fun fact about somebody that you're there with. That's a fun that's
a fun ask. Yeah and I think that and so but right now I'm doing the Joker's tour so there's
no room for new material. I pitched it. Right. I said no. And I pitched it they all said
not funny enough so we moved on. And I have a bunch of cruiser coming up and then lately
I've been doing more corporates. I don't think it's the kind of trick I want to do for corporate
yet. Right. I want to like put it in a live environment first to feel what it really is
before I figure out what the corporate version is. So I'm trying to figure out when the hell
I can add new shit to my show. But the first time the first opportunity I get I'm adding
that to the to the routine. Oh yeah. Because it was finishing with a physical production
of the dream when I was touring. And especially for my show a production is a big deal. Because
I'm a one man operation. And I think I have a fun thing for that. I think I have a fun
way to finish the trick out. So we'll see. And you got that. And you got that prop that
I sent you for your new finale. Jacob sent me a sale on like Facebook marketplace for
like a giant fire cage like a disappearing. So you go inside set yourself on fire disappear.
Right. Yeah. The best thing about Las Vegas is people selling magic props on Facebook
marketplace. Well I I gave away my levitation rig on Facebook marketplace and we're interacting
and the person who did it is actually performer here in town. She showed up right. So we're
interacting and also a woman pulls up in a truck and I was like oh I didn't know the person
I was interacting with as a woman. And then it's that thing of like oh God we're meeting
over Facebook marketplace. How do I not be creepy. But then the thought of that makes
me automatically creepy. Right. Plus you were saying all of this out loud. You were thinking
out loud. Oh God a girl. And I just dropped my pants down to my ankles. That's what he
does folks. And I basically was like hi wife wife wife my wife your wife my wife my wife
my wife my wife my kids I have wife and kids. We are not. This is not weird but we ended
up becoming we actually end up becoming Instagram friends and now I'm going to see the rig in
action I think in April. Nice. Which would be great because I never put into my fucking
show. But yeah. So now to be in Jim Kramer show. Yeah. Yeah. But Lexington. So a bunch
of scoops came out to Lexington and obviously obviously like not keeping that fresh in my
mind that we did a turnout here. But yes. Oh yeah. Scoop John B. Mike Wens. Nicholas
Newman his lovely wife. So many scoops came out. I was giving out the chips Paul. You'd
be proud of me. I was given. I am. I'm very proud of you for giving out chips. And the
Christ Angel has a question stickers that Harry the grill edition made for me. Thank
you. And of course we huddled around because as you know everyone's entitled to free high
fives and to watch the video on my phone of the sex doll eyes explosion. Hilarious. I
mean it delivers. That's all I'm going to say. It's pretty intense. I've got to pull
that up and save it on my phone just for when people ask. I haven't saved them for that
reason. Actually send it to me. Send me the text of it. I'll save it. I'll send you all
three videos because you have to watch the first two before. Oh right. You got to see
that. Yes. The awkward set up for the buildup. Yeah. Yeah. I have it all on a messenger somewhere
but I don't have it on my phone. Hilarious. I was a little jock. I'm going to do when
I find the button versus nerd action. Oh am I. Yeah. I'm on the hunt for balls.
Oh. We got an obelisk jock versus nerd today from hey scoop get off my lawn. This starts
at $200. It goes all the way up to $5,000. We have double downs. We have super steals
where you steal the other people's points. You have regular steals where you just steal
the control of the game. And we have 50 50s. That's the other one. Yeah. We have 50 50s
just like the old millionaire game. And yeah. Let's see. The question is the $200 question
is states and it's going to me first. Nobody's doing anything yet. Let's see what this question
is. Which state was founded first? New Jersey, Kentucky, Louisiana, Nevada. Nevada is out.
We know it's not Nevada. Yeah. It was one of the last. Yeah. I mean, it's got to be
Jersey, right? I'll say Jersey. Yeah. Jersey. One of the original 13. Yeah. Oh, it's still
me. Right. Sports. If somebody's gonna steal, yell at me. No. Proceed. The Pelicans, the
minor league baseball team has origins dating back to 1887. What state are they in? Kentucky,
New Jersey, Nevada, and Louisiana. I mean, I think the answer to this is Louisiana. Yeah.
I'm just gonna say Louisiana is the answer to this question. It's Louisiana. Louisiana
Pelicans. There is a minor league baseball team. I think it's South Carolina. That's
the, that's the Pelicans as well. Uh, let's see capitals, capitals. Paul, you love capitals.
You ought to steal this question. No, I really don't. You go ahead and crash. Largest capital
city by area. Spell this capital. Nevada, Louisiana, New Jersey or Kentucky. Largest
capital city by area. Ooh, that's a good question. All right. Nevada is Carson city. It ain't
that big. You know what? I mean, Baton Rouge is pretty big. I would bet Kentucky. What's
the capital of Kentucky? Is it Louisville? Jefferson. Jefferson. Jefferson. I mean, Baton
Rouge is pretty big. Baton Rouge. Baton Rouge. I don't think it's Jersey. I don't think it's
isn't Jersey City. Trenton. Trenton is the capital. Oh, well, in that case, I really,
I think it's even less Jersey now. Trenton. I'm going to say Louisiana. I think it's Baton
Rouge. Trenton is French for the red stick. Interesting. Holy shit. It's Nevada. Carson
city. Carson. Oh yeah. It's sorry, Nick. I meant Frankfurt, not Jefferson. I'm confused.
Jefferson. Jefferson County. I don't fucking know. This is like God, we're on a, uh, uh,
like everyone, uh, uh, Zoom Twitch and zoom and yeah, which is zoom because otherwise
we'd have to just be corrected over emails. Preserve it for life. It's fine. I I'm fine
to be a question for the $800 question comics. Paul, the, uh, it switches over to you, Paul
for comics. Okay, great. Oh, it's always naturally switches turns when I, I missed it. Oh right.
Now I got it wrong. So I lost control. That's how games work. I understand moving. That's
right. That's right. What state has the most comic book stores? 103 is the estimate, Kentucky,
New Jersey, Louisiana, or Nevada. Ooh. Which state has the most comic book stores? Kentucky,
Louisiana, New Jersey, Nevada. I'll go Kentucky. Let's try it. I'm sorry. It's New Jersey.
It was between New Jersey. That's pretty great. Oh, and the switches over to Matt just in
time for magic. The thousand dollar question. Yes. How is Penn and Teller's bullet catch
trick performed? Ah, is it a mirrors AI search? Which state has the most magic shops? Nevada,
Louisiana, Kentucky, or New Jersey. Well, now what do you consider magic? Uh, are we
talking like stage magic or are we talking like who do voodoo dolls and shit? Louisiana
got it all beat. Oh, Oh, I thought you were going to talk about the other card shops,
the magic cards. Oh no, no, no, no. Those are specialty though. And it's rare to have
just a card shop. Those are always like multiple games shops most of the time. What? I know
the one in Kentucky just closed. So Kentucky is right out. It's gotta be. Well, I don't
know when he wrote this obelisk, Matt. That's true. That's true. It is a few weeks old.
I'm missing Lexington. There was a magic shop was only open for an hour a week. It was also
a clock repair shop and I went for an hour a week. He would just be, yeah. Yeah. And
the line was out the door with people holding the clocks because there was like one that
was a much bigger need than selling magic stuff. I still, I bought a chop cup and a
couple of other little magic things from there. That's cool. That's cool. But he died. So
it's gone. Oh, Oh no. Lazy ran out of time. Did he go with Jersey again? Let's try it.
Oh, Nevada. Oh, Nevada. Makes sense. It's cause there's a bunch of them in the strip.
Is this one of those that like Penn and Teller's a merch booth counts as a shop on AI or something?
No, but I can, I can name three here in town and that's, that's a lot. Three is more than
most towns have. Yeah. Most towns don't have magic time for audio video. $1,200 question.
Are they stealing? Nope. According to AI search, which state has the most audio video stores?
Oh, like best buys and shit. Nevada, Kentucky, New Jersey, Louisiana. All right. I'm taking
Louisiana out. People in Louisiana don't have money. It ain't about money. It's about, did
you get that base in your car? Did you want the jams? Yeah, man. I understand what you're
saying. They ain't got no money. I bet it's Jersey. I bet it's Jersey too. I'm going Jersey.
It's Jersey. Yeah, they got their electronics in Jersey. We're known for our malls and the
amount of malls we have. And so there's gotta be an electronic store in every mall. Yeah,
of course. Oh, let's see. I've got gambling. So $1,400 question gambling. Which state has
the second highest revenue from gambling? Louisiana, Nevada, Kentucky, New Jersey. Jersey
again. I don't know. Louisiana's got all the casinos. Oh, Louisiana's got a bunch of river
boat casinos too. Yeah. She's got Atlantic city. Yeah, they've got Atlantic city. Oh,
yeah. I mean, they've got casinos in New Orleans and there are a bunch of river boat ones. Yeah.
I like this play, Jacob. I like where you're going. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it is like, there's
more in Louisiana than you think. Yeah. That's what I think. I feel like is out. Well, Nicholas,
we have to go to Indiana. How much money is just better than the Kentucky Derby alone?
Oh, sure. Yeah. God damn it. Horse racing. Yeah. I mean, that's gotta be the Kentucky
Derby in the super bowl. I think are still the two biggest gambling events, like single
single day gambling events. Even the chat split on this all over. This is a crazy one.
This is a head scratcher. I'll try. I'm going to, I'm going to Atlantic city. I'm going
Jersey. It is Jersey. Jersey pride. Eat it. $1,600 question. It stays in my wheelhouse
drugs. I will steal. Oh, I think Paul said it first. Paul stealing. I'm stealing drugs.
He has the most drug related death. New Jersey, Nevada, Louisiana, or Kentucky. I'll go with
Kentucky. Let's try it. It's Kentucky. Yeah. I honestly feel like all three of us would
have gotten that right. No, you know what's crazy? Like honestly, the last time I was
back in Kentucky, this was probably 10 years ago. Plus now, uh, driving in my hometown
of Richmond, the areas that were just normal, everyday little side streets were absolutely
ramshackle crack house. Yeah. Death row looking just awful. It's awful. I think meth has just
ripped through that state. It's, it's meth. It's a lack of money. It's lack of good jobs.
It's lack of people, uh, feeling like they have, uh, somewhere to go. And like a, a finish
line and life to try to get to it's awful. I hate all of it. Yeah. Uh, speaking of really
good things, alcohol would have helped those promises. Less immigrants. God damn. Oh boy.
It's so crazy. Uh, Matt, you stealing the alcohol questions? Yeah, I'm stealing it.
You want you stealing or you super stealing it. I'm going to steal just because of this.
I got to stay right. Cause you're going to super still for me and I have to be able to
super steel back. Which state has the most alcohol related crimes slash deaths, Kentucky,
Louisiana, Nevada, New Jersey. Oh, this is a tough one because obviously that's gotta
be Louisiana, right? Or maybe Nevada. New Jersey is a huge population, but Nevada man,
people get drunk and run people over here. That's just, yeah, we were, it's our, it's
our state task. We just had an article touting that we were actually did not hit 400 vehicular
deaths in Las Vegas this year. I saw that the first time since 2021. We finally celebrate
our first time. No one was on the road first time since horse and buggies. Yeah. But Jersey's
so huge. Yeah. Jersey's big. And Louisiana, I mean, yeah, I mean, that's not, that's not,
it's not a sober state. Nope. Nope. I call it related crimes, but it's not per capita.
All right. I'm going to go. He's got a lot of bourbon. I'm going to go with, uh, uh,
Richard and Chad sub 400 sub 400. I'm going to go with Jersey just because of the population.
Jersey. It's Louisiana. Oh, good job, Louisiana. Whoa. All right, guys. Getting with it.
Paul is getting happiness. No, he's not. I'm stealing. If it was, I would have guessed
Louisiana the second of this state is ranked fourth in the U S uh, in happiness in recent studies
fourth, the fourth happiest. So fourth happiest overall, I guess, probably Nevada. Cause there's
nobody living there comparatively. Yeah. Like Nevada's population is pretty low. Right. Oh,
we are a lot of self-esteem down here in Nevada. We do. Uh, I feel like Louisiana is not happy.
I feel like it's filled with not happy people, especially right now. They're all snowed in and
iced in, uh, shout out to my mom's neighbors who, uh, took my mom and my, and my sister-in-law and
my niece when all their power was out generators. They have a generator. So my, my family stayed
with them. That's very, that's very sweet and neighborly. Certainly. Certainly. Uh, I would
expect nothing less from these neighbors. They're, they're wonderful people. Uh, it's got, okay. I'll
say, I don't know, Nevada. I'm not happy with this question at all. Oh, wait, no, I want to 50 50.
I'm 50 50. Oh, that got rid of Nevada. I got rid of Nevada and Kentucky, Louisiana or New Jersey.
It's gotta be in New Jersey. Then I'll go see New Jersey. Oh yeah. Living in the shadow of New
York and Philly. Just so unhappy. Supersteel. Paul is super stealing category birth over 80% of people
born in this state. Never leave it for residency. New Jersey, Louisiana, Nevada, Kentucky. Wow. 50
50 me there, Dick. All right. My name is Jacob. That got rid of New Jersey and Nevada. I was
going to say, I'm going to go with Kentucky. These, these were the two that I would have
questioned is Louisiana and Kentucky. Got to be. It is Kentucky. I wouldn't be surprised by Louisiana
super stealing game. I didn't think this through money is the category. The estimated net worth
of all residents in this state is $7.79 trillion. The estimated net worth of all residents in this
state is $7.79 trillion. Kentucky, Louisiana, Nevada, New Jersey. Ah, 50 50 me there, Dick.
That got rid of Louisiana and Nevada. Yeah. Uh, which I feel like we're the two easy ones to get
rid of. I felt the same way. The word residents and that got rid of Nevada and Louisiana as I've
discussed in this show ain't got no money. So once again, I mean, Kentucky, Louisiana needs to have
a fucking Patriot ongoing state of Louisiana. I'll tell you that just, just the horse farms alone
in Kentucky might be worth trillions of dollars. Yeah. Uh, you know, New Jersey, like I said, it's,
it's, it's a community. You got that old money. You drove me past all those mansions. They have
rows of mansions. Yeah. And it's, and it's, it's right near New York and it's right near Philly.
Yeah. They got that money and I got that money. Giving it up, giving it up for a new Jersey,
Jersey. All right, let's see it. It's Jersey. Oh my God. He got it all. He got it all. And that is
the game. Oh yeah. Atlantic city. Paul and I are tied with zero points a piece and Matt eat out
the wind with, with 16,800 points. Springsteen and Bon Jovi live there. You know what I mean?
Like it's gotta be way up there. There's some, there's some money there. Uh, thank you. Who,
who created that? That's Hey Scoop. Get off my lawn. Thank you so much. Get off my lawn.
If you want to send us an obelisk or any kind of jock versus nerd or any kind of a scoop mail,
head over to HeyScoops.com. HeyScoops.com right there on the homepage. You can sit as a jock
versus nerd. You can send us some scoop mail, do all those things right over there at HeyScoops.com.
Do it now. All right. Uh, I want to thank all the people who, uh, listen to our show week in
and week out. We really appreciate it. Um, if you want to help us out, uh, in a, in a way that
doesn't involve, uh, cash or money, uh, can you recommend us to a friend of yours? Could you pick
one person and one person only check out a couple episodes of our podcast. It's called the obelisk
scheme because the pyramid scheme is unethical. That's not what we're about. So recommend us to
one and one person only and see if they can dig our show. Uh, and that really helps keep this podcast
going. Uh, all these years as we enter your, as we approach year 13, 12, we'll never know. Oh,
oh, who could say? Well, we started, we'll never know. We started in 14. No one knows. No one knows.
Uh, and, uh, uh, I'm also gonna thank some of the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
These people, uh, selected a tier that entitles them to, uh, an on air thank you. And all of these
people, uh, have both a high net worth and very low, uh, drug death, uh, percentage in their
households. Oh, good job. Peter McDougall, Phil Rendley, Phil Tomlinson, Phil Guyton, uh, Phil
Guyton, by the way, he's one of him and Andy made me go back and watch the season finale of land man
when I wrote it off. They're on my list. I'm not happy with Rachel Forrester, radioactive scoop,
Ralph Barrett, Randy Norris, uh, Robbie Batia, uh, Rebecca Boonstra, Rebecca Gardner, Richard
Fastnot, Richard Hill, Robert Lyle, Robert Ward, Rodimus Scoop, Roger Edge, Ryan, Ryan Gravel,
Ryre Appledorn and Sad Fish Tacos. The following people have decided that they are going to conjoin
with a couple other folks in a human centipede style so that they can perform Irish music on a
cruise ship. Salt Lake Scoop, Sanja Petrovic, Scoop Bucky, Scoop Knack Pattywhack, Scoop Lindsay,
Scoop Nick, Scoop Nurse, Scoop of Henley, Scoop Skywalker, Scoop Hall's Drag Race, Scoop Mids,
Scoop-a-Luga, Scoopy Geek, Scoopy Ramones, Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess, Scoopy Bartfast, Scott Muldering,
Scott Roben, Scott Schofield, Sean Kellner and Seanathan P. And the following scoops all went
into a record store in Asbury Park and asked for the most popular album and that's how they got
their CDs of Southside Johnny. That's Sir Scooby McScoopers and the Third, Smells Funny, Smitty
Scoop, Sola Scoop, Soundman Scoop, Stab and Dash Scoop, Stacey Coleman, Stacey Westerlin, Steven
Clively, Steven Landon, Steven Biggs, Steven Marinelli, Stuart Wilson, Sugar Rossocio, Take It Evie
Podcast, Teddy Mueller, Tess Miller, Tess Sterling, That Thing in the Attic, The Bad Humor Man, and of
course, The Didgeridooche. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. If you want to be thanked on air
and you love this podcast, you want to keep it going, you can support us over at patreon.com/hayscoops.
What? That's really tough. Why don't you just type in preachingfun.com?
Come visit preachingfun.com. It's better than hanging with your mom at a pee pit.
Or if you enjoy writing down your dreams and then throwing them at magicians, go to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts, farts in abag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz. That along with preachingfun.com, it takes you over to our
Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. We are
dependent on our Patreon supporters. So please, if you think this show is worth more than $0,
preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those are the places you can go. Head on over there right now.
Yeah. It's pretty good. Do it.
Yeah. And thanks everybody for all the scoops who were able to stop by our Zoom today,
all the people who joined us on Twitch. We appreciate you for everyone listening out there.
We love you. Stay safe out there and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
We're preachingfun. We sure are.
See ya!
Life moves fast. It's fierce, persistent, determined. At City of Hope Cancer Center,
we are too. Our groundbreaking research and discoveries have impacted millions of lives
globally. Moving science forward with the hope, passion, and speed every diagnosis deserves for a
cancer-free future. City of Hope, Chicago. Pursuing cancer cures at the speed of life.