oh hello there I'm so happy you're here this is the part of the show where we
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers I don't have a new list yet we might get one before this one goes out I
don't know so you may or may not hear this part of the show that I'm saying
right now you might hear names instead but in case you don't how you doing you
good we look right we are recording a couple days earlier it's true if you
would like to be an ice cream truck driver deliver that fucking ice cream
shake everybody's fucking ear holes head over to preaching fun calm preaching
fun commas we're gonna sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the
life you save maybe your own or it may be a program hey Johnny do you want to
go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
hazel honeysuckle in the house today boldly strip.com is the website if you
like movies and Star Trek go check it out I like two of those things I like
Star Trek and the left one the left one only yeah this is another great reason
for patrons to get on the ball and put in that couple bucks a month to join us
on these live podcasts and zooms hazel is in full Trek regalia you can see her
in her I mean it's dangerous she's in a red shirt but yeah yeah she might not
last the whole podcast but she is and she's sitting in front of the Sun on her
video so I mean it's it could happen any moment yeah yeah yeah have any Star Trek
characters ever died by just being thrown into the Sun that's got to have
happened in Star Trek right I'm sure the actual person often they do oh that's a
good point Paul you're telling just a star plenty of people fall into stars I
think but I don't know about our son yeah oh I mean stars are other other
people's sons that's right let's not disparage other people's sons people
the Sun of Vulcan one of Vulcan Suns exploded and Osmos the whole sure sure
that was son of Vulcan Sun exploded and the osmosis and the whatnot then we used
the Sun our earth Sun's gravitational forces to go back in time and save the
whales using a Klingon bird of prey so sure for now we should we should hashtag
for now I don't think it took I don't think it took I mean what was the last
like proper Star Trek invention you attended oh god as an actual I don't know
I mean the last time was two years ago at Rio when I was doing a fool us and
happened to be there at the same time I didn't really get to go to the con
proper though I got to just see people walking around and well when was the
last time you like went out of your way and I'm gonna go to this Star Trek
convention got yourself a ticket did the whole nine and I have never I have never
gotten a ticket for a Star Trek convention you never enter through the
Stargate or wherever they walk through to go I have never gone through as a
civilian I've always been there for work all right okay all right then what was
last time you worked convention when they still had them at the Hilton so it's
been a minute it been a minute it's been it's been probably a good solid 15 years
since I've been in a very long time none of them have closed they're just on
hiatus right how long until the Star Trek experience comes back I have no
idea I have no idea well first turn back into the Hilton well here's the thing
hazel is on the ground floor out there she is amongst the people's what scuttle
butt have you heard about people trying to bring back the experience scuttle
them butts hazel I mean there's a whole chapter new book just about scuttling
butts the butts the butts are saying oh so much to do that oh they should bring
about it would be great they don't they don't understand is anyone saying oh I
should do that is anyone say oh I with the money that I currently have should
do that oh that's a shame yeah here I am just stuffing them in my ears and
wiping my ass with them why don't I put them towards Star Trek it'll make the
same amount of what I tell you a bunch of people though we're like hey you know
that you know that Empire strips back show you should do that you should do
one of those for Star Trek oh right that's that's that's it and and how's
that going well um I think we're gonna need another Kickstarter for that one
right but I use the Empire Strips back seems to be going well right I think so
yeah yeah it's a great show it is a great show I got to see that here in
Pittsburgh oh yeah yeah it seems to punch above its weight class it seems
to deliver more than what you're expecting mm-hmm oh I would agree with
that yeah first scene they come out strong in that in the first scene of
that show they come out just swinging they're real good yeah Jeff Loomis is
saying that Empire Strips back touring show was close to a sellout for an
entire month in Seattle oh wow so that you go on the ground reporting ticket
sales we love it we love well and it's and it's it's doing decent business in
Vegas it's got it's found itself a residency of sorts right oh I hope they
did well during the Star Wars was calling me right now I'm gonna put him
on speaker oh jeez oh boy the chaos yeah it seems like a lot of people were
going to see that show well hi Brian you're an old yeah sure going
no that's it you've reached the limit I mean by virtue of her age and race yes
there he goes there he goes big tribal chief Brian brushwood everybody I gotta
take the moral stand there Andrew heating everyone Andrew heat that was
heating that was heating for sure mm-hmm so there is crossover than Hazel
between the Trek and the Wars oh yeah yeah of course of course I mean I drive
a stormtrooper car and I was a Klingon so it's all good yeah right but that that
that hurts the idea of doing a Star Trek version of Empire Strips back you
think yeah yeah it's already done you think it's cannibalizing its own
audience yeah you're not gonna fly out to Vegas twice to see two different
burlesque shows I don't know I think there is a slight possibility that you
could man I really like your logic there you get the same person you could make
the trek one way more tech forward I don't know I don't know you know what
the key would be I'm gonna be shark tank here I'm out I'm out here's what was
that if is that a foot that was coming in what in the hell was that what is
that why I wanted to turn off my background why was that is that a
Horta oh it's a dick rock oh it's a big old dick rock it's not a Horta all
right but it might as well be say Horta one more time ball Horta thank you
Horta got that you know the way to do it this here's the successful thing they
just closed Muppets 3d we almost had it with Borg 4d at the experience but what
they didn't do they had stuff that would move your butt in the seat they had
water that would squirt in your face but they didn't have things that would
attach to your junk so if you get into a theater and you get Borgified in the
crotch uh-huh and the show literally fucks you while you're watching burlesque
preach then you are going to go see that show a couple times probably probably
we got to go back because you slept through the second half of the first time
you gotta go back twice the smartest person handling the Star Trek IP is
hazel honeysuckle that's right this person doing the smartest thing is
combining her superpowers as a nerd and burlesque artist and it's true hazel
what's your website it's boldly stripped calm boldly stripped calm and what will
people find when they go to boldly stripped calm oh people will find a very
excellent Kickstarter campaign where I'm where we are raising funds to create the
second version of boldly stripped I've noticed only stripped to a bit of
electric boogaloo a simplifying a bit of paring down of the options that was
offered a boldly stripped one like lessons were learned I think so it's not
where we can get the button put on it upside down or or to the left or to the
right depending on which box you click for delivery purposes like with all
kickstarters it's full of all kinds of options so that you try to keep simple
you must have understood when it was the first one was so much more successful
than you imagined it was going to be why did you just go right away what took
you so long to come around the thing about doing version 2 I had to wait long
enough until I forgot how much work it was that's a real thing yeah that's it
that makes a lot of sense so now you just launched you've already achieved
your your goal and your stretch goal yeah we made we've done three stretch
goals so far and you've nailed them all and nailed them all and you're gonna add
more stretch goals or you're done with stretch goals never done with stretch
goals yet because one should be a Star Trek convention watching Paul sit
through a show in his own taint tickling chairs one should be that should be one
stretch call I want to know exactly what he wants attached to his junk during the
show no no you would sort of device you think you want to know that but you don't
I thought I wanted to do that one time I found out I didn't want to know let's
just say the question implies that he's picky and he's not I'm imagining I'm
imagining a Borg's head comes up out of the chair in front of you and you just
take that Borg's head are you supposed to imagine the Borg says attached to a
sexy body on your own or are you supposed to be picturing skull fucking a
Borg that's what I'm the Borg's head yeah the Borg's head will be all on us a
skeletal spindle like the Queen did like the you know is gesturing how the head
would go towards him and Hazel yes it'll come out on a hanging spine and then and
then you pick the orifice this is the thing so either you can go choose your
own adventure you can go for an eye socket because it's a Borg yeah or you
know if you want to get wild you can go for just a straight-up mouth or you can
have it add on like it's got like a tongue attachment or something for the
lady - I'm going for the ear because I wanted to hear me I want to hear me
coming okay yeah you can go for the ear or it could be a or it could be a Borg's
butt with the words ass simulate on it that could be kind of cute as simulate
that's what it is Borg for board 5d plus ass simulation that's it simulation we
got there everybody who we've arrived who's gonna work there that's what I
want to know who to clean up after the audience and they all your remnants is
mopper resistance is futile and your remnants are puerile that's how it's
going space just mopper space just mopper someone's got to do it it can't
be any worse than the shit that was going down during chicken jockey during
the minecraft movie so upset about us disparaging you're right fuck plastic
sci-fi things in an open theater that you're just taking random shots of the
minecraft movie look this is just the next step in the popcorn buckets tell me
I'm wrong I'm wrong that it's just one more month until a popcorn bucket fucks
you they already sold a big old galactus head and he had big old ears you could
hold on the dune worm no the dune worm was just a that was the shot across the
bow and people did not answer the call and I'm disappointed
was just a pocket pussy but it was also one of those like unattainable goals I
mean that was it that was like a eight-inch mall you'd have to be the
girthiest tuna can motherfucker to even experience standard for everyone does
everyone not have see now that that's the popcorn bucket right there this is
how I will always picture hazel oh where do you think the butter goes that's a
butter reservoir for the popcorn you need a little butter refresher just give
it a squeeze just dunk it yeah hazel how many characters did you play in volume
one we did 14 different photo shoots okay so it was 14 is it how many hard to
come up with 14 more or is it easy in the Star Trek universe have 14 more
different characters um I haven't decided on all of them yet because yeah
you know we got we got all of the most obvious ones in the first book yeah you
can revisit them right because people do multiple you know oh yeah yeah I might
might redo some of them you know different situations or or eras who was
your most popular what was your most popular creature from volume one oh yeah
what most popular species oh the green one the Orion woman okay that's the one
that everybody likes by far when you sell I mean you sell these at the
conventions and stuff yeah yes yes at Galaxy con and do you start right do
they just start thumbing through it right in front of you right there at the
table did they just start going through them all well I ask people to I say look
at the book then they're like oh wow look at all these girls and I say that's
me and they're like that's you yes so way the way the opposite of what I
thought where I thought it was going that's really funny Matt thought it was
gonna be awkward but in the other direction yes no plenty of people make
it awkward too what's the most awkward somebody's made it um gosh I don't know
like do they touch the picture in front of you do they put their finger on like
a body part like some sometimes people pick up the book and look at every
single page and then just put it down and walk away data committed to spank
bank thank you recently I was at magic live and Mike gave me was selling these
really awesome books one was the history of song a woman in half and the other
was just a kind of like a history of magic but I knew they were like $200
books so I didn't even pretend to thumb through it I just I was I dared to read
the back of one of them and then I was like I'm gonna stop touching these books
all together cuz I'm not spending but yeah so but that guy had no problem that
guy just thumbed right through it left his oily residue on every page this is
why I have you know the table book which has been thumbed through many times
have you considered have you considered going kind of a Pat the bunny route
where like you have a patch of some kind of real tactile stuff in the middle of
the book that continues throughout that you know I don't know what it could be
Star Trek wise could be like a moon rock kind of thing or something I don't know
I don't know I thought for sure you're going Merkin like a silicone that could
be that could be yeah I'll just keeps moving towards fuckable objects the
ultimate goal today moon rock that's really not fuckable I mean oh come on
anything is fuckable if you try hard enough and important to storm any
part better attitude I'll tell you they call me lunar lander what sponsor today's
show is brought to you by the fine makers of this following product have
you heard of the product not yet oh a new film by Gwyneth Paltrow the gloops
the gloops that's from the microscope in 2025 the gloops I'm Gwyneth Paltrow I
used to be married to Coldplay now I make movies again because I got left
behind from that guy in jail now I'm doing what I want to do with my life
instead of making Oscar bait I'm making a movie called the gloops what's the
gloops you might ask well it's the passion project about my website called
goop right that's my website goop but the gloops is the poops you get when
you're living the gloop lifestyle if your poops are gloops then you are gooped up
you get it that's how it works me Gwyneth Paltrow teaching you what to put
in and out of your body that's how it works don't let others fool you this is
my real voice not manipulated anymore by the Weinstein company they know what I
really sound like I'm basically a walking talking Grover lady but that's
me Gwyneth Paltrow go see my new movie gloops in theaters only in theaters
equipped with Borg 5d fuckable technology and race groups check out
yeah okay I think I heard you all like skin care products are you all like
some what's some gloop I got it oh lord she's an alien
Lodi Oh Gwyneth Oh speaking of a L speaking of aliens speaking of aliens
guys they're aliens two nights ago I wake up to go to work I'm up at almost
3 a.m. I'm letting my dogs out and straight out my back door up in the sky
I'm seeing UFOs now I say UFO because to me they were UFOs they were
unidentified unidentifiable they were flying it was a straight line of about
five just dots of light okay and then occasionally lights were blinking in to
the left and right of the column and zipping in towards the column then
disappearing blink in zipping toward the column disappeared and then the column
was going up and then disappearing and then another one would start at the
bottom and disappearing strange were you watching an elevator no okay but here's
the fucked up thing I would say that modern life has accomplished its goal I
didn't have time to just stay in there and keep watching this shit I had to go
to work so like so I'm broken I can no longer three rocks off the ground
shoved one in your butt fuck the other two went to work I can no longer stand
there and raptured at the majesty of the mysteries of space I have to go I can
work so I'm just I feel like we're just broken it's over like I don't even know
what that shit was I can't I don't know but I can't even have time to watch it
all the way I'm out of here this is just thanks whatever you are just so
frustrating thanks that's fine I hope you're from space yeah I'm going to work
now did you think to get your phone and film it no I did not I did not I should
have but I didn't in the moment which is weird seems unlike you I know again
think that he's just over it I mean do you think that he's just like yeah yeah
they're aliens yeah that's kind of where I'm at like it's of course there's some
weird shit going on who knows what it is but if aliens showed up tomorrow would
you react with with surprise joy or or just kind of a board like of course
you're here I'd be like hmm I'd be surprised yes I'd be surprised and I'd
be like wait we didn't get ready hold on we gotta fix open up open up a flap and
get some of this heat out of here what somebody open a flap wait we're not
ready but open a flap if I saw clean up the aliens land in front of me I'd be
like oh man this is gonna be the worst Paul is right email I've ever got on the
pod oh it'd be so terrible so your first concern hazel is a tidy house when
aliens come you know like like the like the Federation they always always wait
till like the society is ready they have to achieve warp capability they have to
achieve your capability yeah yeah but they can't join the Federation until
they've like got their shit together right you know which blows my fucking
mind that the earth was ever even let in like even if you look at the if you look
at first contact and you're like wait a minute they came to earth they saw that
from Cochrane go warp and then they went oh yeah this planet just recently got
decimated by full-scale nuclear assault think they're good to go come on join us
guys but then they got their shit together for like you know I don't know
50 years or something oh boy oh boy I we were we we should never have been
allowed in the UFP it's all there is to it that's it preach yeah you know me
preach if I was on a walk and the aliens landed it would be so sad as I'd be
concerned about my family and then I would like awkwardly not be able to run
full speed back to my house like I'd have to like jog for a minute and like
keep walking fast then like jog for another minute and the aliens would just
be standing behind you with their arms crossed just looking at you in judgment
like don't give me wrong I'm one of you making fun of Tom Cruise running in
movies right like oh there he goes ha ha I mean well I can't do it I couldn't
even do a Tom Cruise movie if you paid me it'd be really tough no it's to be
fair though I would I'd love to give it a shot so if anybody would like to pay
me Tom Cruise's going rate to make a movie I will happily attempt to make
that movie absent of money I'm just doing the Tom Cruise fitness challenge
and that's where I will try to become a better runner and also strap my thing
strap myself onto various dangerous objects and see if I can pull off a
classy stunt at my age so that's those are the two things I thought you were
gonna say strap myself to various objects and fuck them like Canada RMS Nicole
Kidman shout myself to those objects meanwhile the Penelope Cruz longing for
a for a nice piece of cod the whole time you know what I could really go for right
now some cod did this isn't that possible come out or it hasn't come out
yet nobody cares that's right yeah yeah nobody cares anymore
nobody gives a rat fuck that first the first one the first one that he had the
audacity of that last one to be like oh it's a two-parter and it's also 18 hours
long like eat my butt sir no one has time for your garbage bullshit but the
end but the bad guys might get an AI thing Paul you're not totally wrapped up
in that that apparently was the whole thing like the the the MacGuffin they
were having like all these discussions about what's the MacGuffin what's the
MacGuffin and Tom Chris finally like just nuclear bombs just make it nuclear
bombs and that's what they did it's like bad guys have nukes good guys need to
stop them done this is so dumb I don't think it was I thought it was like an AI
thing like a computer that could that could control nuclear bombs oh got it
okay oh that's what sunk that submarine that submarines full of nuclear bombs
that's the whole beginning of the movie which is all I watched how many mission
impossible movies has Tom Cruise made everybody no price is right rules just
how many how many hazel's hazel's correct she just yawned while you asked
that yeah yeah that's correct that's the right answer that's exactly it it's
boring because it's cuz nothing's gonna happen the answer is fine the answer is
eight and I had no idea you know just three you know what I think um fast and
furious was benefited from the tragic passing of Paul Walker in so much as
something could actually happen to a main character but I guess in the in the
fictional world he's not really dead is that right are they gonna AI him back
into the new movie is that what I'm hearing now I don't know wait Paul what's
his name Walker Paul Walker they're gonna AI Paul Walker into a fast and
furious movie I think so let's see here the new one seems like a mistake I think
you're right Matt I think it's a terrible mistake and a terrible precedent to set
to bring back dead people into movies yeah but if it goes I'm totally making
Ben her too and I'm bringing everyone back Ben her too remember they did a
Ben her remake today like who the fuck has a ball it was it was remarkably bad
right but who even has the balls to even go you know what we should make again
Ben her yeah what epic the fuck could you even add to that oh my god I love
remaking things they do the upcoming the upcoming fast and furious movie the
upcoming final fast and furious movie rumored to be titled fast 11 fine Jesus
Christ set for release in April of 27 is planning to feature Paul Walker's
character Brian O'Connor will likely use CGI and potentially AI to recreate his
likeness Oh not his corpse they're not gonna string him up like a fucking puppet
weekend at Bernie's them I'm glad they told us how it's all about family not
some child he didn't know he had dressing up like him and trying to look
like him in the movie because it's been that long it has been that long his his
kids are alive I think he really is like supposed to be like on vacation kind of
thing in the storyline he's on hiatus I don't know or maybe he's dead in the
story and then they're gonna bring it back but everybody dies in that thing
now too and they bring him back same thing with what's your head hey whatever
Paul he's family all right and we take care of family family never dies family
never dies here's Paul fucking Walker family never dies take a look you think
I'm joking motherfucker look family never dies this one literally never dies
they could do they could do a crossover could call it Paul walking dead I've
literally never been more interested in the Fast and Furious franchise I bet
Kirkman could get on board he's a magician he could write some great shit
for that he could make it work can owes Atlanta tax credits they help make it
happen no Paul walking dead and any thoughts for putting video content as
part of your attached to your your your magazine with with animated Paul Walker
driving you around funny you say that because no except for the Paul Walker
part yeah we okay so one of the shoots we're gonna do is a Ferengi mm-hmm oh
whichever you know I know everyone was clamoring yes well the thing is tell
tell everyone the thing about the Ferengi ladies the thing about the
Ferengi ladies and they're not they're not a very you know progressives progressive
civilization not at all but their women their women all are just naked all the
time and they're not allowed to do business profit which is like their
their whole society is about earning profit right so the women are naked and
they can't work and like the kinkiest thing is for women to wear clothes like
them and this is this is how they they got the the main characters like the
main Ferengi character to put it on would land them in jail is that what was
that what happened ah it's like oh the main character like goes home and his
mom's like wearing clothes and he's like oh gross gross mom and then she takes
their clothes off and he puts his head in her lap oh boy it's weird no what you
said sounds great yeah yeah so the rest of the show like this so to do a risk a
Ferengi female boudoir shoot as it were yeah you're gonna have to put some stuff
on she's gonna put it on yeah yeah it's gonna be the only clothes character in
the entire book I mean that could be funny to have it go in reverse to start
off it really would go oh it's it's definitely going in reverse completely
starkers and then yeah full clothes by the end of it that's what that would be
a really funny burlesque routine like a bad camp act you know where you just
keep putting on clothes and so you're like giant like a snowman you know oh
what was that yeah that guy wore all the t-shirts how many t-shirts did he get
to didn't hurt himself real bad doing that one guy who's famous for wearing
t-shirts Paul just asked three questions none of us have any idea what he's
talking about I just remember this guy wearing so many t-shirts and it got
really bad and I don't I think it was I think it hurt him Jacob what are you
even searching for what did you type into the search bar I pulled up a search
bar and have yet to type anything very curious what words you know what did a
guy hurt himself here it is too many shirts to death calm here we go I don't
think he died did a guy hurt himself by putting on too many shirts let's see
here Google is shrugging at me Google has no idea I'm just picturing Hazel
wearing like a thousand outfits to look like it looks like almost like Jabba the
Hut with a tiny head out of a bunch of clothes and then a bunch of Ferengi dudes
just like totally on the ground just like wasted from the eroticism they've
experienced just yeah just lounge opium den like napping just throwing bars of
Latin America like like like you know those those machines that throw a bunch
of money yeah but they make it rain guns yeah yeah which is like which are like
metal yeah go press latinum would bean somebody in the noggin it's like going
to a strip club in Canada man they make it hail loonies right in your hand you
got all the loonies going up there oh man I got another loony bruise above my
eye yeah no your honor it's from a loony it's from a loony yeah yeah galactic
president scooper star my scoops a lot talking about ear rubbing equals Ferengi
grooming or gooning rather yes yeah it is it's umox yeah so you're sitting down
in the writers meeting for one of the Star Trek's right and you know I had no
no I got the world guys Ferengi right they're a little backwards all right
everyone's naked everyone's like I'm listening like and then you know what
everybody else is all of this project Donnelly you're handling the Ferengi's
by yourself go on and you goon by tugging your ears I regret my decisions
film this yesterday this was scooper Nova girls saying I'll explain the DS 9
documentary and there is a story that Armand Shimmerman tells because he was
one of the original Ferengi in deep space not or in the original or in next
generation right they were originally gonna be the new big bads they were
gonna be like the Klingons of next generation ah that was the start told us
about this before I think I have and and there was there's a scene where they're
on this planet and they've got you know the Frank you have these fucking laser
whips and you know they're coming hard for the fed yeah man Marauder Moe type
shit yeah look out their energy whips yeah but they ended up being really
goofy that's it they they they use the sonic weapon against them and the
directors like oh yeah grab your heads and like writhe around in pain and Armand
was like you know if we do this we're gonna look stupid as fuck and nobody's
gonna think nobody's gonna think that these guys are scary at all ever again
and he was dead right and they became these very clownish aliens from that
point on but they wanted they wanted to set them up as like the big bad alien
species for the for the whole series and that no one bought it no no one's like
those those goofballs grabbing their big Dumbo ears and screaming no I don't give
a shit about them yeah laser energy whips energy whip I have myself an
energy whip sir I do declare if you wish to get more forceful let us adjourn to
the next parlor and we shall settle this like gentlemen with our energy whip sir
Desmond fits me my sonic gun this this ragamuffin has a laser whip do not bring
a sonic disruptor to a laser whip fight sir I hope you enjoy the tanky zip of my
energy whip and that was I shall make a sandwich of your innards what that was
of course the episode that Tennessee Williams wrote for Star Trek Hazel Leon
Casab just asked you about what was there a something in the first boldly stripped
what what is that and is it an axiom a talaxian that's how you say that okay and
is there a talaxian in the second boldly stripped and what is it not so far come
on what's it so axiom it's a neelix it'd be a whole cooking scene it's a neelix
come on Jacob it's a neelix moving on it's a neelix and expect me to know what
the fuck you're talking about again this is that this is what you you would lose
your mind Jacob and Matt if you were ever in these writers rooms because
neelix that's correct neelix was supposed to be the Voyager breakout
character they're like oh this whole thing this is gonna be such a great
thing this neelix character and they fucked it up six ways to Sunday they had
him dating a twelve-year-old it's like guys no no no she was she was like yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's awful I was trying to make it sound a little
more yeah okay so yeah so what it like this looks like she Tara's ugly step
cousin oh the neelix wait there was a female problem is female to Lexi and
Ethan Phillips they don't allow female to laxians on the internet I bet you
anything Ethan Phillips is a chill guy from what I've seen of him he seems like
a nice dude the actor who portrayed neelix that character is so fucking
annoying and stupid I don't think it's Ethan Phillips's fault I think he's
great exactly that's what I'm saying but he's kind of like oh he loves to like
sell stuff to people and he's the cook yeah so he's always cooking weird alien
things okay yeah let's make a hairy farting cheetah
clown that makes food no one likes let's do that let's put that in the chin hair
he's everything and then they bring this they bring this like hot girl onto the
show but they're like oh yeah her race only lives to like 10 so she's full
grown at like two years old and so she's dating the weird cheetah guy I think we
know who a secret executive producer was on this
by Diddy just a bevy a bevy of bad ideas neelix or flocks who is better asked
scooper nova girl flocks by leaps and bounds leaps and bounds X spells flocks
huh yeah dr. locks he can inflate his face he's all I care from a planet of
swingers yeah go on every every denobulant marriage is at least like
several different people they all have they all like have you know kids with
that one kids with this one his wife comes onto the ship at one point it
starts flirting with with the with the engineer and he's like really
uncomfortable and that's fun yeah I mean that's from enterprise just do it mm-hmm
take a big step for the commercial come on trip yeah let's just do it let's do
any other commercial hey you know who else is super turned on Star Trek talk
I don't know somebody probably is somewhere the following sponsor today
shows brought to you by half a glass of water from Pommy bastard scoop in 2021
today shows brought to you by half a glass of water hey there everybody it's
me Tim the otter I'm here to tell you about half a glass of water that up but
up up up if you're thirsty don't you wait make sure that you do hydrate have
a drink before it's too late have half a glass of water you know kids a lot of
the times we don't want to drink everything that's in our cup but we need
to get a little more h2o in the old body flow to make sure our days go smooth and
we're feeling ready to roll if your tongue is dry and you need a drip well
go on over to the sink don't slip and pour yourself half half a glass of water
drink it on down it's a big old gulp have some it's delicious and it's gonna
help you if you don't get enough h2o your cells can't repair themselves in
the proper way do you understand what I'm talking about that's the way to do
it hazel get yourself half a glass of water a day at least 8 to 12 ounces and
as much as you can after that and I think you're gonna find that after you
have that first half a glass you're gonna want to go back for the other half
that's right yeah so if you're tired worn down and you just can't go there
might be something you need to know a little bit of that h2o have half a glass
of water yeah make sure you keep drinking you motherfuckers wait hey
scoops a check out I think Jacob wrote the end got your attention doesn't it
ugly bags of mostly water says galactic president scooper star may scoops a lot
wait I felt like Leon popped out for a second to say something and I missed it
what'd he say Leon were you talking to us or were you just talking we just did
sorry hit the button in my pocket great he's got a button in his pocket are you
just happy to see us it could be the nukes get him Tom Cruise no oh Greg just
bought himself a ticket to scoop fest and you should too yeah Greg just got an
email from Greg saying that he bought himself a ticket to scoop fest scoop fest
comm head over there we're doing it in September hazel's gonna be there she'll
be selling books of boldly stripped I bet she'll do an act at some point you
'll be holding the variety show again hazel yes great have plans oh yeah guys
seriously our variety show when that shit hits you leave there like god damn
I saw the best thing in Vegas and you really did you've seen probably one of
the best shows in Vegas after you've seen our variety show mm-hmm if you
combined all the ticket prices for all the people that we pull favors from to
get good lord play our variety show it would be one very expensive ticket it'd
be incredibly expensive yeah yeah we're like a best of Broadway if that doesn't
make you run race to the internet to buy your ticket to scoop fest we're like the
best of Broadway our state fair is a great state fair mmm-hmm all right well
hazel so what should you already are you most looking forward to already from a
book yeah yeah no just in general you got some just in life what's an alien
species that you're really looking forward to uh to getting dressed up as
okay so we're gonna do a duo shoot with a friend of mine a model named Ashlyn
Dye and we're gonna we're gonna cross streams and do a star wars oh snap see
same audience told you yeah yeah you're right we won't do the Star Trek show
fine but we're gonna do we're gonna do the Twi licks that have the tentacle II
what do they call the Twi licks you said we like the ten tentacle Twi licks only
two figure two well doesn't help the alliteration I guess two does two tentacle
yeah okay yeah I'm sure the zoom what Twi licks are cuz I didn't know what
they were it was the the one that was the exotic dancer in Jabba's Palace yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah they have two big floppy horns why are their
horns so floppy why are they such a floppy horned people they're not horns
they're they're called lekku actually they're like zoom tight and they're
bred that way because they've gotten more docile as they reproduce because
no one wanted to keep the aggressive ones as pets so slowly but surely
they've gotten dangly they just got floopy they got droopy over time the
same thing happens that happened a basset hound ears no did I did I do the
beholder and scoop fest yes yes I did yeah was that last year or the last one
we did right that was what you did yeah that's what yeah that was the D&D thing
yeah yeah yeah um thing with the eyeballs that was great I've been I've
watched Sandman I finished up Sandman on Netflix okay you watched the second
season I did I started to watch that that animated kind of wrap up of the
final first season that they just put out uh-huh and I and I and I couldn't
even get through it I was too depressed I had to stop it was it I was like our
where where where's the population at with Neil Gaiman are we allowed to say
we watch Sandman are like salmon are we not allowed to say we like Sandman I was
Neil I mean he he's problematic as hell at this point yeah he's been accused of
being a dirty bird that's right at home yeah yep and what stinks I thought
Netflix did a really good job of creating the comic to the series I didn't
watch the animated thing I just watched the actual episodes smart because I had
to nope out after I watched the first five minutes I was like oh god I can't
take this this is and I basically was like breaking my heart true to the comic
look at it go and I think it's a fascinating world that was created that I
really liked when I read it because I was like yeah it doesn't really advance
it doesn't like it's not driven by like a plot plot more like you just keep
exploring worlds and the rules that go with the world's similar what we've
been just doing here today and so I thought like it was really neat
compelling it's also great to watch before going to bed it's not it's not a
compelling plot point with cliffhangers so you can just watch one weird dreamy
scene and go right to bed no problem and then I was like I don't think I can talk
terrified about sleeping at all I've worried about whatever happens once I
fall asleep can be completely leveraged against me and generations of my family
no problem and oddly enough as you're watching it though the character dream
which obviously is influenced by Neil Gaiman himself and the whole fashion
trend that came out of that and it's all about guy regretting his past and moving
around see if he can go about possibly changing who he is and I was like man
I'm trying to keep my mind off of things and this thing is just poking the bear
of what's happening in real life and it's really strange oh I have a hard time
with those shows he does not the character does not have a good
relationship with any of his exes I'll tell you that much right now and so
wouldn't it be great to see a show one time where everybody's like oh yeah that's
my ex we get along fine but there are actors in it that are amazing I enjoyed
the first season very much she is really fantastic yeah I watched a few episodes
of the first season it was good I don't know why I stopped watching it I might
have just forgotten about it maybe I went to sleep you might have seen the
whole thing it was only like eight episodes Jacob oh maybe I saw all of it
that yeah cuz they weren't long right no yeah now an hour okay yeah but let's see
you guys want to do a little scoop mail here oh my gosh more than anything on
earth let's do a little scoop mail we are one from dirty rotten cone artist
dearest Paul your gnome repair operation from episode 1194 wouldn't make an
excellent YouTube channel you could film your gnome repairs and put them up as
fun videos you could then parlay that and then selling the gnomes from the
videos people could send their gnomes in for restorations and you could film
those and charge for it the money prints itself I look forward to the
meteoric rise of Paul and Anne Anne's gnome dome fucking with the face that's
the dirty rotten cone artist Paul have you thought about opening up a gnome
hospital we thought about it we actually did talk about it a little bit and was
like maybe we could just do this and I was like oh no I'd love to do that
today so Paul might might be having problems here I said you know and said
maybe we could just do this and I thought yeah that'd be great but I don't
I don't think so oh I'm gonna work out it's over guys it turns out gnome
repair does not provide health care so but gnome repair content does provide
extra money that is true I'm not ruling it out in the
future fixing up stuffed animals I'm not ruling it out in the future I'll tell
you one problem though with some of that repair video shit I don't know if you
guys are how much how deep do you guys go in repair videos because I watch quite a
bit awesome all I'm doing I used to watch a lot of them like fixing old game
systems and whatnot but it turns out like a lot of those channels just fuck
up the product and then pretend to repair it you know what I mean like
don't intentionally they're filthy liars yeah yeah yeah yeah Jeff Loomis do this
on your video you could you could like carry a gnome up to the roof and then
parachute it off and then you'd have to fix the gnome they go oh no my gnome you
could just uh you gotta be what if you took the gnomes and you know just you
turn them into something you can fuck I'm glitching out sure now you're
glitching up your honor he's too busy fucking that gnome glory gnomes is a
great name I'm back Paul has terrible internet today recording his own end but
but he has real bad internet hey Fendi or flindy flindy flindy flindy put up a
post about how they're going camping in a forest in New Hampshire last weekend
of October the post and scoop group about it
the monsters scoops up there oh nice I've actually been at a campground with
flindy because I did the porcupine festival as a magician and what's a
porcupine festival it is a honestly it was it was probably still is a very
libertarian themed outing for people go camping and a bunch of people in New
Hampshire who are trying to start like a government-less state free state try to
try to hold some lectures there's a lot of crypto lectures and then I went and I
just I did like two magic tricks and talked about Penn and Teller for like an
hour and they offered to pay me in crypto and I said no and lessons learned
lessons learned yeah yeah yeah but yeah go camping with Flynn they they make the
best food they make good camping food I went by a weather campsite we ate lunch
oh nice I still have there from Keen New Hampshire I still have the bag I put all
my podcast up in this bag it says fucking great from a foe restaurant in
Keen oh King great that's uh it's one of my favorite bags let's do a little
speaking of favorite bags you're my favorite bag let's do a little jock
versus nerd all right
everywhere we got a scooper to come in as today from pony scoop it's Emma the
categories are pop culture ponies hoof and glory scoop stable and horse sense
ooh Matt you're up first horse sense 400 if a stallion loses the family jewels he
becomes a hmm it's not stud okay shoot I know this I know it oh I'll go to hazel
for my lifeline please yelling gelding a gelding I'm sorry it's a stud a stud was
the correct no it's gelding for the people this thing Paul you're up you
know also side note my dad we might have had a solution for not for long the
podcast as a viable thing because we talked about trying to use a patreon to
like own a horse and then we turned out that all right like that was like crazy
money silly even with a discount my dad found a site called racehorse.com where
you can buy like small shares in horses for like a hundred nineteen dollars my
dad bought a share in this horse and I was like oh well that's patreon money we
can probably do and so we can we can we can we can buy steaks and young horses
and I can buy a small steak and follow their travail yes okay yes could we buy
like a frozen package of horse steaks with that money we can buy steaks in a
horse will buy steaks from a horse yeah two different websites but we could
totally do it okay okay Paul you're up I will try pop culture
thanks to make Paul go this episode nothing else skull fucking some head on
a spine but that was fine that's made of plastic that's plastic it's putting your
wiener in some plastic that's not eating a horsey oh man the sexiest kind of hole
is plastic holes everybody knows that there's only one type of plastic small
enough for me to fuck it that's microplastics yeah some people have
microplastics inside of them I like to be inside of microplastics I need a
microplastic popcorn bucket please boy I'll take pop culture ponies pop culture
ponies the palomino that only talks to Wilbur Post in a 1960 sitcom of course
of course that would be the famous mr. ed the famous mr. ed it's me I'll try a
hoof and glory for 400 the final jewel of the u.s. triple crown that would be
the you have the Derby of the Kentucky Derby then you have I think the Belmont
is second so I think the pretentious is third I think you're right
third you switched no you fool I did switch you fool I'm at Paul Jamie just
as qualified as from hosting a force podcast it's um I will take I knew all
three of them I will take horse sense for 800 please long in the tooth comes
from the fact that a horse's teeth keep doing this as it ages growing getting
sexier yeah there you go growing or erupting oh yeah
erupting yeah oh I'll continue with pop culture ponies please I'm just gonna say
it would have been really funny if Matt's answer to that last question had
been erupting oh it's easy right that had been like oh they're erupting Matt
Damon narrates the life of a wild Mustang in this 2002 DreamWorks adventure
oh what was that called I was here every night on audio just listen to him spirit
it was spirit spirit the stallion of the Cimarron oh I thought it was cinnamon I
am gonna stop listening to it whoever's reading the audiobook is doing a
terrible job spirit the stallion of the cinnamon this cinnamon it's me I'll try
I'll try pop culture ponies 1200 and the Simpsons episode saddle horse saddle
sword galactica Bart rebrands the family's gentle race horse with this
tough guy name I I don't fucking know I don't know this one Jacob yeah I don't
I'm passing it to Matt I refuse to answer I will pass Matt is pleading the
fifth and Paul has signaled to me silently that he also doesn't know the
answer to this question I really don't be moving on oh you really don't I really
know this is this has got to be like season 20 or something I don't know oh
okay let's see furious D oh Jesus I didn't know that one I have not I have
not seen saddle store galactica excuse me like that name though excuse me sir my
furious D is caught in this plastic head I seem to have some beans on my furious
D I don't think hazel knows about the beans but I don't know what the beans
tell her some other time let's move on yeah no I'll do a horse sense for 1200
please that has never moved on faster in the breeding shed a stallion can drop
roughly how many inches of equipment plus or minus two inches how big is a
horse's cock that's exactly what this question is asking yes hmm trying to
think I'm just well so goes past there don't forget you can use hazel remember
that early ass fucking video from hazel tape measure any can you measure your
arm real quick you're going with hazel arm as a competent comparison yes boy
pass it to you good old hazel horse dick arms honeysuckle they used to call her
the delicate flower now they call her horse dick arms I'm going well danger is
not her middle name 38 inches 38 inches is just over 20 20s like 38 right if
you've got horse eyes that is I'm telling you baby it's 38 believe me pop
culture ponies for 2000 please with my no money now boo with your no money and
Bob's burgers the adult superfans of the Equestria knots proudly call themselves
the Equestria what hmm I don't know I have to pass you can't that's a it's a
day I can't pass Equestria knots Equestria the Equestria knots so the
Equestria knots I take it are a band probably
Equestria Terrians I'll go Equestria Terrians let's try a question Terrians
quest there it is it questicles that's me I'll try what was hoof and glory about
I'll try hoof and glory for 800 the indoor arena that fills with 1.4 million
pounds of dirt each December sits on the campus of this Nevada University
oh it's just the University of UNLV yeah UNLV all right it's good stuff all
right Matt I just got that right I don't know I don't know what tell you so my
instinct is to keep clearing out the horse it's kind of reset that I actually
only used one answer I got from hazel then I passed the other two so I'm gonna
actually switch to scoop stable please for 400 Matt's gonna make a change let's
see listeners listener letters become scoop mail but if a horse delivered them
the segment would share its name with the 1860s all equine postal service that
galloped across the West that would be the pink pony club the pink pony club
that's the way you deliver letters pony express the pony express of course it's
the pony express I've read that they did not actually gallop the very far they
would it was apparently a what do you call like a publicity stunt they would
gallop into and out of town to make it look like they were just galloping the
whole time but you couldn't gallop a horse that long so they just gallop in
and out of town and then just walk the horse that makes it was apparently like
a publicity thing that they did on purpose yeah those man the whole world
is bullshit man yeah Paul hoof and glory hoof and glory for 1200 and the 1973
Belmont this chestnut won by a record 31 lengths secretariat secretariat is
correct huzzah the only one you know Belmont be a third race it's the third
race rub it in yep I know that I don't know who wouldn't know that I'll try
horse sense for 2000 boy you died the bullet there man did and I jumped in
front of it a horse can't perform this normal mammal function which is why
choking or stomach upset is a medical emergency done done done done done they
can't regurgitate something right they can't like like like cough something up
and like vomit or vomit regurgitate cough it up I don't know if they swallow
something basically they can't like vomit it back out okay okay
vomit yeah yeah show me vomit vomit there we go man I was you not I was not like
if you gave yourself points for regurgitate because those are different
things no they're not are they no they're not rotating vomit is not
regurgitation I believe it just from an attention standpoint no but I mean you
can say that birds regurgitate baby birds mouth the thing that took down our
podcast with us vomit versus vomit like I went to counter I was like I don't
want to have this I don't want to have this argument at all I shouldn't have
even said what I said I suppose there I mean like it's probably the bird
probably is regurgitating food that hasn't gone all the way past it's uh now
there has to be a difference I think Matt's right there has to be a
difference I just don't know what the difference is yeah Matt you're up scoop
stable please for 800 what is the name of the official pony of pod therapy oh
it's Emma's pony if that helps Jim's dad is a horse oh you had one too many
letters on that I don't know is the answer let's see if you were going to
buy your sons maybe when they were a little younger you might buy them some
some toys like some trucks or something to to drive around on the living room
floor to talk about what oh what was that to Tonka oh oh maybe maybe a little
less stutter is Tonka Tonka Tonka aka Tonka truck the pony Tonka is what they
called Buffalo famous wrestler from old WWF days to Tonka I don't know why
you're putting an extra tee on this mat all of my kids trucks are buffaloes is
what it says I named my horses after buffaloes I'll try hoop hoof and glory
please hoof and glory for 2000 at Paris 2024 Snoop Dog rolled up to Versailles
and full breeches and tailcoat along this homemaking icon his longtime TV
bestie that'd be Martha Stewart this sure that's Martha Stewart yeah I don't
know what the fuck she has to do with horses she owns horses oh great maybe
they're implying that she is in fact a horse ah that's new Bridger like a horse
she's horny let's do this who rider wait like a pony that's genuine no yeah that's
genuine we're like well like ecu wine nobody's happy with that joke I liked it
I liked it nobody didn't say that nobody agrees with that that is the best joke
you made the whole show good joke just nobody likes it Matt and I are both died
at 2400 Matt Paul has 1200 we got scoop stable for 12 and 2000 I guess I'll get
I guess I'll get the big one and try and with the game 2000 how dare you big one
Nick's transport rant mentioned that crossing the US border with racehorses
triggers USDA Coggins paperwork testing for this blood-borne disease named for
the bacterial agent EIA objection your honor this yes this is scoop stable
scoop implies ice cream social there have been two pot therapy questions in
this category I'd like it banned I like it stricken sustained sustained this
question will be stricken from the record information on the blood-borne
bacterial agent EIA there was a horse you've got a disease yeah I mean I I just
don't think there's any way that I would possibly know this pass Matt I'm just
reading through it to make sure I actually understand the question cuz I
really didn't the first time I was to be distracted by why am I answering pot
therapy questions but I'm assuming this is a bit that we did on pot therapy at
some point that I don't remember yeah it's gonna be a pass for me Jacob Paul
could it be hoof and mouth disease I got hoof and mouth disease from my nieces
right yeah did you get in your hooves like Oh Shetty yeah just turn turn them
into who's the whole guys it makes your eyes get really big that's what I was
doing mouth that's why I was doing horse sense categorize waiting for the horse
I questioned it never came equine infectious anemia oh that'll just nice
facts as hoof and mouth of course and Matt closing out the category and the
game scoop stable for 1200 in the show pod therapy which therapist on the show
pod therapy does the most pod theropis Matt that's Jim Jacob if Jacob names a
foal after the show's tagline its jockey club approved name 18 characters Max
would read like this or preaching fun no uh different different tagline
preaching fun is really more of our tagline but but maybe something else
that could be confused as a tagline oh what what in the but uh farts in the bag
dot biz keep going I'll just pass Paul I don't know I was going with preaching
preaching f you but it's I don't know I pass I don't know I mean I wouldn't it
be the FYI TF oh fuck you in the face you dick and tit farmers you dick and
tit farmers of which are you dick and tit farms of which I am the farmer
right that's yeah that's my answer oh no just preaching fun it's preaching fire
would have been the whole thing of preaching fun okay I was right I was
right the whole time why doesn't matter cuz I was wrong and so either way Matt
wins yeah Matt wins with 2400 I'm a 1200 Paul is in third with negative 800 and
that was a pony go go and my lady's pony scoop six times bigger than I than you
think it is because I have horse eyes
too much change in my pocket it's horse sense I want to thank the inspirational
hazel honeysuckle for stopping by yes thank you hazel would not have come up
with the clearly award-winning theater piece of the Star Wars fuckable seat
franchise that we launched because of this episode without you I can't wait
to start development I'm picturing a Borg head and we just we somehow mount a
fleshlight inside of it that's the prototype be why I like boldly strip
calm is where you can go to support hazel's Kickstarter for volume 2 of her
piece go go there support it right now yeah I did I got I set it for both
versions again Wow thanks Matt you got it and it's a really fun project and
then we'll see hazel at scoop fest hazel well yeah boldly ship commas where
people go to support your Kickstarter where else do people go to support what
you do well you can you can come to Galaxy con in San Jose next weekend when
you can come to scoop fest yeah you can also go and see absinthe at Caesar's
Palace yeah you go there you go I'm a little fairy short and stout I will be
at the Magic Castle August 23 24th good luck getting in there and then I'll be
in the Magic Saloon in San Antonio very accessible Magic Saloon San Antonio
September 1st is December 8th come there I don't know anyone there so come hang
out I'm hoping it won't be as hot as it was last time I was there where I
basically hid inside during the day and only went out at night like some kind of
vampire but yeah and I want to thank people support us over here on our
patreon page we don't have a list just yet and that's it's my fault I moved the
recording to Monday instead of Wednesday fucked up the whole system guys but just
know if you're supposed to patreon we love you and we thank you and really
appreciate it and if you have it within your heart and within your wallet please
throw a little jingle our way at preaching fun calm
or if you also don't really know the difference between Star Trek and Star
Wars like you get them all kind of confused in your head maybe like one of
the hosts on this show head on over to farts and a bag dot biz that along with
preaching fun calm it takes you to our patreon page where for as little as three
dollars a month you can upkeep this show on the air if you think this show is
worth more than zero dollars head on over to preaching fun calm and farts in
a bag dot biz today and of course head on over to boldly stripped calm nudie
Star Trek books who wouldn't like a nudie Star Trek book for the holidays my
mother keeps one on her coffee table at home right now it is a conversation
starter it's great she loves it all of her friends love it get yourself a nudie
Star Trek book over it boldly strip calm or as I like to call it sci-fi smut oh
man if you get that first book you may even read a passage or two influenced by
my filthy innuendo give it a read guys give it a read looking at that makes my
teeth erupt this is what they need to put in the seats horse mouths that keep
erupting they bite harder as the film progresses in sexuality and with that
lovely notion we'll see you soon secretariat 5d
saddle up indeed
rounded the final lap and yes they're in my intestine we're back on see ya