That's wrong.
Hold on. How's that wrong?
Off to a fantastic start.
I should put my headphones on.
That's how it's fucking wrong.
I don't know how to do things.
It's an abomination your lack of headphones is disgusting to watch.
Hello!
I'd love to thank all you ice cream truck drivers out there.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
Well these are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now I'd like to thank
Paul's brother
Pyro
Richard Dunn
Sarah Boyle
Sax Guy
Jimmy D. Scoop
Scoop Brady
Scoop Du Jour
Scoop Cotta
Slurpee Ka-A Motherfucker
The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver
Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop
and Travis Jaguri
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I sure hope you do, preachingfun.com is where you can go.
Preachingfun.com, go there, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
Here's the show!
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
We've got our friend Jonas Wolferton stopping by the churn today.
Paul created a football on Patreon with the most ridiculous post ever.
We can finally announce, we can finally announce where we were.
Our mystery show that we were talking about.
It's time for Matt and Matt Hickley's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt!
Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul!
Sitting in Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy!
We're preachingfun.
I want to start with an apology.
I just blamed Paul for something that was Jacob's fault.
That was me, that was me.
Jacob took credit on it, which is great.
I mean, eventually it will be my fault.
Yeah, yeah.
Very soon.
I thought Paul had already done it, so I jumped on it the last second and did it.
This is for the Zoom hangout.
I already told the people that were in the Zoom early.
But yeah, that was my fuck up.
I thought Paul had already done it.
Paul thought I had already done it.
So I just jumped on it and did it real quick.
It didn't think about any problems that I was going to create in the future.
So I get all the Patreon emails and it just was like, wait, what?
What's that, when, where, what's going on?
Yeah.
See, you get those and you were bothered by those.
I get the Zoom email.
Every time somebody tried to click through the link and go, I was getting an email as
well.
Oh man.
Well, we offered a new feature for Patreon off-air hangouts on Zoom.
Paul was going to host the first one and then we're going to be more detailed going forward.
I did, but it just, we did get it cooking.
Yeah.
So I got, I got to still chat with you, Matt, a little bit later about Patreon stuff, getting
in there and then I'm going to get myself all situated with the Zoom coordination stuff
so I can actually send those out real soon.
So I'm going to do that and then I'll talk to you, Matt, later this week about getting
all that.
I'm busy.
But congratulations to Casey and Josh on their recent marriage.
Yes.
It was lovely.
Such a lovely time.
And there was a surprise.
So the surprise, the secret, the reason why we did the Tierney show is because Paul and
I were hired to go surprise a groom on his wedding by having his two favorite podcasters
stop by and do improv on their rehearsal night dinner.
And we surprised Josh by pretending to call him on our way to another gig.
And then we walked out of our car into the wedding venue.
And there's nothing more special as improv comedians to walk into a room where two people
are very excited to see you and 50 people don't know what's going on.
But to their credit, they got on board real quick.
I was like, my son was like, how'd the show go?
I go, well, no one was expecting to watch the show.
So the fact that they watched the show and participated was a real, I was like, imagine
if it was everyone polite.
Imagine if I just came into your classroom with Paul and just did an improv show.
That's the same feeling as everyone else at that dinner.
But they were down and they loved it.
And the main thing, Josh was super surprised, really shocked.
And Casey was very pleased that we got the desired effect out of him.
So that was it.
No.
And again, like we say, we have the best listeners in the world because we attract the nicest
people.
Sure enough, that wedding was filled with just amazingly awesome people who were very
kind to us.
I was playing chess with their son.
I was invited on the dance floor numerous times at the wedding.
It was just a lot of good hanging.
So yes, it was incredibly delicious food, libations, games.
Oh, Paul, that actually brings up a sticky subject.
I did get a note.
You were only hired as the guest.
You weren't actually supposed to eat anything.
So I do have a bill.
It was an invoice.
They did send a bill over.
I get it.
I had an extra ravioli or two.
That's for sure.
That is noted on the invoice.
Extra ravioli or two.
Yeah.
We should maybe address basically how this all snowballed in a way that made sure that
Jacob wasn't there.
I think maybe we should get into that as well.
Okay.
So originally I was called and I was emailed because I was a magician.
And she said, I think my husband likes your podcast, but he likes magic.
And so I think you did a duo.
And she brought up Nick Paul.
Nick Paul, who I just did the magic castle with.
Yeah, yeah.
I said, oh, so you want the magic show that Nick Paul and I did at the castle?
And she's like, yes.
And I said, great.
So I called Nick Paul.
Was he available?
Yes.
And then I basically, on a follow-up email, was like, so you guys saw us at the castle
or whatever?
She goes, no, we've never been to the magic castle.
And I said, so how did you find about the Nick Paul and I show?
Because Nick Paul and I do shows together, but like at the castle and a few other places,
but not often.
Right.
And she was like, well, I just know that my husband listens to the podcast.
And then I started going like, uh-oh, Nick Paul, Paul Mattingly, she might think she
has the name right.
And I said, listen, right now, you have a magic show booked with myself and Nick Paul
and Nick is available.
This is far enough away that maybe you want to, without giving anything away, figure out
whether he wants to show up with the magician that maybe your husband's never heard of.
Or the podcast partner that she has heard of.
Which is really funny.
If you show up at somebody's wedding with a magician that the groom has never heard
of, it's great.
I imagine he's like, hey, Matt, hi, sir.
Hey, pal, thanks for being away.
And Matt's helper.
What a surprise.
I'm Josh.
And so like a month later, she's like, yeah, yep, you were right.
I'm wrong.
And we do not.
So I had to call Nick Paul to be like, hey, pal, you're no longer one.
No one likes you.
You sure have a popular name though.
It's his name.
Yeah.
So all that kerfuffle, we ended up, you know, booking an improv show with Paul and I.
Had it come earlier to my attention that just simply about Ice Cream Social, I might have
said, do you also want Jacob there?
It was such a kerfuffle and a hubbub to pull it off that I totally, it wasn't until I was
at the wedding and everyone was talking about how much they liked the podcast because we
met another scoop that was there, Ryan.
Ryan, who actually turned Josh on to us way back in the day.
Yes.
He obelisks Josh.
Oh, funny.
Yeah.
And he didn't make it to the rehearsal dinner and was so pissed when he found out we were
surprised, showed up there and did a show.
He's like, fuck.
But anyways, it was, I really had a lot more fun at the wedding, knowing that Jacob probably
should have been there too.
And he wasn't.
And that made me really feel great.
Well, I wasn't at the party.
I was at home working on things.
I will say, not having any fun.
It would have been nice to have Jacob there to deflect from the possibility of your early
onset death.
He would have, he would have advised me, or more to the point, he would have been in charge
of knocking on your door and he would probably would just wouldn't have stopped knocking until
you had to.
Yeah, exactly.
He would have said Matt, he would have said Matt and I would have heard a voice that wasn't
housekeeping is what would have happened.
I just knocked twice and assumed you're dead.
Yeah.
In fairness, every time I do go to wake Matt up, I do impersonate a housekeeper.
Housekeeping.
Yeah.
I don't always do the same accent.
Sometimes I go Dutch.
Sometimes I go Slavic.
You know, it just depends on my mood.
And then my instant boner wakes me up and I have to go like, all right, I'm up.
That's right.
But it was amazing.
It was so wonderful.
We're going to bury that right now because we have our friend Jonas Wolverton here.
Exactly.
Speaking of instant boners.
He headlined our variety show at Scoop Fest this year.
Certainly.
Yes.
The ball's on him.
Jonas, how you doing, pal?
My balls are doing well.
Good.
We were worried.
I could tell you.
I could see the fear in your eyes.
All good.
Hi.
Hey.
How you doing, everybody?
So you have a solo show coming up at the -- it's not ArtSquare Theater anymore.
What's it called?
Vegas Theater Company?
Vegas Theater Company, yeah.
So I'm doing my solo Mack and Fro show.
And Mack and Fro is the bad boy of tennis who you guys saw at the Scoops Fest.
That's right.
So you're a variety artist.
You juggle.
You do a sear wheel.
Where did you end up coming up with the John Mack and Fro idea?
I have always loved John Mack and Fro.
Yeah.
No relation.
Oh, interesting.
If you're listening, lawyers.
No related.
Nothing related.
Did you play tennis in your youth?
Very rarely.
Okay.
I was a New York City kid.
I played baseball.
All right.
Thick ball.
But no bad.
Shortstop and third.
Oh, come on.
I call him infielder.
He had infielder vibes.
Yeah, yeah.
No, that was pretty good.
Infielder vibes.
Come on.
I feel pretty good.
I still feel good about that one.
Yeah.
So I grew up watching John Mack and Fro have some serious blowouts.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
He is the most New Yorker of all of the tennis players from that time period for sure.
That's why I love him as well.
He is the most likely for a New York kid to enjoy who doesn't play tennis.
Yeah.
That's where New York kids are going to gravitate to is John Mack and Fro.
Exactly.
That and the 86 Mets who are all high on cocaine.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I got caught watching like a documentary on Dwight Gooden and Daryl Strawberry.
And it just kept getting like...
The clickety click of the roller coaster, all the heights are right at the very beginning.
And then it just goes down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
And I was like, Jesus, will someone stop this documentary?
Please.
Somebody stop this documentary before someone gets hurt.
Get the present day.
It's so dark, the whole thing.
Oh, my God.
Halfway through the documentary, you get a proof of life.
These are my heroes when I'm eight.
Perfect.
Yeah.
So I love Mack and Ro and I love the sort of performance art aspect.
Not really knowing what performance art was as a kid, but later on from reflecting about
it, I got a gig with World Team Tennis to do Sear Wheel, which is what you guys see in
the back there.
And I was like, hey, I've been thinking about doing this bad boy of tennis character kind
of an homage to Mack and Ro.
Would you guys be cool with that?
And they're like, yeah, absolutely.
So I got hired to do a gig.
I did a Sear Wheel act as him and also interacted with the crowd and filmed the whole thing
as a sort of...
I didn't know what I was going to do with it.
Make it like a documentary, a mockumentary or something.
Because Mack and Ro, for people of a certain age, he's an iconic character.
But in the circus world, most people don't even like sports, let alone famous tennis
players.
So was there any time where you were floating the idea of doing Mack and Ro and just another
circus guy was like, what the hell are you talking about?
Please don't do this.
What are you doing?
No.
My world is the world of the clown.
And so that's actually my first entrance into circus was through clown.
Okay.
I went to the Clown Conservatory in San Francisco.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
And I did a whole year long program in clown.
And so my attraction to the circus is originally through clown and through character.
And I'm a theater kid at heart.
And that's my first passion.
And so I wound up...
And that's the cool thing about the clown is you can literally draw from anything in
the world and find what's ridiculous about it and find what's funny about it and find
the absurdity in it.
Right.
So how old are you in the Clown Conservatory?
Where are you in your life?
This would be in 2001, 2002.
So I just graduated from college in film and was working in film and was like, ah, man,
I was making a documentary about a sideshow circus and wound up getting like literally
ran away with the circus was like, this is so cool.
I don't want to be making the film.
I want to be the film.
We actually had a stand up comedian.
Come on.
That happened with his documentarian as well.
Yeah.
So, so you literally, here's the good news is like, if you turn to your parents, it's
like, you know what?
I don't want to do stuff in the film.
They're like, Oh, thank God.
But I do want to be a clown.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
His parents more than we thought we did.
Monkey pod.
No more film.
Bad news.
I'm a clown in San Francisco.
But they, but they were behind you in your choices.
Thousand percent.
That's great.
Yeah.
Always.
I mean, um, that's, that's, are they artists also?
Uh, no, not at all.
Not at all.
My mom like worked in book publishing.
My dad's a, um, a political guy in Brazil.
So a political guy in Brazil.
That sounds like mafia.
That sounds like mafia to me.
He's kind of like the fixer for the president.
Okay.
This is not, you're not dissuading my, my conclusion.
I'm nailing it.
Infielder, mafia dad.
I'm nailing it left and right.
Yeah.
But, but for good, because he's actually a good president.
He's, he's, he's on the side of the people.
So yeah, he's, he's not one of those assholes.
That's, you know, he's, he's very much against the current American regime.
So, you know, let's, let's get on this for the second year, but like, how do you keep
up with all that?
Do you follow the like Brazilian news and stuff?
Um, I am, I have Brazilian citizenship.
So I try to keep like one eye open to what's happening in Brazil.
Also as an exit strategy for this country.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
Are you, I didn't realize people were thinking about what other countries they could live
in right now because of.
It's just in the back pocket.
I wasn't immediately jealous of your Brazilian citizenship.
I'll tell you right now.
Wait till you hear about my Canadian.
Go fuck yourself.
I mean, I'm also a spy in addition to being a mafia.
So, so that's, that's gotta be crazy to follow your dad's career a little bit.
Yeah.
And the thing is, my dad is actually the one who got me in a circus.
You can think about it.
Like he, he was always into clowns growing up.
I hear stories about him.
Like, you know, back in Brazil in the center of town, like the circus would still come
through the town and they would do this thing.
The clown would do this thing where the kid that would help the clown out to get all the
other kids to come to the circus.
They'd put a little bit of ash like behind their ear so that when they showed up to the
circus, they could like see the kids who had the ash behind the ear and they would get
in for free.
Oh, that's a, that's really romantic.
I like that.
Yeah, so there's, I was very small when I saw my first circus in Brazil.
I was like five years old, I think.
It was either Ringling in New York or it was in this small like rural circus in Brazil.
And I just fell passionately in love with it.
And so it's been, it's always been this idea of, oh, I really want to be involved in the
circus in some ways, always been in my mind.
And it just, it just came out after I went to college and got, had a film career and
I was like, fuck it, circus.
This is it.
This is the new thing.
We're going this way now.
As someone who works in a circus, I am always fascinated, fascinated by people who see that
and go like, I got to do this.
I'm someone who is in like a, in that area, you know, mainstream kind of like show business
and then saw variety arts is like, oh wait.
Yeah.
Variety arts.
You can work all the time.
You don't have to try to chase fame or awards.
You can just get work.
And I think that's, I think that's what's really attractive.
It really is.
But there is this thing of, cause it's so much of showbiz, what people, I, I, this is
probably wrong because I'm in showbiz.
And so I'm trying to picture what people who aren't in showbiz think about it.
But it seems like, you know, from the, from the movies and stories and everything, people
are attracted to the kind of glitz and glamor of showbiz.
And circus has very little glitz or glamor.
Hard to disagree.
It has its own type, sure, but it's not, it's not that red carpet.
I can't think of any more glamorous than Jonas wearing a giant afro wig and a G-string and
having all these scoops pelted with tennis balls.
Name anything more glamorous than that.
I stand corrected.
Yeah.
I mean, I've, I've, I've performed in, you know, um, like dirty rock clubs, like right.
The double.
Yeah.
You have done a show at the double down.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Double down.
I do combo the clowns, uh, wheel of misfortune.
What's it called?
Wheel of Paul.
Just, you know, that, that club is not named after the KFC to fry chicken breast sandwich.
It was before the sandwich.
I'm not going.
It's a happy accident.
No, I, I know about the double down.
I've been the double down a time or two.
What's, uh, ass juice.
That's the, uh, the ass juice.
That's the, the bartenders at the end of the night will take the, the trays where they catch
all the detritus and they will, they will pour you shots of whatever is in there and
you can, and it's in a little toilet bowl too.
Yeah.
There you go.
It's a, it's a specialty of the house.
Yeah.
I know me some double specialty, but I've performed a double down, but I've also performed
for the, uh, the spulton of Oman.
Get out of here as a double down as Mac and pro you've done the Mac and just generally
over my career.
Okay.
Nice.
So that's, that's, that's a good spread for sure.
You started in clown, but you've learned other skills.
When, when, like, when did you start figuring out like the seer wheel?
Like what's some time was like, Hey, you're too athletic to just be a clown.
You should maybe do other things.
Yeah.
I thought I was a clown, but I started, I was like, Oh, I'm old for the circus.
Cause I'm like 25 or whatever.
And uh, and then I saw Daniel seer, uh, he of the seer wheel, uh, the inventor, the inventor
of the wheel.
Yeah.
He invented the wheel.
I didn't even realize it was that new.
Yeah.
He, he premiered his, his, uh, act in Paris festival of Paris is one of the largest circus
festivals in the world.
Sorry, we should say quickly that like for anyone, seer wheels, like a giant metal hoop,
you kind of say like a giant metal hula hoop or whatever.
That a person can fit inside, yeah, yeah, so the person kind of the Vichy retruvian man.
Ah, yes.
That's a great, yeah.
Yes.
You're basically spokes of a wheel and you are generating the, the, the spin in the wheel.
Um, and you can roll and there's, and there's, um, you can manipulate it.
There's a whole bunch of like, uh, vocabulary that when I first started out working with
Daniel seer, um, yeah, which is, it's, it's a six foot tall bull for me.
It's my height.
It's six foot tall ring that I get inside of and spin around.
Um, I started working with Danielle, uh, seer in Montreal in 2003.
He just won the, um, the silver medal, I believe at the Paris festival and he premiered a brand
new circus discipline.
And so when I started out, there was four people and before that I saw him and what
got me interested in it was I was in clown school and we had to choose an apparatus.
We had to choose like juggling or, or, um, hand balancing or, you know, whatever circus
discipline or apparatus you wanted to choose.
And I, um, saw Daniel seer perform while I was in clown school right at the beginning
of it.
I was like, that's it.
Oh, but it didn't even exist back then, right?
There was nobody had a ring.
Right.
Just kind of, right.
You know, it was just Danielle and I was like, he make his own, I guess he had to, yeah,
he manufactured his own ring.
And then, uh, I, he, and then he's like, on Amazon, they're not there.
Nope.
Yeah.
You can, you can get them online now.
They're, they're, they're more accessible and stuff.
And a lot of people, a lot more people are doing it now, but, um, I fell in love with
it.
I, the one thing that did exist that was kind of similar was a German wheel, which has two
rings.
Um, so I started training on German wheel and then, um, wound up creating an act in
German wheel, a clown act, and then, um, auditioned for Daniel Sears company in Montreal, Cirque
l'Oise, and got hired to, to create, be one of the creators, one of the creative artists
that originated the show called Rain that toured the world.
Oh yeah.
I remember Rain.
Yeah.
We should, we should actually point out, like, you do love the Sear wheel because you, you,
when we asked you to do Scoop Fest, you said yes.
And you said you had a version without a Sear wheel, one with, and I said, okay, what,
what, what conditions do you need for the Sear wheel?
And you laid out like three factors and we met none of them.
We asked for, not one, it had to be a wooden stage and not carpeted.
We had a carpeted stage, stage had to be a very, very big, uh, our stage was very small
and eight feet, eight feet, that's the record.
That's the record.
Yeah.
I just kept saying, I kept saying, maybe do the version without the wheel.
And you just kept being like, I'm going to bring the wheel anyway.
I'm going to bring it just in case.
And we had, we had some rather messy acts before you.
Yes.
I was legit concerned.
Oh, Paul was worried the entire time.
What was going to happen to your wheel at the end of the show?
All he was thinking about was your wheel at the end of the show.
I'm kicking banana husks and, and goop and pieces of lettuce and tomato off the side
of the stage.
I'm like, fuck.
You shouldn't have brought a sandwich onto the stage in the first place.
Banana, tomato and lettuce.
You even added a criteria that would made it even more difficult for me to perform.
So thank you guys so much.
You literally put a banana peel on the stage.
What's funny?
Tell me what's funnier.
That's exactly it.
I was, I was like, this is, this is, this is the shit show.
This is what it's going to be like.
It's perfect for the world of Mack and fro, cause the world of Mack and fro, he's, he's,
he's on, he's on the outs, you know, if you're not, if you're not frustrated, if you're not
at the butt of the joke, then it doesn't really work.
Right?
Yeah.
The more obstacles you can put on in front of Mack and fro, what is the sear wheel, uh,
tiny stage record?
Do you know or do you have, I mean, really did that to me.
But I mean, seriously, is there anybody that performs sear wheel on a smaller space than
eight feet?
Do you, I mean, talk, get ahold of Guinness.
Are you asking Jonas, is there someone dumber than him?
No, it was fucking, it was fucking fearless.
It was awesome.
Are there producers less considerate than us?
That's what Paul is asking.
I know that, I know the answer to that.
I fucking know the answer to that, but it was great and, uh, yeah, it was just so cool
to see.
And I was legit worried, but it went off without a hitch.
There is the world record for a sear wheel performance does not currently have a smallest
stage category.
Okay.
However, the minimal, uh, the minimum, uh, space generally required for a professional
artist is 15 foot by 15 foot.
Look at that, you math whizzes out there might notice that that is bigger than eight.
Yeah.
I didn't know that we were actually the measure how professional we are, which is, uh, we
are 56% professional.
We've got that shit on video, you can just, you can just send that into Guinness and be
done with it.
There you go.
Here it is.
Now that you've challenged me, I'm going to do it.
I think about this all the time where I think, uh, my kids who want to go to college, I've
said this on the, on the podcast many times as like, or I have said, or they can learn
the sear wheel and just work the rest of their lives, right?
Playing for the sear wheel, do you, do you accidentally, at least once crush your fingers
on the wheel?
Yes.
Oh, I did it.
Oh, that, that's the only thing that bothers me when I think about it all the time.
I feel like it has to be more than once.
No, it's like Johnny dangerously once.
And then that's the lesson learned.
Huh?
And it's, it's, it's when you do the coin spin.
So you're like, you're, you're, you're, you're, uh, spinning like a coin and you're kind of,
kind of wobbling down to the ground.
Yeah.
With your, with your head, like throwing down to the stage and coming back up and you're,
and you're letting you pushing the wheel and you're grabbing and pulling it up and you're
pushing it and pulling it up.
And yes, that is the trick that everyone inevitably will crush their fingers on.
That's the one I crushed my fingers on.
And then I learned, I learned how not to do that trick.
When you crush your fingers with it, is it, is it just painful or does something usually
break?
Uh, no, just, you know, just put a little ice on it.
Or just like, you know, slamming your finger in a car door.
This isn't like the story of our all seer wheel artists don't have fingernails or something.
Cause when I first watched that act, I always thought, I thought, are there designs where
there are whole handholds inside the wheel or anything?
Or was that like an early on?
Yeah, but they're kind of, some people do that, but it's, it's very rare.
I think it's, it's just the simplicity of having a ring that's so, right.
You don't have to.
Yeah.
It makes it clear.
You don't have to do any excess stuff.
It's just like the, the, the focus is on the figures that you're creating with your body
as opposed to, um, your eye getting distracted by some kind of unnecessary thing.
It's just like the German wheel that you mentioned earlier, like your hands are inside of two
rings and the, and the German wheel already.
So there's already kind of an apparatus that does that anyway.
Yeah.
And it's, it's, it's very German and efficient in that way.
Like this is Rebecca.
Oh, Rebecca.
She got unmuted because she had to answer, uh, we, we, um, it reminds me of, uh, contact.
Remember the spaceship and the scientists decided that they had to have a seat in the spaceship,
but didn't need a seat.
So you're probably right.
It makes it a much more elegant beast when it doesn't have the extra constructs in it.
You're right.
That's exactly the, the, uh, analogy I was going to use.
And also the wheel I saw that had hand holds on it, it shook so violently when the guy
was using it.
I also have a theory in that, in that, um, that I spin left.
So I'm spinning counterclockwise and I'm getting, I'm, I'm, uh, it's just the way that Danielle
spin when he taught me, um, he spun left, some people spin right, but I spin left and
I have a, I have a theory that that keeps me young.
Oh, you're Supermanting it.
Turn it back time.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's right.
You're running the car reverse.
Take the miles off.
Taking that odometer back.
So your show, you're doing two nights?
Yeah.
So I'm doing two nights, November 21st and 22nd at the Vegas theater company.
Um, it's called the Mack and fro show.
And then I'm also doing the Mack and fro show in LA.
Okay.
And then I'm also doing the lesion theater, um, which is going to be December 3rd at the
lesion.
Um, it's a, it's a big hub for comedy.
Also the same exact show, but it's going to be my, my, my debut in LA on December 3rd.
No clown is huge right now in LA.
Like it's very, yeah, yeah, it's blowing up on the internet too.
I follow like three or four very specific, strange clowns on Instagram.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
And that's kind of the hub is, is, uh, is, is at the lesion.
So I'm going to go, I'm going to take my clown to go meet their clowns.
Nice.
Oh, that's going to be so fun.
That's awesome.
And is there a website or anything that people can see the dates and times on and maybe buy
tickets?
Yes.
For Vegas, it's theater, uh, spelled in the British way T H E A T R E, uh, dot Vegas.
Um, and then for the lesion theater, I believe it's Elysian E L Y S I A N theater spelled
the American way.
Great.
So we fight over tea and how to spell theater.
That's just the way it goes.
No, let's just figure that out.
We should decide right now.
Should we, should we just make this call right now?
Uh, I always default to the British spelling.
It looks more elegant.
I do.
I also do RE Matt.
Do you do RE or ER motherfucker jersey trash?
I may, I may, I just had a petition of Toby Keith through the halftime show, the zombie
body of Toby Keith.
This happened to me this week.
I'm bringing up a real thing.
Yeah.
That's real.
That is real.
They're going to AI him as the halftime.
No, there's a petition to make him be the halftime performer.
Because the halftime performer is an American, but has tan skin and speaks Spanish, there's
a legit petition to have Toby Keith instead.
Yes.
Because the NFL is going to listen to a petition of 50,000 bigots because you have to, you
have to, you have to say yes to that.
You have to.
Look, I understand being a bigot.
I don't understand spending your effort on the halftime show.
I don't understand burning these calories to be a more effective bigot.
There's so many other companies that have DEI policies.
Why are you going after the super bowl?
There's so many ways to be a bigot where you'll, you'll affect a group of people.
This case, you're only affecting bad buddy and he's already doing very well.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I went to home Depot this week to get a piece of hose.
I needed a piece of hose and it needed a very specific diameter for this hose.
And I was like, I think it is a seven eights or no, I think it's a seven sixteenths rather.
And so me and me and the guy, we find a piece of seven sixteenths, so we find a piece of
seven sixteenths hose.
I have a little piece of hose that I brought with me and I hold them up and they don't
match.
I was like, Oh, the seven sixteenths is a little big.
Let's drop down to a three eights.
So we find a three eights hose.
Paul, this is all math.
Don't worry about it.
We find a three eights hose and sure enough, it is a little small.
So somewhere between these two sixteenths of an inch is where the hose that I have is.
And I say to the, to the guy, I go, I don't, maybe it's metric.
Do you think it could be metric?
And he gets the most offended look on his face, genuinely and goes, well, cause I told
him it was for an ice maker.
I said, he goes, uh, did you, did you buy it in the United States?
And I kind of chuckled a bit like, well, sure, then it shouldn't, then it shouldn't be metric.
And I thought he was joking.
And I kind of played along with it and I went like, yeah, yeah, they get these metric things
and they bring them into the, to the things in the United States and yeah, I bought this.
I got the US, but who knows where it was made.
You get it.
And he, to my horror, he didn't get, was not joking and continued on that conversation.
And I felt very strongly that something that was purchased in America should have freedom
units.
Okay.
Shouldn't be in metric.
Your first mistake was Home Depot.
I mean, we, we got, we got a boycott that fucking place.
Sorry.
Uh, scooping over girls.
Right.
It's George straight.
Not Toby Keith.
I got, I got George.
He's dead a lot longer.
Either way.
I just speak English.
You know what I mean?
That's all we're saying.
I'm going to get the artists wrong.
Speak English.
Don't use metric.
Yeah.
It was metric.
By the way, it was 10 millimeter.
This is what I mean.
This is what I mean is like, okay, we have known that we've had, you know, an undercurrent
of racism as part of our culture in this country for a very long time.
No, this is the problem.
We thought it was only an undercurrent, but now it's becoming an overcurrent.
And the fact that like this person literally is spending their emotions being upset about
metric units for metric, dude, it's metric.
You have things in this store that are metric.
Like it's just, there's ways to build stuff.
Yes.
Fuck Home Depot.
They're the option.
Correct me.
I right.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but from the jump feet as a measurement started as being measured
by the Royals foot length.
So if you're sticking to feet, I thought it was a Roman thing.
No, it was the length of the length of the King's foot.
So you're telling me that you're down a mile is something like a Roman thing.
I think, I don't know.
But I know with feet it was, and it changed from King to King.
So you're just telling me your measurement system is so fucking crazy and it all depends
on one dude's fucking feet.
So you're going to just bow down and kiss the foot.
That's what you're telling me.
You're literally in the chat is telling me that a mile is not the length of a King's
foot.
So sorry.
Sorry, Rich scoop for clearing that up.
Well, I mean enough inbreeding.
You never know what you're going to get.
Oh, I forgot.
That's true.
I forgot my crown.
Let me turn around.
No.
Sideshow Bob to the extreme anti-royal anti-fascist metric system is actually the way to go.
That's what I'm saying.
Absolutely.
Yeah, absolutely.
It comes down to more democratic to use the metric.
It's far more democratic.
Paul and I saw Kurt Brownler do a bit of the standup about the way to convince Americans
like the metrics, the mores by start submitting our dick length in centimeters.
Yes.
Everyone's going to feel like a lot better.
Do you want a three inch dick or do you want an 18 centimeter cock as the bit is really
good.
I'll tell you who else wants an 18 centimeter cock and that's the following sponsor.
I'm sure that math is completely wrong.
Don't convert Paul's math on that.
Today's show is brought to you by Gregorius Griffin's Gardening Gadzookeries.
That's right.
That's from Danny Olwein in 2021.
Gregorius Griffin's Gardening Gadzookeries.
Hey everyone, it's me, Gregorius Griffin.
Are you here for gardening?
Well, Gadzooks, I've got the gear.
You go ahead and grab a garden weasel and get to scrubbing.
Scrub out all them weeds.
Scrub them with your hands and your fists, twist it and pull it.
The gardening Gadzookeries will clear up and open ways and pathways for the seeds to take
root.
Don't you know?
Make sure that they're planted in rows, rows of where it's at and make sure you measure
it with the metric system.
You don't want feet of crops.
You want metrics of crops.
Think about it.
Do you want a foot of cabbage or a meter of cabbage?
Get right.
Make your crops more meter-y.
Enter Hayes Group's checkout.
Jonas, did you ever finish your documentary?
Did you ever finish the doc that you were shooting?
No, I didn't.
I wound up making a short doc on it.
But that's funny because the sideshow troupe is the Bindlesip Family Circus in New York
City.
If anybody out there in New York probably knows who those guys are.
And they actually hired me like 20 years later to do a gig for them.
Oh, funny.
After I left Cirque du Soleil, which I performed in Zumanity for 10 years, I've been freelancing
since about 2019.
And nobody was like, hey, where's that doc, buddy?
Where's that film?
They did ask for the footage though.
And I was like, you know what, I'm not going to make this into a film but so you guys please
have this for your archive.
So they copied all the raw footage and everything.
And back when we were shooting on tape, yeah, back in the day.
Was your gig for the Sultan one of the craziest gigs you've ever done?
Yes.
So I was on that gig with Daniel Sear and one other performer, a woman by the name of
Valerie and it was in Oman and we were treated like royalty from the get like, I literally
if I wanted to like a legit massage, like anytime of the day, I could have one.
I literally did two back to back 90 minute massages on the Sultan of Oman's dimes.
Well, they got a lot of oil out there for the massages.
That's the whole thing.
Yes.
That's it.
It's all oil.
You were like Kobe beef by the time you went out there.
Marbled.
So it was the randomest thing.
It was for a Toyota dealership opening, which I guess Toyota trucks are like big in the
Middle East.
Okay.
They love trucks.
I'm just random.
But anyways, we're like, okay, we're opening this dealership and they hired Sear Wheels.
And and about an hour before the show, this massive sandstorm kicked up.
And like, like biblical sandstorm.
Oh, no.
And so we were on stage in these white flowy outfits that were basically giant sails.
While you're in your Sear Wheel?
While we're in the Sear Wheel, getting blown around.
That's exactly what you didn't really have to do any effort to move.
You just kind of go with the wind that made it much easier, much easier.
We were getting blown in one direction, like off the stage and Sear literally got blown
off the stage.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Were they okay?
What happened?
Not happy.
They're still they're still rolling.
It's terrible.
It's the worst thing that can happen to a Sear Wheel artist.
That's how Daniels will disappear.
He just kind of like rolled away.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So like we get blown one way and then like I'm doing actually two people in one in one
wheel with his woman, Valerie, and we're spinning together and getting blown like towards as
if we're getting blown off stage and we had to like find a way to maneuver ourselves to
get back towards the center.
And you had more than eight feet to work with at that point still.
Goodness sakes.
Yeah, there's at least nine feet on that.
Wow.
That is that's bananas.
Yeah, that was a wild one.
We're staying there in the sandstorm to watch the performance.
Yeah.
But I didn't see them really cannot see the audience there.
I was assured later that they very much enjoyed the full sand out.
Now what's it like with the sand underneath?
I mean, that's also a slippery kind of thing, right?
Was that even?
Yeah.
I mean, it was not it was not good.
It wasn't quite scoops level conditions, sand, more grit than old tomato hunks.
Okay.
Sandstorm was not quite as bad as Scoop Fest, it was close.
Did they did they did the sound affect the performance too?
Because I know when those things comes in, it's all did it did it did it did it did it.
You can't hear anything.
Yeah.
It's been a long way to make that joke than I expected.
Thank you.
I'm I'm I'm nothing if not patient song and then just like stop it.
That's how the town knows it's kind of an air horn.
Yeah, you're just walking around all seizure.
What?
Oh, no.
I'm gonna get inside.
Oh, shit.
Was that it?
Oh, yeah.
That's definitely coming.
That song gets me pumped.
It's a great song.
You know, pumped up to hide from sandstorms.
We should write some lyrics to it.
I don't think I could do that.
Those are the lyrics.
I guess.
That's it.
Sandstorm.
Yeah, sandstorm.
Yeah, it's been just been some crazy wheel gigs.
You know, I toured with the Dresden Dolls and you know that that band from the 2000s.
Yeah.
So cabaret, punk, duo and I performed on a US tour with them.
So I had to clear out entire like rock venues like the floor of the rock venue, the pit
area and then I would do Sear Wheel in rock venues and stuff like that.
That's always fun to do.
I love rock clubs and performed at the Roundhouse in London with them and cleared out the pit
and did Sear Wheel in there.
That was fun.
So this is really taking you literally all over the world.
Yes.
I have five continents.
That's so cool.
I performed five continents.
Yeah.
Which one?
Which tour are you missing?
Australia.
That seems like an easy one to get.
You should be able to get one of those.
Yeah.
No, I love I love Australia.
I was honestly before I before Cirque hired me to move to Vegas, I was going to move to
Australia and just overstay my visa and marry an Australian.
Just do that.
No problem.
Yeah, that's just you know, that's what you do, right?
When you're a vagabond circus corny.
Yeah.
And then and then I say also France, even though it's not a continent, France, the theaters
in France always had like lovely cheeses, like really stinky French cheeses laid out
on every board of stinky French cheese and in France.
I think I think I not only spent all my per diem, I may have spent most of my salary on
food in France.
That's fair.
That's pretty fair.
The food is better over there.
I hear good things.
Theater RE in France.
That's why Matt will not perform at those theaters.
Is that the best kind of pre sear wheel move to cheese up?
Is it?
Does that help you?
Oh, yeah.
You don't want to you don't want to be flowing free while you're spinning around that sear
wheel ball.
You want to you want to clog that shit up.
I guess that's true.
You want to be bound up like a cat in a cage before you hit that wheel.
One thing the fun thing to do is to chug a bunch of water.
Oh shit.
And then do a coin spin and then just feel the water sloshing around in a circle in your
mind.
I honestly thought for a second you were going to tell me you pissed while you did it.
That would have been wild.
Like some kind of avant-garde design that you make on like a canvas.
Do a sear wheel on a camera.
Have you done it with paint?
Have you made like sear wheel art yet on a giant paint?
Let's skip over the urine.
But let's go back.
Let's think about paint.
We could we could use the wheel on a giant canvas.
I don't know.
I don't know why Paul is naysaying my art here.
I have I have tried with with paint on the wheel.
It's a little bit slippery.
So you can't really do very much.
You can create patterns of that.
I've also drank a glass of wine while spinning in the wheel holding the wine at the same
time.
Wow.
The wine glass.
You kind of have to tilt it ups because you know the the the G force is taking it out.
Right.
So you can tilt the glass and drink it like that.
That's funny.
You can drink a beer to you know what you're spinning as well.
Since you've worked with sear himself, does he have like pet peeves?
Has he seen people do stuff with the wheel that he considers an abomination or anything
like that?
Oh no.
He's actually really just impressed and you know sear is very impressed with the way the
discipline has been expanded upon and just completely taken to really wild wild lengths
doing things that we never could have imagined when we were first starting the discipline.
There's some things that that the kids do nowadays and I'm like, yeah, that won't work
on a scoop stage.
Does he have the market corner?
Does he have some merchandise yet?
He needs some merch, right?
Does he not have a searing is believing t-shirt yet because that's no you've got to have it.
I know.
He's he's he's kind of like been in the shadows.
He kind of like made this thing made his just circus discipline and then like just drop
did a couple.
Yeah, he kind of did the show that I was working on.
He did a couple.
I did a Cirque show as well.
Corteo.
He designed that act and then he kind of just like was like like like Homer Simpson into
the like my work here is done.
I have accomplished all that I need to.
Yeah.
Yeah, he was he was a wonderful, wonderful mentor and this is what a what a right place,
right time.
You know, honestly, like I just it's just when you hit it just reminds me like to whenever
I'm kind of need to make a choice on what I want to do on something, a creative project,
whatever.
I'm just like, what is the what is the best possible scenario?
What what what what's the thing when I have a vision or an inspiration hit me, I really
got to follow it to its to its conclusion, because you never know what can come from
that.
You know, literally, I have had a 22 year circus career based on one scene, clowns in
Cirque du Soleil, Dralion, a clown troupe called Les Voila that inspired me was like,
oh, God, clowning.
That's it.
Yeah, of course.
I love Charlie Chaplin.
I love Buster Keaton.
Like, I'm going to I'm going to be a clown.
And then the second sort of lightning flash was seeing Daniel Cyr perform and being like
that.
Cyr wheel.
Yep.
That's it.
Amazing.
Like, really, to just hone in on my intuitive sense of like, what's going to inspire me?
What's going to what's going to make me what's going to fulfill my soul?
You know, like what's going to what's what's the thing that's going to make me passionate
to get out of bed in the morning and and or not sleep and travel, you know, halfway across
the world and do a show.
John McEnroe and John McEnroe is the answer to that question.
Why?
I got a friend that I can I got a friend in mime, no relation, Lauren Saw and Lauren got
to work with Marceau before he passed.
And like, I feel like you've got kind of a similar thing here now that you are a direct
line from Cyr into this unique art form.
So have you already been approached by people?
Are you?
Are you an instructor at this point in that way?
Are you are you leaning into that kind of bearing of the torch for this art form now?
I definitely can instruct to do private lessons for people who want to.
I'm really more into the creation side of it.
I've realized that I'm not really teaching for me is is it's cool, but I much rather
make a one man show, you know, a character based one man show that that's where I like
my I find my passion.
I mean, I am going to have you teach my children just so that just to save me on college money.
Just really at this point, it's as good an option as anything.
It really is.
No, for real.
Like that's the thing is like you like and you can go to circus college in Montreal.
They have the Ecole Nationale de Cirque, which is a it's a university.
It's in Montreal.
And if they are passionate about circus, kids who are 18 can audition.
Well, I think one who's not passionate about anything, so I feel like I am going to be
sending him to that school.
Just because I find find a passion there.
Yeah, for sure.
Like it's such an amazing program.
I actually funny thing I auditioned for the National Circus School of Montreal the same
week I auditioned for Cirque-L-Oise, so I had two intense days of auditioning for the
National Circus School of Montreal back in 2003.
And then also, I had three intense days that turned into four because I got a callback
for Cirque-L-Oise.
You grew up in New York, right?
Yeah, originally in New York City.
Was anyone in the circus starts or anything like that when you were growing up?
No, we had we had Ringling Brothers, Barman Bailey Circus every year, which I would go
see at Madison Square Garden.
And we had the Big Apple Circus.
Yeah.
All right.
But all these circus performers were like of circus families, right?
So everybody was they had generations of circus knowledge.
Our friend Brian is ringmastering the Big Apple Circus right now.
That's right.
Brian Alters.
It's so cool.
I just saw that.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
So happy for him.
And so I figured out I didn't figure out that circus could be a possible thing that I could
do.
So I was twenty five and I was like, oh, there's a clown program.
That's amazing.
Like, let me let me audition for that.
And I think that's the whole movement of New Circus, right?
And Cirque du Soleil is like you can have diverse you come from diverse backgrounds.
So a lot of the house troupe comes from gymnastics, right?
You can have a soloist that comes from the dance world that then trained in circus.
Like it's it's actually to your benefit to have an to have a new family history.
Contrary to popular belief.
Yeah.
No, it's like it's a it's a whole new world where you can train yourself in a year or
two or maybe more, depending and really get to a high level of circus.
There is there is a whole new breed of circus artists out right now that are doing what
what he's talking about.
I mean, this is a brand new thing.
It's really great.
I mean, social media has done that.
It's like it has to the magic world, right?
It's the reason why magicians are finally a more diverse group of people.
We're not like going like what a woman doing a magic trick is still say that, come on.
But yeah, yeah, that's one of the one of the many positive aspects of the Internet is one
of the three positive aspects.
More people are getting into circus.
It's pretty cool, well, Jonas, we'll send people to theater dot Vegas, theater re dot
Vegas or the at least inside of it, you can go see them in L.A.
What do people follow you in general because you travel obviously travel over the world
reform over the world.
What do people follow you in general?
Yeah, you can follow me on Instagram.
That's usually where I put all my shenanigans at zoo punk, Cirque.
So it's spelled Z, you punk, P, U, N, K, Cirque, C, I, R, Q, U, E.
OK.
We'll put it in chat for anybody.
Yeah, we'll put it in the bio of the episode as well.
Perfect.
Yeah.
That's Instagram is usually where you can find out information about Mac and Fro Show.
I'm also in puppetry of the penis.
We didn't even get to that.
Right.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Sure.
That has its own.
There's literally a trick in puppetry of the penis.
That's an ice cream cone.
Ice cream.
Next scoop fest.
We are.
I mean, we know we know a lot of puppetry of the penis, people.
Like, I'm buddies with Jamie and well, you know, Jamie, of course, too.
And you know, you know, he hired me.
Yeah.
Well, you know, tons of puppetry.
We had the original guys that came out here, Barry and, oh, Barry and Rich.
Barry and Rich.
Yes.
They did our first scoop fest.
Yep.
And it was really funny because there was 200 people laughing, applauding and one person
who just turned and looked at a wall during the performance.
It was awesome.
It was amazing.
Yeah, they couldn't.
It was a fascinating wall in my defense.
That paint was nearly dry.
I got to watch that paint just completely dry.
It was amazing.
I still remember because, you know, scoop fest, we just say like, hey, if you want to
do a slot, do whatever.
We just want you to do it.
You just tell us what you want to do.
And so they said yes to doing it.
And then I never clarified what they were going to do.
And so before the show, I was like, I don't know what you guys want to do, if you guys
feel comfortable, where you're at or like how much longer of a slot do you want, blah,
blah, blah.
They go, oh, we're whipping our dicks out.
I go, okay, okay.
Okay.
And that was the full conversation.
That was it.
Okay.
The most important question of today is how much space did they need to whip their dicks?
16 by 16 foot stage.
Yeah.
Get us on the horn, folks.
They had so much room for activities.
Metric.
Metric 16 by 16.
16 meter.
For all you listeners out there that can't see this podcast, I'm making the hamburger
right now.
I like that you're like, you saw I must do the clown.
You saw the cereal.
I must do the cereal.
You saw the hamburger.
You're like, I must make shapes of my penis.
I must.
I must do it.
I was already doing it, right?
Right.
I get paid?
Sure.
It's like every man's dream, you get paid.
How often do you do that show?
That's Thursday through Sunday in Vegas at the Erotic Heritage Museum.
Okay.
Eight o'clock show, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
And then I'm also at the Wizard of Oz doing this really cool immersive experience after
the movie at the Spear.
I like right now there's some listeners who are like, yeah, whatever, I'm just going to
go see him play with his dick.
Wizard of Oz, sure, but I'm going to go to the dick thing, I think.
I mean, it's the last one of its kind, it's holding on as we're celebrating 10 years of
puppetry of the penis in Vegas.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the Wizard of Oz at the Spear.
Although I do have to make a couple of jokes in puppetry about Wizard of Oz, I'm like,
you know, you had all these choices in entertainment and you decided to come to, you know, you
could have went to the Wizard of Oz at the Spear and dick it, but you chose this.
That's it.
That is it.
A different kind of flying monkey, that's all.
Choose your flying monkey.
Oh, you got to come up with a new cock and balls trick called the flying monkey in honor
of the Wizard of Oz.
Oh, we got Halloween coming up, I'm trying to like this week, figure out what the best
trick would be.
Well, yeah, you guys do the bat wing, right?
We could do bat wing.
Yeah, I want to maybe the vampire, like I've got these teeth, these glow in the dark.
Oh, there you go.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to work that into the show for the Halloween for on Friday.
The dick that sucks itself, the vampire.
You can have it.
Take it.
I want that show to run forever.
I have news for you.
Paul's not going to do it.
I'm not.
You wanted to open for cock.
You could.
Yeah.
Some one of these that had to develop some kind of a stand up bit.
Something I could just do the hamburger later on.
I can only do the slider.
I need to go back to my ventriloquist days.
I need to get a ventriloquist bit worked up.
That's what I need to do.
And how do you do that?
I'm going to do the slide.
I need to go back to my ventriloquist days.
I need to get a ventriloquist bit worked up.
That's what I need to do.
And honey, I need to move back to Vegas.
Important work.
Yeah.
Really got to go.
And yeah, I know we just repainted the house and we're loving our life out here.
Time for me to go play with my dick.
You'll support me, right?
As long as I don't have to anymore.
Okay.
Great.
Somebody said the Marilyn Manson trick.
Oh, I don't know.
Is that for a dick trick?
Is that just sucking your own dick?
Oh, that's the whole, you cut your ribs out.
That, that whole.
Right.
I think David Gahan from Peshmo do that too.
Urban Legend.
Yeah.
Well, Jonas, we're about to descend into a bunch of Halloween bits, so you're welcome
to run away at this point if you want to go, go, go live your life.
I'll stick around in it because I'm going to practice my, you know, I'm going to be
my vampire trick.
Oh, good.
Good.
I'll tell you who else is going to practice their new vampire dick and balls trick while
we wait.
And that's the following sponsor.
Oh my.
Today's show, Men, Men as Ice Cream and Soul Show, is brought to you by Black Hole Baby
Diapers from Teddy Officer Scoop, also in 2021.
That's Black Hole Baby Diapers.
Hello.
It's me, Carl Sagan.
I'm here from beyond the grave to tell you about the billions and billions of infants
shitting and pissing themselves throughout the nation.
It's a high time that you buy them the proper undergarments.
What I have is Black Hole Diapers.
What these will do is, of course, open a rift in space time that we're not really certain
what's on the other side of it.
But we do know that the piss and shit of the children will get instantly sucked into it,
spaghettified into the tiniest, smallest form that it can be and thrown into some alternate
dimension or whatever.
Again, it's all theoretical.
We don't know what lies on the other side.
However, we can, with some assurance, state that on the other side of our Black Hole Diapers,
there's a great quantity of piss and shit.
Go ahead and buy these Black Hole Diapers for your children.
Make sure that they don't sit directly on the hole.
That's the trick.
You don't want to spaghettify your babies, or maybe some of you do.
I don't know.
This demon-haunted world is enveloping all of us.
Why not let it envelop your piss and shit from your children?
Do the environmentally sound thing and send all the piss and shit from your babies into
the nether regions of time and space.
That's Black Hole Diapers from Carl Sagan.
Enter Hey Scoops at checkout.
Well, let's see.
Oh, my Uber Eats is here.
Hold on.
I just have to go get my Uber Eats here.
Oh, my Uber Eats driver.
It's vampire Bill Cosby.
What do you know?
What do you say?
How you doing?
Hey, hey, hey.
It's Bill Cosby.
I'm here to give you what you ordered from the store and some things.
Oh, thanks.
Some sundries.
There you go.
Have what you need.
Theo is dead.
Boo.
He's a ghost this year.
Yeah, that's right.
He came with me.
He's right here.
This is my son, Theo, who's a ghost now.
He couldn't scare the fuck out of you.
That's what he does.
He's scaring you.
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
Was he scared?
Yes.
Well, you should be.
Good.
This is my ghost son who died in the ocean trying to save his baby, but he did, and he
did.
Oh, boy.
It's too bad.
It's a terrible thing.
Well, thanks for coming by.
Thanks for bringing my groceries here.
You know, I'm never going to miss a chance to come and hang out during the holiday.
This is my favorite holiday.
It's on the holiday.
I get released.
It's not true.
I'm free now.
I can do whatever I want.
That's right.
No jail can hold the cause.
Oh, vampire Bill Cosby.
I'm so sorry.
I have to answer the story here.
I'm going to turn into a bat then.
Poof.
Goodbye.
Flap, flap, flap.
I'm gone.
Oh, that's too bad.
He would have really loved to have met our next guest.
It's actually Piff the Magic Dragon.
Piff, come on in.
Right.
I'm a magician, isn't it?
Hey, what do you want?
We've got some free candy for me, mate.
Come on in.
Where's your grub?
Give it over.
I want some MPay days, right?
Here, I'm a dragon.
OK, yeah.
Here's some candy.
Yeah, too, right.
I'm going to sit on a hoard of candy.
Piff, I just want to congratulate you.
Your 10-year anniversary is coming up soon.
10 years of being a Las Vegas headliner.
That's got to feel pretty good, huh, buddy?
That's right.
It's a decade of decades from Mr. Piff the Magic Dragon.
What, what, what, what, what?
I'll be entertaining everybody.
Can't nobody hold me down.
Hey, look, guess what I'm going to do?
I'm going to make all you bitches disappear.
Poof, where'd Chris Angel go?
Oh, fucking no, do I?
I'm taking over his spot.
Yeah.
That bitch is off.
Done.
I'm the king.
One king.
Are you still going to use the wind machines and blow garbage on people?
I mean, I wouldn't be much of a drag if I didn't blow off people with some fire and stuff.
That's kind of what I'd do.
That's fair.
That is fair.
That's right.
You're going to be touring next year with Penn, doing Piff and Pop.
You say so.
No, I do say so.
It's happening.
I'm all right.
I'll take you word out.
Oh no.
At least I got top billing, didn't I?
What?
Isn't it?
It sounds like you need some, maybe some, some legal advice on how to deal with this
tour coming up with, with Penn here.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I think, I think it's all settled.
I got top billing.
That's all I need.
Uh-oh, somebody else is here.
I better run away.
No, no, this is great, Piff.
What?
Stick around and chat with, this is our friend, the forgetful goldfish lawyer.
Maybe, maybe the forgetful goldfish lawyer can help you out a little bit.
Uh, what is it you need?
Uh, uh, Piff wants to make sure that he understands he's protected in this, uh, tour that he's
coming up with, Ben Gillette.
Okay.
Let me look into my briefcase here.
Well, it looks like all I've got in here is Tetraflakes.
What were you asking me again?
Uh, uh, you, you want to, if you want to take Piff the magic dragon as a client.
Who's that now?
He's a magician in Las Vegas.
What's your name, sir?
Oh, I'm Matt.
I'm the co-host of this podcast.
Okay.
Uh, let me go ahead and call somebody.
Hmm.
I've forgotten all the phone numbers.
Okay.
Well, okay.
That's what goldfish do.
We just forget.
I understand.
Uh.
What?
You, you forgot something?
I forgot to breathe for about a minute there.
Oh no.
Oh gosh.
It happens.
Yeah.
But, uh, you know, we don't, you don't have to make any calls now.
I just want to know that you're, you know.
Well, I'll tell you what I don't want is this idiot representing me for anything.
It's a bullshit.
Piff, this is a great, he's a great lawyer, Piff.
The fuck he is.
I'll tell you, the only thing he's got in common with the law, he's got the scales of justice.
That's about it.
He can fin his way right out of the fuck out of here.
Go on and swim away, you dumb bitch.
Isn't it?
Oh, wow.
The lawyer is leaving.
That is, that is horrible.
He was, he was.
It's upsetting.
It's just hard to see.
He ran into a light post.
Oh my goodness.
For an idiot he is.
I'm going to go chase him.
I will see you later, Piff.
Thanks for coming by.
Bye, Piff.
Happy Halloween.
Fuck all of you.
Wow.
Jesus.
Fuck.
Really, really acerbic over these 10 years.
That was, that was by far the most, yeah.
He's changed.
It's gone to his head.
All that, all that success.
All that instant ease.
All that, all that golden princesses.
It's really gone to his head.
You know, being a Las Vegas headliner is so easy.
It's all gone to his head.
So easy.
Yep.
Well, it's been a good week, everybody.
How did you guys have a good week?
I had a great week.
Are you asking me?
I, sorry.
Yes.
I was asking you and then three notifications somehow popped up on my screen all at the
same time.
It really distracted me.
I got to re-watch Groundhog Day this week.
Oh yeah.
Over and over again.
Yeah.
It was on over and over again.
And it really struck me how much faster he accepted that the day was happening over and
over again to him than I believe I would have in that situation.
Oh, he's just like, second day, he's like, "Oh, I see what's going on."
He's like, "Oh, I guess this is happening."
Yeah.
I've got it.
He really just kind of took it all in stride pretty well.
I watched, on the plane, I watched Sinners.
Oh yeah.
How was that?
Michael B. Jordan.
Love it.
It's a vampire movie, but I don't know if you, I don't think anyone wants to talk about
this.
There's like racial undertones to it.
Oh boy.
I just, I was very subtle.
I picked up on it.
Interesting.
You know, I saw some stuff in the trailer that made me think that that might be part
of what they were going to talk about, but I, but I couldn't really tell.
Yeah.
I saw no seeds until I watched the movie.
I was like, "Wait a minute."
It's so good.
I fucking loved Sinners.
It's a great, it's really good.
Michael B. Jordan is so good.
He crushes it, yeah.
And they really kind of, really try to anchor the whiteness of the vampires.
They do it with, specifically with like, kind of like Irish music.
And I felt like a little, a little, a little attacked then.
Not, not the white part, but the Irish part, the Irish part.
As you should.
Wait a minute.
But yeah.
Oh, that is, that is terrible.
Oh gosh.
Oh, oh shit, it's B. Arthur's candy cooter corn now with nuts.
Wait, that's a commercial, not a character.
I agree.
These people are sneaking in extra commercials into our social media feed.
Picture it, Sicily, 1939.
My daughter's cooter is overflowing with waxy candy.
We should say that all of these characters are submitted by our listeners on all of our
social media channels.
So these were all put on our Facebook and Instagram posts yesterday.
So if you're not following us on social media, we do the Halloween episode and the Christmas
episode where people stop by.
That's right.
And we just pimp Paul all episode.
Who's next?
Whoa, bring it says Paul Paul's like, whoa, ring the bell, Jacob.
I could out of that cooter corn.
Holy shit.
It's Ding Dong Mitch.
The guy who doesn't understand how to ding dong ditch.
Hey, hello.
Hey there.
Gotcha.
Hi.
What do you mean?
Gotcha.
You answered the door.
Boom.
Yeah, gotcha.
Did you ring the doorbell again?
Might've been me.
Gotcha.
We.
What?
How did you get us?
Gotcha.
Most people answer their doorbell.
Hey, check.
Check this out.
What's that?
Gotcha.
No, I don't think that's how you get me, buddy.
I don't know.
We saw you ring it.
I don't feel gotten.
Yeah.
Do you understand?
Okay.
Because my doorbell works.
Is that how you got me?
Look, is there somebody at the door?
Yeah, you.
Yes.
Better go.
Better go answer the door.
I am.
Hey, check it out.
Hi.
Could be your other door.
Okay.
I'll walk to my.
Did you check your other door yet?
I'll go walk to my back door.
Gotcha.
It was this one.
It was this door.
Hey, hey.
I hate this guy.
Still me.
Still me in your door.
Gotcha.
Hmm.
Ding dong.
Mitch.
Basically a force of nature over here.
Check it.
All right.
Thank you.
There you go.
Okay.
You're.
One more.
Gotcha.
Bye.
I hate that guy.
I'll see you in a little bit.
Mike in chat says he submitted characters on our Truth Social account.
Are you getting any?
Are you reading from those, Jacob?
Are you reading any of those, Jacob?
Yeah, yeah.
No, I've got our Truth Social account.
Okay.
Yeah, I definitely.
Truth Social account.
I'm definitely reading all of those.
Yeah.
Oh, actually from the Truth Social account we have the woke truck driver.
Here he is.
There he is.
Hey, God damn it.
Where's your pride flag?
Fuck you.
They just, they break down with the wind and stuff.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we got a little sun bleached.
Oh, I just.
I just didn't have time to put it up this year.
Well, eat shit.
Well, I was gonna.
I was trying to.
Uh, yeah.
Sure.
But I had to get to my, my, uh, my friends.
I'm going to my, my friend's daughter's basketball game.
And so I wasn't able to get the flags up on time, but I gotta go.
Right.
I'm sure your friend's daughter's basketball game where I'm sure they've talked a bunch
of shit about trans athletes participating and they haven't allowed some, isn't that
right?
Outrageous behavior.
Absolutely outrageous.
Do you know trans rights are human rights?
You piece of shit.
You know that, right?
Fuck you.
Okay.
Apparently you don't know that.
Why don't you go eat your own shit, you non pride flag having son of a bitch.
Wow.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, apologize to my fucking fist when it goes to your head.
I will.
Yeah.
You better.
Do you want some candy?
Only if it's been made with LGBTQIA professionals.
Okay.
I want the gayest candy.
You can give my skills.
That is it.
You win.
Okay.
All right.
Back in top of the day to you, top of the day to you.
I'm going to taste the rainbow.
Sounds good.
Have a good night.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You too.
Yeah.
Fuck y'all.
Oh, it's Truman Capote Truman.
What brings you by?
Well, I've just terribly excited and I was hoping there'd be some candy here.
Oh, that last guy just took the last of the Skittles.
That's all right.
Those don't feel nearly as good inside of me as a mounds bar does.
Sometimes you do feel like a nut.
I do every time.
Oh, wait.
That's all I'm enjoying.
Sometimes you don't.
That's mounds.
Fair enough.
Now, Truman is a movie out right now.
Springsteen was obsessed with the Nebraska, the murders in Nebraska.
You wrote the book in cold blood, right?
That's right.
I did.
The stock weather events, they were terrible tragedies, but very American, if you know
what I mean, but ultimately it's good that we're talking of this on Halloween because
it really comes down to the boy didn't get enough candy.
That's it?
Oh, is that the, that was the root?
That's really the crux of it.
Yes.
Stock weather was starved for some chocolate.
Okay.
Well, that's a shame.
That's good to know.
Yes.
So, you know, is that something that could happen to future people if they, if they don't
get enough Halloween candy?
Give your children lots of kisses or they might murder people.
They might murder people, Hershey it up every Halloween.
All right.
Hashtag can't bury it up.
You had buried it up.
I should say you heard it from true.
You should bury it up.
Did I can't bury the lead?
Now, Truman, did you get to see the Bruce Springsteen movie?
I certainly did see it was something.
The boss is the boss.
Did you have a favorite moment in the, in the film?
I enjoyed the credits rolling very much people to get their due.
My exit of the theater was loved.
Yes.
I appreciate seeing all the hard work that went into that mediocrity and just reassures
me that, you know, even when I'm working with Harper Lee, you know, nothing's guaranteed
you know, I wrote that book essentially, okay, yes, but I was just saying thank you for coming
by Truman.
We appreciate it.
You would say that.
Have a good night.
This is you did not see the Springsteen movie.
Is that correct?
I have not seen the Springsteen movie.
I'm actually going to watch it tomorrow.
Okay.
Paul and I did go see it together the day of the day of the wedding and stuff.
I did get the re-release Nebraska album though, that I've been listening to.
Oh cool.
There's some gems on there.
It's a fucking banger.
Yeah.
No kidding around that re-release Nebraska.
I haven't listened because it's a multi-album release and one of them is the him doing Nebraska
at the Count Basie theater.
Ooh.
I have to check that out myself.
Yeah.
So it's really good.
I've listened to the 2025 remaster of it so far and it is excellent.
I have a very exciting interview actually for you guys.
I haven't told you guys about it.
We're closing out the show with it.
The guests should be here any moment now.
This is really going to be exciting.
It could possibly be the last interview on Ice Cream Social depending on who is touched
by who in this.
Oh good.
They're here.
Ah, this is our guest for the end of the show here.
It is the Death Snail.
This is the snail that slowly crawls after all of us and if it touches us, we die.
That's right.
So we have to avoid being touched by this snail during this interview.
Thank you for coming by snail.
I'm just going to get away.
I started walking towards your house last Thanksgiving.
Oh, well, I'm glad you could finally make it our way.
Are you aware that you were part of our merchandise sales?
Our Kiss the Snail campaign is actually sold very well in our store.
Yes, I saw.
Boy, I hope I can one day afford a new shell.
Oh, so sorry.
Is it a burden to kill everyone you touch?
Burden is a heavy word.
I do like my powers.
Oh, you like you kind of like being an arbiter of death.
When you're an incredibly slow moving mollusk, you have few options in life.
But having the ability to kill things instantaneously evens the odds a bit.
I suppose it would.
Do you do you leave a traditional snail trail behind you after taking these lives?
It's somewhat traditional, but it has a design in it.
You know that special S that people always make on their folders and things?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
That's what I leave behind me.
You leave the weird little S thing that looks the same no matter how you look at it.
That's right.
Because I don't know if you're aware of this.
I'm also an automobile engineer.
I was not.
No, that's do you work for a specific dealership or anything?
No, I'm a self-employed.
I'm kind of like, you know, make my own sort of deal.
The tires have that S on it as well.
And you know, that's to make the imprint very clear.
So when you drive one of my autos, everybody knows where your S car goes.
I want to thank Pinch Let's Greatness podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I want to thank Thomas Overton for stopping by.
Thanks, Jonas.
And for staying around for this bullshit.
If we can't go out on an S car fun, I don't know what we can do.
Look at that S car go.
I want to thank the following people.
All of these people crushed their fingers just once training on a sear wheel.
That is Dan 33, Kappa Scoop, Chris Meyer, Cream City Scoop, Craig Little, Craig De Farmer,
Court Myers, Country Scoop, Counselor Matt, Courtney Scoop, Coriann Ichimura, Cone Photo
Scoop Sector, I think I said that right, Colton Satmary, Colleen Fisher, Coffee Bean Scoop,
Coconut Time Travel, Coach Rat Bastard, Cloud in a Brothel, Clayton Shoney, and CJ Magnata.
The following people can hear a sandstorm coming from miles away, Charles De Shecky,
Charles Eaton, Cassie Rice, Carolyn Albert, Captain James T. Scoop, Canadian Scoop, Crystal,
Cameron Hall, Callie Ghost, C. Wick, Buster Kamikaze, Brian Traves, Brian McLeod, Brooks
Lyle, Brian Richard, Brian Maddox, aka Anarcho Scoop, Brendan Allen, Brendan Light, Brad
Martin, Bobby Becerra, and Bob.
The following people all got three hours of exotic farm massages with heavy oil and no
happy ending, I promise.
Chronicler Scoop, Christy Salinas, Christopher Huff, Christopher Heyworth, Christine Starr,
Christine Elsesser, Chris Melikon, Chris Kay, Chris Yorg, Chris Jackson, Chris Fisher,
Chris Ellis, Chris Bartsey, Chelsea Farr, Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Charlie Thompson.
Thank you so much.
The following people have the same dreams as Jonas to run off and join the Three Cockring
Circus.
Bowson Scoop, Blue Line Scoop, Bill Beatty, Bike Scoop, Big Sexy, the Digital Nomad, Big
Lotus Scoop, Ben Sherman Scoop, Ben Smith, Ben Gao, Ben Dennis, Ben, Belgian Triple Scoop,
BJ Joyer, Bear Scoop, and Bearded Scoop 3.
The following scoops all have giant penises that are measured in the metric system.
That is B.B.
Hermit, Basecamp Scoops, Bart Vonk, Bad Pirate Scoop, AWOL Scoop, Avin Zarls, Aramis Saar,
Apple Scoop, Anton Jernberg, Ant Foods, Angry Face Scoop, Angela Chan, Andy Cheek, Andrew
Ostruck, Andrew Koenig, Andrew J. Hughes, Andrea Anderson, Ameristat Scoop, All Star
Scoop, Alla Scoop 6666, Akshay Mysore, AJB, Adam Stickney, Adam Goff, Aaron Wintling,
Aaron Boyd, Aaron, A Scoop of Root Canal, A Ranch Slunk, One Small Scoop for Man, The
Unbanned Scoop, We All Scream for Mark McLean, Underscore for Shaping, The Micro Scoop, and
Signature Curl Scoop.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do appreciate you.
If you want to be thanked on air or get a myriad of other offerings that we do, find
a tier that fits your budget and support us today over at PreachingFun.com.
Or if you don't like your wheels, Siri, you like 'em German, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com, it does take you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
If you think this show is worth more than $0, fartsinabag.biz, PreachingFun.com, those
are the websites that you need to go to help keep this show on the air.
Do it now.
It's kind of awesome.
I actually bake my wheels at a low temperature over a long period and I just sear them at
the last minute.
Smart.
You do a reverse sear wheel.
I do a reverse sear wheel.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
You cannot be serious.
Did you buy this in America?
It should have American measurements on it.
I thought he was kidding.
He wasn't.
We are in for a metric ton of bullshit.
That's all.
We sure are.
We're PreachingFun.
They're going to sell tape measures and they won't have the centimeters on the top side
of the thing.
They'll be like, no.
They're just crossed out.
Get them off.
They just took a Sharpie to it.
A Sharpie.
Just blacked out.
Just cheap.
Just blacked it all out.
You motherfuckers.
It's still there.
I needed that.
Just blacked out.
I can't do the conversion in my head.
I need it on the tape.
Damn.
Oh, no.
Love you, everybody.
See ya.
Save big on everything for your next project, now at Menards.
Breathe easier with Best Air allergen air filters.
They trap larger airborne contaminants to keep allergens out of your home and they last
up to 90 days.
Save big on all Best Air products at Menards and refresh your home today.
View our entire selection of air filtration products on Menards.com.
Plus, check out our weekly flyer and find great deals happening this week.