(upbeat music)
- Oh, hello there, I am so glad you're here
because I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Fifi, Frankie's Tiki Scoop,
Galactic President Scooperstar McScoops-A-Lot,
Ice Blue Scoop, I Wanna Scoop Baby,
and Jacob Dinkalager.
If you wanna be an ice cream truck driver
just like these fine folks, and I hope you do,
PreachingFun.com is where you can go, PreachingFun.com,
right over there.
You can sign up to be an ice cream truck driver,
and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
And now, a program.
- Hey Johnny, do you wanna go to an ice cream social?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Great, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- We had a party at the house last night.
I stayed up too late.
- Oh no.
- Too late, I say.
- Were you drinking?
- Sure.
- You were drinking, that's what's really funny.
- Of course I was.
- It's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, PA, that's Paul Mattingly.
Also sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
- We sure are, yee-haw.
Well I did it, guys.
I taught my first improv class in a long time.
- Woo!
- Well I've been teaching other improv classes,
but this was my first structured improv class in a long time
where I'm having the same students over and over again.
I got 12.
- The second woo was for the structure,
not for the improv class.
- 12 wonderful students.
- You got a good structure.
- And I gotta say, I'm a little apprehensive
'cause of course at the end of class,
what do you think I did?
I obelisked all of 'em.
I gave everybody a chip.
So you know.
- Give everybody a chip.
- I'm either gonna have some people coming back being like,
oh wow, Paul, okay.
Or people are like, who am I learning from?
Good God.
(laughing)
So anyway, yeah.
I took the gamble. - Hello, students.
You fools.
(laughing)
Hello, Paul students.
- Exactly.
I took the gamble and we'll see.
But big thanks again to Justin
for getting things cooking again with Skit
and for giving me the opportunity to teach.
I'm really, really excited. - Love of the game.
- Yeah, and no, it's gonna be really good.
- More good stuff happening.
- If you haven't figured it out,
Justin Zell's not in it for the money.
I don't know if you have to figure that out yet.
- Or if he is, he's bad at it.
- Well, no, and you know what?
Well, the other thing is too, neither am I.
I mean, you're not teaching improv to make,
but it is helping me do less target work, which is great.
- That's exactly it.
That's exactly it.
- Yeah.
- One less day of working at a target.
- That is precisely it.
I have cut back to basically three days a week now
and it's gonna save my ass 'cause, oh man.
Oh, cash grab Mattingly.
That's right, Rich, too. - That's good.
I don't want you walking around Target too much
because I don't want that sweet, sweet derriere to fade away.
- I mean, it's true.
The words of-- - You gotta keep them cakes, baby.
- The words of Sir Mix-A-Lot ring in my ears every day,
especially days like today
when I'm slurping on a little chocolate milkshake.
I don't want none. - You can do side bans
or sit-ups, but please don't lose that butt.
- Oh, trust, trust.
This shelf is firmly intact.
This shelf is here, baby.
Yeah.
- Matt Donnelly, you're back on dry land.
- Yeah, man, yes.
Yeah, I'm sorry that I cannot attend your party,
but literally I haven't been home in a month,
so it was like--
- Oh, SJ was like, I sent Matt and Sara a text
about the party.
I didn't hear back from them.
I didn't say anything to her,
but I was like, they are not coming.
(laughing)
- I think Matt is back on land.
They're not coming to our house.
- No, no, no, we're very happy.
Two nights in a row, got to have all four of us home
with our children, and then of course, yeah,
I was on full soccer dad duties last night,
which took me around town or whatever, but yeah.
- How are the boys?
Did you notice any changes since you were gone?
- Uh, yes, yeah, yeah.
- Have they gotten employment?
- Yeah.
- Lots of six, seven?
- Oh, so yeah, so I was in the car with my oldest
and somebody that goes to school with, driving them home.
And I told them, I was like, you know, my son now,
my oldest son now goes to performing arts middle school.
So that means I'm probably gonna play improv games.
- That's awesome.
- Totally.
And so we were comparing, 'cause I just went home for,
the last thing I did was I did my improv jam room,
which I want to talk a lot about on the show.
- Yeah.
- But we were going over improv games,
and I said, yeah, these are games I started playing
when I was like 16, 17 years old.
And they started laughing.
(laughing)
And I said, wait, 16, 17 counts as six, seven?
- Ah.
- Oh, did they get called out?
Didn't they were like, oh.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, they were laughing, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Good, good, good.
- No, no, they're not subtle about it.
Like we were driving the car and my kid is like,
perfect time.
And I look and it says six, oh, seven on the dash.
(laughing)
Like it's not subtle.
- No, it's everywhere.
It's everywhere.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Craziness.
- The new South Park is all of it.
- All six, seven.
- People know that it means nothing.
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Right, yeah, it's just gibberish.
It's just gibberish, yeah.
- They know that like it just happened to be in a song
and then some guy did it on a TikTok
and it's all out there.
- Yeah, it's just in there.
- And it vaguely annoyed some of their parents.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So yeah, but I went--
- Theotic clumsy.
They were just laughing at the idea of you being young.
- Yes, that part is definitely true.
(laughing)
Well, that's the whole thing.
Even we were putting together the improv lineup.
We're like, you know, I know it's been 27 years
for me to do this, it's been 27 years for me to do that.
And I go, can we, we should stop saying 27 years.
It's definitely been 31 years.
- Oh my God, that's what's blew in my mind
when I'm teaching again.
- It's been 27 years and then a few more.
- Yeah, one of my students asked me straight up,
it's like, how long have you been teaching?
How long have you been teaching?
I'm like 20 years.
And I'm like, wait, I've been teaching like 22 years.
And if I've been teaching 22 years,
I've been improvising 35 years.
- Oh my God.
Let's not go down this rabbit hole.
- This is a depressing rabbit hole for any of us to go down.
- But this is like what I was talking about.
Like as my buddy, Pat, my buddy, Pat,
he's gonna be doing the tyranny thing with us this Thursday.
I found out that I've been spelling his name wrong
for our entire friendship, which was embarrassing.
He was like, I'm pretty sure we talked about this
multiple times.
I was like, I have a false memory of you telling me
how to spell your name properly.
Where I, it's Pat Shepard.
I've been spelling it with the second,
I've been spelling it Shepard.
And I thought for a fact,
that's actually what he instructed me to do one time.
He was like, it's like Shep and Hart.
And I was like, great.
And I literally had a conversation with him
like just like three days ago.
Or he was like, nope, never said that.
Never tried to do that.
Definitely been all ease on my last name
the entire time you've known me.
And I was like, how do I make up
for the fact that I've been spelling you?
Like I can't, that's like, there's no mea culpa.
Like we're lifelong friends.
Like we are our friends for entire improv lives.
And I think the only thing that you can do here
is tell him how to spell your last name incorrectly.
And let him spell it incorrectly the rest of your life.
- My brain was really racking like possible
like big time solutions.
'Cause it's so embarrassing.
How do you undo 30 years of mistakes?
Like it's also like, it's the number one bitch
behind my back, right?
If you're like, guy doesn't even spell my name right.
We're supposed to be brothers.
You know, like I have no defense for being like,
if there's any sense of like, I am a fucking ogre, selfish ogre.
It's like, I never learned how to spell.
- It's better than what I thought you meant though.
I thought you meant you were misspelling Pat.
- No.
P-I-T, Pat.
- Shit.
- And it's not like we're casual friends.
No, like possible side effects.
Many press releases, many articles,
many listings of who's playing in the shows.
I've put out his name numerous times
and shouted it to the rafters with incorrect spelling.
Just 30 years.
- I don't think, I don't think that you can change it.
I think the only way forward is to continue on.
- He was like, no, we've definitely had conversations about it.
I was like, well, clearly I don't remember.
I go, I just want to say clearly.
One, I'm sorry.
And two, this wasn't some elaborate trolling
that I've been doing a bitch for 30 years.
Like I don't, I know I'm capable of these bits.
This wasn't it though.
- Oh man, side note on the word bit.
Fucking, so jealous.
Amy Poehler, great podcast.
And she's interviewed two people about two elaborate bits.
One is the guy, Cole Escala, who wrote "Oh Mary."
- "Oh Mary."
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- They are so fucking funny.
They are amazing.
- He has a bit where he calls someone
and on their voicemail, he leaves a message
as if he's talking to someone else's voicemail
about the person.
So he's talking about having to kill the person
he's leaving a message for to another person.
So like if I called Paul, I'd be like, what's up, Jacob?
Look, it's gotta go down.
Paul's out of hand.
(laughing)
- Like he's accidentally called the wrong number?
- Yes, yeah.
- We have to murder Paul.
- So that's a bit he does with all of his friends.
Like he has to murder, he's colluding with their other
friends to murder that person.
- Great, that's pretty great.
- Which I'm so jealous of that bit.
And then fucking Aziz Ansari.
His bit on Amy Poehler's was fantastic.
- So he found out Amy Poehler's kids,
the names of their best friends.
And so when the kids would visit set,
Aziz Ansari would walk by on the phone,
pretending to talk to their best friends and ignoring them.
- Amy Poehler's children's best friends.
So he wouldn't speak to her children.
He would pretend to speak to their friends.
And it's like Dalton or something like that.
But it was like, oh yeah, hey Dalton.
No, I haven't seen Amy Poehler's kids around lately.
Yeah, I don't know where they are.
I'm sure they're fine, but I don't know where they are.
- But let's get together.
Let's play this, let's do that.
Like he's just like making plans and like,
and I'm like, oh, that's a really good bit.
That is a really, really good fit.
But yeah, so we got together hilariously
at Kevin Smith's Smod Castle.
We did the reunion, right?
- Yes.
- And so I just walked in and I am just surrounded
by Kevin Smith, everything, right?
They've decorated everything.
Just a ton of memorabilia.
- I just saw, he just got the mall rats poster,
original art, very, very recently framed up.
That's the Drew Struzan piece who just passed away.
- He just passed away, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Legendary artist, Drew Struzan.
Yeah, so.
He did, I mean, really, it's worth looking up that guy.
He did every movie poster he wrote.
- Oh, everything that we grew up with, for sure.
Drew Struzan, yeah, he did.
- Oh, yeah, that's something that I've been wanting
to get into kind of quietly for a long time
is old movie posters and start collecting those.
But that is, the bar to entry,
getting into that kind of collection is intense.
- Well, if you're getting like,
'cause I mean, what he bought
was the original painted work.
- Right, right, which is even crazier.
- Yes, it's like 30, 30 grand.
- I'm not even looking at that kind of stuff.
But yeah, even just the original prints, though.
- Oh, sure, the ones that used to be in movie houses.
Because a lot of those are double printed, right?
So they can be illuminated from the back
and that kind of thing.
- A lot of them are double printed
or a lot of them have like multiple things
with the silver, it's all, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- All right, sorry to completely derail,
but yes, you're in this podcast
and you're full of all this memorabilia.
Even one part, there's the poster with like,
it's one of those stereoscopic vision posters where you--
- Oh yeah, with the sailboat, the schooner.
- Yeah, yeah, and so it had Jay and Silent Bob underneath
and then Jay talking.
I have a button that was misprinted
and has Silent Bob talking with the comic book bubble.
- Oh, funny.
- It's one of my like little pieces of memorabilia
I'm keeping for if it should be valuable one day.
It's a misprint.
So it turns out Kevin Smith decided to do
a mall rats full cast reunion video,
I mean the movie watching and Q&A with the entire cast
on the same exact night as my informant.
(laughing)
- Yes, did you get him a chip?
That's all I wanna know, that's all I wanna know.
(laughing)
- I know, I know if Matt got him a chip or not.
- No, this is--
- I've already shared on this pod,
I believe some of my friend wrote me like hey,
maybe we can get a picture of Kevin Smith
and I said maybe you can.
(laughing)
I'm all for you know, forgiveness and sleeping dogs,
lie and stuff like that,
but I'm not like about to initiate like hey, it's me.
- Not on that night, not on that night, right.
- Hey, while you're back together
with the entire cast of Mall Rats,
do you remember kicking me out of a film when I was 17?
(laughing)
I just want you to know that I passed it.
Wanna grab a photo?
(laughing)
By the way, I don't know if you've heard this thing
called a podcast, but I have one.
Here, please.
- Here's a chip.
- Here's a chip, check it out.
- I don't know if you've heard of this thing
called a podcast, Mr. Eighteen Podcasts.
(laughing)
- Hilarious.
- So yeah, there was no in on me and Kevin.
I only thought it was funny that I ran--
- Hey, I don't know if you remember kicking me
off of a movie 20-something years ago.
- The only thing that was funny
is that I basically ran right into him.
I was crossing the street and he was rounding the corner
and then there he was and I literally just stopped dead
in the sidewalk, in the crosswalk, walked backwards
and just let, I just like, I don't even wanna be here
but then, I'm not, I'm not doing it.
(laughing)
I just laugh.
- If he happens to see me, it happens to recognize me,
I don't want this to happen right here.
- Yeah, I was like, no, I thought I was gonna be okay
if we just happened to run into each other.
It literally happened.
I was like, nope, I'd rather just let it happen.
(laughing)
My heart was like, just you do your thing tonight,
I'll do mine and we'll just be happy, okay?
- Hilarious.
(laughing)
- Let's just get through the rest of our lives, man.
We don't need to worry about this.
- No, no, we're both just--
- We got plenty in our lives, we can just move on.
- Nothing is plenty of dirt on top of that hatchet, right?
Nothing buries that hatchet plenty.
So, I'm not saying it's--
- Well, nothing buries it to the point
where it's not embarrassing the next time
you have to have a conversation.
- Yeah, because the truth is there's a 90% chance
he doesn't remember at all, do you know what I mean?
Like, there's just a chance he does not remember
whatsoever, you know?
And I also have to remember that that film
did not become like "American Pie."
It did not go on to do like, I can't point--
- It wasn't "Mallrats."
- I bring up the movie and people go, "What?"
And you're like, "Yeah."
So, it's like it's not, I even, you know,
the more important is that I buried the hatchet
with Brian who wrote it and had to suffer, you know,
that whole political situation and still get his movie made.
- Right.
- But even I hopped on one of his Instagram lives
and it was like, he was going over how it just came out
on DVD, now you can just buy it.
- Yeah.
- And then I popped on his Instagram live
and he's just going over how amazing the cast was
and everything was amazing.
And I was like, "Well, maybe I'm not totally over it.
"Okay, bye."
And I just kind of clicked off the live to be like,
"That's enough."
(laughing)
You know, so I've still, you know,
I've still spoken with everyone in it.
We've all done everything else with our lives.
It's all fine, but I just was like,
"Oh God, what a funny curve ball to just have."
You know, there's a lot around the block,
not for improv jam, you know, the whole bit, right?
But we got in there.
They set up a little stage for us in a movie theater
and we sold out.
We sold out the show and it was a tax house.
And I met holding a grudge, I'm shocked and surprised.
I'm doing my best to not be a Jersey stereotype, all right?
I'm trying to be an evolved person.
- You're doing great, buddy.
You're doing great.
(laughing)
- I tell you who doesn't hold a grudge,
the guy who wrote "Improv Jam,"
because I left that in a very fiery,
political way at the time, you know?
(laughing)
- 20 some odd years ago.
- Yeah, it was 20 something years ago
when I wanted to show Kevin Smith what what.
I took my college money and funded a TV pilot
with my improv group, not our improv group, mine.
I left my hometown improv group, started my own college,
and took the most inexperienced group
and decided they were the ones I wanted to work with
and we did a TV pilot with them.
Again, if that became a real TV show,
maybe I wouldn't be invited back to the reunion.
But again, it went on to no success like the movie.
Just a bunch of people holding grudges,
throwing money around and no one's better for it.
(laughing)
And in fact, there was the original core group of the show
and then there was the class that came right after us.
We're all reunited, right?
Because my buddy Pete never left the group
and so he stayed on and bonded with another,
the crew that came right after us.
So it really was like two classes of the show reuniting.
30 years and some years later.
And I was laughing 'cause someone's like,
"Where did these new guys come from?"
And I was like, well, they came from the fact
that Tom, Pat, and I quit and started our own group
and went up north to Jersey and left it.
So it created a vacuum of availability for the cast.
So.
(laughing)
- You're like, "Oh, I can answer that question."
- Yeah.
- Hoisted by your own petard.
- Exactly.
So it was a 14-person cast.
All of us playing games we haven't played in years.
I'm the most recent player.
- Holy shit, that's a lot. - Of all of the games.
And Jacob, you're gonna laugh at this, right?
So they put together a game and Pete did a good job
distributing all the games to all the different people.
And he gave to Jeopardy and he went to Jeopardy
and he was like, blah, blah, blah.
And he goes, "And Lance, you'll host."
And Lance made a face.
And I literally froze.
I go, "Freeze, Lance."
I go, "Yeah, was hosting Jeopardy your thing
"when you did the show?
"'Cause I was not part of your cast."
He was like, "Not really."
And I go, "Do you know how to host Jeopardy?"
And he goes, "No."
I go, "Okay, switch games with me.
"I will host Jeopardy.
"You do this other game."
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- And I was like, and I said, "I'm really sorry."
I was like, "I don't wanna step on anyone's toes."
I go, "But hosting Jeopardy is super hard.
"And I just made this mistake.
"I just made this mistake.
"I made our audio guy with no improv background host Jeopardy
"and I forgot that the Jeopardy host
"is the hardest job in that game."
- Right.
- It is to sell everyone's jokes.
You have to repeat and sell everybody's jokes.
And you have to move the show along
based on the funniest answer.
And you have to get a sense of whether someone else
might have a funnier answer.
It is not, you just throw somebody in to do it or whatever.
And so I--
- It's a showrunner more than--
- Yes.
- It's a showrunner more than an imp--
Like now, I know exactly what to do with it.
- Right, right, right.
- Like now I can just do it.
(laughing)
But like that day, I was like, "Oh, y'all want what now?"
- Yes.
- We got on stage, it was like, "Oh, it's this.
"It's this, I see now."
- Yeah, even when, it's the most like joke,
like pimping you into making dumb jokes game.
It's even harder than 185 or those games.
- Oh yeah.
- And so I hopped on that grenade, Jacob,
and I was like, "Oh, I'm hosting, I'm hosting Jeopardy."
- How'd it go?
- Oh, it went really well, it went really well.
I mean, the most thing was that honestly,
like the thing was that Michael Keefe
was the guy who ran Improv Jam when I was a kid.
He was the funniest person I'd ever seen
when I went and saw that show, like he was so funny.
And I would steal his bits and do his bits in high school
and get attention for it.
And then I finally got in the show
and got to perform next to him.
And when we all got together, he was older than us.
And so I could, but I could see him,
like he had 14 people, he's bouncing 14 people.
And I could see that he was like not,
like he was kind of chanting a bit, a little bit to be funny.
And he was kind of, you know.
- Oh, right, right.
- He was kind of making sure everyone's getting fed
or whatever.
And so when "Dating Game" came around,
I just was like, he was explaining like there are three contestants.
I go, "Nope, there's four contestants in this one, Mike,
and you are contestant number four."
And so I threw him in a dating game.
And then all of a sudden I was up for Jeopardy
and I turned to Pete and I go, "I'm gonna do it again."
And he's like, "There'll be three people up here."
I go, "Nope, there'll be four people playing
in Jeopardy at night, Mike, four.
And you're playing in that one as well."
I was like, "We're doing this."
- That's great.
- Yeah, I, the only thing I was really happy for myself
was that like I, because I had departed
and even reconciled and departed multiple times
on shaky ground, I actually just straight up
after his last game just said, "By the way, everybody,
like all of us are here and all of us went on
different things with our lives over the conference
that came from doing this show.
Please let's give Mike a proper round of applause
for what he's done for everybody here."
And we got standing ovation in the theater.
- Oh, that's nice.
- I was happy because I really, like I said,
I was very driven and certainly at times very egotistical
and I was definitely went off doing my own thing
and I had my own political battles with that.
Of course, when you look back, you're like,
boy, am I just a dumb 18 year old kid
in those arguments, right?
- Yes.
- And that show just meant so much to me.
And I did not realize the nostalgia factor.
I was too busy trying to make sure
that we were getting 14 people into a show.
I knew I was pretty experienced compared
to some of the other people coming back.
I was really trying to make sure.
- You were the most practiced,
you were the most recently practiced.
- Yeah, and so I was trying to really just kind of make sure,
you know, 'cause our shows with Brad and Jonathan,
I mean, that's like keeping up
with the fucking two amazing Titans, you know.
I certainly felt like very in shape for this reunion, right?
- Yeah.
- I did not give myself like the, I did not for a second,
I was like, oh wait, you're going back
to the epicenter of your entire creative life.
Do you know what I mean?
Like, you're going back to where you were 16, 17,
and you started doing this show.
- Ah, 16, 17!
(laughing)
- 16, 17.
- I'm so young and hip.
- No, like, so like, my buddy Tom,
who had a stroke nine months ago,
and we were literally just told, like,
check in with his wife day out.
Like, whether he would make it or not,
whether he'd want to play or not, or whatever.
And so, Tom walked in, and my buddy Nick,
those were the guys that were in the show before I got in.
Those were the guys that I looked at,
to be like, I want to play on stage with those guys, right?
He just walked in, the first person he saw was Nick,
and I just saw Tom and Nick hug,
and just seeing those two together,
I literally just started to lose it, like, right there.
It was like five o'clock, the show was at eight.
- Oh, you were done?
- Yeah, I was like, good Lord!
You know, and I just wasn't really,
all this was like, how the hell do we make
this 14 person improv show with a bunch of people
who haven't practiced go well?
That's all that was on my mind the entire time
going into this, like, this has to be good, you know?
And I was not prepared emotionally to be like,
no, buddy, you're going back to, like, day one.
You're going back to, like, the starter space
on the game board.
And it was really crazy to just feel those,
all the people playing games and going like,
I was feeling 17, but I was like, oh, I love this game!
I want to play this game, too!
You know, like, I was like, I want to do all the games!
And I just was like, right back to being a 17 year old,
just like, loving the show.
Also, like, this weird thing, like,
Mike came from a sack theater in Orlando.
They start, they coach the crowds and they say,
for every scene, scene in, and the whole crowd goes,
five, four, three, two, one, and the thing starts.
- Oh, that's fun.
- It is fun.
And none of us took it off on our separate improv endeavors.
Like, all of us went off to do other improv endeavors,
and we never did that.
So, we were all just waiting to be introduced,
and he coached the crowd and doing it,
and hearing a full theater do the countdown again.
We all, all 14 of us back, or 13 of us, Mike's on stage,
all 13 of us went, oh, like, we like, just got,
we all just got hit in the stomach with a bowling ball,
like, right off the bat.
Like, before we even hit the stage,
it was like, this crazy nostalgia of it.
And it was awesome.
Everybody really impressed me.
Everybody really held their own and did all the right things
to start all the games, and the crowd was into it.
There was a lot of people who was their first improv show,
which I was--
- Going to see their first improv show?
- Yes, because it was listed on the Smodcastle newsletter.
- Oh.
- So, like, half the crowd was nostalgic people.
- Half of them were just like,
oh, I wanna go see some improv.
- Yeah, and it being fucking 30 years,
a lot of people brought their kids
who were the same age as we were,
like, when we were watching the show.
- Yeah.
- So a lot of people were showing their kids
what they watched when they were their age.
- Oh, yeah.
- And that was a really big trip.
- That's a head of a half, yes, sir.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I can see how that would be a thing, sure.
- And, yeah, it was just, it was just a blast.
It was just a crazy night out,
and, yeah, we did all the old games,
and it was a crazy, nutty thing to do.
I was really glad we did it.
I can't imagine doing it again anytime soon.
(laughing)
And then with that in mind, we're only getting older, right?
So, like, to wait 30 years to do it is crazy,
and then you're like, well, 10 more years,
then it gets really weird,
because there was no way we can do all that shit, you know?
Even when Mike went up,
we made him do "Emotional Roller Coaster,"
and that was always like,
this is the strangest thing about this show,
is that that was our closer before we did a music,
we would close with a song at the very end,
but the last game we'd play was "Emotional Roller Coaster,"
which basically was a tip of the cap
to whoever we thought was hot shit, right?
That person got to do all the emotion changing.
So, like, our way of ending our show was like,
now one person gets to show off for you.
Like, it's really weird.
It's like really weird to look back.
So I was like, oh, Mike is gonna change.
Mike, we'll make Mike change.
He'll do the last game, and he'll change.
And to incorporate everyone else,
I had everyone else call the different emotions.
I just went down the line to every performer,
and they all changed their emotions or whatever.
But I was like, we made such a weird show
that was oddly popular, and it was not like,
it was not a wholesome improv, everyone gets along,
we're all looking out for each other kind of thing.
It was a very, looking back on it,
we were all like young, hungry comedians.
It was very competitive.
It was very much like,
I've earned my right to do a motion roller coaster.
Like those things came back into my head, you know?
- And not like a, and not a formula
that you can just go and recreate
with a different group either, it sounds like.
- No, I mean, this is, like I said,
I've had a very blessed improv life, right?
So I've gone off to many other places
and seen short form and long form shows everywhere.
And when I say things like,
oh, we would close with a motion roller coaster,
people go like, what?
Like that's a starter game.
That's like a, that's a first three gamer
in most people's repertoire.
It's just a silly throwaway game.
But like, and I said, and I've said this
when I came back to them, I go, you know,
every short form show basically becomes a review.
Like it basically becomes a kind of a rehearsed deal
where you do things with a certain energy,
you perform it a certain way,
and you basically also kind of maybe steal
other people's bits and jokes
to create like a greatest hits version of this game,
which just is inevitable.
It's inevitable.
It happens every theater, it happens everywhere.
And no one wants to admit it, but basically,
but that's why those shows basically when you come in,
you go, oh, 'cause I love trying to sit in with every group
and try to get everyone's vibe.
And it was always very interesting to see like
what elements of their shows were just like,
oh, this is just a piece.
Like even though this is an improv game,
this is a set piece that I can't help.
I can't walk onto this.
I can't help this out.
I have to hands off this piece for this particular group.
- They have a thing that they do on this one.
- And it's part of what made me hate short form
for a long time.
It's part of what made me resent it as not improv
and made me like a long form zealot for a good, you know,
15 years after the fact, you know, like it was like,
I'm doing actual improv and you're doing a review, you know.
But as I got older and we learned Paul
with our various endeavors in Las Vegas,
sometimes putting together a review is really fucking hard.
- It is, it absolutely is.
- Sometimes it can be really not funny at all.
- Yeah, it's very easy to fuck up games.
- Yes.
- I mean, they're, you know, generated to help you succeed.
But if you don't know the tricks
and if you don't know how to intro the fucking thing.
- Right.
- Look out.
- That's the thing, Mike comes from Sack Theater.
Sack Theater is where Jonathan, Wayne Brady, Nathan Fillion,
all those guys came from.
A lot of friends that Paul and I have came out of there.
And yes, they'll be quick to remind you like,
oh, when you intro this game, don't forget this bit.
You know, like, so we did Jeopardy,
I forgot that we used human buzzers, right?
So we bring humans up and then Mike literally goes,
oh, and don't forget, we have to say,
before we start the game, you put your buzzers down.
And then I go, oh, I forgot.
I totally forgot about that bit.
And then I said, oh, all right, before we start the game,
go ahead, just put your buzzers down.
And they all start insulting the people
who came up to help them.
- Hilarious.
(laughing)
- And it gets a huge laugh.
And I was like, fucking bits, man.
The fucking little shows.
- Little zings that just keep things flowing,
keep the energy high.
And it's another one of those things, you know, again,
I love teaching level one
because it always keeps me on my toes,
keeps me remembering that it's basics, basics, basics, always.
And that's just it.
Like, just reminding people that it's a show,
reminding people that they can relax
and we know what we're doing, even though we don't.
- It's that we know what we're doing.
Like, Jonathan-- - You're in good hands.
- Jonathan Magam does a bit.
If you put Jonathan in charge of writing something down,
you have to remember that he does this bit
and I've only done, you know, how everybody shows it.
But you start saying things for Jonathan to write down
and then you wait, and like the third one,
you go, you getting all this, Jonathan?
And he will go, oh no, I'm just drawing a cat.
And he'll turn over the pad and show that he's just drawing
a cat and written nothing down.
- Yeah. - And that bit,
if you nail it, kills. - Kills, yeah.
- Like, if you do it wrong too soon,
if you forget he was doing the bit,
he'll finish it himself and it goes, okay.
But you have to remember that Jonathan does the bit
where if he picks up the pad, he's gonna draw a cat.
(laughing)
And those are the things that make it a review
and not a pure improv show,
but it's the kind of thing that makes an artist go like,
oh, these guys, these guys have it in their back, pop.
- They got the shit together.
- Yeah. - Simple little stuff.
When we did our show on Saturday, the teacher show,
I just grabbed a few pieces like,
we were doing puppets and just the old,
make sure no one touches the bikini zone.
That's just one little thing like that,
it's a little throwaway line,
but it just gets a laugh and gets everybody going.
And at the top of, we were doing,
we did a little 20 minute or so long form,
after an interview, the interview was pretty heavy.
And so at the end of the interview, I was like, okay.
So what we're about to do now
is a little bit of a long form piece.
It's gonna be a little more theatrical, more scenic.
Things might come in, might go away, might come back.
You might see characters return
in different times and whatever,
but that's what's gonna be a little more theatrical,
a little more long form.
And it's all intended to be comedic,
which I've grabbed from you,
which is all intended to be comedic.
And it just ends it with them like,
and then the audience laughs 'cause they're like,
but it's good to remind them that yeah,
we're trying to be funny here,
even though we just talked about some really deep shit.
We're gonna be fun, right?
- Is I've added to that bit, Paul.
I go, I'll pause and go like the whole time.
- Oh, good, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, intended to be comedic, like the whole time.
(all laughing)
And I only added that bit because Kamie's gotten dicier.
- As it ever.
- As we've gotten older, you know?
- That's it. - It's gotten different.
- Well, we were interviewing this gal
and just stuff just kept coming up, you know?
And she's like, you know, just some heavy stuff.
And she's in this meeting and stuff is getting very
politically charged and partisan for no good reason.
And it's the only reason. - Oh, cool boy.
- And so I'm like, and I'm like,
no, I really appreciate you telling us
that human rights are partisan now 'cause I wasn't 100%.
But now I get it, okay, this is good.
'Cause yeah, 'cause that's what she was dealing with
was just these insane things that are happening.
'Cause it is, it's insane times, it's insane times.
- It is insane times. - What?
And it was good to do our show 'cause like Nick, right?
Like his specialty was to bring in political stuff
or do a little satire or do whatever.
And he was saying after the show that he felt weird
that he couldn't play the way he normally played
because it's too heavy. - No, satire's dead, baby.
Satire's dead.
- It's just too much to throw in an audience.
- How can you make fun of this shit?
It makes fun of itself.
- I know, yeah, it's beyond parody.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, yeah, I mean, yeah, just a fucking crazy thing.
Oh, so one of the games we play is a game called Space Jump.
And the way Space Jump is-- - Okay.
- It's kind of like a freeze tag-ish game
except that when a person starts off dancing,
you call freeze, you come and you make a scene
based on the way that person's frozen, two-person scene.
They keep doing something physical, freeze,
someone changes it, third person comes in,
and you go, like typically in our show,
we have five or six people in the cast.
Six person would come in first and leave first.
So you do a six-person scene,
and they find a reason to leave.
And then you go right back to that five-person scene,
go right back to that four-person scene,
go right back to that three-person scene.
- Oh, you keep adding, you would keep adding as they come in.
Nobody tagged out.
You just-- - Nobody tagged out.
It just gets more and more and more.
- You just grew it from the freeze.
Okay, cool.
- So P.K. Pell is like,
we're gonna do a 14-person space jump.
And I laughed really hard, and he had a moment of doubt.
He goes, right?
And I go, oh, I'm sorry.
Yes, we're definitely doing it.
- Absolutely, fucking yeah.
I'm already laughing at it.
It's great.
- Yeah, and in my head, I'm like,
this might take a half hour.
Like, this might take up the majority of our things
or whatever.
And-- - And it is intended to be comedic.
- And instead, everyone nailed their opening lines.
All of them.
And so it was either call or call and response, freeze.
Big laugh.
Big laugh on the freeze.
And so it was like lightning fast all the way up to 14,
and then it became this hilarious game
of trying to remember all of them on the way out.
- Oh, right.
- And that was the whole game.
- What were we doing?
What were we doing?
- Everyone was looking at each other to be like,
who's seen, is it, who's supposed to leave or whatever.
And it was just, and it just paid off huge.
- Yeah, it's easy for like 14 and 13, maybe even 12.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You get down to like 11, 10,
and then you get to like eight and nine.
- Yeah, one of them was that they were frozen.
They were frozen.
They were hands up holding a casket.
And obviously the physicality changed.
So they literally was like six people
staring at each other.
And then one guy finally remembers and goes,
"Oh, we dropped the casket."
And everyone just laughed.
(both laughing)
So yeah, just so many moments.
My dad came out, check it out.
- Oh, wonderful.
- Nice.
- And I said, "Man, it's been a while.
I've worked hard to get in this show."
He goes, "Oh yeah, you were terrible when you started."
(both laughing)
And I was like, "Not wrong, not wrong."
He literally like portrayed,
like it was a vivid memory in his mind
of me having stage fright the first time I was in the show.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
And he literally was like, "You were like..."
And he posed as me, like frozen on the sidelines.
And I was like, "That's exactly what happened
in my first show.
I was absolutely, totally stage-fritten.
I don't know how to say it past tense, but yeah.
Yeah, I was just, yeah, it was a really crazy,
crazy emotional experience to go through.
- Wow.
- You know who else doesn't know
how to say the word frightened?
That's the following sponsor.
(laughing)
- I like stage-fritten.
- Today's show is brought to you by Spanx for Skanks.
Yeah, that's right.
That's our magic show.
Magic Shell Scoop in 2024.
That's Spanx for Skanks.
- Hey, I'm Crack Whore Jessica,
and I love me some crack.
I also love to look fit and tight in my Louboutins
and my hot couture.
So after I smoke some crack, I throw on some Spanx,
but not just any Spanx.
Spanx for Skanks.
Their number one customer is me, Crack Whore Jessica,
and my crack pipe.
These Skank Spanx are built for Skanks like me.
They got a crack pipe holder.
They got a place where you can put your weed.
They got a place where you can pee right in 'em
when you're wearing 'em and won't nobody see.
That's right.
These things are made for Skanks.
You can skank these Spanx up like nobody's business
and nobody will even know.
Meanwhile, I'm walking the red carpet high as fuck
and don't nobody blink because I'm wearing Skank Spanx.
Everybody thinks I got it all together.
I don't.
The only thing that's holding me together
are these tight-ass undergarments.
But I'm pissing in 'em and don't nobody know.
So I say that's a win.
So go.
You take that Skank home and you just open it
like a mattress that was just delivered.
You slowly get those Spanx off and then.
Oh, it's expanding!
I'm sorry. It's expanding!
I can't help it now.
They only last for 12 hours.
That's the Spank-Skank guarantee.
12 hours, but after that, it's like the fucking.
There's Cinderella Spanx.
Yep, it totally, it'll pumpkin your ass real hard.
So watch it.
Watch it, watch your time, girls.
Set your watches and shit
'cause that stuff will explode on you.
Enter Hayscoops to check out.
The worst part about that is
her parents named her Crack Whore Jessica.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nominative determinism.
That's right.
(laughing)
That's the first thing that popped into my head.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Yeah, so I just got back from the doctor,
got my neck ultrasound, good times.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When do you find out the result of this neck ultrasound?
The lady said things are running back.
Oh, it'll be like a week or two.
And I said, "Well, I'm heading out of town now."
She's like, "Well, that's great."
So yeah, it'll be like probably two weeks.
There's nothing with my neck that means I can't fly
because I'm gonna go fly somewhere.
Exactly, that's the one thing I kind of thought.
I was like, well, if I do have any kind of artery problems,
I guess the flight's gonna just do a number of,
whatever, who cares?
You know what, you're gonna figure it out.
I can promise you at 50, feeling the way I do,
my blood is not flowing as perfectly as it should be.
I can say that definitively.
I think it's, I don't think there's any major blockages
or anything, but it could stand to be better, I'm sure.
One of our friends came to the house last night
and he had, what he said at first was
that he nicked his lip shaving
and that it was bleeding profusely.
Well, I thought that was odd.
It turned out it was like the beard clippers.
Oh, okay.
The clippers took a- He really got in there.
Yeah, like took a little hunk out of his lip.
So it was like a deep, deep, deep dig there.
Yeah, but it was bleeding for a couple of hours.
It was bleeding. Oh my gosh.
Like profusely for, 'cause it was right on his lip.
It was right on like the, not above where your mustache is,
but like down on the lip.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So anytime he would smile, move his lip,
and move his mouth at all,
you know, it would just open right back up.
Oof.
Yeah, this is how we live now.
This is just how we all live.
You can remind him that, of course,
the area of the mouth and eyes are the first to heal.
So there you go.
I'll remind him next time that happens.
I'm laying down and she, she gooed,
she put a towel under my neck and everything.
And then she gooed me up with the jelly.
And then she, and then she ultrasound to me.
And I got to hear my heartbeat
for the first time on the monitor.
I really felt like I was my own baby.
It was really interesting.
I'm a boy.
I was like, oh, oh, it was like, oh, we can hear a heartbeat.
We've got a heartbeat.
I could hear whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.
You know that, that sound that comes through
with the heartbeats.
I was like, oh, and she had to do that eight different times
and find it just right out and whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.
And I was like, oh, I can hear him.
He's in there.
It was just really interesting to hear my own blood.
- He's fighting to get out.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like, oh, that's sweet baby boy.
He's bleeding inside.
He's just a gushing and a swishing.
But from my untrained ear sounded pretty much the same
on both sides.
So I don't think there was anything.
- Did they tell you like what they're looking to diagnose?
- Yes, they're looking because again,
because it was isolated to my left eye.
- Right.
- 'Cause this is all from a few weeks ago
when you went to an eye exam and they had a moment of,
they saw something they didn't like in your eye
and it was bleeding.
- There was retinal hemorrhaging, yes.
- Yeah.
- So they went and they, I went to the eye doc,
the expert and they checked it out.
I don't have anything going on with the right
or I didn't at least.
And so, but I still have had no vision impairment,
no vision changes, still ongoing.
- And you still look great.
- I mean, thank you, thank you.
But the concern was there are the arteries
that go back and forth there.
The concern was because it was isolated to one eye
that it could be some kind of blockage
or some kind of impediment as to the going
or coming of the blood in that area.
So that's what they're flushing out.
And then she's like, I'm gonna check both sides.
You got any questions or anything like that?
And I was like, well, I mean, I just,
I know that the focus is on the left
because it is only isolated to the left
and that was kind of the weird thing.
And she's like, well, they check both sides
in order to kind of get a baseline of what is normal.
And then I went.
- All right.
- Oh yeah, of course.
This is the every day medical exam of the Joe Layman, right?
You get up, you're like, oh shit,
that really hurts over here.
What the hell?
And then you feel it.
And then you feel the other side and you're like,
oh, that's pretty much the same.
I'll be okay, right?
That's the whole thing you do.
The symmetrical nature of our bodies.
That's what we do.
We go, ooh, my knee, what's a, oh, okay.
How's this one?
No, no, that's pretty much the same.
- We can always do like A to B comparative shopping.
That's what we can do.
- Exactly, that's right.
Exactly.
- And that's why as far as I know, my liver is fine.
- That's the one, that's one of the tricky ones.
It's the internal stuff that gets really tricky.
External stuff is a little bit easier
to diagnose from the self, quote unquote.
But yeah, that was what.
But I thought that was funny.
- He checks his left penis, then his right penis.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, well, as a Klingon, I do have to.
- As a echidna?
- Yeah, yes, it is the echidna.
- Well, no, that's exactly with checking everything.
In fact, I think it is Santa Claus,
who was the very first to practice
this symmetrical diagnoses.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, he makes a list, he checks it twice.
(laughing)
- Gonna find out who's left and who's right.
- Yeah, gonna find out if it's an ass,
if it's an abscess or not.
Yeah, Santa Claus is rectal exam.
Yeah, that's it.
- I wanna give a shout out to Sparta Avenue Stage,
who hosted me for two shows Friday night
before my improv reunion up in Sparta, New Jersey.
I sold out the first show,
and then no one likes to stay out late in Sparta.
No, not after that.
- Sidewalks roll up at eight, huh?
- Yeah, yeah.
But no, I know all about that out here.
First crowd, they gave me a standing ovation, all right?
- Wow, fantastic.
- And they weren't just leaving.
- No, no, no.
- They weren't just standing up to leave.
It was a legitimate standing ovation.
- I didn't say, "Wait, guys, turn around.
"Just do it this way."
- You didn't say, "Hey, everybody,
"let's give it up for children with cancer."
- Yeah, I blew garbage at them.
- Cancer babies, huh?
Stand up, stand up for cancer babies.
Thank you, good night.
- Oh, side note, I was on a cruise ship
with this couple, they're big time magicians,
but they're now more social media people than magicians,
but they're Kyle and Misty Knight.
And they also-- - Oh, sure.
- They work backstage with Blaine
when Blaine comes to town, that they're on Blaine's crew.
So I told them that I have--
- Michael Blaine.
- So you were in the theater, Chris Angel was there,
and then we started talking about the story,
and I was surprised the next day,
I gave him Chris Angel as a question stickers.
- Oh, awesome. - That I give out at my fest.
'Cause I give those out at my shows
to any Penn Sunday school listener.
- Did they love it?
- They asked for an extra one for David, so I gave him.
- Oh, that's great. - Good, good.
- Did you give 'em a chip?
- They are all chipped up.
I don't think that-- - If we can obelisk
David Blaine, our life is complete.
(laughing)
- How funny would it be to have David Blaine
come do some crazy, death-defying shit at Scoop Fest some year?
- At my show, do you listen to podcasts or whatever?
And I'm jokingly, I'm referring to my own,
and then people will be like,
I like this American life.
And then-- (laughing)
- Nobody says that.
- But I have my chips and stickers ready for that,
when I'm going to my show. - Kick ass, that's awesome, man.
- I do properly chip people at my shows.
- Oh yeah, baby, always obelisking, baby.
No, no, no, but you know what,
and that's the best way to do it.
- Well, that's good, because that way, if they get lost
and somebody else takes them to the vet,
they'll be able to know that they're yours.
- Well, no, but you're also--
- Oh, this is Matt Donnelly's audience.
- You're on the road.
You've only got so much capacity.
You can't have all your chips at your disposal, so.
- No, I can't.
Literally, I'm down to three, I have three pounds of leeway.
(laughing)
- Exactly, right, yeah, you gotta go light for it.
- And they are often exactly like 49 and like 47 pounds.
So yeah, between the two of them,
some of it goes up to 50 on me and I get mad.
But yeah, I've definitely multiple times been that guy
at the airport who's opening both cases
and shoving one jacket from one case into the other.
- Yep, yeah. - All that stuff.
So yeah, no, those chips are heavy, those chips are heavy.
- Do you feel a sense of betrayal
or maybe this hasn't happened to you
at the airport very often?
It's happened to me once or twice
where the scale at the airport is obviously calibrated
differently than the scale at my house.
- Yes.
- I'm not saying one of them's wrong and one of them's right
'cause I don't know, but they are different
and that is the most maddening thing
that can happen on those travel days.
- No, it is.
And like, it's not that it happens,
like I don't have a scale at home.
I really do just lift it up with my arms and go like,
this feels about the time where it feels right.
And I'm actually pretty good, right.
I don't wanna brag, but I will lift any of you up
and tell you how much you weigh.
- Tell you if you're over or under 50 pounds.
- Carnival Parker blood.
- That's it, just over or under 50, that's it.
That's the only task.
- I don't know, you're good.
You can get down there, you'll be fine.
- Oh, you're at least 53.
- So when I pack the same exact stuff
and it also is like 51 pounds at the airport
when I'm going out, I'm like, no,
I packed this exact same case on the way in
and it was 49, you jerk.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Liars.
- And do they let you go?
Are they like, okay, that's close enough.
- Or are they jerks about it?
- Do my original foolish trick, but for real.
Just to get a calculator, start guessing people's weights
and then when they say this thing is 53 pounds,
I rip open my shirt and I have 53 pounds
on a piece of duct tape on my chest
and then I rip it off and hand it to them.
Yeah, so wait, what's your question, Jacob?
- I don't remember.
- Great, moving on.
Jacob, I had a curiosity for you actually.
- Okay, hit me.
- A guy came out, I was unloading groceries,
I left my trunk open and then I got caught in the backyard
talking to my family and then a guy knocked on the door
and then I came up, I was like,
I bet my trunk is open still and I opened it and he goes,
hey, someone let you know your trunk is open.
I said, oh, thanks.
He goes, do you help with your groceries?
No, stranger, I do not.
And then he goes, hey, we're walking around the neighborhood
and we noticed your windows and your beautiful home
and we wanted to sell you discount windows
if you're willing to put our sign in your front yard
that you're willing to do this.
And I go, wait, I've turned this down all the time.
It's probably the fourth time I've turned a guy down
with this offer that my house is a model house.
But you did this deal, right, Jacob?
- We did, yeah.
- Did it work out?
Was everything good?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Oh, oh yes, everything was great.
We saved a lot of money
and they took some pictures of the house.
- It feels scammy, right?
And I was trying to figure it out because I was like, wait,
I think Jacob did this and we never got like a bad report
after the fact.
'Cause I think I would have remembered
if it went south or something, right?
- No, everything went great.
The bad thing that happened after it was right at,
'cause it still cost us a pretty penny to do all of it,
but it saved us, it ended up saving us like three grand,
maybe 3,500 bucks, something like that.
So not nothing, significant savings for sure.
- Windows are very expensive.
- Yes, the downturn that happened at the end of that story
was right after we did that,
like a few weeks after we did that,
COVID shut everything down
and most of our income stopped coming in immediately
after spending a lot of money on windows.
(laughs)
We would have been fine.
We would have been fine not swapping them out.
- That was us with fake grass.
We like called to be like,
can you not install the fake grass?
And like you already cut it.
So you save just the installation fee.
- It is done.
- And I was like,
and you just have like a mountain of sand
on your side of your house, you know?
And I was like, oh man.
I guess go ahead. (laughs)
- But so I'm trying to think of what the,
I think it might simply be the con of it
is simply that Anderson windows are the standard.
Anderson windows are expensive.
And if you offer cheap windows that aren't Anderson,
then people think they're gonna get shitty windows.
And so the discount element just,
and by complimenting your house, you feel flattered.
And then the idea that you have to hold an advertising thing
to save money is like, it's like the same as like,
as Paul would say, taking the bottle of water
for the meeting, right?
You don't take the water when they offer you water.
You know, it's like you're creating a currency exchange.
- Yes.
- So like, I guess like it's simply about like,
you want to compete with Anderson and you can buy price.
Competing by price doesn't work unless you do this bit.
Is the best that could come up with.
- I don't, yeah, 'cause ours were,
ours weren't Anderson, but they were another big brand.
I forget what it was.
But they're like two or three big brands in town.
- Isn't Pella one of the big ones?
- Acme?
Acme?
- Acme, that's it, that's it.
They sell windows and anvils.
- Nevar break?
- That's it.
But yeah, so it was like another big brand.
And so we felt okay with it.
- He offered me six to 7% off and then we just laughed at him
until he left our yard.
He didn't know why.
(laughing)
- New windows, new windows.
- I'll tell you what, I'll just go get some new windows
and they're gonna pay full price.
That's the following sponsor.
- Today's show is brought to you by...
Greek yogurt.
Yep, that's it, Greek yogurt from Scoop of Henley in 2022.
This show is also brought to you by Greek yogurt.
(grunting)
- There's a bowl.
- Enter Hey Scoops to check out.
- Did you just shit yogurt?
(laughing)
- I didn't just shit it.
I put it in a bowl.
- He makes a lot of good points, Donnelly.
He makes a lot of good points.
- Good point, good point.
- Scoop Jesus in the chat is pointing out
that it's interesting that they did take some money
off of our windows to pay for advertising
and now I can't tell you the brand name of the windows.
(laughing)
- Also why we thought it was a con is that your yard
gets no visible, there's no foot traffic,
there's no traffic traffic that goes by your house.
You live very, you live very remotely.
- The sign thing wasn't the big deal for ours.
The big deal for ours was the pictures.
- Yeah, pictures on the website.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that makes more sense.
- 'Cause we have a weird looking house.
That was, I think that was also why they liked our house
was because it's different looking for a Vegas house.
- Yeah, it looks like a little cocaine compound.
- That's it. - Some cartel.
- Right, that's precisely what it looks like.
- That's what everyone, everyone who comes to the barbecue
thinks that someone might just break out a machine gun
and mow everybody down.
- Yeah, it's a fair concern.
It's a fair concern.
- You've almost got like a conversation den,
conversation pit designed for the living room.
- Oh yeah. - Yeah.
- Dropped floor.
- So I am doing the second show at the Sparta Avenue stage
up at Sparta, New Jersey.
Wonderful theater, great community,
run by awesome people.
- Awesome people who go to bed early.
- This is the late night one sparsely attended?
- Yes, the sparsely attended one and it is,
they boosted us by reaching out to their friends.
Of course, it's a local magic community surrounding that.
So my magician to regular human ratio
in my second show is a little off.
- Sure.
- And this is the thing, it's like magicians just don't,
as much as they want, even the most respectful magician
is just hard to be a regular audience member
when you're doing magic, right?
So a couple of people who just don't want to do certain,
they give me a look like you don't want to use me
for this kind of thing when I'm trying to get people
from the audience.
There's a lot of volunteers on my show.
- Yeah.
- This one guy was kind of like,
I busted his balls a little bit
and he was a very chatty person.
And then, so for, when I have a small amount of crowds,
I don't get new people, you know, for straight as Jack.
- You use the same folks over and over.
- I just go to the two guys
that have stood out the most, right?
- Okay, yeah.
- 'Cause basically like I can't,
I can't constantly get two other guys kind of thing.
And so I just call them by name.
They get up quickly, they get on the show faster.
And so I bring a guy up
who I've been messing with a little bit throughout the show
and he'd be messing with me back a little bit.
But I go to raise the curtain and he covers my face.
And this is a bit that comes up oftentimes
with drunk dudes on cruise ships.
- Right.
- Where I'm trying to do my finale
and I do the joke where they raise the curtain too high
and get them to lower it, I talk over it.
And then some people think it's funny
just to keep covering my face.
And I let that laugh happen
and then I try to move on with the trick
and then they keep doing it.
And then I point out to them,
hey, this bit's getting diminishing returns.
Did you have people laughed at it and now they're not?
Just letting you know.
You can stop doing the bit and let me go.
- It was a fine bit.
It was a fine bit a second ago.
- And this guy won't stop doing the bit,
won't stop trying to say funny things,
won't stop trying to upstage me through the entire thing.
It basically kicks all of my jokes right in the dick.
And I can't, I can't.
- Can't get it going.
- And so it ends fine.
The show ends fine.
I still get out, it's still surprising.
I produce beers, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And the show's over.
And then he comes right up to me after the show,
some signing posters right there
and hitting up chips possibly.
And--
- Not to this motherfucker.
- Right.
And he goes, hey, just wanted to say,
I've really enjoyed your show.
I've been a professional magician for the last 34 years.
- The fuck you have.
- No.
You've been a professional cocksucker.
You've been a professional piece of shit.
- That's exactly it.
My head just goes, that just can't be true.
- No.
- That just can't, that just can't be the information.
- Did you ask him when his last paid gig was?
When was the last time people paid you to perform magic?
- Even backstage.
- Yeah, what'd you pay job?
- The other magicians who helped me pack up were like,
that was really weird.
He was, that was weird of him to do what he did to you.
And I was like, I agree.
- Especially if he's claiming to be a magician.
What a fucking asshole.
- And then on top of that,
because the way the guy introduced me,
it felt weird to just go right into like, whatever.
And so I started talking about
how I became a magician to the second crowd.
I was just trying to, they also, no one would sit up front.
So I was trying to like endear them and to be like,
hey, we're hanging out.
So I just told my story of learning how to pen,
dare me to learn magic and all that other stuff.
And then I went into my show.
I'll do that if I feel like an audience is like super cagey.
I'll just tell my actual story of becoming a magician
to be like, we're cool.
- Try and change the temperature in the room a little bit.
- Yeah, yeah.
So I guess that compelled him to like,
then he wanted to tell me his entire life story as well.
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
Oh, this is great.
- And then I'm trying to get chips and stickers
to two people I recognize
from coming to my show multiple times.
- Oh yeah.
- And he almost seems like annoyed
where like he gets through part of his thing.
I was like, oh cool.
And I went like, let me just get this thing real quick.
And he seemed like annoyed that I wasn't like hearing him
tell his story. - No, you can't.
I'm fine with coming up to you and telling you a story.
I'm fine with saying I'm a magician as well.
I'm fine with all this.
You don't get to be annoyed when the group of people
that you're doing the thing with
is still a group of people.
- Exactly, exactly.
- Nothing has changed here.
- Oh.
- Jeff Loomis in chat says
that he has to be your apprentice.
Jeff, in a way he was asking me to become his apprentice.
- Right.
- In a way.
He basically was saying like-
- And what did you say?
- I heard your story and just let you know
I'm way more experienced than you.
- Oh my fucking God.
- Oh.
- You probably noticed how well I handled you on stage.
That's just a little taste of what I can do.
- Yeah.
I don't know if you saw me fucking destroying on there
during your bit.
Taking your bit to the next level.
- Oh, destroying my show?
Yes, I saw that.
- I didn't see you destroy my show as a matter of fact.
- Yeah.
- Wow. - Yeah, yeah.
It was, I, it was, that was the,
that was the strangest part of it for sure.
- Yeah.
- Did you see "Chaotic Clumsies" line?
That's, you should use that in the future.
- You tell me it's bigger tits to be that irritating.
(laughing)
- I am gonna steal that.
- Yes.
- Yeah. - That's pretty fucking good.
Pretty fucking good.
- His were pretty big though.
His were pretty big.
(laughing)
- Okay.
So you say he was justified.
- Yeah.
That was, that was really, really, really strange.
- Sorry, you had to go through that shit.
- No, no, no.
I mean, I overall had a fantastic night.
It was so fun. - Right, yeah.
- And it was, you know, even, even,
even though the audience was a little different,
you know, for the second show,
obviously if you do a show that's sold out
and you get a setting ovation,
the second show's not gonna check all the same boxes.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But you've got that one in your pocket
rather than coming off a bad show
trying to get the energy back up again.
- And it basically, like I said,
I'm recording both shows.
So it's usually, it's, I'm finding that the moments
that I find most awkward from my shows
are making the best reels on my social media.
(laughing)
- Of course.
- Well, I was like, well, at least this is taped
and I'm sure there's more bits
that come out of it this way.
- There you go.
- I bet, I bet the clip of him upstaging me
with the bit is gonna make a fine clip
for the social media. - Oh yeah, mm-hmm.
- But it was, yeah, so I just went to the second show,
just like, great, another show, let's just do it.
But it was super fun, super fun.
- Nice.
- Yeah, that was just the only thing.
- And so would you say that your, I don't know,
roughly eight months away from your family
have been worth it?
- It feels like it, it feels like eight months.
Anything more than two is just, yeah,
everything feels a little weird at home.
- When SJ said last night, she was like,
oh yeah, I texted Matt and Sarah about coming over,
I hadn't heard from them yet.
And I was like, oh, Matt has,
I don't know if you know this,
Matt has been gone since ScoopFest.
- Yeah, and also, - She was like what?
- ScoopFest doesn't count as me really being at home either.
- Right. - Right.
- You know, like, I don't really see anybody in the fam,
so it was really, ended up being a really weird thing, so yeah.
- Extra weakest shit, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Kids are all grown up.
- Well, there was like, there was like a crisis.
Like, my kids' soccer team while I was gone,
that I wasn't there for, that was annoying.
- Oh no. - Basically.
Like, my youngest kids' soccer team,
they don't, like, they always keep
a certain core group of players
that always get new players every year.
- Okay. - And my kids'
soccer coach is not like, you know,
basically, as teams get, you know,
move on and stay together or whatever,
some coaches basically recruit.
You know, basically, - Oh, sure.
- Help other kids hop over to the other team.
And my kids' coach does not do that.
He just takes the random allotment.
Like, I believe that's actually fair to the league, right?
- And probably the healthier way to go about it as well.
- Right, so, but what ends up happening
is that we end up getting kids who aren't quite
in demand for any other team.
- Right.
- And they're not in demand, not because they're maybe bad,
but sometimes they're not in demand
because they don't like Trilla.
They just don't, they don't.
- Sure, they're not reliable.
- They're not reliable.
And so, basically, my whole season,
my youngest has been playing with, like,
either one man down or just enough to play the whole game
with no subs for the entire season.
- That's hard, how can you even win
when you don't have any fun?
- They almost had a forfeit of game while I was gone.
And so, it's been a bummer to not be there for him.
- If you had been there for that one,
would they have let you suit up and head out on the field
to be the last player that they needed?
- I mean, I have my cleats, you know?
I have my shin guards.
- Good, good.
- And I have a forged birth certificate
saying that I am 10 years old.
- Well, you got everything you need, though.
- I'm willing to just march it on out.
- Is that kid, I don't know if that kid's 10 years,
we need to see a birth certificate.
- You know what, no, seriously.
- Let him play, don't worry.
Do not worry about him.
- If you think your kid can't outrun that guy, you are wrong.
- You'll be surprised to know, Matt,
that currently, what you just talked about,
cleats, shin guards, and a forged birth certificate
stating you're 10 years old are also required
to work in a bodega now in America.
- Interesting.
- I'll tell you what's not gonna work for you,
this jock versus nerd, you're gonna get whooped.
- Bullshit, I'm getting crack on.
- You're doing a jock versus nerd action?
- Oh, am I?
- Fuck yeah.
- I'm on the hunt for balls.
(upbeat music)
- No!
Oh, we got an obelisk coming to us today
from the upside down under scoop.
This is the one where you have the pyramid
of all the different prices.
The questions start at $200,
they go all the way up to $5,000.
We have double downs.
We have steals, we have super steals,
where we also steal the other person's money,
and it's a 50/50 thing.
If you miss a question, you lose control of the board,
and that's how the game works.
The $200 question's coming to me first,
and the question is about Famous Dick, Famous Dick.
I'm not gonna double down,
I'm betting nobody's gonna steal,
so let's see what the question is.
Ron Jeremy was also known as A, The Hippo,
B, The Hedgehog, C, The Horse, or D, The Whale.
D, The Whale is a great porn name.
My name is D, The Whale.
- D, The Whale, Dick, The Whale.
- I would say The Hedgehog, he was The Hedgehog.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah, there he is.
- He's been just, he's just bad, bad, bad.
Is he in jail now, did he die?
- I believe he's in jail. - I don't think he's dead.
- I don't think he's dead.
- Okay. - Oh.
- Yeah, he's been bad, he got bad.
- I agree. - He got worse.
He was bad from the jump,
but he got worse as time went on.
- Sure, and man, his version of Miley Cyrus's Wrecking Ball
is still fantastic, though.
- Oh, I don't know if anyone heard it.
- Separating art from artists there, no problem.
- That's right, that's right. - No problem,
because Wrecking Ball is just beautiful.
- We can do that. - Yeah.
I'd say Famous Tits, Famous Tits, anybody wanna steal?
- Oh, I mean, it's a category I feel great about,
but it's too early in the game to steal.
- This is one that you know a lot about.
I'm glad it's a low dollar question.
This set of Famous Tits are held in place, allegedly,
by a 40 double D bra, Dolly Parton, Anna Nicole Smith,
Pamela Anderson, and Kat Dennings.
- Ooh. - I'm pretty sure
this is a Dolly Parton story,
so I'm gonna say A, Dolly Parton.
It is Dolly Parton. - Hooray.
- Anna Nicole Smith was the only one
that gave me pause there. - Oh, she does have
Famous Tits.
- Ah. (laughs)
- Well, that's Dolly Parton. - It's not something
I ever think about with Dolly Parton.
Famous Farms, Famous Farms, anybody Famous Farms?
No, here's the question. - Told McDonald's.
- Tyler Sheridan owns this Famous Texas Ranch.
Two sixes, five sixes, four sixes, or six sixes?
- Oh my goodness. - Well, I don't know.
I'm not using a 50/50 on this one.
- I'm at a loss for Taylor Sheridan.
Who is that?
Is that a ball player?
- Also known for his tits and from the south.
- Oh, okay. - Huge tits.
I think it's, let's say five sixes, B, five sixes.
No, it's four sixes.
I was one six off. - Oh, one six off.
- So close.
- Matt, that goes to you, Famous Farmer.
Anybody wanna double down or steal?
- I'm prepared to answer. - Here we go.
(laughs)
This Canadian farmer supplements his farming income
to the tune of around $1 million a year
with YouTube videos jabbering on about farming shit.
Is it the New Age Farmer, the Millennial Farmer,
the Geriatric Farmer, or the Gen X Farmer?
- I doubt it's the Geriatric Farmer.
- Gen X Farmer, the Millennial Farmer, New Age Farmer.
- B and D feel right to me, but I don't know.
- Yeah, exactly.
It's like, yeah, the social media's conditioned younger
people to just constantly talk about their generation.
(clicks tongue)
- Let's see, I'm gonna go B, the Millennial Farmer.
- Let's try it.
It is B, the Millennial Farmer.
- Hooray. - The Millennial Farmer.
- Well done.
- Oh, all the math was done, it just worked out.
And in one question, Matt is now ahead.
(Matt laughs)
The $1,000 question, Famous Dick, Famous Dick.
- All right. - Anybody wanna do anything?
Here we go.
This porn actor from the '60s
reportedly had an 18-inch denus, a denus, dingus, a denus.
- A denus, a denus. - A denus.
Funky cold, a denus.
Is that Long Shlong Silver, Long John Delver,
Long Dong Silver, or Long Dong Delver?
Good Lord.
Come on, Matt, you were just talking about this guy.
- Long Dong Silver.
D.
- C.
You said C or D?
- C, Long Dong Silver is correct.
- Hooray.
- There we go.
- I mean, it had to be Long Dong Silver.
- Long Dong Silver.
- That was me pretending
like I didn't have all of his catalog.
- Number one super guy.
Do you remember that Chris Rock portrayed Long Dong Silver
in his SNL sketch?
- No. - Yes.
- There you go.
Yarn in six, what are you eating?
- A $1,200 question.
- You don't have to get online, you can just type it.
What are you eating?
- I'm very curious.
- $1,200 question, we're back to Famous Tits.
Famous Tits, anybody wanna do anything?
- I'll steal.
- What?
- Paul's gonna steal.
- Regular steal.
- He loves them tits.
This modern day Romanian porn star
has a bra size of 34 M.
- Jesus Christ.
- Is it Busty Emma, Busty Juggs, Busty Boobs,
or Busty Elma?
- I'm gonna go Busty Elma, 'cause she's Romanian, D.
- Dad, let's see.
Oh, you're so close, it's Busty Emma.
Busty Emma.
- Chocolate Moose Tracks ice cream,
well, that sounds delicious.
- Well, at least I don't lose any points.
- That's true.
- I still have a super steal.
- Credit to Yarn in Six for making this
an actual ice cream social.
- Yeah.
- Well done.
- Matt, it's back to you, it's a $1,400 question
about farming, about farming.
Anybody wanna do anything?
- It's back to me, I'm excited.
- Yeah, it comes back to you, Paul stole it
and got it wrong, so it just comes right on back.
- Oh, I see, okay.
- That's cool.
With harvest not far away for us down under,
how many hours a day on average do I sit
in the tractor doing my thing?
24, 12, 10, or 15, doing my thing is definitely masturbating.
- Right, and then these numbers must be minutes or seconds.
- Or a refractory period afterwards.
- Let's see here, I have no idea.
So let's go 50/50 on this one.
- All right, that got rid of 12 and 10,
so you got A, 24, or D, 15.
- Well, he's not 24 hours.
- There you go.
- He's not on the tractor on average 24 hours a day.
- It's harvest time to start meth-ing for a few months.
- Ah, good Lord, I lose more teeth every harvest.
- Just so much meth.
- So I'll go with 15.
- Let's try 15, D, 15, and the 50/50 answer
has never worked better in this game.
- Out here gathering my molars at harvest time.
- Ah, holy shit, it was a $1,600 question.
Matt has 3,200, I have 600, and Paul has zero.
- Oh, but you still have a super steal.
- I do still have a super steal.
- You can take all my points.
- You still have a, we all still have double downs.
- Yeah.
- And definitely not a cult.
I'll try a steal, I'll try a regular old steal.
- All right, that protects my points.
- It does.
This chart doesn't officially have cult status,
but it is the starting point for a few cult leaders
like David Koresh and George Spate.
Scientology, Catholic Church, Seventh-day Adventist Church,
or Church of Latter-day Saints.
I mean, I feel like we could just say
the Catholic Church is the root of all of it.
But I believe this is Seventh-day Adventist.
- I mean, the Catholic Church doesn't have cool compounds.
- That's true, that's true.
- They have one.
- C is, I mean, the Vatican.
- They have one cool compound.
- But it's not really cool unless you're into fucking kids.
- Yeah.
- Allegedly.
(laughing)
- We all just stopped and thought about
the different jokes we could make,
and we all decided to just move on.
- That's all very true. - 25 words is all the question.
- I was like, nope, nope, nope, nope.
- That's it, I thought of at least four,
and I passed on all of them.
- But here's the offer, once again,
there are many, many people in the Catholic Church,
fucks a lot of kids, and I don't know why,
that's not a bigger deal for us taking on this earth.
- It is one of those things that I will,
I will put my stake in the ground on that,
and I will speak about it because it is infuriating to me,
and it has affected my life directly
in a lot of negative ways, fuck the Catholic Church forever.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Famous farms, famous farms, anybody wanna do anything?
Stealing, I don't wanna double down on farms, here we go.
This Australian station, just a big farm,
it shares a surname name with a famous Aussie movie star.
Is it Crowe station, Jackman station,
Robbie station, or Kidman station?
- On that tractor, I'm doing Jackman station.
- Yeah.
- For 24 minutes.
- Um, boy.
I'm just gonna guess at this one, I'm gonna say,
this feels like a Hugh Jackman,
I'm going with the Jackman here, let's go.
B, Jackman station.
Oh, it's Kidman station.
- Damn it.
- Nicole Kidman and her big ass farm.
(laughing)
Shit, it goes back to Madigan, dick locations.
- I've got a super steel.
- Oh no. - Paul with the super steel.
- You son of a bitch.
- I mean, I'll probably lose.
- This dick themed Aussie beach
located in Queensland is called,
A, Dickie Beach, B, Peter Beach,
C, Todger Beach, or D, Dick Beach.
- I'll go C, Todger Beach.
- Todger Beach, Dick Beach, private hide.
No, I'm sorry, it's Dickie Beach.
- Dickie Beach.
- I would have done the same exact answer,
I would have thought Australia's gotta have
weird words for dicks and love names
after those weird words.
(laughing)
- Todger. - Holy shit.
It goes back to Matt.
- Talley Whacker Island next to Dick Beach.
- Dick locations.
Matt, are you doubling down?
- Yes. - 'Cause if not,
I'm stealing.
- I'm doubling down to ward off the steal.
- Matt is doubling down.
- Smart.
This tit themed Aussie town in Victoria is called,
A, Tits Creek, B, Titty Song,
C, Titty Bong, or D, Boobs Head.
- All right, this is where it gets tough, right?
I already used my 50/50.
- I should have used my 50/50, I'm a dummy.
- Yeah, you're dumb, but.
(laughing)
So from Paul's mistake, logic dictates Tits Creek.
But boy, does Titty Bong sound Australian
as anything I've ever heard in my life.
- That really does, man.
That's what I was going for, is Titty Bong.
- And Boobs Head.
- And Boobs Head also feels Australian to me.
- Yeah, but Titty Bong.
Like, isn't Billabong a Aussie thing?
- Yes.
- So, Titty Bong.
Also that could be mistaken for the universal greeting
of the junkieons.
Bah-weep-grah-nah-weep-nitty-bong.
- I was gonna say that, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That's the universal greeting.
- Yeah, of the things, yeah.
- I'm just stalling for someone to type
the right answer in the chat.
- Ha, you sneak.
(laughing)
- I'll go, I know it's gonna be wrong,
but I can't help it.
I have to put all of my might behind Titty Bong.
I just want it to be that.
- All of the eggs going into the Titty Bong basket.
- Yeah! - It's correct!
- I would've got that right.
(laughing)
- Titty Bong is always correct.
$5,000 question.
I have to super steal it here at the end
for a random question.
This is the game.
My favorite ICS episode is, hint, it's polarizing.
- Oh.
- A, Don Poseidon.
B, Taco Bell Hospital.
C, Bonnie's Ball Hospice.
That's the Milk Leg episode.
Or D, Rod Stewart's Bread Surrogate.
- Oh, those are all polarizing episodes.
- My guess would be A or C.
- Let's see, either Don Poseidon or Bonnie's Ball Hospice.
But I mean, Taco Bell Hospital is,
that's the gnarly one that has all of the,
it's gotta get a lot of gross stuff in that one.
- I guess so.
- And Rod Stewart's Bread Surrogate,
that was, wasn't that a Great Night episode?
Wasn't that another Great Night episode?
- Bread Surrogate was not.
- No, no, that was, we did that way back in your house,
way back. - Okay.
Oh wait, I have a 50/50.
I'm gonna not be like Paul and use my 50/50.
- Yeah, smart, use your 50/50.
- That got rid of A and D.
Don Poseidon and Rod Stewart's Bread Surrogate are out.
- Yeah.
See, I thought it was A or C, so.
- You know, I've wanted Taco Bell Hospital
from the beginning.
I'm going with Taco Bell Hospital B.
- Oh, really?
- Final answer.
- C? - It's Bonnie's Ball Hospice.
- It was C.
- It's Bonnie's Ball Hospice.
I got that wrong, losing all of my points.
Matt eked out the win today.
11,200 points versus zeros for both Paul and I.
That is from the Upside Down Underscoop.
Thank you so much, Upside Down Underscoop.
- Yes, thank you.
- If you wanna send us a scooperty
or a Price is Skryte Jock versus Nerd
or an Obelisk Jock versus Nerd,
head over to Preaching, not that one, HeyScoops.com.
Head over to HeyScoops.com, right there on the homepage.
You can do all of those things.
You can send us some email.
You can do all kinds of things over there at HeyScoops.com.
Oh, you can buy the Scoop Fest merchandise.
- Yeah. - That's right.
- So go over there, buy yourself some Scoop Fest merch.
Oh, I think y'all, thank you.
- I guess we've said it explicitly,
but the mystery item this year was a Fez,
was a Scoops Fez. - Yes.
- And so a lot of those have been selling off our website
as well.
- For sure.
- It's been a fun item to get your hands on.
I don't think we'll be restocking the Fez, so definitely.
- No, no, no.
- It's a one-time thing.
So these are gonna be-- - Yeah, yeah.
- These are gonna be very-- - The Fez is gonna--
- Very collectible, very-- - It's gonna be good
while it lasts. - Yep.
- Yeah, and if you're hearing this right now,
Paul and I show it tomorrow night.
If you're hearing it the morning it comes out, Thursday,
Paul and I have a show tonight at Tierney's Tavern
in New Jersey.
- Get there, be there. - 20 bucks at the door.
Go, come on up, come on up and check out the show.
- Hottest comedy spot on the East Coast that night,
right there.
- It's gonna be a really fun collection of people.
- It is.
- It's gonna also be less than 14 people,
meaning it's also gonna make it more fun to play.
But it's gonna be me, Paul, my buddies Pat Shepard
and Dijory Douche from my old improv group,
Possible Side Effects.
My buddy Dion Flynn, many people know from playing Obama
and other characters on the Jimmy Fallon Show,
and of course, famous stand-up Kurt Braunler
will be doing stand-up and improv with us there.
That's tonight at Tierney's in Montclair, New Jersey.
Get there if you can, or if you know someone
who might dig that show, just come out
and check out that show.
- It is almost guaranteed to be one of the funniest things
you can do in Montclair, New Jersey that night.
- That's true, that's true.
- Yeah.
- And so, but sorry Andy, I will not film it.
That's just the rule of asking old friends
to do an improv and an improv in a while.
We do not film it.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, it's too dangerous to film it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But so, yeah, come check it out.
I wanna thank all the people who check us out every week
and put us in your ear holes.
Andy, thank you so much.
I wanna thank Penjulev for creating this podcast.
- Thanks, Ben.
- And then, Jacob, did you send the list?
- I just did.
- Okay, I will look at my phone.
(laughing)
- This is a good part of the show.
- I wanna thank the five people who support us
over at Patreon.com/HeyScoops.
These people all knew that it was long dong silver
the whole time.
- Oh, yes.
- That's nice.
Private Parts, Nesticle Scoop, Neil Fleisch,
Angela Paulton, NeckPews, shockingly on theme for my credit.
(laughing)
Nathan Hooten, Nathan Clay, Natalie McGiutin,
Mrs. Johnny Australia, Mr. Head Scoop,
Motor City Smitty, Monica Day, Monodnock Scoop,
de-de-de-de-de, Mohan Nair, Mitzula,
Mississippi Churning Scoop, and Milkleg Scoop.
- The following people almost ran into Kevin Smith,
but they changed their direction at the last minute.
That would be Mack McKenzie, Matt Glowacki,
Matt AKA Stormageddon, Matt Scoop-O-Fail,
Matcha Ice Cream, Matcha Ice Cream Sunday,
that's what that is.
Mark Wilson, Mark Pickenheim, Mark Mattinson,
Mark Gates, Mark Dryden, Mark Cohen,
Mario Rosa, Mark Sadowski, Marble Tulip Scoopy Tree,
Maple Raisin Scoop, and Mama Ninja Scoop.
The following people all felt overwhelming paternal feelings
when hearing their heartbeat from their own neck.
That would be Mike Wenz, Mike Six, Mike Federley,
Mike, Michelle Yiser, Michael Shaw, Michael Martin,
Michael Calder, Michael, Melissa Arachiga,
Malia, McTits, and Max the Ginger Scoop.
- These people will explain to you
how they are superior to you at Magic
and want to tell you their whole life story.
Macho Scoop, Randy Sprinkles, M. Hertz,
Luke Mellon, Logan C., Linda Brandemere,
Lil Red, Leon Kassab, Leon Cox,
Lemur Screamer Creamer, Leif Forrest,
Lee McGarrel, Lee Drummond, L'Oreal's Roth,
Latter-day Scoop, and Larry Goodale.
- Matt Donnelly will do impressions
of the following scoops at Tierney's Tavern.
That's Lance Aiman, L.A.J., Kurt Hendrickson,
Kurt Egner, Kristen Claddock, Collin Tony,
Kiwi Fruit Scoop, King Scoop, Kinshidou Scoop,
Kevin Dorey, Kevin Chamberlain, Kinsoto,
Ken Fargi, Kelsey Kandari, Keith Robert Corning Scoop,
Keester Sunday, Kay Mathis, Justin Robert Young,
Judy Schneider, Juan Galvez, J. Rock Scoop,
Joshua Wilson, Joshua Tarr, Josh Roberts,
Joseph Palero, Joseph Foster, Jordan Campbell,
Jonathan, Johnny Parker, John Jacob Schkuppenheimer Schmitt,
and John Holshin.
Thank you all so much.
- Hey, you guys mind if I get in on this?
That's my Kurt Egner, that's my Kurt Egner right there.
- Solid.
- Just to give you a little preview.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, all these people that we thank,
they support us over at Patreon.
You can too.
Just figure out the tier that fits your budget,
either monthly or yearly,
and go over to preachingfun.com right now.
- Or if you would rather get a neck exam than listen to this podcast again,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com,
it takes you to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
If you think this show is worth more than $0,
patreon.com/hayscoops, that's way too long.
Preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz.
Get there, it's awesome.
- All right, thanks folks, everybody stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
- We'll see you soon.
See you at the home, see you at the boat, see you at the company, see you at the company, see you at the boat.
(upbeat music)
For a bridge and vital.
See ya!