That's a mistake. It's a mistake. It's it's always a mistake
Here we go
We've got the money maker
It's time. It's time for us to thank you the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you ice cream truck drivers
It's a new month. We don't have a new list yet
But we want to thank each and every way to our thank each and every one of you ice cream truck drives
I'm reading while I'm talking it's a bad idea
Yeah
Now I'm all I'm all discombobulated now
Yeah, so thank you to all the ice cream truck drivers out there if you want to be an ice cream truck driver
Preaching fun comm that's where you can go preaching fun comm head over there sign up to be an ice cream truck driver
We will thank you at this part of an episode this month that who knows
Life you save may be your own
Maybe now a program. Hey Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to
Great, let's go
Happy birthday, Paul. Thank you
50 fun years old
I feel it
Social
Barely sitting because of me issues. It's
Fun yeah, wait you you have knee issues. I have a bum knee right now. Yeah, I think there's something going on
It's my right knee is just acting a fool
I don't know why
It's just been last five days the left face. So we have a different disease entirely. Absolutely. Absolutely different. It's tough
Be careful fellas. It's spreading completely different shit. I don't know. It's just you know
I think it's possibly the change in the weather combined with the fact that I
Worked my ass off for three days straight. I don't know
Who knows whatever it's you know, what's fucked up but good it gets better the more I'm up and on it
So I guess that's our weird. It's when I sit down that it starts to get really bad. Oh, it's like tightening up
Yeah, I don't know. So I'm having to stretch a lot more and all that kind of thing, which eventually is good
I do need to do more stretching and and all that kind of thing
what's happening with your knee Matt I
Just heard it
Playing in a soccer game with adults versus kids soccer games. Oh, yeah smart play. Okay
Oh, hold on one second guys. I gotta hit this button
Because my knee hurts too
And what I'm finding is that I am a restless sleeper
I toss and turn so what happens is I
start to feel better and then I wake up in my knee it hurts the next day because I because you've been jerking around my
Leg around all when I like okay, so I worked yesterday early in the morning
And I had a full day and stayed up past my normal bedtime
Which I was I had three days in a row so I was getting to bed at like five o'clock
so I wouldn't play I wasn't playing any games and sick as a dog so I was trying to take care of her a little bit and
Not get sick myself and so far so good. Yeah, I got a little stuffy head today, but not too bad, but
When I stay up late like I did last night past my normal bedtime my
Legs start to get real
antsy and they start to hurt they start to hurt and they get jittery and I have to like
Shake my leg and twist my leg all evening. It's like go to bed. Go to bed. Go to bed. Okay, fine
But yeah, I was up pretty late. I mean I wasn't up that late. I was like 930, but
Well, I
Forgot that I'm here. I'm a see I'm in the ocean. Yes. I'm actually actually off-shore some rando
Thomas Island that princess owns
Whoo, but
I've seen it and
I
Forgot to pack a knee brace because I found it was helping my knees
I was going to sleep with a knee brace which doesn't help me sleep better
It just helps my knee feel better the next day. I sleep worse. I sleep more restlessly wearing a knee brace
Okay, right
Sounds grabbing my knee. Oh shit. I'm watching Alien Earth. So I assume some alien has gripped my knee. It's like my knee cap
By the way, I I hate the modern
TV show where like you you kind of like slow burn
Middle episodes to like to like peak almost peak boredom and then they and then they really stick the landing on the final
Two and a half episodes and you're like, yeah. All right
You did pick it up and I it's like I'd rather watch the show that I just watched at the end the whole time
Are they I hate it too. And what makes me crazy is in our day. We had 24 25
Now they can't even get fucking eight. Yeah
Well, yeah, I think we look back at the quality of those 24 episodes we're not gonna be like nail of them
I think yeah, I think we'd be surprised. I'd be surprised
Well, here's the thing here's the right not nailed them take up with take a pause recording
Let's all go watch Hill Street Blues and let's come back
Go watch in the heat of the night. I mean my my base thought is
We're gonna sit down everybody and all watch a different world, let's do it
I just think they're trying to get rid of even more episodes. We're trying to prove that they can't do where I want to agree with you
It's just money. We just were spending movie money on television now and so you can't afford to make more than eight episodes, right?
but
Compelling drama that can resolve in an hour. That's where you're talking about. That's what you're talking about. Paul is
These episodes are these these modern TV shows are secretly just super long movies. Yeah, which is gross, you know
Yeah, they're like they have some they have some kind of arc. Yeah
But they
An episode of Star Trek their slow burn in the shit. Well, that's the thing like Trek is sort of
Responsible for all this too because it was season three where they did
You know best of both worlds. That was the first
true
Season-to-season cliffhanger that had ever been attempted in syndication
Oh, I see it was it was the end of a season and then the season break. Yes
Gotcha. So half of the season half of the cliffhanger was at the end of the season
then you had to wait four months five months before the next one started up again and
You know
tantalizing but it
Patrick Stewart became the other thing that the when he became locutus. Yes
That is are the what's the Borg that's the Borg that became locutus of Borg
Yeah
And that is that was the model that they then went forward with from then on out with all the Trek series
all the Trek series had
season cliffhangers I
still remember as a kid not knowing how like I didn't necessarily like we didn't get like TV guide to the house or anything, right and
Different strokes. Yeah, they snuck on the set of Knight Rider. I remember that and they were hiding behind
He was with that kid from Terminator not the main kid from Terminator the other redhead kid from Terminator
Who I think was also on salute your shorts. Yeah. Yeah, the little punk that was him and and
Arnold hid what happened they hid and they almost got killed
They hid they hid in the set and the set was gonna be exploded, right? Yeah. Yeah, and everybody goes. Yes
The audience goes and I was like all summer being like I have to remember to watch the first see if they die
What happened?
Young me was wondering whether
Gonna get dead in the explosion like they start the series be like so sorry every character is dead
They all do well. Well, it wasn't every character was just Arnold dead space
The cast broke on to the set of a James Cameron movie and James Cameron murdered them
Was gonna happen in terms of that like Arnold's death. Yeah
I don't well the little kid died in a set explosion in the Simpsons in the first season
Child was killed. There's that classic episode in the first season of Simpsons
They're all classics, but that one where Homer finally goes to try sushi
Any fucking loves it and then he decides he wants to go for the forbidden sushi the fugu
Which is the blowfish which if not prepared properly can be poisonous and deadly
And yes, so the whole premise was will Homer die
Eating this poison sushi and the commercials that you didn't get TV guide
I got TV guide and the TV guide commercial was a little blurb a little picture with Bart
Coming up to going. Yeah, right. Like they're gonna kill the main character of a
In the first season and you know
So it really was you know, it was before Game of Thrones. They were do that back there
They were always on their ear. They were always putting stuff
Anything within I also saw?
Damn, I just saw a tick tock to me. So say I'm not gonna talk about it. Anyway, uh, I
Wanted to say before we go any further. I
wanted to say thank you to Matt and Jacob because
Guys, I don't know if you know but they always come through when it's my birthday and sure enough here
We are recording on my birthday
And they did it. They gave me permission to use my soundbox throughout this episode
Birthday buddy, there we go. So that's what you have to look forward to
Is zoom cutting off the fart box? Let's see if I want to go through the recording here, but we won't
Zoom as a thing where it cuts out like weird weird weird noise stuff
It's part of it's part of its noise cancel like things that you only hear the what a bunch of shit
Correct that it is going into the episode
Okay, that's great. So it'll be really funny
That it will uh, you know
It'll come up only in the episode
So that'll be a whole surprise for later. Yeah, that's right
So yeah, but a couple of people said it. I already had it pulled up to I'm sorry Paul
Star Trek didn't do it first. Who did it first?
Dallas who shot JR. Oh, I guess you're right. Yeah 10 years 10 years earlier Dallas was 1980 Star Trek
Did it 1990?
Yeah, yes, they did the the season break who shot JR
I'm sorry Paul. Your precious Star Trek didn't do it first. Hey, look look I'm I am I
Have no problem giving Brandon Braga less credit. Fuck that guy
It's all good he can eat
Brandon Braga's a piece of shit
Man now my my computer's asking me if I'm playing music. No, I'm not playing music you dumb thing. I
Mean I played a tiny little piece of music. Well now I can't really do it. It's not fun
If I know I can hear it. It'll be fun later though. Anyway, oh, I got a message for so
Well, not only did I injure my knee playing soccer
But we decided this year man. We did a whole
Is if Nick Newman
Totally influenced my whole family about Thanksgiving. It's basically this is the unit because seated our kids hate
Thanksgiving food. Oh
Would you do it? That's right. Your kids do not care for Thanksgiving food. They never have they do not they do not and
Sarah's you know, basically a vegan. Mm-hmm. And so I rest that there's only one person the household that was looking forward to Thanksgiving
It was me and I was like, well, I'm not gonna I'm not gonna you know, be a fatty dictator
Oh, you know that
And so we blew it off I've never done it before in my life we blew off Thanksgiving
I'm so proud of you. It feels so weird. I feel icky about no. No. No, what'd you have?
Just normal. So here's what we did. We rallied a
Kind of like friends friends with kids kickball game. Okay. Mm-hmm
and
We brought turkey and roast beef deli slices and croissants and right and some fixings
Some hummus and penis pita. I said Pia penis penis, okay
So we did we did our we did our new tradition of dipping our penis and in hummus
Mine the pine nuts and
We have like a basic like half-ass picnic that's not a new tradition, you know, what's weird Matt
You know what what's strange about that tradition is I personally have never had anyone I've never paid anyone to penis on me before
Nobody's buying that
There ain't a carbon zone of bean on me
The bill could never go bond so done Trump's been that's right
But shit
So then so we're playing kickball and both Sarah and I pop the hamstring playing kickball
And she was like this is terrible this is the worst thing Sarah really Sarah really pop
But she was going to run for a ball and you know, like like it's like you like music professional injuries
But they're running and they just stop and you go
Yeah, like Sarah's Sarah's running and also it was like nope
I could have ran to the next base and I stopped like no God and then the very next play I
Pop my hamstring running from second to third
So, uh, I just it's my brain
Subconsciously cannot let Sarah have any more attention that she already gets good
We have to do it. Well, we had inadvertently a similar situation at my home because
The day before Thanksgiving and got terribly sick like
Knocked down drag out sick still had to go to work still worked and almost dying
And so I was like, okay. I better make at least some kind of backup plan. So on the way home, I bought
Warm up mashed potatoes and mac and cheese. So at least we'd have something that resembled a Thanksgiving. Okay, right and
Got home and sure enough. She was just out of it. We were done. We didn't get to go down to the the in-laws
But we absolutely had
chicken nuggets mashed potatoes cottage cheese
That was that was Thanksgiving dinner
That was it
Wait, where's the cottage cheese? Is it countries of its own dishes to go on top?
I put mash I put cottage cheese on the mashed potatoes. I can't I love that. That's my favorite
This has come up before and I I still don't understand I talked about it all time. It's one of those things
I just have to I love it. Just did a triple take up on his view
I love mashed potatoes
I always have it's so good. Are you pregnant? Are you expecting? I mean
by the looks of me you'd think when when's that fucking thing coming, but
No, I
See Nick see Nick Newman top baked potatoes with cottage cheese, I think it's a southern thing. I think there's some kind of weird
You and Nick will not represent the entire
Okay, but I'm saying Kentucky fine
I'll say Kentucky because I my mom my mom used to make lasagna using cottage cheese instead of ricotta
So I that's I prefer cottage cheese and lasagna to ricotta
Any day of the week? Yeah
But I just really love a little cottage cheese on my mashed potatoes according to the Google
It's not a it's not a southern thing or it doesn't have a particular area of origin
it is touted though as a a nice higher protein version and a little healthier version of mashed potatoes if you're not doing like all the
Yeah, if you're not doing like the loading mash up in their sour creams and bacons and all that
No, I just do a little just a little cottage cheese. Just a dab of potatoes and some cottage cheese in there a little salt and pepper
Yeah, sure. Yes little salt pepper. I'm sure every doctor be proud proud of you switching the cutters
Oh, I mean, it's the healthy lifestyle choice of a generation as you can tell
It's done wonders for me
It's really move the needle. I
Mean it got you to this birthday. It did. I mean, hey, I made it to 51 better than a lot of people do I
Bet it's better than half the population does so there you go
Rfk approved don't be saying that lemur creamer lemur creamer in in in chat
What's this if I'm going to get all those horrible dyes of the cottage cheese?
With the mashed potato
Paul you are okay, we can't hear you, but I know it'll be on the broadcast
Right horrible fuck poetry, man, he's so nasty he's so nasty. Oh
I would pay
$14.99 for a book of rfk's poetry. Oh god
Don't say that he'll publish it. He'll do it. He'll he don't give a fuck
He does a little like
Yes in a kickball. We all ate sandwiches and hummus and
Then went home and I had we had leftover pizzas from the day before because we had all a bunch of kids over if we
all saw wicked okay, and
So it was it was leftover pizza was the other Thanksgiving course that we had and then
There's off the Mac Kings for dessert. That's pretty great
That sounds like a nice day
It was super fun it was it was it was really nice not to take Thanksgiving that seriously yeah, and it was like gosh
Really good idea to not stress out of all Thanksgiving
I performed it in the max Thanksgiving variety show nice good
He asked Brad Sherwood and I since Paul couldn't make it Paul was invited
to do a some kind of improv song bit how fun and
Then I called Spadoni and Spadoni was available so we had Spadoni there beautiful and
then after arranging all that I got a text from Brad saying you got a minute and I was like
Oh, no, he's gonna fail. Uh-huh, and then I I call him and it is not him bailing. He's like hey, it's not a wild idea
It's like what if all right? What if what if we do?
do it all in Shakespeare and
You do magic tricks, but I play like your hype man like your producer
And I'm just blown away by all the magic you do and I just narrate everyone's thoughts
I
Like this and I said
The one thing that Mac King's show has is bad, yeah
Arguably lousy with it and
You know we were specifically asked to do music yeah, it goes alright, why don't we do it as a musical?
Yes, and motherfucker
Mm-hmm. So we did
We did what we called the the Shakespeare repertory presents much to do about magic the musical great
Funny that's cool
It was so well that some people thought it was written which is always the best
exactly and
Brad and I want to do it again
Find a way to like we were not satisfied with just the 10-minute hunk that we want to do it again
This is the trick right like we're finding these new ways to expand on improv like
Colin Mockery is doing the hypnoprov
Yes, Brad works with Colin a lot
So yeah, I imagine he's seeing the bold new adventures that can be like what else can we use improv to mine?
Well, yes, so Brad and Colin perform
I've been formed together for 15 something years or more than that. Maybe okay
So so anytime you see hip improv performing. That's Colin not performing with with Brad. Ah
It's just I think that's the the most delicate way I can say it got it. Yeah
So, yes, Colin has discovered that trying to sell the hip improv thing they tried it in Vegas it was too soon
It was a mistake and there's also bad timing. Yeah
and and and did not
Did not get a lot of positive show reports from that. Hey man of experience. Where did they do that?
Muppet improv didn't hardly fucking work in Vegas. No, it's it's fucking tough
Muppets didn't work in Vegas for a different set of reasons. Oh fine, but it's still it's still
Improv with awesome shit not working. So yeah, there's the crazy cocaine habit of all those puppets that really did it in. That's it
They really do good lord those felt-lined straw. They are just
hoovering it hoovering it
They are bald they are
I'll tell you who else is sucking up a lot of cocaine into their felt-lined noses and that is the following sponsor
Which I have in my hand right here. Oh
This is Paul's emergency toilet paper socks Paul's emergency toilet paper socks
Monte Cristo
This year that was this year
We've all had the horrible embarrassment of
Having to shit in a place without a bathroom
Oh
When it happens not if but when
Will you be ready for the challenge of?
the necessary ass wipery
Because that's the real challenge of going to the bathroom without a bathroom the cleanup
Introducing Paul's emergency ass wipe socks
Paul's emergency ass wipe socks are equipped with a double layer
one for absorbency and
one
to be discarded and
then used again for absorbency I
Was to number one there are two number ones
Yeah, but one of them is for number two when you have the Paul's emergency shit socks on you technically are wearing four socks
The first outer layer is the more absorbent layer
And that is the one to be used upon first blush if you will
getting the most
liquid out
of the system
The second is less absorbent but no less important
But we advise you go ahead and employ both socks
use the second socks first layer of
Absorbency to make sure that the rectal area is clear of all juices
then
With the third sock which is the first sock second layer
Go ahead and do what we call the check it tab
Tab it up there take it back out and check it. Where are we standing folks? Did we get everything if?
we didn't
invert the third sock which is the second sock of the first sock
After the check
You go ahead and you use the fourth sock, which is the second sock of the second sock
that one of course is
rounded up and
tucked as a muffler
to prevent any further seepage and
Hey scoops to check out
It just makes too much sense
Jacob take me we got to figure out the zoom thing because everyone's turned off their cameras and so we can't see if anyone's laughing
I
Saw a few or maybe everyone turned off the camera just a vomit. I saw
I saw a few laughs
Just in time for Christmas
Merry Christmas shit, so you cannot hang them by your but you can hang them by the fireplace, you know
Well, I mean you had a drive out somehow. Yeah
Have you been yes, if you guys been watching the show physical Asia on Netflix is that the one with the really strange
Japanese Olivia Newton John impersonator
Yes, yes, okay, that's that's the show that I'm alluding to right now
Japanese Olivia Newton John impersonator physical Asia. Yeah, that was very odd, but I mean, you know
Oh
That's so much better than the Japanese person singing physical that I thought you were about to do I didn't do that
So it's a it's a crazy reality competition show
Where they do these insane like physical tasks and everything it's different Asian countries
Participating competing against each other. Also for some reason Australia
So it's like all these Asian yeah cuz Olivia and John and Australia because of Olivia Newton John, of course
So I'm watching it last night
And they they do it's all overdubbed all of the language is overdubbed
Which is kind of neat just as a side note all of the teams competing against each other
In the overdubbing watching watching the show. It just sounds like they're all speaking English to each other, which of course they are not
They're all speaking their native languages to each other
Which means nobody else can understand them in the competition so they can just
Work together and talk to each other in their native language and the other team can't understand their planning and it's it's really kind of a neat
Twist but the thing I want to talk about was the overdubbing
Because they do all of these crazy physical things where they're like grunting and yelling and everything while they're while they're doing it
And they overdub all the grunting and yelling
Consistent it's so goddamn funny that makes no sense. Oh
Really strange it is the best thing to watch once you realize that that's what they're doing and like oh right
That's not the that that's the same overdubbed voice that is now yelling which is not what that person actually sounds like
Yeah
It's so good. It's so good. What are some of the physical challenges they have to do they do shit like I mean
It's it's really insane stuff
the the first one they do is like a king of the mountain type thing where they have these these each team is six members and
They're all like MMA fighters and
wrestlers
Track stars, it's it's quite a few former Olympians
All this stuff. I mean it sounds like Battle of the Network stars
Kind of but in like a hardcore way. I mean it's it's hey battle network stars was hardcore
I'm telling you Paul
Meatloaf could not have gotten through the first leg of the first competition on this show
He would have died into the board. I
Was worried we're gonna present a vigorous defense for Battle of the Network stars. I will I will
It's Paul's birthday, man, of course, we're gonna present a vigorous defense of Battle of the Network stars
You know, I also saw Jacob. I don't know if you're aware of this new show that they're doing
they've gone in and they're doing this whole retelling of
The guys who came up with the atom bomb
But it's set back in the in the 50s
So it's like it's like a future backwards. So it's like it's okay
It's the the the scientists that made the atom bomb, but they're all
High-schoolers in the 50s, right? Okay, so it's up up and hop up and stop up and sock
Oppenheimer is what it's called
Oppen sock Oppenheimer and can't say the title of the show of the first three tries
Oppen sock Oppenheimer, I said it there. I'll stop sock Oppenheimer and it's also starring
Olivia neutron John
That's how it works, yeah
The show was a bomb I'm assuming it's that's Pluto TV and it's Pluto TV. It's a Pluto original
Good call man. Good call Pluto original
Oppenheimer I said it again
Say Oppensock Oppenheimer five times fast. Good luck. No, I'm not trying to watch Pluto TV
No, they do these insane challenges like they they do stuff that if the three of us tried to do a
Single one of these games we would die. Oh, I can't play kickball
Oh the first thing I heard about on Thursday night was how injured you and Sarah were
and
Sarah and Sarah's like, oh Matt and I are so hurt and keeps watching these
These tic-tacs with these physical challenges. Have you seen some of these where the couples do these extreme physical moves?
With each other they do like these very gymnastic. They'll see a gymnastic move and then they like okay
We can we can do that, you know, and they're in there like little home gym and they're trying to do it
and sometimes they fuck it up some of them well
Over Thanksgiving. She found this one where these guys are doing a new tradition right after the Thanksgiving meal the men
grab the their wives and hoist them on their shoulders and run a race and
And it's laughs of strength. Yeah, and was laughing her ass off
And I was like I could do it. Let's do it. And she's like, no, no, you couldn't
Pick you up. Let's go
Pick her up and she wouldn't she wouldn't work with me at all, which is probably trying to convince and let him pick her up
Is the video that we all need to see wouldn't do it. She would not do it. She's like, no, no
No, I can't do it by myself. You got to give me a little jump so I can you know get it going here
But she would not she would not commit to the bit
But to be fair, she was also coughing up a fit because she was still very very sick
But I don't get picked up like that. That's right
She doesn't get picked up like that and she didn't get picked up like that because I did do it
but she was she was ridiculous, I could have done it but
Yeah, I see all these things Jacob. Did you ever see the the Japanese one with the wall and the shapes?
The wall and the shape yeah
Did I see a television show made in Japan that had a wall and some shapes?
Yeah, is your question? Yeah. So what happens is
You're standing you're standing. I saw Shogun Paul. You're standing in this you're standing in this
Hallway. No, wait. Oh before you go on I'm trying to think of a show that doesn't have a wall
What happens is the outdoor set shows like the Bear Grylls site things where he's surviving in the wilderness
I guess I don't have walls. There's plenty of shapes though. They have shapes but no walls
this the wall has a shape cut out of it of a
silhouette
Uh-huh, right a per a person's physical silhouette. Okay in some sort of stance. Oh
And the wall I have seen this wall moves towards you. Yep
And you must assume the stance to Wile E. Coyote style
Fit through the silhouette as it you have to pass through the wall or yes backs you
Yes, you have it's called hole in the wall. There you go buddies on it
It's called hole in the wall. And so I thought it's called any portentous storm
any portentous storm
It depends on what region you're watching it in some of them is called any portentous storm. So I'm gonna call it hole in a wall
I've watched every episode of any portentous storm
So that's what happens and the wall keeps going up and then either you get through it or you get smushed
They're gonna do a two-person version of that Paul. Have you seen that? No, what is called death in the doorway?
Oh, it's a gentleman's game
Any portentous storm also has a lot of smushing as well a lot of smushing a lot of smushing
There was the cocaine addicted muppets was they had a solo show with miss piggy
Called any snort in a perm and she was just out there hoovering hoovering cocaine
So much money
Piggy Oh
Kermie Kermie, I got some of this fresh Colombian white. It's not even been stepped on. This is the real skag. Oh
Shit bitch. Why didn't you say so? Oh for real frog? Come on. Let's go get fucked our minds explode
Let me do that off your tail. Come here. Come here. Let me straighten out that tail
Easy being green
Come over here and rub it up against my gums
I'll tell you what wants to have a broad
Johnny Depp in the fifth Pirates of the Caribbean
Allegedly Dix what dick tit fertilizer? Oh God Dix tit fertilizer by the marsupials
That is from September 18th, 2021 Dix tit fertilizer. Yes, a a one fertilizer
Go ahead and get the Dix tit fertilizer
Yeah, really don't the crop
And her hey scoops to check out that's it
She's a great stuff in the chat here Matt dirty says people tell me they're California sober I tell them I'm Colombian so
That's really funny Leona because I just said, oh my god, did this biggie just like licking Kermit to get high
Kermit always does on a straight and biggie's tail dart frog a dart frog. I dart the hell away from this crazy bitch
Colombian sober is really funny. I like Colombian sober a lot. I'm truly stealing
Even all out on Thanksgiving. Oh, we did we did we tore it up from the floor on up. We had
I don't know 15 20 people over at the house had a big old turkey on the smoker had we had we had house
Guests in town that week. So they were they were around
We had a ton of people it was great though several people even commented on it
We had no stress the whole cooking of the of the meal and everything
We were just walking around having a nice time. That's how you do it baby. No stress at all. Yeah, great. Everything just worked out
We had a nice big spread set up outside in the in the yard
Yeah, just so so so nice
That's beautiful. This is the only adjustment. I should have made just I should have come by your house after kickball
It's the only adjustment I should have made. Yep
You're gonna you're gonna limped over to the house after kickball and had some turkey
Nice pack from you. Yep. Yep. I would help you out with an ice pack
The best thing happened that I doubt I'll ever be able to repeat
That is what we had the big spread set up. We had all the people a
Couple hours later. I had to go to work. I'd do shows that night
That's where I saw the the injured Sarah that night and we talked about the kickball game of doom and uh, I
Got home a couple hours later
There was still about five people at the house and the first thing that SJ said to me when we when I got home was
Hey, there's no leftovers. Everybody ate all of it. Wow. Oh
Oh Mike we did it. We did it. We got the exact right amount of food
It got grazed on after the after the meal was over and it's just all gone. That's great. This is magical. I
thought like I I you know grew up with with four brothers and a sister and
We you know, I I am I am the shortest of my not by a lot, but I'm the shortest of my brothers. Uh-huh
so
never
Never had leftovers. Yeah
Never no, no meal. No meal leftovers. Yeah, that checks out
Yeah, my mother-in-law does this thing where she insists on trying to make like a turkey soup with the turkey carcass of the
turkey thing
And like it's just a whole it's a thing that takes up the whole next day, right?
All that all that started was to make sure that Sarah and I stopped cooking turkey. That's all that happened
Is that we just don't we do?
like
We don't want to spend the whole other day making soup and we don't want to spend the next four days eating that soup
Yeah, it's just not just not the world we live in
But
Yeah, but look I saw on Instagram. It looks like you had a fine spread at your house there Jacob
Oh, yeah. No, it was it was so nice. Yeah. Yeah, we had a we had a ton of people over and everything
It was great. I love Thanksgiving. I don't know what y'all are talking about. I love doing the the whole meal
I love doing all of it. It's it's great time. I
Did too I think I really I
Promise I'm making a very good turkey. Yeah, I just was simply alone in my house
As as Nipman famously said all Thanksgiving food tastes like napkins and that's what my kids think too. So there you go
And it was it really was this show that changed my perception
So first I was like I have to as their dad
Keep making it until they like it
It works and there's only on this show. I found out so many listeners hate Thanksgiving food. Also as adults. Oh
You should show your boys do you ever watch a Garen the guy out of Ireland, he's very funny. He's a
Thanks for watching. I'm delicious
You ever seen him? He's really funny
He's he's really really funny. You should look up some of Garen stuff, but he did
from Ireland
Just a couple days ago. He cooked his own version of a traditional American Thanksgiving dinner and
I was very surprised by what he liked and what he didn't like
So he was okay with the turkey. Okay
He hated Kraft macaroni and cheese box dinner
The box fine at which I mean, I guess yeah, that's not really Thanksgiving food in anyway. Well mac and cheese
Yes, it does mac and cheese is a Thanksgiving food. That's what people I suppose so sure people get
You're bringing a very fiery debate. Yeah, there are people that that insist Mac Jesus not a Thanksgiving food people system of this
I don't have it as a Thanksgiving food, but I'm not upset if I see it show up. I love it. I love it
Mashed potatoes. He made his own mashed potatoes. He has a special recipe for the mashed potatoes
Great, so he wasn't expecting the mashed potatoes be anything but delicious. They were he made kind of a cheese
Does he put in his mashed potatoes? What kind of cheese? What kind of white cheese does he put in there?
Oh, no, he does not do the no. No, he doesn't do the cottage cheese
It's just curds and weights barely even cheese. It's like halfway done
So then he had the green bean casserole
Which he was very suspicious of but he liked
Yeah, I like a green casserole and then he made pumpkin pie which they don't do pumpkin pie in Ireland at all apparently
No, they do potato pie. Yeah, but I mean they don't mash potatoes. They're new pumpkin pie at all and
He was really super suspicious about it all but he made it and he really liked it
He was suspicious of the pie. He was suspicious of the pie
He said he was took him some time to get over the he's he was like what's got this vegetable II?
Mush to it. I'm not used to like a dessert and he says and then I went on I watched all your fucking videos of all
Your fucking celebrations and I saw how all you got all you only got these these yam potatoes all these sweet potatoes with fucking
Marshmallows on top so many fucking marshmallows get fucked. I don't want marshmallows anywhere near my dinner. That's bullshit
I do agree with that. I don't want the marshmallows. I agree with that too. He says I know a lot of you say it's great
I don't know more power to you. Keep those fucking things away from me. It's secretly deserting early
That's what I don't like about it. Yeah, it's like what's it because was I have marshmallows and sugar and brown sugar and cinnamon on something
I'm like, well now I don't want to eat savory things anymore. You've you shift my gear to dessert, right? It's unfair
Yeah, it's like it's like a hip. It's hip broth like we do we do the the sweet potatoes
We do the sweet potato casserole and it's got brown sugar and pecans and everything. It's not healthy
It's not it's not a it's definitely still a dessert masquerading as as a dish
But it doesn't do the full-on swing over with the marshmallows
Sweet potato the masquerade
Galactic president scooper star mix groups a lot stuffing on a waffle iron. That sounds amazing
Stuffing on a waffle iron is legit. I saw that earlier. I've seen that before
It's a that's a fucking idea. Do you put a little gravy on it and then kind of sear it all in is that how it goes?
I think you gravy afterward though. You have like a little I suppose
I suppose you're right. Yeah. Yeah, you just make it
I think you want the hot gravy. Yeah nice hot gravy then pour it on after you waffle iron it
Oh, man, because when you get something that has crispiness and moisture, that's the key. Yeah, right
So that's that's that seems really good. It's fucking good
But Paul was the hot crispify some gravy, which is also ambitious. I mean as long as it has a skin
Me that me that skin give me that gravy skin gravy skin is not not no, it's no good
How do you know? No, I'm just I'm just upset because
Well, I'm not upset upset is the wrong word
disappointed lightly
That I can't just go get the food that I want on my birthday without driving an hour and a half out of my way
Yeah, like it's literally an hour and a half drive for me to get even fucking Panda Express
It's like fuck Nick newman the chances this conversation for me must be what is like when the topic is football for other scoops
There you go horse racing, yeah
Yeah express you're absolutely right rich
Yes, it takes way too fucking lot. So like and that's the thing. It's by the time I get back home
I'm like, oh, well, I drove an hour and a half for Panda Express
Might as well just give fucking McDonald's. It's just it's turned into
Shit at that point. I mean, that's the same thing, right?
Kind of Panda Express and McDonald's. I didn't even say it's all owned by the same company, right? Well, we're thinking of
Maybe going to Costco on Wednesday
Get that good old hot dog. That'll be fine. So what did you guys what you guys think of wicked - didn't see it
What? No, I didn't see you didn't rush up to see the sequel. I did not I've only seen it seven or eight times
So I I don't really have a fully fleshed out opinion on it yet
I know it's really cool when they breakdance to save the car wash. That's really amazing
Have you seen that is that what you're talking about?
No, there's
There's a bit of the plot of breaking -
Okay. Well, I'm gonna blow your fucking mind to show you shit
You're not gonna show me anything
Program I'm gonna tell you about it as it's happening
First is it take a long time to pull it up though. I don't know if I have the plot right from breaking - I'm not looking
It up. I'm just we're just moving on. No, all it is is it's the old Donnie and Marie
Or the Osmonds that's what it are. No, no, it wasn't the Osmonds. It was a fucking what he called. It's a Brady Bunch
the break you remember the Brady Bunch hadn't had a
Their variety show. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah where one of the kids I forget which which kid one of the kids got replaced on
It because they couldn't get the whole original cast back together
That is correct. I think it was one of the young kids. It was just like a new kid. Oh Jan. Thank you
You're like the president. Yep, they had to replace the Jan
Well what you just and Jan sickly stick-ups issues cutting ropes to see
I just would fall from the top of the theater and there's a cliffhanger. That's right cliffhanger ever right
You just joked about Matt happened and it happened with none other than rip Taylor as the
Lion and the rest fucking Brady's dressed up like the people from Oz
Doing the theme from car wash. They're doing car wash at the car wash
Yeah, and then fucking Greg Brady dressed up like the scarecrow and rip Taylor is the lion to be in his flamboyant as he can be
Just out of hand and I thought this would be really funny for somebody to slip into a copy or one of the edits of
Oz - or we could do wouldn't be really funny if this showed up all uh, you know
Somebody's just like watching that on TV in the background or something. No, no, you know, what's the
Fight Club like in Fight Club. Remember how he would always slip in little snippets of pornographic stuff
In all the movies if you can put this in and just make everybody upset
That is true
That is quite a fever dream as none of the elements make sense at all. No, it's fucking bizarre and
And rip Taylor of all a rip. Yeah rip Taylor of all people. He's like, hey, it's
You you'll never get rich, but it beats digging a ditch. Ah
I think I said you guys the funny the meme I saw which is that don't worry Glinda and Alphabot will be back in the Avengers
That's awesome, I just keep this doll thing that there's a doll channel on tik-tok and
The guy he's mad at there's a lot of now Madam Mova or whatever name is you know
There's dolls of all these figures, right? There's dolls. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah sure. So he's got all the dolls stacked up and
then Madam Mova
Comes in and it's playing that that song from the drag race stuff
Here comes the hurricane bitch Katrina Katrina Katrina Katrina Katrina Katrina Katrina
Katrina Katrina Katrina Katrina and she's knocking it to all the dolls and the bounce comes down and crushes
It's fucking funny Katrina Katrina Katrina here comes the hurricane bitch. I'm just yelling Katrina. It's funny
It makes me laugh. So what what did you really like it? Did you not like it? Oh
That was funny. That was good. Would you be able to watch it all in one sitting?
Yes
That's that's that's my only takeaways. They added three songs to it and those three songs aren't on par with the actual Oh
Core soundtrack. Yeah to basically strength to basically make the second
Movie fill out. Yeah. Yeah
Is it they're not terrible. There's not there's nothing - is it closer to the book or the?
Musical do you know I?
Wouldn't know is my wife would know either my wife loved the book and we went to see the musical and
She was so upset because the ending is so really yeah
The ending is so different and just all had to carry her out of there like it was a Thanksgiving Day prank
I threw on my back and she laughed the whole way home
It was crazy
It undercuts the meaning of the whole
Story, the ending Cooper Nova girl in the chat says that it's the musical on screen nothing added from the book. Well, that's unfortunate
For Anne. Yeah, that means go good. It's so poorly but
No, the the ending of the musical is bupkis deus ex machina bullshit
That's everything now though. I guess you're right. There's so much
movies for happy endings, dude
Worried about that. There's so much of the any TV show. I watch any movie
I'll watch like half of them now at least have the have the
God from the machine. Yes a sex Machina
Just some kind of supernatural thing or somebody comes in or something
But something off-screen happens and the plot resolves itself. Do we know do do our do our audience members?
I think most of our audience members know deus ex machina
But you know where that really comes from from back in the day in early theater. There was actually a hand
Yeah, the Greeks had an actual hand of God that would come down from the top of the
The thing and touch characters or zap characters and that was a way to resolve plots by actual divine intervention
Yeah, they would they would just say like, you know Medea is doing all of these things
Off off stage right now, right and then the gods interfere intervened and and now it is this and now here comes
Everybody to bow. Yep
Yeah, there you go. Yeah
I was told that people kind of get off scripts and and kind of go haywire with stories and stuff and and so like that
Was a way to like just clean everything up. Yeah. Yeah, and somebody did ten minutes of Shakespeare and magic
I can tell you we can go haywire fast. I'll bet no haywire. I'll bet it got loosey loosey
You know you ought to do that again
Nope, we're gonna and Paul Paul might have to take a flight. We might do the thing. I would fuck
I would fuck. I want us. I want to I want to see Brad schedule, but I want to submit it for
French. Oh, yes
That'd be really fun. Yeah
So I you know for people to see the movie I don't want to you know, it's a good movie
I don't want to pass the whole thing. Yeah, there's one part that really stuck out to me that I was really really like like
Really laughing because it almost took me out of it. So this whole thing's like basic family-friendly PG ish PG 13 ish. Uh-huh
story
but there's a part where
The prince has got to get it on with somebody they they they they they run off and they're they they're finally by themselves
And they're gonna there's a hookup that's gonna happen. Oh, yeah
And it is the weirdest shot
Thing ever it's like this weird like it's like it looked like an old Chris Isaac music video
Like everyone's just drifting from one room to another
stuff and like
What am I watching? It took me out of it completely. I literally was like almost laughing. I was like, what is the scene?
The title of the song is
That's what it must have been
Video listeners do yourself a favor and Google them
the Wicked Games video
So take the characters from one room to another like taking off clothing, but then also putting on clothes
Like that's great bizarre
Someone said big ups to modern love where someone puts on a sensible shawl to have sex
Old jet alpha
the
Matt I don't want to frighten you but if you back up just a little bit
Back back your head up just a little bit. There you go. Perfect. Stay right there
everybody in the chat
Don't move
Is it me or is the shadow of the Baba Duke behind him?
Am I crazy is that the shadow of the fucking Baba Duke over there? Yeah. Yeah, it's the Baba Duke
Why are you worried about a shadow of a big cartoon Great Dane behind you know, they talk about this
He's gonna get you they talk about they talk about, you know within
Spooky stuff ghosty stories that they talk about the hat man and all that kind of thing
Baba do definitely qualifies as a hat man. Yeah, that's pretty scary. It's kind of creepy. Yeah
All right, well
Have a good night sleeping tonight with the Baba Duke
In there. Yeah. No, Baba. Duke is now a gay icon. So I think you're safe
It truly is Baba Duke has now been taken over by the gays which I think is awesome. Oh good. Yeah
The gays do good work. They fucking do they rehab the Baba Duke of all of all critters. Well, I got him go. Yeah
Let's do a little scoop mail. We got a scoop mail though. I want to get to today
Let's do it
We got a scoop mail here from Josh greetings you fabulous face fuckers of whom I have met too
Oh, it's been about a month since the wedding Casey and I have returned from our honeymoon and life is returning to normal
The story of Matt and Paul being the surprise entertainment at the rehearsal dinner is a hit among friends who weren't there and I'm so happy
That in the month since I've met you any new listeners from the wedding have heard about Paul shitting himself and
ejaculating tie infused jizz
Heard all about Paul
Shitting and jizzing on himself. Well, I mean not the hero we need but the hero we deserve I'm staying on brand
I'll tell you I've been turning on a lot of my new students to the podcast and and they're still on board
They they're all right. I I'm coming yet. I preach truth in comedy. So here we are
The surrealness of how I came to meet you two is starting to wear off
Of course you two were at my wedding
Of course
I have pictures with the two of you with Casey and the kids and of course all three of your names are on the guest
List for any future parties brings me to Jacob. Oh, no
I am so sorry you weren't at this one
Not just because I'd love to meet you in person
But because you missed out on two amazing dinners and two open bars. I do love
Vegas is on the list of places that Casey and I would like to visit. Hopefully there's a chance to buy you a drink
On one of those trips. Absolutely for this first non uh for this first groom update scoop mail
I have a question for the boys
Did either of you two hear the airplanes leaving the Italian airfield as you were driving away from the wedding? Yep
We had ourselves a bit of a slow-burning medical themed air show over the course of the next day
First oh, no
The planes collide at 2 30 in the morning when my stepson son wakes up to tell me that he's not feeling well
Only to then yell i've just thrown up. Oh, no
There I am cleaning up vomit in the middle of the night
Casey and d were able to fall back to sleep, but i'm awake until about five in the morning
Second the burning jet fuel lands on me at six in the morning when I am woken up by a text message
My sister texts to tell me that she's on her way to the doctors
Due to some distressing medical symptoms and will keep me posted as to how she's feeling. Oh, no
Lastly for the grand finale of the flaming wreckage hitting the crowd
I get a call from my father at eight that evening saying that my stepmother is in the emergency room
Jesus fuck
Long story short she ended up face planting onto cement and looked like she'd been hitting the eye with a baseball bat
God damn my god
This italian air show ultimately becomes an ontario business meeting though as both my stepson sister and stepmother are fine
No long-term damage and everyone is healed up fine. The new running joke is if you party with us, you better have
You have a better than zero chance of ending up in the hospital. Absolutely
Fuck's giving and a merry chris bosh to all an early chris bosh present for casey was tickets to see matt perform
In saratoga in march as part of the jokers of magic tour fantastic. I love you boys. That's josh
Oh, thanks josh. Yeah, the groom. That's wonderful. We asked him if he would uh, send us an update and he sure enough fucking did
That's great. There you go. Oh, that was such a wonderful time. We had a we had a lot of fun
We had a lot of fun with yeah, it's really like having jacob out there really helped
Yeah, really submitted the whole the whole thing have a lot more loose fun and just enjoy ourselves
No, this is the thing man all three of us jacob the wet blanket audio guy
all of us have shit to do and things come up and we can't make it all these things sometimes but uh,
You know, we're gonna we're gonna figure it out again. Hopefully as things progress here and this becomes more and more our full-time gig
once the
The oh by the way support the kickstarter not kickstarter
The is it go fund me the go fund me for the for the film
Support the go fund me for the hay scoops movie so we can get that launched
Uh as primo as possible and it gets picked up by many major outlets and is shown worldwide
And we attain even oh, it's 90 funded. Fantastic. Uh, richard though, but we want to crack it even further
Hey scoops the movie help finish. Hey scoops the movie if you just look for hey scoops the movie on go fund me.com
It'll take you right over to it. We'll toss it in there again. But yeah, uh as we
Grow that out and as we can grow our patreon and make this more our full-time gig
Then we can use those funds to not only just pay ourselves
but also
uh
Buy ourselves around to get to places we need to be for events and things like that. Yeah
And again, if you uh, give us three billion dollars
We will uh do an experiment to see if we can be better billionaires than the current ones
I mean if you like science
You have to get behind this project. Yes
I and i'm and i'm very I know we make a lot of jokes on this show
I'm very serious about this if anyone gives us three billion dollars
We will run this experiment to see if we can be better at being billionaires than the current ones. Yeah. Yeah
Well, you I think this is a good experiment people, you know, i'm a proponent of doing things for science
I have done it on this podcast many times
Oh greater science presenters than paul mattington
Here at matt and mattingly's ice cream social. We believe in three things pro science. We're pro women and we're pro wrestling
That's right. That's right
In fact, just like the t-shirt I need to carry I need to carry out that previous previous experiment two more times because I need to control
and
I need to do one for control and I need to try I need to try to control your ass
You need to have some fucking control over your ass pussy blowing it out of your ass pussy pussy
Jacob just quick you want to tell quick note to people who bought pheasants and robes
Oh, they are by the time you hear this they should be uh, all of the ones that have not been shipped out yet
Uh have been shipped out by the time you hear this. There you go. Okay, great
Yeah, we've been getting a few little updates here in there shifting on the uh questions came up during the uh, yeah
Some of them are out but yeah
Yeah, there there are a couple of them that are out. They're actually sitting right behind me right now
Uh, they're gonna go in the post today. There you go
I think two or three more that I have to package up and then they're going out today
Thanks everybody. Yeah, it's on its way. Yeah, another quick reminder that if you come to see me in chicago
I'm doing the thursday saturday and sunday. I'm not doing the friday show
I got an email from a scoop asking for a meetup post friday. That's an eek. I'm not doing the friday show
uh, please uh, uh
Adjust your ticket
Adjust your ticket. Yeah, see if you can shuffle it around. It's it's the signature show at chicago magic lounge
Uh of the 18th 20th and 21st out there in chicago
um
I'll be with a bunch of drunks in missouri on friday night
But don't you also have a gig?
Yeah, okay. I was told specifically by my agent. This is blood buddy
That's right. All right. This is gonna. Ah, I can't wait for the stories on this one
It's gonna be a handful get ready. It's gonna be fun. Yeah, it's gonna be fun speaking of getting ready
You're not ready for jock versus nerd. So you say so you claim
Fuck yeah, i'm on the hunt for balls
On the hunt for balls
We got a scooperty today coming to us from keester sunday greetings gentlemen
I decided to complete my trilogy of scooperties and like the third entry in any trilogy
It was slapped together in record time with minimal effort and sure to ruin all of the goodwill that its predecessors have fostered with
Uh thoughtfulness and craftsmanship. Okay, please enjoy
The categories are 80s comedy again 80s horror again 80s action again
And 80s sci-fi again. I can't get enough of all this
All right, let's try i'll open it up with 80s sci-fi for 200
Commonly known as the film where john landis killed vic morrow
This anthology mostly just reimagines tales from the classic 1959 tv show
It shares a name with for real though. Fuck john landis. I'm sure his son is a really cool guy though
People don't like john landis. What's wrong with john landis?
Because of this because he killed him. Oh, oh, yeah fine. Uh twilight zone
Yeah, there you go
Uh matt you're up
Um, i'll do um 80s action 200
About that action even with a stiff neck. Mr. Mom is surprisingly badass when he kicks jack
Torrance's ass in this thrilling 1989 film that spawned three sequels each better than the last
This is batman, yeah the batman
It is of course the batman jack torrance is just in a different movie
Oh, but he's so good. He's so good
Amazingly all over he's great. I remember as a kid seeing him in that movie and I was like this man is delightful
I don't know what is happening here, but i like jack nicholson. I'm going against jack nicholson
He's gonna be the joker. I'm sure they should have cast me as the joker. That's what i'm gonna do
Every scene that of this movie that i'm in i'm going to audition for the joker paul
Uh 80s horror for 800, please
Oh in this 1984 king adaptation sarah connor and her husband are the targets of a rural cult of children
Run by cousin it and hans clopec looking to sacrifice them to their god
He who walks behind the rose that's nebraska for you, uh children of the corn
Children of the corn. Yes children of the corn
Children of the in the fields they're born in the fields. They're born have some corn on the morn
I'll do 80s action for 400 daily double
On the corn your cows will graze while the natives call it maize children of oh
I get it this daily double there is a parentheses
then a zero
then another point to see
And then another zero and then a closed parentheses then another zero then a closed parentheses or then another zero and then a closed parentheses
And that is from I believe that is referencing the film total recall with arnold schwarzenegger total recall
Yep. Wow. Uh, yeah, I know it came out in 1990, but it's an 80s film my heart and this is a half-assed scooperty
That's cool. Yeah, great. What's that? Uh, is that something he sees when he gets a message?
No, it's three. It's the three titties. Oh the three boobies. Oh, it's the alien with three boobies. That's right
How could I forget?
Yeah, one was paper mache. Oh, that's how I forgot
That's the hottest one. Yeah
Matt the hottest one i'll do uh 80s action 600 paper mache with a heating element in it
Ever the one to always say and do the right thing mel gibson portrays a post-apocalyptic drifter willing to aid a helpless australian
Community against murderous marauders as long as they're able to fill up the tank in his car in this
1981 sequel
Oh
What's the name of the secret?
I mean, it's not mad max 2 which is called something else. Yeah specific title
Think think legendary wwe pop
What's it wwe, uh, there's a there's a tag team
that
They are legendary. Oh, is it beyond thunderdome?
No, the the sound that would the audience would make when this tag team would come out
It's a little remember a legendary effect
Huh, I I don't remember your your your hand's not up, but we saw pass, uh
Oh, it passes to paul. I think thunderdome's the third mad max movie road warrior
road warrior
It is the road warrior. Yeah, so when the road warriors would come out
It's still legendary hawk an animal then the noise that the crowd would make was like deafening and that is still slang
Like if you if you come out to big cheers everything like you got that road warrior pop
Yeah, matt, yeah road warrior
Of course later they became the legion of doom
But what yeah, you don't have to tell us about that paul. We all know all about that and it's all the fucking same
What do you want paul, oh what do I want sci-fi for eight
sci-fi for 800
I have come here to chew bubble gum and kick ass and i'm all out of bubble gum
Watch keith david and roddy piper getting a rowdy street fighting this cynical
Carpenter satire about aliens that have secretly enslaved humanity. They live
They live of classic
See, it's all wrassling
It's me all right
It is all right. He's action for 800 when the queen of the wrassling company is dismantling the education system in your entire country
It's all fucking wrassling
And answer your question matt. Yes paul has already won
Uh, this 1989 classic starring raiden from mortal combat mr
Krabs and the guy that said you're the man now dog is about an immortal and surprisingly sober scott hunting down
Kurgan the last man standing between him and the prize
Which okay, I know the movie
Who's raiden in mortal combat? It's the movie is highlander. The movie is the highlander. That's him. He was in mortal combat. He was
Oh the the christopher lambert
Oh
That's oh he was in that first. That's right. That's right. I can't believe you all are here to survive
You're going to defend earth realm against shao khan
Your christopher lambert in mortal combat impression sounds a lot like ren and stempy. I mean, that's kind of what he sounded like
You idiots
johnny cage you idiot you have to fight goro in the pit. Yeah, that's it
Oh you eat you're up
Uh, I guess i'll do 800, uh 80s comedy. All right
If this is 1988 classic mario must clear the name of charles flesher's voice after he's accused of murder orchestrated by professor plum
Also, did that cartoon redhead give anyone else a boner?
Who framed roger rabbit who framed roger rabbit, of course is it
I love that movie. Oh, that's a great movie. So good. I will go with 80s comedy again for six
In this 1982 celebration of how far we've come as human beings a rich
Jackie dleeson literally purchases a black man as a plaything for his son
Portrayed by that kid who got his tongue stuck to a flagpole in a christmas story the toy
the toy of course
I have that on dvd another good movie. That's a hell of a movie
richard prier
Uh, let's see. I'll try um
sci-fi for 600
Zach galligan plays a child whose father gifted him a monster with a long list of needs
Keeping it from unleashing hell on everyone that he purchased in a smoky back alley from an asian stereotype
Also, don't mention lincoln's birthday
Gremlins
Wait, is this okay? I thought that'd be the sequel because the lincoln's birthday thing comes up in the sequel
Oh gotcha. Gotcha. Well, he buys the thing in the first one. I don't know whatever. Yeah
The sequel is great. Uh, also you should watch the sequel to gremlins
You should watch gremlins 2 and then after you get done watching gremlins 2
You should uh on youtube pull up the key and peel sketch about the makings of gremlins 2
That is great that is 100 percent a real suggestion watch that movie then watch that key and peel sketch
You'll love me. Yeah, matt you're up. Yeah
uh
80s horror again 600
Uh, where's horror? There it is
Now it's for a thousand
A teenager seeks the help of his favorite horror tv host
Roddy mcdowell after no one believes him that his sexy new neighbor jack skellington is a vampire
It got a remake in 2011 starring an even sexier penguin from the batman
Oh, no, I don't get any of this um
Even sexier, so that means uh, uh denny devito. No, the batman is the um, the one with the twilight guy in it
It's the batman
Oh that batman, okay, but the penguin was in that one
Yeah, you do
Do I yeah, you had the same guy from the show. Yeah, he had all the fucking work on. Yeah
18 hours of prosthetics to play fat motherfucker. I'm not sure if I ever actually watched that
Let us men of size have a role once in a while you shitbag
I can't figure out what the plot is that they're talking about so I can't figure out this question. It's a daily double
There's a movie with these people in it
Um, yes. Yeah, I would give you clues if I had any I like who is jack skellington
that's uh
boingo boingo
Oh, what's his name? He did the uh, yeah
Sheesh, you know the music danny alfman. Yeah
He does the voice for jack skellington. I didn't know. Yep. Yeah, he was placeholder, but they eventually just were like, okay
He's it. Oh great. Yep
I don't I don't understand this question. I don't understand the the plot that i'm supposed to decipher
So is this someone saying I gotta tell my neighbor's a vampire?
Is that what it is?
uh
Jack skellington is a vampire. Yeah, so somebody thinks that their neighbor is a vampire in this movie
Okay, I can't it's daily double I can't pass uh pb's big adventure. All right, let's try it
Fright night, uh, right right night. That's not what i'm really familiar with. It's night clearly
Clearly it's not one that any of us are very familiar with. I don't think i've seen it
uh sci-fi
Sci-fi for 400 in this adaptation of do androids dream of electric sheep
Hans solo must hunt down biomachine replicants created by the bartender from the shining also
Red hulk might be one of them. Luckily. They never made a sequel needlessly
Revealing if he is a blade runner the blade runner. Yes
Hilarious
Mosquito, it's me
I'll do a quick score check in here paul has a lead. He has 3200 i'm right behind him though with
2000 matt is also playing this game. I'll go copy again for 400. Thanks for having me
In this wholesome family film, uh goose and the caridine
Who didn't die jerking it in bangkok bangkok hotel room seek perfectly equitable retaliation against jefferson d'arcy
And the rest of the jocks tormenting them
That would be revenge of the nerds there you go revenge of the nerds
Uh, yeah does that hold up matt?
Uh
Horror 400 sure
A year before he told arnold that boys have a penis and girls have a vagina
Michael or mico hughes is run over by a semi against the wishes of herman munster
He's put in a cursed native burial ground only to return as a tiny evil murderer
You know that road that road out there. I got trucks going too fast on that road
That road
It's bet cemetery stay away from that road
There's a road. Keep that kid away from the road
Uh, i'll do horror
Might as well for 200 bruce campbell is a comedic splat stick one-man show in this
1987 horror sequel that is also a pseudo remake about the skin-bound
necronomicon and demonic possession at a cabin deep in the woods of tennessee, uh, that is
uh
evil dead 2
Evil dead 2 electric boogaloo
So good
And i'm closing out the category and the game comedy for 200
Rotten tomatoes has a 42 rating for this beloved
1988 film about race stance and poca king gus polinsky
Sharing the magic of leeches bugs with glowing butts and bald-headed grizzly bears with their families
So fuck rotten tomatoes. Oh, this is a good
42%
Really?
Is this?
um
Is this canadian bacon no
Which one is this
This is the 80s one
This has got uh acroid and um
What's his nuts candy?
john candy
Yeah, yeah
And yeah, that's race dance and poca king. He eats that big steak
the big steak challenge
Ah
This movie is great
Oh, is it uncle buck? I'll say uncle buck. No
Uh, what is it then? Oh the great outdoors
That's right
That's the game paul wins with 3,400. I'm in second with 2,200 matt's in third with 400. That's been keester sunday
Thank you keester sunday. That was a wonderful one keester sunday. That was a great one
If you want to solve any questions
Matt didn't do well on it, but it was a really good scooperty
If you want to send this one if you want to send this one
Hey scoops.com as we can go make us a scooperty make us a price of scryte jock versus nerd make us an obelisk jock
Versus nerd do all those things over there
At hey scoops.com
Also send us an email. That's right. Yeah
Uh, I want to thank everybody joined us, uh today on twitch
If you want to join us on twitch you have to become a member of uh on our patreon feed at any level
That's right. So head on over to uh
Preaching fun dot com set up for level today
Come visit breaching fun dot com
It's better than hanging with your
And if you like me know that matt meant zoom when he said twitch head on over to farts in a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz and matt is absolutely right if you go over to farts in a bag dot biz or preaching fun
Dot com and sign up for any level it starts at three dollars a month or you can do it yearly as well
What a deal invited to our uh, twice weekly usually if we're doing the regular schedule twice weekly zoom meetings
Where you get to be in the audience, uh, you get to be in the chat
You get to interact with us a little bit whenever we're whenever we're paying attention to that chat over there and everything
Also, you can help keep this show on the air. We are uh
Dependent on our patreon supporters. So please preaching fun dot com farts in a bag dot biz
If you think this show is worth more than zero dollars, those are the websites. You can go to to show it head on over there
It's three bucks a month. You can do it
Yeah, if you do we uh, we we thank you usually this section of the show. It's a brand new month
But we'll get our right use up soon
Um at any rate, uh, thanks for listening to us
Uh any at any time any amount of time anywhere we appreciate it. Yes, we do. Um
If you want to help us out in a different way turn someone on to our podcast recommend us to a friend
Choose one person and one person only choose them specifically choose someone who would fit our awesome community
And see if they want to check out ice cream social episode or two or three. Yeah, see if they get on board
The if you're wondering how to obelisk someone, uh, just a smart way to do it
I've seen a lot of people who do it this way
Uh, they put our podcast on and then they perform oral sex on the person that they're trying to obelisk
Oh, they uh, they relate our podcast with a nice feeling in their genitals while they're receiving oral sex relate the phallate
Yeah, that's right. That's right. So that's that's one way to a new program the relate the phallate program
All right, stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you soon
Suck that opulence
See ya
In cox estamos un paso adelante como el muchacho que ya sabe la orden de tu cafecito incluso antes de pedirlo
Ose caf con leche sin lactosa un toque de vainilla templadito sin azcar en cox tambin nos adelantamos a lo que necesitas
Por eso el precio de tu plan no subir por tres aos y nuestra seguridad avanzada proteger tu red de amenazas antes de que pasen cox
un paso adelante ose llamada de tu jefe en tres dos uno al menos 500 megabits por segundo de velocidad y cox
impuestos y carros no incluidos en garanta de precio velocidad de datos mviles reducida tras usar 20 gigas al mes
[BLANK_AUDIO]