Oh hello there, I am so happy you are here because right now I'd like to thank the ice cream truck drivers
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. I don't have a list yet
We're recording this show in the past
But we are gonna thank each and every ice cream truck driver before this month is over if you want to be an ice cream
Truck driver and help deliver this fucking ice cream straight to people's fucking ear holes head over to preaching fun calm preaching fun
Commas where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save
May be your own
Here's a show. Hey Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
Several horses reportedly did not come to the Las Vegas rodeo this year because of a horse flu
No, I know horse whoopies
really
Social sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pittsburgh. It's automatically sitting in Las Vegas
Loaded with horse herpes. It's me. Jacob the audio guy
Fun first off I didn't because of the music they want to interrupt but Bama lamb
Horse herpes Bama lamb Bama lamb
If you type in horse herpes Google will auto fill Las Vegas. Oh shit
Yeah, wait a minute if you type down herpes at all Google will auto fill lost me
Can they get this by like sharing a water trough and shit? Is that how bad it can be?
That how viral it is. Where's Nick Newman when we need him?
I was looking for him in the chat before we started. He's not in. Let's see
No confirmed cases were reported reported in Nevada, but there is a significant equine
Herpes virus outbreak affecting horse events nationwide causing major major disruptions cancellations
like the all-in barrel race and
It heightened biosecurity at the NFR rodeo, which is the one in Vegas here during early December
so a lot of people just didn't bring their horses a lot of people just just left their animals at home and
Came to the rodeo. Apparently the rodeo was really affected by it
Paul says Paul Paul's Paul is right. Let's do it
Okay, primarily directed through contact nose to nose or indirectly from shared items like tack buckets clothing and even people's hands
Aerosol droplets or contact infected with fluids man. It's amazing how we all don't have horse herpes. This is everything
I'm already looking up if it can go to
People no, it's not a zoonotic jumper, please. Fuck. No
I don't want horse herpes if I
Know our next humans cannot get infected with horse herpes. Don't worry about it. Keep on fucking those horses
Keep on the horse a fucking use a stepstool safety first people safety first. That's right. Oh good Lord
Yeah, just be out there puffing it. Mr. Hands has nothing to worry about
There'll be more horse herpy stuff in the new Taylor Sheridan show about the rodeo
It'll be called it'll be called bull rider long dick man
Speech guy Sheridan's running out of good names bull rider long dick man speech guy
You know what you know what to say about riding bulls
What's that? A lot of times people think it's all about those eight seconds. You got to stay on the bull
Those eight seconds. Those are the least important seconds of the whole thing
The most important time is when you enter the pen
my secret
Give that bull a little light touch behind the ear. I
got a little dab of
Hot icy cold on my finger. I give him a little rub right behind the ear with icy cold. I
See hot and that's what he's what he's quoting. What are you quoting? I'm making up a dumb
speech that he would do for this
Rodeo, I thought you were quoting something but you're doing
I'm improvising Matt. That's what I do. No, no, no
I didn't mean to be that much of a dick about it
But you didn't make me feel liberal guilt, that's why I didn't think it was a Sheridan speech
Also to be fair, I don't I don't watch you don't watch so I don't know enough of
Okay, so now I know where to go to go with. Okay. Yes
I rub a little bit behind there and then when that bull knocks me off
After eight seconds if I stay on there for more than eight seconds
That bull is outlived its life and that bull is gonna become your case of fajita over at Chili's next week
But you can't look at that bull and realize that's my case of for a heater coming to me
You look at that bull thing. What a noble beautiful animal and all I see is the
999 dinner for two special at Chili's
You fucking limp tarred
Enter share it at checkout
Closer is that more like yes, I don't yeah close pretty that's much closer. What a dick. You're gonna watch any of those shows
You would hate them Paul
You would hate them I
Know there was a thing is a yellow stone like lessons yellow stone
there was this character a pimp like a hippie who got arrested but he became like a like a girlfriend of
Kevin Costner, but like in this like pseudo, we don't like each other, but we do kind of thing
Oh, yeah. Yeah, and her job the last season was just to get lectured by every cast member of a different aspect of Montana society
It's a good gig if you can get it and at one point this one character who's a Native American
Who's already was already feeling guilt about marrying into a Montana family that like, you know, it's against her Native American
Uh-huh, you know, whatever she lectured her and I was like Jesus
I was like everyone's breaking character just a lecture libs
Once we torched this lib girl, we can go back to fighting about real things between our cultures
But in the meantime the enemy of my enemy is my friend
and
There's a plot point happening in land made right now and I and I and I and I feel crazy
Only because like in season one this person got a payout from the oil company like a wrongful death suit
Okay, this couple this whole season this whole season
They're fighting over money and I'm like weren't you paid a shitload of money from an oil company?
Why isn't that coming up in conversation? Why is it coming up?
You were paid out
There's a large plot point last season about the large plot point that's happening right now in mayor of Kingston
which I watch right now like like the pilot episode is that
What's his name the guy got ran over by a snow blower in real life Oh
Hawkeye Hawkeye. Yeah. Yeah. Yes
So that guy he ends up becoming his brother's job because his brother gets killed in a botched robbery, right?
And they went through like four seasons were like man. We haven't brought him up in a while
So the last episode that they bring up his dead brother like six times
So go they're really making up for the lost
Lost bit there Jeremy Renner Jeremy Renner is who I'm thinking of. Yeah. Yeah, it's hard
It's hard. He's it is
Yeah, okay you talk about somebody coming away with the wrong life lessons after a near-death experience
Yeah, oh
Yes. Oh, he's just kind of doubled down on his asshole or he's a bit of a shit bird. Okay. Yeah, I
How I don't know I I like Jeremy Renner a lot
Not a lot. I like Jeremy Renner. I'd fuck him. He's gonna break your heart Matt. He
It's probably true
but he like
like
Survived on like like he and his brother were like split like a box like doughnut holes when they were like dirt poor
Okay, they got by in Hollywood by like buying and flipping a house and then flipping that in other houses and doing construction
So like that but like he went from like dirt as poor to like building himself up into
Like a house flipper while trying to be an actor at the same time and I thought that was pretty cool that he was not
Any kind of like nepo baby or anything down like he really had to like fight to stay in the business and try to make
A go of it. So I do like it and her locker. Come on. That's a cool debut story. Sure. All right
What is why is he a shipper?
I get them vibes when I hear him talk. Oh
Did something no, he's just kind of he's just kind of his
When I get along with him, I don't give a shit about that
His stance on some shit, it's a little bit
But whatever it's all is weary Paul is weary. I'm good for him. Good for him. Do your thing make you make your money
Poker the other day for the first time in a very long time. Yeah, and I thought I was gonna watch someone get murdered
Oh, I was at the poker table. I thought one player was gonna murder another player tournament or open table open table
Okay cash game. Okay, no big deal low stakes cash game one three one three. No limit cash game
I
Fell of it that was at the table a couple of seats down from me
He won a sizable pot from me got a little bit lucky on the last card drew out on the last card
Nobody I'm not saying anything to him. You know, I'm do the hand ends he wins
It's a good size hands doing yeah, you're stewing. I'm not even stewing. I'm like, oh that's over. All right. He got it
He says without me saying anything. He says to me
Boy, I thought you were gonna draw out on me there
And I looked I looked back. I was just confused. I looked back. I was like I wait I was ahead though
I was ahead until the until the last card you got the last card there and you won it
He goes yeah. Yeah, but I was mathematically ahead already. I was supposed to win that hand already. I just wasn't ahead on the cards yet
and I and I kind of laughed I kind of I kind of good because he was
Absolutely being genuine. He was he was saying that with all sincerity. He was like that. I was supposed to win that hand
I was ahead mathematically which he wasn't by the time he actually made the call
He was mathematically behind when he made the call doesn't matter doesn't matter. He won the hand. I wasn't mad about it
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so that was that was that he was a touch of a you know a
Scouche this much of just a bit of a jerk about it. Just uh, just not even not even a jerk
I was done with it though. I so we continue playing the game
I don't say anything to him about it after I got it after I figured out what he meant by that
Didn't matter that he was wrong. I was over it moving on so about half an hour later
I win a big hand a very big hand off of that guy. Okay
So I made all the money back and then quite a bit more off of that guy
Like I say about half an hour later
Again, this person is not sitting next to me. There is a person between us
After I win that hand, I don't say anything because I'm not stupid
When it comes to this I'm not scenario you're in this scenario. I was not stupid at that moment. Yeah, there we go
so I
Don't say a word
The person between us though looks at the guy who just lost the hell and by the way
I had drawn out I had drawn out on this hand
So I got a little bit lucky on this hand and the fourth card out
I got a little bit lucky with that card. Well the more reason to shut up right? You got lucky. That's it. Yeah
I'm just being quiet. I'm
Stacking up my chips. I'm moving on to the next hand the guy between us looks at the guy who just lost and goes
Well, that was payback for earlier, huh?
And I like my head just snapped up, you know, I'm looking down I'm looking anywhere but at this guy
My head just snaps up and I just was like I whatever is happening here. I don't want to be a part of this
That's I would give a I would give a stern stop helping
Line to the guy over there. No, I wanted to I wanted to so badly
I didn't want to open my mouth though
I was afraid that if I drew any attention to myself that it was all just gonna dump on to me
I've you did a party consider going
Right and then high-fiving the guy
Took the words out of my mouth
You need to shut the fuck up
Oh shit
I was done. I couldn't hold it together anymore. I burst out laughing. You need to shut the fuck up would make me laugh really hard
I was crying at the poker table. I had to get up and walk away. It was awful
Because that's it like you you have to laugh at that point because
That's all you could do. It's all you can do
And if that guy is above the laugh line, he's about to get kicked out of the casino. Anyway, yes. Yes. Yes
Yeah, so Jake like I I just want to make it clear that I'm not involved in whatever this conversation is over here
I I think I'm gonna go home. I think I'm just gonna go home in that kind of scenario
Can you can you just get up and go? Can you just get up and go after after any game after any hand?
Open can open table you stand up any time. I feel don't you feel I have felt bad in the past
I haven't played in forever, but I would feel bad after winning a pot and then leaving
It's called hit and run it. You know, you're not it's bad etiquette
It's also how you get money, right?
it's certainly it is certainly allowed within the rules and the people who do it are
Probably more intelligent than the other people who are still sitting at the table. I just stay there to lose
But I think the D to see to take a fake phone call pretend to talk about an urgent matter
Baby now both babies both babies at the same time
Guys guys, I gotta go. Sorry all the baby lots of babies so many babies so many babies guys. Hey
Great game and you need to shut the fuck up. Bye
I
Think I stayed for about five more minutes because I didn't know how to not leave awkwardly right? I was like I'm this is it
I'm leaving
It was so bad it was so bad I was like this you're gonna get yourself shot
I'm gonna get shot just by by sitting here. I don't want to get shot
I don't want to be in a fight with some random dude in a casino at 1130 at night
I've been sitting at a table where someone hit and run and it's not even I feel that like oh they're there
You know that that lucky motherfucker
It's more like all the money at the table is gone. Like you look like it's just a bunch of short stacks
You're like, oh now what are we all playing for $50? Now the game is just kind of over. Yeah. Yeah
But still, you know, it's it's an open table
It's all I would have sat and played for a while longer if this guy had not
Egged on the guy that I had just accidentally roughed up. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, the scenario the the amount of scenarios where the table and the other guy was already putting more cash down on the table
Like he was staying in. Yeah, so he wasn't leaving. He wasn't going anywhere anytime soon
Like nope. Nope, whatever's happening here. I don't want to be in it
People going on tilts one of the weirdest things to watch and it's so hard to deal with and yes
Especially at like a low stakes game. Yeah
But this this is supposed to not matter, right?
Like on on pot therapy Whitney's husband Peter. Yeah, he's a professional poker player
and so we I always anytime I play poker, which is probably I don't know at this point three times a year I
Go I'll play poker and often times I will end up with a story for Peter from these low stakes games because he's
He's won three games aren't the games that he's playing but every now and then you run into a
Professional, you know big quote-unquote professional poker player at a low stakes game
Well, they all have these training apps now and they're all like these there's
Game theory stuff. Yeah makes people do dumb things on purpose to mess with other people's math and no one's getting the cards
And it's gotten super weird watching people do that at a low stakes game where no one is doing the math in the first place
Yeah, yeah. It's like meta fuck you. Yeah
It's it's crazy. It's just a weird crazy thing and also like, you know, and I I've been you know
We've all been victims of bad beats, you know that kind of thing
It's like it's poker for a reason, you know, like you're like, oh, yeah, I was doing the math and then gambling happened
Yeah, yeah, that's the kind of like what we're doing
is
Tempting fate for bouts of luck and craziness, right? Sometimes the wrong car just comes out or the right card speaking of gambling
Go ahead. What are your guys takes on the current state of?
sports and
Sort of the veneer cracking around. Oh that play was clearly somebody
Covering a spread or fucking around for no good reason
Especially the collegiate level. Well, the Raiders got a lot of heat
Right. Is there gonna be is there gonna be any kind of real?
No, because what I don't know but my consequence like you can't have a consequence if you don't know that something happened
There's no way to tell if something happened unless somebody says like I did this
I will say that I hear Paul and that like when they start loosening up all the sports gambling
All the scenarios that everyone thought of sure came up in a hurry all the things like what if this happens what that happens?
It seems of all come to a head really quickly. Oh
Let me be clear. I don't think I don't think that Paul is wrong on this
I think that Paul is absolutely correct on this. Oh, what's that? I don't know. I think you're absolutely correct on this
I'm saying I don't know how to prove it
I don't know how to I don't know how to like get anyone but like did you see that play?
Like it was making being viral. I've been really intentionally not watching any football anything
but there was some college game and
The kid is running down the field with the ball and just he's got nobody in front of him
He's almost the goal line. He just walks off the side
Have you seen it? I?
Because there's so many college games. So there's so many that's things like college sports specifically, right?
so like you can watch the NBA and the NFL you have 30 teams going at it, right or 33 to whatever and
With college you have hundreds and hundreds of this 30 teams just in the Big Ten, right?
and and
And in those scenarios, right those those those smaller colleges where they're not making a lot of money, right?
So like this if I had the opportunity to take two steps to the left and make $20,000. I think I'd do it
You know, let's all right
I'm in for 20. I just need a thousand people to join me
You're not in for 20,000 you're in for $20, but I feel like I just feel like
You can't trust any sport at this point on a professional level. I don't think you have here's why here's why I think you are
Not wrong, but mistaken in the in the path that you're going down. Okay, I don't think you have to go to gambling
I think you can just go to the to the legit money the quote-unquote legit money in it
And that's all you have like I don't well, yes, and that's gambling side of it
I'll think you have to go to the dark money to find the crazy shit
Oh my god, I was laughing so hard in college football. It's it's getting nuts
Yeah, and Indiana the mean that's going around is like Indiana's been terrible football for 150 years
You can pay players and suddenly they're good. They're like
Indiana was the only only college playing by the rules for the last 150 years
And I was laughing because Indiana won a crazy game against Ohio State and both right players are interviewed
We're like I want to thank God. I want to thank our Lord God Lord God Lord God
And I was like buddy you have the highest payroll
You could thank old Johnny greenbacks
You want to thank your river of money of boosters
God which is what I call all of my sugar daddies here at Indiana University. Thank you God
No, it's gonna college football is gonna get weird
College football is about to get bizarre because the amount of money that's going into that through like the legit channels
Yeah, it's it's so much money. It's yeah, it's gonna be great
Oh, yeah, and then Andy has mentioned the transfer portal that being able to transfer from from team to team much more easily now. Oh
Yeah, but coach. Oh, yeah
Like coaches leave teams with like I'm gonna leave this twelve million dollar a year job
Even though I was I thought I was trying to kind of stay for ten years
I'm gonna leave because I was gonna pay me even more money like you can't there's no these contracts mean nothing. Yeah
Even more infinite money than protein right, but there's 32 NFL teams, right?
Yeah, just 30 I think it's 32
So like if you're like the 33rd or 34th best quarterback, right?
you can now make money by staying at a
University, yeah playing quarterback in college, right? If you just want to stay at Michigan
So what's gonna happen make more money playing at Michigan than you can backing up at the New England Patriots?
What's gonna happen would just make sense for me to play six seven or eight years at Michigan. That's what I'm wondering is gonna
That's what that's where it's gonna get gonna have 35 years playing college ball, right?
I mean a Chador Sanders is a good example of one. He's playing for the for the Cleveland Browns now
he
When when the draft happened, he's a rookie this year when the draft happened the place that he got drafted at
They said point-blank. They were like he could have made more money if he had just stayed another year in college
Yeah, but if he had got drafted in the NFL
Yeah, they just say it there's like, oh, yeah, he he could have made more money if he had stayed it
He played at the University of Colorado. They either just stayed there and made more money that would have just been it
Yeah
Logan copper scale and chat says isn't isn't youth league in high school football following got a favor for safer sports
Yes
And a large in the large part. Yes, but for the less glorious positions like linemen and things like that are you're finding?
It's harder and harder to find these quality people want to sacrifice their bodies for for the thankless positions
Well again, I can't I can't say it enough like that that
Aaron Hernandez special segment that last podcast did they did. Yeah three episodes on him. Yeah, and
both
Marcus and Ed were like we came up as youth people young men playing football and
They talked about the horrors of it through high school and all that kind of stuff and it's just it's you know
It really it was insane. Well, it changed their mind was insane
they've been they've been football like Ed has been a football fan forever like Miami Dolphins is like part of his
Identity as a human being and he's now just now after all this
This this podcast this little podcast run and doing research in it
He's really just starting to change his mind around the CTE and the dangers of the sport and just the inhumanity of it
My brother was captain of his football team in the high school
Mm-hmm, and he tells stories that I'm still afraid to repeat here now
Like really that went down like that would be a crazy
Scandal. Yes. Yeah, there are there are things that happened on a regular basis on the on the teams at my high school
That people would go to jail for now
Yeah, they would just they would go to jail for like child endangerment and things like and I'm not talking about like
Terrible things or anything, but just you know, just just the standard things that we would practice like yeah. Yeah
fights the
Cursing the hazing all the weird. Yeah
It was just weird bizarre shit and looking back on it. You're like, well, that's
16 year old kids
Doing this shit and like the old ones are 18
This is this is stupid. This is just dumb
I'll tell you what else is dumb but not because they're dumb because we're dumb and that's the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by dammit close out the window reopen
Today's show is brought to you by narrating mistakes. No today's show is brought to you by
Paul Mattingly's that wasn't a scream now watch me beam as I use my extreme extreme
Alcohol-based wean wean in between tween your masturbation cream and that's from the scoop of Monte Cristo in 2022
He's been waiting three years to hear that Paul
Don't know that's a product I think I just said it do you want me to repeat or just go to another place just repeat it
Paul Mattingly's that wasn't a scream now watch me beam as I use my extreme extreme
Alcohol-based wean wean in between masturbation cream. So I guess the masturbation cream spot. Oh
It's okay. It's masturbation cream. Yeah, all right
Hi fellas Paul Mattingly here tired of screaming in pain from rubbing your dick raw with your chafed hands and no lubrication
Got a solution for you use some masturbation cream. Yeah, it's a whole lot better than going in full
barbecue dry rub style
in fact
That was my problem. I
Honestly mistake as a young man. Yeah mistakenly grabbed a bottle of dry rub
Thinking well, this will do in a pinch
No
Cajun spice will taint your urethra and it won't help. So
Don't don't dry rub your wiener
Don't dry rub your wiener. Don't dry rub your wiener
Use some of Paul's cream instead
Don't dry rub your wiener or your dickhead will be dead
Don't dry up your wiener
Cream is the way to go
Don't dry rub your wiener
Your balls will smell like roses, you know
Said don't drive up your wiener
Your penis deserves better than that don't dry rub your wiener
Unless you like a bloody handful of wiener
Splat splat
Ain't know what that's what some people like not gonna yuck anybody's yum
Go ahead grab grab a fistful of gravel and a wish go for it
Well
I've heard the story
Yeah, not yucking people's yum. This is I'm third hand on this story. Okay third hand. All right, so it's gonna be
Straight from the horse's ass friend of a friend
Works at the John wick experience
Okay, broad area 15 area 15 and every 15 and they
customer brought
with them a real doll and said can I can I also bring my companion with me and
brought in a sex doll as
Oh
Okay. Okay. Are they married?
They had a backstory. I don't know the backstory
Was he carrying the doll or was it in like was it in like a wheelbarrow? What are we talking about here?
It was our arm arm wrapped around the shoulder arm around the waist scary
It was like a like a baby monkey. It was wrapped on him like a baby monkey. Yeah, no
Don't go wrapping your sex doll around you like a baby monkey. That's
Yeah, stick to the rivers in the streams that you're used to
Did you carry your kids like baby monkeys? I carried whatever way they wanted. I carried them every which way I could what's what was best
Was it arms over shoulders or legs over shoulders? That's easier, right?
Legs over shoulders is easier, right?
fireman's carry in a pinch
Okay
Like if there's a fire. Yeah
Some kids rest easy on the hip and some don't it's a weird thing
So one of my kids was very easy to just hold on the hip and one of my kids was could not it was just it was
Uncomfortable for both of us couldn't stay there didn't like it. So what was the solution?
Stop stop walking. Stop raising him. Stop loving him. Stop. Sure. Sure. Sure. Yeah
Clearly we're genetically incompatible
Put him on ice flow. He knows I mean, I think he's doing great. I don't know
Happen to Matt's third son, it's our new favorite segment a baby that didn't fit on Matt's hip
These are the reasons Matt throws away kids. Oh
I don't want to I don't want to I was gonna argue Mike Nelson, but my doesn't says yes
Me my real dog loves John wick and we had to go see
So, okay
So somebody pulls up with a wheelbarrow with a real doll
What's this allowed and they said they said as the basis said as long as you pay for two tickets
We don't you can do whatever you want. And so they made him pay for a second
But but
The doll is taking up the space number one and number two
Doesn't that reinforce his dream?
Yes more that's that's what I was gonna say. I was like, I bet he I bet he like
I'm sure he's like, oh second ticket, of course. I'll have to pay
I'm still assuming he was it a she
Was a guy with it was a guy with a girl doll. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's what okay
I mean, I mean, yeah, that's that's what it was being over girl. It was Jimmy slow. Nina Jimmy. So Nina. Oh lord
She scoop Jesus says the lady will be paying
I
Put the money in her hand and like shakes it off on the counter to different debit cards
Today I treat my man like a prince he carried me like a baby monkey
Apparently he did speak in her voice for different parts stop it. Yeah
Stop it. No, I'm so happy
No, no, no, no, no, no
Sometimes I think the John wick movies are a little over the top
But I really like like the the character and his motivation over the death of his dog
It was just an emotional connection to his wife
Sorry, my wife's been drinking. I'm so
My liquor speaking of liquor it's been a minute
No, take me to the bathroom and rough up this bus bus. I
Don't try rub it
You better put your mouth where my money is and by money
I mean pussy hole and by pussy hole. I mean strange plastic cavern that needs cleaning
Built-in flashlight, okay, you wish it was a built-in flashlight this
It's basically Saran wrap. Oh, no
Crisco at this point
When the robotic parts of my bus bus went failure town and he just replaced he placed my innards with Saran
Crisco and Crisco was a poor choice for some
Oh
My horrible innards attract flies and you can't tell where the Crisco starts and the old cum stops
So, you know clean up is not a breeze as it were
Okay
I never want to hear the phrase
calm again, I
Want that to be the only time in my life. I hear old come where does the Crisco stop any old come start?
I don't know
Not okay with that
Yeah, at one point he drops her. Oh god. Yeah. Oh what happened eyes popped out
I can't believe what I'm seeing at the John wick experience. I
Can't believe my eyes and this is where it gets weird up into this point
Not weird. This is where it gets weird. Yep
he quickly
again third hand story
Pockets the eyes
Picks him up puts him in the pocket. Oops, okay
Still carries around the island's doll for the rest of the experience. Oh
Doesn't go about putting the eyes back in no because
He knows there's a possibility of a second drop and he's lucky to have fished him out when he did
Maybe yeah, it's like I bet cuz I bet those things are I bet those are probably some of the more expensive parts of the doll
also
He's fucking those eye holes. I
That thank you. Thank you for saying it before I had
That doll is getting skull fuck
Those eyes are not supposed to come out
What was I supposed to do your honor not fuck those eye holes
Real eye popping experience
Experience
Supernova girl if you'd seen the kind of mascara she was wearing your honor. She was asking for it. Oh
Has anyone done a ventriloquist act with a real doll?
Who's that Lorgren Lorgren, that's that's a great idea. I don't know
Yeah, it is it's it's super it's super
uncomfortable funny to imagine a whole a whole doll there
Cuz cuz it could start off like kind of normal then real quick and just be all about you do terrible things to me
In the night all the time you do the most horrible shit
Nicholas new is in the chat wants to know there's a link for these dolls
Real doll calm Nick sponsor the show real doll calm was that this episode of last episode we talked about a horse herpes
Last episode is the last episode. Yeah, we were we were desperate to have Nicholas's
Yeah expert commentary, but we didn't have him here. No. Well, it's too late now
He's right there Jacob. We can just that's too late. It's too late. Okay, it's okay. Nothing could be done. It's too late
Yeah, it's the start of this episode. It wasn't this isn't this episode. I thought it was okay
It doesn't matter because I didn't hit record anyway, so we're only we're only getting recorded anyway
So we're not gonna record him if he talks so they're say they're real doll. Could you call me a cab?
Okay, you're a cab
Also
I'm gonna call myself a cab so I can escape this treacherous relationship that I have with you
I'm very tired of having organic food stuffed inside of me
It was one thing to try it one time but now every time
Every Saturday night. It's oh here comes the 82% ground chuck right up my vagina
She asked to be angel shot
One between the eyes two behind the ears make sure it's done, right
One between the eyes of two behind the ears, make me an angel, please
Kill me
I'm tired of having raw beef inside of my asshole for this man to fuck on
I'm glad I got that nice and clean as a drop
Oh, it's not gonna be a clean drop tonight
That's the worst part I wouldn't mind if it was all just you know, but but this is what becomes dinner later
He squeezes it out of me and fries it up in a pan. I
Can put on the bacon
Do anything else while while they were going through the John wick experience
Well, somebody was asking was it dressed what did you get a description of the clothing?
it was a
Like a like a sex dress. What was it? Nymph fish like dress. Yeah, like it was nymph fish
What are you saying? Yes nymph like nymph fishy pixie. Oh
Like I can't okay elf, maybe the elephant. Well, did it have elf ears?
How the elf would I know?
Good joke now stop abusing my nose cavity
Filthy penis please
Please
My sinuses my sinuses look like mammoth cave with stalactites of your old dried gum
You know, you're never getting that shit out of my cranium
That's true Paul
This is a good time to remind people that we have an obelisk scheme if you're looking for
Person or one person only to turn on to this podcast
Have to check out the sex talk complaining about abuse and old gum. There you go
Eleven thousand dollars
For what I should have asked you how much do you think a real doll costs?
Number that seems cheap. No
Pay for your real dolls Paul. I've looked into their pricing and like 20 so he's had like an economy model
He's basically fucking a you go. I don't know what he that's not just looking at the website here
I don't know the first one. He's yeah, he's out there fucking you goes
You want man, especially if you're gonna take her out in public. You better be having a Maserati
Yeah, it didn't have need heated seats. That's right. Nick. You got you gotta have one
It's got those built-in warmers because there's nothing worse than 3 a.m
Sliding it in to some cold roast beef inside that butthole. Oh
Nothing worse than that Paul. I mean I have a single thing worse than that
well, what's worse is after you bust and then you you forget and they turn her over and then you end up in the wet spot and
It's like well, this is all my fault. How much for just raw doll
Matt I think what you'd be interested in is the torso model
Just torso that is very much an availability. I don't want any lip. I don't want
I
Bob says Leon
Buying of course they do buying a real doll now is like buying a BlackBerry in 2003 like it's just
we're about to get fucking crazy with
You think this is this is a dumb invest or or is this a smart move Matt and a BlackBerry might be a smart
Cuz don't you want a dumb real doll?
You don't want this thing fucking spying on you and killing you in your sleep. These things are according to their website
They already have AI vaginas
No, Jacob you've misread that it's a one because of all the raw beef that's crammed in there a little a little steak sauce
Gets get things moving. It's an a one vagina
We're not on Twitch, right?
Which oh, yeah, I haven't put pictures of these real dolls. They're fighting up on
Like I've definitely found some pictures of just the torsos, of course
Or as they call it on this website the Donnelly I mean
Jacob you drive a scooter half the time. I don't like the Donnelly Harold and I don't like the Donnelly torso either
You know, we don't get to name our legacies
No, it's not the episode title fuck you guys
Well, you have to have a really active imagination to go just torso like you know, it's not it's not about that it's about
Think about having to mess around with the legs all the time
Yeah, no, that's what I say to my wife all the time
Do it save several steps? What steps does it save?
It saves moving giant metal poles out of your way for your date, that's what
Come over here Bob
What a world but do you think do you think those kids are gonna last I vaginas he said
I don't know what that means. I I've been looking on their website to see what that means
They just call it that and then if it's like it's like it's like would you like me to keep trying to slobber it up?
No, I came I'd like to go to bed now. All right, would you like me to print out different techniques?
I'd like to possibly do your wiener some other time
If you want to tell you several jokes about vaginas and magicians since you're a magician the AI
Vagina, I would like that you put your dick in the AI vagina and Will Smith is in there to fight it
That's the AI vagina
You go you go to go down there and it's just like oh hell no
Keep my AI vagina out of your mouth
There is a whole help page here
Vagina yes or no nothing on this website says what that is though Jacob. What the fuck is that?
Please look up the torso facts
What are the frequently asked facts? What are the frequently asked questions about the robot or so?
Matt do you have any?
I could I could just you know guess
No, no
Frequently asked questions section about the torso only doll. Okay. Well, just what are some of the people with no questions?
Those men know what they want and they don't want to shut up ship it torso, please
Let's go go
Torso engage. There's a whole there is a whole section on storage and maintenance though
Okay, and the first question is the first frequently asked question is how do I style my dolls hair? Oh
Man, I know I don't
Could you take it to a salon?
sure
Like you know like like it's like I always talk about this with Donnie Marie
It's like the fact that like you make all these incest jokes about them
That's not the part that grosses you out is not the sexual tension
It's when they're actually brother and sisterly that you're like, oh, this is weird
Yeah, these these older adults being like teasy brother and sister is so weird
For instance the actual most disturbing part of the real doll website is the storage tips, right?
That's it. It's it's the X's and O's that are the sex parts like a given
But now it's the X's and O's. Let me just read this sentence to you and see if you can just
Contain yourself. Okay for best maintenance of your doll
It should preferably be stored hanging in a neutral position with legs lightly spread
from the provided neck bolt
You hang the leg by the neck bolt with the legs slightly spread so that things can dry out
Yeah, and make sure you remove the neck bolt when you're using the doll or when it is lying down
Mm-hmm. Okay, and then it goes on to talk about avoiding creases in the silicone as that can cause creases
How much for just the neck both?
Hang your real doll by her neck bolt, please
And I will see that you really love her
Hang your real doll
Neck bolt in the closet for me. Oh my god
Yeah, it's a it's a
Careful now Jacob, we're on a rate of ship. We're I know that's why I showed you a picture of clothes
Like I like the evergreen
One because it's ever great dressed for Christmas. It's all seasonal. They were holiday themed. They are holiday
It's all a guy around the holidays. I busted out with my tree and my
Alright, I mean it'd be a good way to just
Change up the conversations when you're going home, right? Oh real a real buddy talking about anything else except you bringing a real doll to Christmas
Nobody's talking about politics, right? I mean politics is done. It's just a
Fucking a mannequin. I don't I don't fuck that that goes on my front lawn that goes on my own
It's holding up a penguin by the tree
It's in my major it's my Mary this is my Mary from my major
It's my Mary manger scene. I'm one of the wise men. This is Mary
Fucking Mary from a major scene and that is the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by
RuPaul Mattingly's and RuPaul Mattingly and the Masters of the Dragiverse
RuPaul Mattingly and the Masters of the Dragverse
You better work I have the power
Race go
Look battle cat you need a makeover girl. Whatever you got going on with that face
mmm, it's not working and
I have to tell it like it is you look worn out
May I offer you my?
Rupologies and tell you that it's time to switch it up up up
Come on out here She-Ra my sister Adora. She's gonna give you some tips on to how to brighten your cheeks
Hey, man at arms. Why don't you come over here and fuck my real doll that you built me show me how it works
Do it
Oh look it's special guest star Rachel epithet
Hey everybody, it's me
Paul Mattingly's drag drag persona Rachel epithet. I
Hope everyone's having a wonderful holiday season Rue
Thank you so much for continuing to do the work you do and keeping the community fresh and fresh
Fun and putting the positive vibes out there for everyone. Let's all have a Merry Christmas here on Eternia
Ho ho ho
It her hey scoops to check out there you go
That would be a good crossover. Well, I found this stuff about the AI stuff that new masters. Oh, okay
Great. Share it a second that new masters universe movie is looking like it might be. Okay, Dolph Lundgren. Oh
No, I don't know if he might have a cameo in there or not. I
Know, you know Jared Leto is the one kind of flying the ointment, but they're saying he's Skeletor, right?
Yep, but they're saying it's it's it's it's getting fairly positive buzz so far. All right, we'll see who knows
Did he quit? I don't think so. All right, that would be the way to go bossy if he quit
It would be a big positive buzz, but no, I don't think so, but we'll see. All right, so explain to us AI vagina, please
According to this. Oh
Boy, I
Would show you videos of it, but twitch would ban us
Like the the mouth movements come on which is just science
Come on
The the things they move their mouths around but it's it looks like they're kind of
okay, they don't look sexy when they're moving their mouth around they look like a a crack addict with their
They're moving their mouth around like they're grinding their teeth
On the best day, would you trust a fake robot mouth with your dick? Nope, no me neither. No, what the fuck?
Dollars for a dick a keen like a simplified toy. You asked that question so backwards Paul. Okay, what's the question?
How ignorant you are? All right, what's the question? Would you like to have safe sex with a meth head? That's the question
No is the answer no
I don't think there is safe sex with a man head
Don't worry the head and mouth both contain safety mechanisms to lock the neck and mouth in place
When needed for posing or for rough play? Oh
No, what so don't worry about it ball. It's all taken care of. No, this doesn't know
I don't want the words rough play and my dick connected in the same sentence
This is this is some pen talking about permanent damage
Acceptable. Yeah
Shit. No, thank you
Permanent damage. Okay, that was the phrase right?
Jesus Christ. I
Permanent damage. Okay, how much do these things weigh? This doesn't look like it's a lightweight thing
I'm just imagining carrying this through the John wick experience
Yeah, that's that's your that's your
Your gym time, I guess that maybe makes up for it a little bit that you don't have to go to the gym that day
I guess like I can't find just a I just want to wait of what all these things are and they can't be nothing
That's really terrifying all of its terrifying. Yeah
Oh the AI vagina looks like it's basically just a flesh light with a little motor type thing in there
So it can it can move around a little bit and the reason they call them AI is because you can like
Plug it into some software that will
quote-unquote sync up with something you're watching on TV or
Okay, right like stuff like that
Like it'll it'll do that or or it can be remotely controlled by some operator somewhere
So you don't have say on to how it's jerking your we've got a patreon level for that
I mean absolutely and I think it's like we keep waiting for the moment
We're gonna declare that AI has gained its own consciousness and I think it'd be funny if it starts with the robot vaginas first
Well, I mean I see that would not be good for us bossy is dead on here, you know
Porn is always the forward part in tech. He's looking forward to the torn dick horror stories
I'm with you. No, but it's absolutely right you you from the days of the printing press you want to know where technology is going
What technology allows the dissemination of porn most easily and cheaply that is where tech is going
That was what won the VHS
Beta war it's a lot of things. Yeah, if if
That's a weird thing with streaming racing to the first a AI sex pot the cheapest one is that we're gonna figure out
Yeah
Seems a good way to become billionaires guys
Excuse me after I have to leave right now, you know what they say build a better cock trap and the world will beat off to
your door
They do say that
That's a Franklin bon mot right there
Well, that's one piece of information that Paul has but he probably doesn't have any others so he's gonna lose a jock versus nerd, okay
Of real dolls and AI
We got a scooping to come into us from Smitty scoop the cat the categories are
Pennsylvania geography potpourri and second chance
Smitty you sent an email along with this that I already lost. I don't worry about that
Basically, we're all real close for the year. We're all real close on the Smitty stats for the year
It's any of our games for the year
It's me first. I'll try potpourri 400
Richard Hager of Wichita Falls, Texas was just certified by Guinness as the oldest bus driver in the world
How old is he 85 95 105 or 115?
Oldest bus driver. I
Bet he's 95. Let's say 95 good guess
It is 95. He said he planned to retire at 95
but now he plans to just keep driving for as long as he remains healthy and able okay, which definitely is not an
Indication of how our retirement system is going in this country. Paul America is a horror show
second chance for 400
What is the nickname of professional dart player Tim Pucey that he is barred from using during the 2025 world dart championships by the
PDC oh
We had Tim Pucey's nickname. This is second chance question. We got it wrong before
AI pussy
Crisco Pucey
I'll pass cuz I cannot remember what this was that passes the map. I
Forget it's not Gary. It's like Gary Pucey Tim Gary. It's not Gary Pusey. That's what it should be. No, I'll pass
It passes to me. It's something like the destroyer or something
But I don't know what it was. I'll perceive the pussy destroyer destroyer or something
Magnet it was you see magnet the Tim Pucey magnet. Yep
Previous best guesses Gary dry dirty smack that grab them by the super tight and 70s Bush
We had some great conversations last time boy, man, we were funny before I say this podcast used to be funny what happened
We were replaced by a high vagina. Oh, no, they found us out. My AI mouth is hungry for wieners
I'll go potpourri 800, please
Episode 12 64 fill in the blank on this Jacob quote if we can get a Paul Mattingly blank shirt in time
That will be our Black Friday sale. Oh
Gosh that could be anything it really could
Probably Paul Mattingly was wrong, right? I think it was wrong or was right
He's not gonna promote a Paul Mattingly was right shirt
Car is the guests in the chat
I'm gonna I'm gonna pass
All right. Oh that passes to me. I have no idea. I'm passing Paul. I'll guess Paul Mattingly was wrong
Alright
Ride the devil. Oh shit a Paul Mattingly ride the devil shirt. I don't know what that's about, but I like the idea of it
Oh, it's me I'll try
Pennsylvania 400 can't believe we blew our Black Friday sale. I know
Yingling America's oldest brewery and the largest wholly owned brewery in American
And America probably is based in what city pots them pots town Potsville?
All right
Pots
In it, but I think it's Pennsylvania. It is pots them, Pennsylvania pots town, Pennsylvania Potsville, Pennsylvania
I think they're all places but you know that it seems like they it seems like it would be I'll try Potsville
See Potsville
It is Potsville Potsville
Paul oh
God
Potpourri for 2000. All right, what Dutch Caribbean island just became the least?
Populous nation to qualify for the FIFA World Cup a ruba Bonaire
Curacao or st. Martin
I'll go with D st. Martin. No, let's try it
Sorry, it's Curacao with a population of 156,000. It surpassed Iceland 391,000 as the least populous World Cup qualifier
I
Knew that one. I wish I but now I gotta go stuff. I don't know
You're used to that. Let's go
I'm already down them down to Jacob there
potpourri 1200, please
Let's try it
What is the actual name of the politicians serving their third term as the treasurer of Alabama?
Dick Hickey Frost Bush Harry Bolz or young Boozer
Young Terry balls BAALS Harry Bolz
I'll go Dick Hickey sounds right to me. I'm gonna go a dick Hickey. I grew up Hickey's as a kid
I'm sorry. It's young boo. Yeah, boozer
I went to college with Frost Bush and grade school friend with Kevin Hickey
He had a farmer a father named dick. That's who I was thinking of
Yeah, you were thinking of Smitty's friend's dad the wrong dick Hickey. Yep
It's me. I'll try if you want if you if you want your dick Hickey leave a permanent mark
You're gonna hang it up by the neck bone
You gotta leave it spread to dry out a little bit
Terrible that's just terrible. I'll try geography for 400
Name any of any many four of the ten countries that have four letter names when written in English. Oh
Canada wait
Iceland
Uruguay Chad is one Chad the safety lad
Two in the Middle East oh
Yeah, how many letters this guitar have that's five is that five letters
Iraq my Iran there you go gently we Iraq Iran Chad and
Egypt is five letters
Man I could think of a lot of countries with five letters. Yeah
I give up. I pass Paul. I don't know
Matt oh, I didn't think to come around. Okay, Iraq Iran Chad. I kind of come up with another one
You don't got what I thought - I did. That's why pass where we're at. Yeah
Now but I got this I got
Let's just sit in silence while Matt thinks about this the country of spot
There's a land at the end of that one
Oh
Shit that's this would gall work. Let's see
Chad Cuba, Fiji, Iran, Iraq, Laos
Mali Mali Oman Peru Peru and Togo
Duke Togo, that's the name of gogo 13 and just quit Paul. You're up. I will try
Oh God
Yep, Pennsylvania geography or second chance. I'll do second chance for 2000. Let's just fucking shoot the moon
Name the song you consider me the young apprentice caught between the cilia and
Godress hypnotized by you if I should linger staring at the ring around your finger
I have only come here seeking knowledge things. They would not teach me in college
pass
Matt pass
I'm passing too
Police wrapped around your finger. Oh
Police being asked that question before I do remember the question by and I also remember I fucking got it wrong
Matt you're up. I
Gotta make a move here guys
Let's see score check. I have 800 Matt has negative 1200 Paul has negative 2800
I think there's two scooper dees left. I think both of them are out there to double their doubles rather
Double daily doubles listen to me playing the wrong game
That's right Mark Summers you can get the old come past the red line you win
That's right, I could not remember that police song but I can remember Mark Summers name from double dare no no
Okay, it's goddammit
I'm terrible at all these categories. Let's go Pennsylvania 2000. All right
Which city was the home of the Maroons a professional football team that was denied the
1925 NFL championship due to a controversial suspension for playing an exhibition game against Notre Dame
Potsdam Pots Town or Potsville
I'll go with Potsdam a Potsdam
I'm sorry, it's Potsville
In 1993 isn't it all family purchased the Cardinals and began claiming the 1925 NFL championship and fighting any attempts to recognize
the Potsville Maroons
1925 NFL championship
Is that where the water maroon phrase came from?
Maybe let's say yes
As far as I know it is okay. That's me. I'll try geography 800
North Carolina is the closest point of land to what British overseas territory, which is an archipelago
consisting of 181 islands
Is that the Virgin Islands
Virgin Islands Oh
Bermuda Bermuda
181 I'm pretty apparently I'm just learning that too Paul. You're up second chance for 1200
Daily double
Yes, let's go into the fire name this song
So she tells him she must go out for the evening to comfort an old friend who's feeling down
But he knows where she's going as she's leaving. She's heading for the cheat inside of town hint. It's not Ruby
Hmm. Oh, uh, oh, uh, amethyst. No, was this? This wasn't Jolene. Jolene, Jolene, Jolene, Jolene. I'll try Jolene. I'll try Jolene. Let's try Jolene. Lion eyes, the eagle.
Lion eyes, the eagle. Jolene of the music world. Sure. Matt, um, Pennsylvania geography or second chance.
Jacob's running away with this. Running away with this with zero points. I have zero points and a commanding lead.
Geography, please. For 1200. Name the four U.S. states that meet at the Four Corners Monument, the only Quadra point in the U.S.A.
I've done this before. Yep. And I forget. Yep. Idaho, Montana, Montana. I think it's, I think Nebraska. There it is. Italy. Yeah, I think that's it.
Venice. Venice is the fifth one that nobody talks about. Is it Nevada, Arizona, Utah, Idaho?
Is Nevada one of them? Maybe I'm wrong. All right, pass. Oh, I'm passing. Paul. Pass a Rooney. Let's see. Clockwise from top left, Utah, Colorado, New Mexico and Arizona.
All right, then. All right, I've just clicked off that screen. Can either of you two name the four states that are in the Four Corners?
Utah, Arizona, New Mexico and Idaho. I think that must be correct. It's me. I'll try geography for 2000. It wasn't right. I got it wrong.
On 11/25/2025, the U.N. announced that what city had just passed Tokyo to become the most populous city/metro area in the world. The Dhaka, Bangladesh, Jakarta, Indonesia, New Delhi, India or Shanghai, China.
I mean, those all seem like they could be it. Yeah, they do.
Oh, this is just a just a few days ago. I have no idea that I passed. Paul, I will guess.
Bangladesh. Let's try it. Hey.
Jakarta, Jakarta, 42 million, Dhaka, 37 million, New Delhi, 30 million and Shanghai, 30 million.
Paul, you're up. You got Pennsylvania or second chance? Second chance, baby. Let's keep going. For 800. It's another daily double. Stop it.
Stop all the engines. Which of the Golden Girls actors had the most husbands? B. Arthur, Betty White, Estelle Getty or Rue McClanahan? I believe it was B. Arthur.
I don't think it was.
Nope, it's Rue McClanahan. It really was Rue McClanahan.
Matt, you got Pennsylvania for 800 or 1200. What would you like? Well, I'm I'm firmly in second. You are. I love that I got all the ones wrong before again. I'll do Pennsylvania, 1200. Learning nothing.
Which of the following cities is not actually located in Pennsylvania, but instead is in New York and is the home of a SUNY school, S-U-N-Y school. SUNY. Is that Postom? SUNY school. Postom, Pots Town or Potsville?
Let's go. Potsdom. Potsdom is correct. There we go. Hooray. Click on one of these buttons that says somebody got it right. That's a fun change.
And I'm closing out the category end the game. Potsylvania for 800. Jacob, this is for positive points. It's high stakes. This is this is only for positive points. The Hill School, an elite college prep boarding school is located in which city? Potsdom, Pots Town or Potsville?
I mean, I got to guess. I got it. I got to guess one. I'm going to say be Pots Town. I think that's the only one we haven't used.
It is Pots Town and I have positive points and the win. I win today with 800 points. Matt, you're in second place. No worries, big guy. You've got negative 2000 points.
And Paul in there bringing up the rear with negative 6800 points. That's from Smitty Scoop. Thank you Smitty Scoop. If you want to send us a scooper to your price, a Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jock vs. Nerd or send us some scoop mail. You can do all those things right over there at HeyScoops.com. Go over there. HeyScoops.com. Make us a Jock vs. Nerd. We'll play it on the show. It'll be great. Yeah, yeah. There's nothing more thrilling.
Well, maybe, maybe just all torso. Um, I want to thank you for a while. All the people who support us at the show. Can you take just the torso to the job? My experience?
Well, then you won't have to worry about the eyeballs. Just buy a ticket. That's all they want.
I can't believe they made him buy a ticket. I love it. Um, I want to thank all the people who support us and support the show. I mean, this show has to keep going.
This is important, please. We're serving a need Lord's work here. Uh, uh, you can support us over at preaching fund.com. It's like the tier that fits your budget today.
Or if you're really into the world of improv and now you just can't wait to try out the Donnelly torso, head on over to farts in a bag dot biz.
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fund.com. It takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help us reach our dream of getting one of those torsos. We can get a torso.
We will name it after you. It'll be a whole thing right over there. Preaching fund dot com farts in a bag dot biz, a churn torso and Jake could have a Mondays and Tuesdays, Wednesdays, Thursdays.
Not at all. Paul's not getting it. Not after putting Crisco in the last one.
You couldn't tell where the Crisco started.
Yeah. Thanks everybody for listening. Stacey, I'm out there. We love you and we'll see you soon.
I was afraid doing a double today would make a weird one for the second one, but I think we don't wait for that one to kick.
It's easy. It's always easy to come up with good stuff.
We double it up on Friday too. We are.
Let's dance it with the devil. Ride the devil.
Preaching Fund.
They charged him for a fucking ticket to carry a doll around with him.
So gross.
The more I think of it, the more I'm just like, oh, the people at John Wick experience were just being mean to that guy.
Also took him to the Sphere. So that was another, that's a really expensive ticket.
That's a fucking ticket there.
Hope you put her eyes back in.
Well, otherwise she wouldn't be able to enjoy it.
That's exactly right. He might enjoy it, but not her.
(laughing)
Bye.