Good clapping won't you stay with me? Just a little longer
Okay
Hello there, I am so glad you're here
I want to thank the ice cream truck drivers who are the ice cream truck drivers
Well, these are the fine folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes right now
I'd like to thank Jonathan Laurie Ellsworth Leon Kassab Malia Mike Paul's brother Pyro
Richard Dunn Sarah Boyle sex guy Jimmy D scoop. Thank you all so much. I love those people
I love them because they are ice cream truck drivers and they bring my ear holes ice cream
I know that sounds more confusing and maybe not something you'd actually want ice cream in your ears. Trust me
It's great. If you want to be an ice cream truck driver and I hope you do preaching fun dot com is where you can go
Head on over to preaching fun.com sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows?
The life you save
Maybe your own
Here's a show. Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
It I forgot to put us on switch
Yes
Ice cream social sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pittsburgh BA. That's Paul Mattingly in Las Vegas
It's me Jacob the audio guy. We're preaching fun
Hey quick announcement for anyone who might come see me in Chicago. I
Am not doing the Friday night show. I'm doing the Thursday to Saturday to Sunday, but Friday I got books
Do this corporate thing?
So I'm literally gonna leave Chicago go to Missouri and come back to Chicago and finish the run
Holy you're not doing the show in Chicago and it's a good thing
Yeah, I mean I was roses were like the I couldn't turn it down
For the for the money and I said do I have to lose the whole weekend or can you replace me for just one night?
I said we can replace you for just one night, which is very unusual. So I was very very happy
That's wonderful that they did that for you. Yes. Yeah, maybe maybe somebody was in town or something
So does that mean another airplane trip?
It do you have to go to the airport fly to St. Louis drive two hours to do the show. Oh my god
That it's an amount of money that makes that worth it. Hey, so it's fine
Precisely. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There is an amount of money that I will I will go to the St. Louis Airport today
I actually was warned they're like they're like this is gonna be just a bunch of drunk people
Fucking with you
Basically being told it was blood money. Do you want to do it? I was like, yep
I was like you make me fine with blood money a corporate paycheck before before Christmas
Certainly that sounds lovely. Do you get to bring your beers this time?
Because of that kind of situation. Oh give him actual beers. Yeah. Oh
Good point. I should just give out actual beers
Yeah, yeah, I've there are they're already what the fuck you're just I believe it's called piling on. Yeah
Is anyone in here Missouri scoop? Is there like a Missouri trash beer? That's like locally like a good trash beer in Missouri
That's that's oh, would that be like a yingling or something? Hey, that's a Pennsylvania trash beer. Thank you very much
My wife loves the yinglings
No, I think it's the answer oh
Mike Neal said in the chat just says everything in Missouri is trash. So that's good news, man. You're safe. You're safe. You're safe
I switched it in text to some other beer when we did brushwoods that one time
I forget I forget now the name of that beer. Oh, there's like large star and fart. Yeah. Yeah fart star fart star. Oh
Old style Chicago's a good it might be a good call. That's a good. That's a nice
cheap beer old style
Just go like go like oh do they still make those fucking ones with the old men who drank
Bartles and James
Do they still make Bartles and James the wine cooler? Yeah
No idea where you're going with the two old men
Do they still make Schlitz Laurie else Roth? Oh, let's
What's is all this is in the era of Pat's Blue Ribbon Schlitz is also a comedy word
Yes, let's is a great word as is Blatt's
Ranch slunk coming through with Blatt's Ballentine's there's Ballentine's ale back in the day
Anyhow, yeah, I'll figure it out. I'll figure it out Schlitz
Yes, let's is still made and is currently owned by Pat's Brewing Company. There we go Wow
They reintroduced the original 1960s formula
It's it's brewed in Milwaukee, but Milwaukee as we know Milwaukee and Missouri both start with an M. So I think that's fine
they have a
Some kind of cornered market on all the
Nasty sounding names for beers. This is classic old beers. It's classic old factory worker beers, man. They all just sounded like
bodily functions
Schafer's
Yeah, I got I got a bad case of the Schafer's. I should have I should have got the Vax when I had the chance
No, I'm not. I'm going through Milwaukee
with the with the jokers of magic I
Was there last time we built the fooler show in Milwaukee and doing Pabst at the Pabst Center was like so fun. Oh, right
I
thought it was more cool than the audience did the audience didn't give a shit, but I
Thought it was super fun
They Pabst their prime. Yep, they're perhaps they are perhaps
I finished up my f1 weekend. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. How was the rest of f1? Well, yeah, I was
basically trying to figure out the story didn't end with last time we were recording so I didn't get into too much of the
nitty-gritty details, but right the bottom line is the
They thought it'd be really funny to have two inept announcers announce some of the marquee events at the ski lodge
For all three nights at at the at the F at the Mercedes tents, right?
And a race is about an hour and a half long and having inept announcers
For an hour and a half for an hour and a half is a little is a little long
Are you one of the inept announcers? Yes
And what was it
Did you have breaks?
Yes, or more importantly, did the audience have breaks? Well, we
Eventually, we figured out yes, you know good good. So we
But it was funny was like so we we were brought in right and then we came up with all these things for all these
Characters to be I came up with Stetson barber. You can call me big Barbie
and
We were gonna do all these games and everything and
All the sudden we were at our first brainstorm session that said oh we just have to you know film something in senator Mercedes
Just so they know what's going on. Oh Jesus
Exactly exactly exactly
Instantly so I was like film what like what are we shooting over right and it was like, you know
And so it was me and Casey Wilson, right?
friend of the print of the show we love Casey Casey and
Mercedes based out of
Germany. Well, yeah international
international
Automobile behemoth Mercedes-Benz. Yeah, where's their core base? Is it Germany? I mean, they're they're originally from Germany
I don't know where they're based now, right?
Now's your chance to put on your best German and give them the kind of inept announcer
That's really gonna sell it. Oh
My neighbor. I can't believe what is happened with the car
The tires they're rolling over and over as a part holes and and the part holes are wet
Why are we so much rain in Vegas?
The rain
Mercedes still based in Germany. Yes Mercedes are going to bends the rules to win. That is what we do
So
Welcome F1. I'm your host Dieter
Exactly. Now it's the time much brackets for every race
That's that's next year Matt. You just Pete Dieter
So we're filming by the way, like Casey and I came in for like a brain door, you know a day at the office
Brainstorming session we weren't dressed
like particularly flashy or well or in character or anything and
So didn't have your you had your casual tuxedo on not your show tuxedo
And so we had different people to manage the project different people to brainstorm. There wasn't necessarily a distinct director
So we're going to make this video I was like what's so what's this video like they just want to see stuff and I was like
which stuff, you know, and so I
Kind of help orchestrate like a four phase flow to take one of the video, right?
Good and we finish and I go, okay. Well, that's the take and then I go we can we can cut up the best bits of
That maybe it maybe we'll do another run
And we'll just do fresh bits who's editing this ah, oh sweet summer child Matt
They're getting this raw they're gonna be lucky. You know what this is. It's gonna be on a flash card mailed by a UPS
And it's gonna get there in five weeks. They're gonna be like vases loss
Well, I was I was expecting you to say what are you talking about? Matt? I just sent it right that is basically
Like well, I don't see myself like editing a lot of it I can cut
That Jack Jacob we need to get you that t-shirt yeah, I don't see myself doing a lot of editing
I was like, well if we're not editing then I don't think we should do a second take right like cuz we're not gonna
We can't edit the takes together and the magic is gonna be lost by the time it gets rather second roll, right? Yeah
I've watched 20 minutes of stuff instead of 10 minutes of stuff that you know, whatever and so I
Know like and I was like, I feel like I basically I think this is a bad idea
You were you were right Matt. You were right. Your instincts
I was like, we're not really showing them what we can do or whatever and they go. No, they just want a gist of what's going on
And I was said to Casey I was like
I've never known any corporate client let alone even production companies
I've pitched projects to to show a single ounce of imagination when it comes to like what's going on
Nobody wants the gist of it
The only thing the finished product is the only thing that that kind of video does is let a middle management person say no
That's exactly I was thinking I was like I was like, that's all I was thinking. I was like, oh gosh
I might not get to do this gig. That's all it is. That's all that is. That's all that that's all they do is say no
Because they're so scared to death of taking credit for anything that could go wrong
right now
To my cruise credit they this is not their first rodeo with Mercedes, right?
So they've gone around around with them before so they kind of knew what Mercedes likes. Well, they just simply
Been like, you know, they've simply presented stuff for Mercedes was skeptical
And then all sudden it goes off without a hitch and they're and they're and they're happy and thrilled and okay
So I that's true. The company has some credit with the with the car company. Yeah
Like for example, this is a multiple times that I was performing a thing called the ski lodge
I'm sure the first time they said hey, we want to shove a giant ski lodge in the back of your
Hospitality area they were kind of I'm sure the first thing was like what what?
How does that make any sense? I'm sure some eyebrows went up, right?
And now it's like some people's like favorite part of the whole attraction
And so now the ski lodge has been getting bigger and bigger with each race and this is like the fourth race
They've had a ski lodge, right? Very cool. It's gonna be an alpine village by the time the next race, right?
I hope so. I mean I doubt I'll be a part of it, but I hope so
It's just gonna be the Winter Olympics happening and an F1 race breaks out
And
So they send off the video and then all of a sudden I get a call is like hey instead of noon to three tomorrow
Can you come from 11 to 5?
Hold on I'm just doing some some quick back of the napkin math here
And I joke I wrote the video went over that well, huh
Yeah, that did anyone I know the answer to this did anyone acknowledge that maybe we shouldn't have said that video no
Have notes we have notes no
No
No one will ever say in any industry. I don't know. Maybe they get it yesterday. I just shouldn't have done it
but this is where the
Our team our team leader was super smart. We came in I say for a long time
And Casey and I brought in stuff to look more professional
And smart smart they said let's do another round but let's bring in everyone from the office and let's do it with it with an
audience oh
That's smart. It was smart. It was smart. Oh
Because your stuff reads with human beings
Yeah, of course no
That's exactly how it is. God. It's okay. They just want the gist of it
It's so different. It's honestly. It's why I love how we're doing our recordings now with our live audience
It helps me tremendously when I'm doing my bits to see if people give it half a damn about it, right?
Sometimes they do the answer is no, but
Once in a while once
Fuck that shit, we all they're all throwing their hands up. Give me the booze
This thumbs down the camera
They're just waiting for you to put on a bikini do shots in a hot tub
That's like all like all the other twitch broadcasts figured out honestly
Only fans and just do it. I'd fucking do it. There probably is a market. I don't know
I've already got something of a user base. Maybe I should look into it
Wait a second Jacob did you just hear that in 20 seconds Paul talked himself into doing an only fans like oh you
Think I've been thinking about this just today, son
Please you started with I can't do an only fans and then in three senses says I guess I can
There was there was somebody who wanted us to do an only fans and do like a stand-up on
On only fans. Do you remember that several years ago? I don't wait
I don't remiss at all someone told us that we should do comedy comedy to us that we should do
Stand up and improv on our only fans. Oh
And I think we all had that reaction. I think we all went like, oh, all right
We've already failed to thrive on twitch we might as well add another platform that we tank on we should just do that
Hey your definition of drive
Pop the brakes we can get on every platform that is made for something else and do comedy
Just just us
Doing doing live performances where people just tell take our clothes off while we do it is the truth is that be really refreshing
I've never felt that attraction, you know that that kind of attention before
It'd be fun Matt take off your pants. Oh, wow, take take them off Matt. It feels good
Yeah, it's nice and airy. I'm gonna start pantsless Fridays
I get that I get that I would be I
Get that it would get old, you know for for any for any of our more attractive listeners out there who?
Suffer harassment on the regular basis. I'm not trying to belittle your harassment. I understand it
Maybe we get old it's just never happened to me. So it's a novelty at this
I think if you open up a channel called bare necessities, I think you'd be a hit and I think
Be good to go might be a different demographic than you're used to but I think
Hey ready to grok attention is attention and money is money man. I don't know it sure is I
Think it would be hard to you know, tell the kids don't come upstairs
Daddy's doing a bare photo shoot for his only fans like it might be a little tougher to pull off though
You're right. It would be hard
Real hard
Lumberjack in it. That's a great name
It's not a bad one. Yeah, I was like ML Kennedy. Hey Scoop starts a farmers only profile
Get my my flannels on here. That's all I need
Only flannels. How about only flannel?
flannels
No, that has to already exist, right? Maybe
Only flannels calm, let's see only flannels calm
The fuck Oh
Jesus
Something goes on there. No, that was another twitch channel. I don't know how that came up. Oh weird. That's weird
Only flannels has a twist channel already
Only flannels calm seems to be a twitch channel. Okay
So I guess that's it smart
Somebody beat us to it. Yeah, good job
Or they I'll tell you who else beat us to that
Lumberjack in it that's sweet sweet lumberjack in it
Today's show men manly's ice cream social is brought to you by
Marcus McGillicuddy's luxury abandoned homes. That's from George scoop stanza in
2024 that's a great scoop name
Marcus McGillicuddy's luxury abandoned homes. Oh
Marcus McGillicuddy. I came over to the United States
And I move to Florida here in the keys a boat a lot of luxury apartments
But they've gone unused for years and they're rotting from the inside
What what that means for you?
Value, that's right. You can get value from my open apartments what nobody's been in for years
Come on down and get your case a Legionnaires disease from my old peeps
And a bunch of mold. Have you seen those moldy spiders? What are we gotten going on? No, they've seen them
There's a cryptid spider mold what's taking them over and turning them into looking like we creepy snowflakes
Well, we got plenty of those don't we?
Come on over not what I meant to say at the top. I mean it again
Value
You won't stay for a dollar
You can stay for a dollar and I do not care how long
That's an indeterminate lease what I'm offering you you give me one dollar
You can stay in the abandoned place as long as you want
You understand as long as you want
But you do have to put it with the spiders and the Legionnaires disease and the squatters
There's already a lot of squatters in me abandoned place
I shouldn't have never bought it when I saw there was already a squatter in there
I shouldn't have done it but I did but you know, I didn't pay much
I paid like 40 grand to this guy and I got like 18 high-rise apartment buildings for 40 grand
I thought that's pretty good turns out the tax lien on him
18 million who knew? Well, I've had a done my due diligence
I would buy dinner. So don't how about you?
Come and stay and then you know, you can buy him off of me for a dollar
I'll sell him real cheap now. You do have the tax lien liability when that goes over but
Who's coming for it? I mean really?
Nobody
Nobody's coming to take take it from a McGillicuddy. You can trust me. No one's come to collect from me
No one wants these old abandoned high-rises
except for circus folk
Apparently circus folk are real interested in the band and high-rises had I had a wee lad and a fat man come over and say hey
How about we take your place for circus use? I said, I don't know
Well, you the big guy and he says yeah, I'm the fat man in the circus and the little guy says yeah
I'm the little guy in the circus and then sure enough they had a giraffe with them, too
And a monkey and a lady who could dance on a zebra's back. I
Couldn't believe it and she said I'd kind of do anything but dance on a zebra's back
I can't dance on regular surfaces because they're too flat
I require the spine of a zebra to impact my feet in order to enable my dancing
I thought that's strange in it. That doesn't make a whole lot of sense
Turns out they weren't circus people at all. They were aliens
So these high-rise apartments are very
Nice looking to the aliens who are coming to take us over
I should have known from the one day who was real big and fat and a little guy this little guy crawled in him
Like later on they crawled inside of him. Yeah, I should have known there's something fish something alien going on about that
I should ask I'm the lady who dances on zebras
She didn't have a zebra
You know, hey, she didn't have a zebra. They did have a giraffe though
At least that's what they told me it was could have been a stretched out dog
I'm not hundred percent. I
Don't know anyway, come on Bay
Try out my houses what are rotten from the inside? They're not good. I'm tired of selling the alien circus people
And her hey scoops to check out. Yeah, that was a that was a good take one
Let's let's go back to one do it again. I went from the top everybody here you go
McGillicuddy and action luxury abandoned homes. Hello. I'm Matt McGillicuddy
Selling luxury abandoned homes in it. Yeah. Look I tell you what
These homes are luxury and abandoned because they're overrun with mice
That's just the truth
Cut right to it. It's all mice
It or hey scoops a check. No, here's the thing
Not like you think it's old stuff from fries electronics
It's actual wired mice
From stem to staring
You can't swing a cat in here and not hit a wired mouse. Please don't
Don't swing a cat. Yes
Damn it
Cuz he hit a wire mouse
Wait Wayne says send that to Mercedes and we will
I've already said it it's been sent. What's this loss?
We had a giant
Concert on the stage in my backyard last night. Wait, what?
SJ is putting together. I'll put it. I'll put the picture up here on zoom and switch. SJ is putting together a new band
And so we needed
rehearsal
No, we needed video
Why we outfitted the stage in the backyard? When did I have trust now? When did you get I have trust?
this week
Now how is that fixed? Oh
It's it's clamped on right now
it's there's trust clamped on to the on the stage and there's curtain hanging from the truss and lights on the truss and
Are you looking to make it permanent or is it gonna just be no, no, that's all it's all that's all down already. Okay
Yeah, no beautiful stage in his backyard, which which the pint of plane trio used for a scoop fest the inaugural performance was
Pike that's right. Did you have the only ones that have signed the stage? I was gonna say
The new band will have to sign the stage
We haven't named to the new band yet is as yet unnamed band
What's the criteria? Nope? Nope?
What do you mean it's a what it's like it's mainly a corporate band it's
name that
Now alright, so so it looks like it looks like general rock is that what I'm saying general rock. Yeah, it's a military band
general rock
There it is. Oh my god. Would that what you say a military band general? Oh my god general rock
Four-star general rock four-star general rock. I
Don't know what I'm allowed to say about the band. I didn't I didn't discuss
press with that
Good point, but uh, but yeah, no, it's a they're there. The plan is to tour around
Probably this coming summer and get a get a lot of dates just all over the all over the United States
How about pussy bucket? I feel like that'd be a good corporate
Ah
That is one that is on the board already. It's it's high up there
It's not number one, but it is it's pretty high up there. I'm on the side between cock magnet and cock and balls magnet
Do do duo front people, okay
Yeah, yeah, that's good that's the name of the band lady song or man song
You pick
Butch and bitch present
General rock general rock is not bad what to have
Who would the the two do it to shoot out and Bonnie and Clyde Bonnie and Clyde? Yeah solid solid like
Yeah, also they were killed in Louisiana, so there's the there's the tie-in
When people are like, why is your name Bonnie and Clyde? We're like, no, no, it's okay
Bonnie and Clyde were actually killed in Louisiana, which is where Jacob is from who's Jacob?
He doesn't have anything to do with this band. It's just a guy that we know
Boney and slide, there we go
A name and then like a thing. Yeah, like a hootie in the blowfish
Yeah, I wouldn't I I'm not even being coy about it
I would tell you the names that we've already come up with for the band
But I can't think of a single one right now. All right. Well, you've already got SJ in the ruckus
So SJ is not gonna front another band with SJ in it
Right, uh, probably not. Yeah, probably not that be saying the commotion. Yeah, that'd be some more
Sarah Jessica and the commotion there. Thank you
But yeah, so that was a lot of fun and now I have a whole lot of truss that is the trust that was in
That picture is a little bit of the trust that we have
I got a whole lot of trust y'all
What I have is I have a way for us to not have to rent pipe and drape for next scoop fest
That's how much trust. Oh, that's awesome. How about this? Yeah sweet bean and the fever machines
Sweet bean
It's amazing that you say that that's already number one on the list sweet bean and the fever machines sweet
We all came up with that one
Yeah, that was basically everybody went away and brainstormed and all of us came back with sweet bean and the fever machine
Right there at the top of our list
I'm sweet bean. This is the fever machine. So say thank you for having us. Oh my god. Can you imagine if SJ got to be sweet?
Bean. Oh
All every time it's time for her to sing a song the other lead singer guy goes take it bean
When I just picture money just showering yeah, yeah so much money coming in I just got hit in the head by a quarter
How about coitus interruptus
When they decide they want to be like a corporate band is
Is there already a demand for corporate bands or is that a market that they want to try to crack?
No, no, this is this is something that SJ and one of her agents came up with this. This is a thought for that
It I'm saying corporate. It's really more like like city and city events
That kind of like when cities hire bands, you know play the riverfront. Yeah
Party, it's that it's that type of thing. Yeah
Yeah, so let corporates the wrong word. I got it. I got it city and county events type thing Chris Bill and the exact change
Oh
Puts it right out there. We're in this with the dough
Yeah, it gives a very professional
Oh Wayne does not like Chris building exact change
You get the thumbs down from waiting on that one
I think Chris building the exact change might have legs, but we'll see. All right. All right, that one's out
All right, how about a bean bean counter and the accountants? There you go
You got that going on and then you can get your sweet bean take it bean back in
And then you could do the the Dolly Parton typing song
These are the account staking account
Yeah, I'm also in the same market that's why I didn't know how much I would be competing with SJ
But I'm doing an all tap dance cover band
So everything every song we play is through the through the toes and heels to the balls over even heels of a tap shoe
Interesting interesting. How about the Louisiana moon dogs?
Paul's really trying which is weird. Are they based out of are they based out of Louisiana? No
All right, Alabama moon dogs and one of them is based out of LA Oh the LA moon dogs
Here's we got moon dogs location TBA
Okay, that's the last percent of the way there the last moon dogs
I'm trying to think of like if it isn't even like, okay
What's in the realm of possibility Paul says a combination of words that make you go to SJ and say a single thing?
What the barrier of entry of like you actually go in that state with an idea I
Don't know I do know that I have not stood up or written anything down
Like she's home right she's here she's in the building with me right now
Thousand Paul and a thousand typewriters
Speaking of tap dancing I saw
Matt's grandmother-in-law
She has a famous YouTube video clip Ruby Keeler. Yeah. Yeah
Tap-dancing on a on a giant typewriter. I saw that clip last night as
Part of a Las Vegas show that I went to
Really?
Yeah
It is a it is a featured clip in a in a show that is currently playing on the Las Vegas Strip
Wait, where?
X country
To see whatever this is
Agreed I can get you tickets
Where is X country? It's at Harris. It is in the the same room with with Colin cloud
Mmm, so it's it's the other it's the late show after Colin's show
I should know late show and Harris boys that were some bread and butter to be happening there, huh?
It was pretty full. It was a 10 p.m. Show and it was
They had the room pretty packed out
Okay, so I'm familiar with expert less because I was there back on tech person for a minute. Yeah
It's that with country music
What are the offerings of X country
Yeah, oh, yeah, it's uh, oh, let's see. What songs do they have in there? Oh, they've got
Trace Atkins honky-tonk, but don't get don't that's right. That's right. Of course. They do the course they do
Tractor
Yeah. Oh, yeah, there's a lot of songs about tractors sexy. There's a there's a pickup truck on stage
They they dance on and around the pickup truck a lot. I'll tell you what I caught a weird
Cow that's the fat
I caught weird cow aides. Yep
That's that's a toby maguire's best song
Really nobody can tell
Maguire's best song
Those those right at the show Spider-man 3 is like I gotta do something else. I'm right
It's mostly moving a bunch of moving in about
Oh
Well, the barn was on fire and so were my pants I was getting to the barn to do the sex dance
By sex dance, I mean putting my wiener in it. Oh, yeah
The cow was there and began to grin it
Yeah, I did the wiener dance right there with the cow
Like I said before it's me putting it down the others got in the way for about a minute
But then I slid to my side and I went ahead and did it
Yeah, and I got the weird cow aides from fucking the cow the weird
Now I'm gonna have to burn the whole barn down or the weird cow
He's gonna spread through the town cuz the town folks come and fuck my cows
Take it Billy
That's a person not a cow playing bass over there don't worry about that
Closely we're about to get back on the tour bus my face player and I my human face player
Cover story for bestiality
Buggery that's uttered in the puritan times. It was called buggery. If you were fucking an animal, is that right?
Yeah, so this is on a Jane Borden, you know, she puts out all these little shorts now author cults like us
We've had her on the show. Yes
Buggery is so when people were so upset that someone might have sex outside of wedlock
some people
Took fucking animals as a workaround
I'm not having, you know pre-marital sex with a human. Sure. I can fuck this animal and so they made that a crime, too
Okay. Oh
Wow, yeah buggery was the name of it though bestiality all of it. Yeah. Oh boy
Really want to fuck something beside your wife I was talking to the pig
Now wait so now out of work that these people are going to who does not fuck this house so the band is mostly rock-and-roll
Yeah
So we're good. We're back to that. We're back to the day. So we don't want like
Fucking animals to go back to this. We don't want country music type names. We want to rock and roll
like Starship or something like that
Flicky yeah flicky being in the buggery wake up SJ. Let's go look like we've had deaf leopards
So let's do another human malady mixed with a rare exotic animal
Let's just try that combo and see what okay
All right
So like like high cholesterol rabbit
High cholesterol rabbit. That's a great band name. How about how about crippled Jaguar?
Huh, I mean Jaguar can be crippled already
Blind melon. Oh wait. Oh shit. I need an animal. I know I just named an actual I did blind in an actual band name
That's what I did. Yeah, that's the joke I went for
About
Eczema koala
Fierce enough animal
Rabbit disease marsupial. Yeah, welcome to the stage
Monica copy bear. Oh
Oh, oh, oh it's gotta be um, oh shit now
I need a good one a real good real good. Ladies and gentlemen a whale with cataracts
That's actually kind of good cataract whale
Cataract whale cataract whale. I'm just wailing along. Hey
Vertical walrus and the penguin knees
Let's welcome this syphilis koala
That'd be great because the Muslim chlamydia so they've got a different disease in the mix I like it oh
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, they those koalas fuck a
Goraphobic honey badger
Mildly depressed kangaroo
We're secretly just doing Spanish job song suggestions. We are that's all we're doing. That's all we're doing
But yeah, I think I think don't worry. I've written all these down
I have sent them I have sent them to Mercedes already. They're gonna get back to us
It's gonna be great tomorrow. I'm gonna go to see
the new wicked wicked for
Wicked good good wicked for good
I'm excited about it. I'm hearing all kinds of things out there ups and downs
Some people are really critical of it. Some people are really like leaving the theaters crying. We're going multiple times. I
Think it's hard to have a sequel to a movie like that
Yes, and they and they shot it simultaneously as well, right and
The and you you lose all the credit you got from the first one where you created these worlds
You can't believe what you're looking at, right? Right. It's such a good job creating that world
Now you go making you like, you know what everything looks like and you're kind of like, okay, cool. And also
This happened with Kill Bill. Ah
When you have an awesome movie and you don't have to stick the landing but just leave a cliffhanger and people can leave a theater
satisfied with a cliffhanger. Oh
That's really that's that's a lot easier to do. That's a lot easier. I mean ask a TV writer
If it's easier to write a season finale or a series finale
Right, right, right, right. Exactly. That's a that's a very valid point. Have you guys watched smiling friends?
Smiling friends. No smiling friends brilliant animated series. I highly recommend it. It's absolutely my kind of humor. It's fucking hilarious
But they go in every season. They just got renewed renewed up to season 5
Renewed up to season 5
But they approach every season their last episode as though if this is it then this is it
They make it so that it could be the end. So they've taken that approach Matt from the jump like that's pretty smart
Yeah, I find it's weird a series
that does does this bizarrely is
Slow horses. You guys watching these slow horses on Apple. Yeah, watch a little name great. Gary. Oh my great
great band name
They always end it like
Satisfactorily like if that was the last joke you would and then they run a preview for next season
Which I find fascinating because I can't imagine they're always renewed but they run a preview of the next season
At the very end of the montage and I'm always like why how the hell do you do that? That's impossible
I mean, I guess they I guess they put that together and run it
Until Apple says you're not renewed and then Apple just takes it takes that part out. Maybe maybe yeah
And also, how do you shoot that? How do you already have it? Yeah, how do you right?
That's the bigger question is where did this footage come from? I find it bizarre
Okay, Jacob chase the blaze
Yes, there you go, that's the one that's the one chase that's the one
It's for people who want to have sex with people with STDs. Chase the blaze. Oh my god a bug chaser
Bunch has chained the bug chasers bugger chasers
Buggery buggery pittery. I only want to have sex with people who've had sex with animals previously. Oh my god
Well, that's the now Matt. You've ruined it. That's the opening song
People and vice versa how about
You're supposed to play bass not sing
You idiot utter embarrassment
Stupid cow. I mean human. Oh
And I'm married to stupid human I'm married to get on the bus I
Know I'm sorry. I had to cut your your hooves to look like hands
Terribly painful for you, but I love you so much
The only way she could play bass
Boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo
Oh
That is music to my ears music to my ears. If only it was a country band. We'd have this thing solved
Man I was where was that? Oh, well, I was doing a week of shows in San Antonio
Mainstream country music is so stupid
Hold on this is breaking news mainstream country music is stupid. There are country songs that are amazing. They're country artists are amazing. Absolutely
but the but the
It's just pop with a
Wawa pedal and they literally it's like I'm literally go like really every song has a drink in a truck in it
Every song has a whiskey and and the truck in it like all of them
Just makes me I basically I get so I'm sitting there drinking like coffee like a San Antonio coffee shop being like who can't write this
Like who like anyone can write these?
This is not surprising now Matt some of them have a wife at home who is not happy
Some of them wish they just could have done better if a couple other choices this has gone differently
Well, you know, there's some shit going on when the AI is beating them all
Yeah, but that's been a problem with all genres, but yes
Yeah, and I don't know how the hell you fix it, but Spotify is being hijacked by AI bands
Yeah
And these AI and these and these people people sitting around with AI are just making a bunch of money off of plays
Instead of actual bands I was just talking to a friend the other day he was you saying that
Doctoral what's the thing that you that you have to write to?
PhD you don't use this a face. Yeah. Yeah, yeah doctoral thesis
Betty stop guessing
the door, but
Stop guessing Betty
Yeah dissertation. Yeah, that kind of thing. He's ready dissertation
he's got it all written out and gave it to his you know faculty advisor person and
Was kind of accused of using AI yeah to to write it. Mm-hmm
and
Basically the the professor said you either used AI to write this
or
You wrote this and it feels like AI either way. You need to rewrite this
Is go fuck yourself
But the the the professor was trying to be helpful because he was like no I did write this
You know, I didn't I didn't use AI to do this
I'm getting my PhD and this is this is what I want to be doing like I'm doing this because I because I want
Want to do it. Yep. So no, I didn't have AI write this and the professor was basically like yeah
But when the when the committee looks at this if they feel like it it feels AI
Then then they're gonna hold that
That's my favorite song shut up Betty get on the bus, I'm gonna cut your hooves again
Finger up your hooves. I don't see Oh McDonald on the set list. No Betty. We can't play that song
Oh, you're such a talkie cow Betty. I
Mean person definitely a person person
But yeah, they were like, oh, yeah, I had to rewrite my whole my whole thing or like a couple of chapters in it
Or something. I don't know but it had to rewrite a sizable portion of it because it felt like AI
It is like this is this is such a weird time that we're in right now because we haven't figured that part out yet
No, and honestly, we're in that weird pocket in history where it's just a pain in the ass right now
Yeah, and college professors are using AI to ask whether or not something is written by AI
so they're doing it too and
Some some college person are using AI to read people's fucking shit and and grade it. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
Yeah, no, it's just it's just like the
Thing anytime technology happens. It takes us a while to catch up to it
I will tell you what's weird and almost like why we think AI is fascinating. Is that I think AI can be wrong and
I think definitely so a bunch of lawyers recently got like sanctioned. I think whatever it's called or sees us
cease-and-desist
Killed no murdered. No, no, but they
basically
Had AI write their legal documents and had false sources
Yeah cases whatever and then so we were putting together our quizzes for
F1 we put together breakdowns of each rate of each driver
And there wasn't a lot but there were three
Errors three lines. Ah, and so if one of them was like, can we go over all of your material before you do it?
I'm sorry Mercedes. We didn't know they were gonna send that video to you and it made up dumb stuff like they had pets
They didn't have or right fears. They didn't have
You can while you're working on on the AI stuff. There are times that you can
That you should go in and just be like double double check all of that stuff
You just told me is all of that actually correct or did you make up some of that and sometimes don't be it'll be like
No, I made all of that up
It'll just tell you. Yeah, right if you don't think to ask then you don't know that's really weird though
I guess it is I asked for a list
I was like, what are words have never been used in word. Oh, because I want to like see if I can get a word
Oh and one if I can commit to a word
okay, yeah, and
It gave me a list and the list was completely wrong. I fact-checked it and it was just like no
It just gave me a bunch of random five-letter words and said it checked two archives and it was just lying
And I'm back in the eighties and nineties
You'd get on and or you'd find an ad or something and you'd hire just like a college student
We write a paper for you or in high school or something. I was asking if Paul's writing down band names. Yeah, I am
fire listen
And he drew a logo, yeah, I don't think you can go wrong with fire lizard I
Surely not
Finest it shirts me Paul if you're drawing my kid needs a name for his three at the and he's a logo for his three
on three soccer team I
Have I have I have
My brother jingle ballers the jingle ballers jingle ballers
So they're like my holiday themed. Yes. It's a holiday theme three on three. It's great people dress up for it
Like it's a really silly. It's a really silly three on three soccer tournament
Kids are there gonna be pictures of your kids in Santa costumes playing soccer
There's gonna be a picture of their coaches in the Santa costume because I am their coach
Yeah, I'll get my tablet in a minute and I'll draw one up. I just did the artwork for this
For this month, it's coming out. Oh, yeah, so I'll get my tablet and draw up a possible logo
I have already tasked Rob with it too. So you're
If it comes in second, that's fine. Okay. Okay, that's what you got. You got a competition. Yeah
III
Yeah, cuz basically like my son's youngest
His soccer team was a disaster this year
Okay, a couple kids got injured a couple kids quit
Some kids would just not show up. They regularly played without like enough kids
Like one kid down my kid would play the entire game. It was a brutal brutal season
So when the three on three came up, I was like, oh
Let's get the five kids who showed up all the time who had and let's put them in a in a three on three together
Yeah, have them play
One one one one a proper finish to their season instead of just constantly getting clobbered by other teams
The five gives you a pair of subs. Is that is that what? Yeah. Yeah, you have up to six and you saw
You sub like crazy and three on three
Okay, and so I was like, let's do it and then the coach who had finished his last evening coached like seven seasons
Was like I'm not coaching again. So I said I imagine you don't want to come out of retirement and he goes no
I do not I said, okay, I said I will coach this team. I'm gonna tell the parents
I have no business coaching this team, but I will coach this three on three team. That's nice, but I'll do it
That's really good of you, man. Yeah. Yeah
So yeah jingle ballers jingle ballers. That's a I didn't want this to become a democracy
So I simply said hey, do you want to play Hilly wants to play a three on three tournament?
Do you want to join him?
He's named the team the jingle ballers because I didn't want anyone saying anything else. I was like it's not up for debate
There's no conversation. It is the jingle ballers. That is that has happened. He was debating that and the snow devils
Snow devils much easier to logo
Jingle ballers will be fun jingle ballers is funnier. How far can we go on the?
innuendo scale
The the Tina one last year they were just called the hard penises and they had a big giant cock
Lots of veins. Yeah, but the the the testicles were soccer balls. That was what made it a soccer
Thing jingle ballers. That's what I'm thinking already. I'm like
Well, they showed up to the game in an Oscar Meyer wiener mobile that they had repurposed into just a giant penis
They painted they painted they just all you got to do is paint veins on it
Just like that boom becomes the cock mobile just dragging to Christmas ornaments for balls behind it like like they just got married
When I say hard you say penis is hard
So, yeah, I guess
They're ten. So use your best discretion. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I got you. I got you. They're ten
So they've only seen ten years worth of internet pornography
Just right keep that in mind, man
I just I think about this every once in a while and I do think about that
I thought about it too when when I accidentally gave Matt's kid a comic that might have a boob in it
But it was a circle in a circle. I like that that's moved accidentally now it I mean it was accidentally
Also, I don't care but also
but also
If I were a child man, I've got a box of hustlers for your kids if I were me at that age
Cuz I remember the kind of bullshit links. I went to to see pornography at 11
We had to go to the woods or somebody's house with a weird older brother
You know or whatever we also watched
in a group
Absolutely, right, which is absolutely weird when you think about it or yes weird now
But like, you know, can you imagine a bunch of guys like gathered around now to watch internet porn around a computer?
It's it's a different feeling. It isn't I imagine it. Yes, but there's no way kids of this day and age avoid porn
You can't turn on a computer. It's it just it's in your face. I think about this like what like because like all our
Our TV apps right have different profiles and the kids have kids profiles, right?
Yeah, and then the kids but the kids know my password to get to my of course file
Right to get to the unrestricted and then I'm like, oh maybe I should change that or do something about that
Then I'm like the least of my concern is them finding stuff on like HBO
Right, like right when they have access to shit. They saw Daenerys's tits
They got on them on the max app and looked up old episodes of the Red Shoe Diaries, oh
That's the thing real sex Red Shoe Diaries. Those are all gone
Those up anymore, right
Now the question is like so because right now they say it's basically a huge problem is that kids
See so much porn before they actually have sex themselves. They get desensitized and weirded out by it. No, they feel
They feel well, yes, but they they feel also pressure to imitate it or that they they want to do like
Porn sex constantly. Yes, right
Like the first time you know when they're losing their virginity. They're like when should I spit into your asshole, right?
Yeah
Do we do we gape now or gape later? Yeah
Like that was my first question. There it is
President Cooper star that's exactly what I came up with. Oh, that's scrambled porn. It was exactly my life
That was absolutely my oh man scrambled scrambled TV porn scrambled TV. Porn is a great name for SJ's band and
It is a good name
Yeah, but basically they're trying to do all this crazy stuff and not enjoying it yeah, yeah
That sucks. That sucks. Yeah
But most people most the good thing about that is I have to have a speech and I'm gonna have to have a speech
they're skipping from age 17 to age 48 and
That's because that's the time when you kind of enjoy sex and after that. It's just like
47 so it's like oh, I didn't realize I was a fucking cuss
Yeah, you're knocking on his door
I'll tell you who else is aging where is edging while they age
That's the following sponsor edging while you age edging while you age
Hold on. I was I lost the commercials. I was looking up buggery
Sandstorms warning systems brought to you by day rude. That's from country scoop in 2025. That's
sandstorms warning systems
right
Hey everybody I I
know many of you out there live in sub-saharan areas and
Places where there's not a lot of rainfall and in fact
there's a lot of dust Vegas is known to occasionally have the
how Bob
Come in from time to time. I believe that's how you pronounce that
How do you say that Jacob how Bob?
Well, everybody knows for those cows on base a sandstorm
You don't want to get caught unaware of a sandstorm no, so we've provided this
sandstorm alarm
All you have to do is install it directly into your ear
It will block out all sound except for the sandstorm alarm, which will only go off
in case of a sandstorm
Did you do do you will know shit? Oh shit?
Wet rags good name for man
Better hey scoops to check out that was Paul. I can't believe you just teeing it up
You everyone knows you superior with the do do do do do noises than I am. I was taking my time with it
I wasn't getting there. No shit
What I mean, hey, I
Buddy balls like talk about we're doing two episodes. Let's ride this pony
Look talk about you talk about the kids watching the sex stuff. It's called foreplay son
For play you got a teeth all bet you got
My foreplay last month sometimes
My resume my roger over 48 breaking news Myra loomerage is upper upter patreon. Thank you Myra
Yeah, I think you're much and the the new sandstorm alarm
Sandstorm alarm you think finally they're providing a service that I need alert alert
You guys want to a little Jack versus nerd more than I guess we have to stop coming up with bad names
We're doing a whole other person I feel like it would be a runner
Yeah balls
Jacob I got I got a thumbs up from Matt blows in the band names rainy Marys
The rainy Marys. Yeah, Jacob. We're gonna scoobity come go to SJ be like Matt and Paul think this is a good
Yeah, please. Please did actually bring bring SJ on next episode and we'll hit her with all these bad names
Help us fill in the second episode
Matt Paul has some band name ideas that he wants you to take to pen and see what he likes for SJ's band name
There we go. Let's be fair. I haven't asked Matt to run anything by pen in like days
Since the beginning of the show
Scuba-tron the categories are the beards
Tissam TISM butterfingers and random Aussie music. Okay
Great. I'll start with the beards for 200
The beards are an Australian comedy folk rock band formed in which ICS famous city Perth
Sydney Adelaide or Darwin. Ah
I think the most famous
Australian ICS city is Adelaide. So I'll go with that. I'll go with number three Adelaide. It is Adelaide. Nice guess
sweet Adelaide
Yeah, I'll go with the TISM for 200
How many current band members are there according to Wikipedia by three five seven or nine?
Boy in the band called TISM or nine and TISM
Shit I'll go with seven three. All right
It's seven. Hey, look at me. Good job
Matt
Paul and I are both off to rock us starts Jesus. This is gonna be tough
I'll take what's TISM mean. I'll just take TISM. We don't know 400
Which song is not on the album?
WWW.TISM.WANKER.COM
Which song is not on that album Matt? Okay. I
Might be a cunt, but I'm not not a fucking cunt
Been caught wanking a hard-earned thirst needs a big cold beer, but I drink to get pissed and
Greg the stop sign
This is a great question, I like a song called Greg the stop sign a lot
The stop sign I'll pass
Passes to me
Let's see the album
WWW.TISM.WANKER.COM
The big I think I think hard-earned thirst needs a big cold beer, but I drink to get pissed. That's the opener
That's the that's the number one track
It's not the money spot, but it is on the single spot, but it's the it's a hard-earned opener there
I
Might be a cunt, but I'm not a fucking cunt. I feel like that was on their earlier album
So that's what I'm gonna go with. I'm gonna go with I might be a cunt, but I'm not a fucking cunt
Now it's Greg the stop sign. Oh wow that one sounded legit to me
Greg the stop sign
It's me. I'll go to um, that uh, that means that's wide open. We can write Greg the stop sign on our own
No, we can have our own here. It's true
I wrote to some for a 600
Which of the Tism band members was credited only as dancing until?
Ron Hitler Barassi
Eugene
Delahot Croybon
Le Miserable and
Vladimir Lennon McCartney the second
I don't know believe it or not. I'll pass
Paul pass I have no idea
Matt my guess is Ron Hitler Barassi
Let's try it
I'm sorry. It's a little bit. Damn. It's let me the rob lice
That means Ron Hitler Barassi is wide open. We can take out a chance. We could take it
Paul
Butterfingers for 200
Daily double. Oh my god. So this is all like Ozzy bands, huh? Sure
Where did the song fig jam chart on the hottest 100 in 2005?
11 7 17 or 71 11
It's 11
Well done boom good job Paul
Hey, yeah, we actually have an Aussie guest in our next episode
We should maybe we could have saved this for them
Although too bad Wayne Geo's in chat saying he doesn't he hasn't heard of any of these and he's he lives there
So there you go. Well, there you go
Matt you're up
well
I'll go with random Aussie music for 200
Which 1970s famous rock band just finished another tour of Australia as of November 20 25. Oh
This is easy. This is only so many 70s rock bands
It's got to be the who are the stones
Those two famous Australian rock bands the who and the Rolling Stone
They're Australian aren't they? No, I think Paul's right. I think I think it's not I think it's a 70s rock band from here
Just fished on the tour of Australia. Oh
But because I'm confused I'll pass
That passes to me. I was just gonna say that the old Aka Daka the old AC DC. Oh, that's probably right
I'm going with that. It's AC DC. Yeah, he was right. It was an Aussie band
Aussie band touring Aussie
I'll try the beards for 400
Which of these are not a Beards band member?
Nathaniel Beard
Facey McStublington
Johan beer driven or Tom beard man
Tom beard man is not real all those others are fantastic. I think it's Tom beard man
It's Tom beard man. Wow
Wow
My answer was right. My logic was not Paul. I'll close out the tism
For 800 tism is an acronym for what?
This is a great question. This is stupid music. This is serious mum. This is so melodramatic
This isn't super meaningful
who
I'm torn between one and four
Okay, so you're between this is stupid music or this isn't super meaningful. I'll go with four
All right. This isn't super meaningful is
Incorrect. Oh both of yours. We're all you this is serious mum. It's a serious mum. You were barking up the wrong tree
Matt
Gosh there's so many places to go where I feel confident
Butterfingers 400. All right
lead vocalist evil Eddie performed for how many weeks solo unintentionally before scraping together the rest of the band a
one two three or four
pass oh
You don't know that you don't know about evil Eddie performing solo
No, you're no, I'm passing to
Paul
Four. All right. It's two
It's me I'll try random. I was so close you were you were just a couple off
The song Eagle Rock by daddy cool was the inspiration for which Elton John hit
Gotta be crocodile rock. I could be gotta be crocodile rock. Yeah, I'll say crocodile rock
Yeah
Paul butterfingers for 600 the band the band has been around since 2003 and still performing now
What year was their latest album release?
2022 1997 2020 or 2025 I'll go 22. I
Like the band has been around since 2003 and one of the options is 1997. Oh
I'm sorry Paul. It's 2020. Oh, wow. Wow, you put an album out in 2020. You did you do some work
Hopefully it was early 2020. They had what real early they had a very safe bubble. Yeah
Matt you're up. Uh
You got the beards butterfingers or random Aussie music
You and Paul are both in the negatives. I have 800 points Matt has negative 600 Paul has negative 1400 wharf
Random Aussie music for 600, please
Daily double
The greatest music countdown
Get back on the bus. Damn it
The greatest music countdown every year in Australia is the triple J hottest 100. How many years has it been running?
36 28 32 or 39
Those are all within a range
They're so close just in case you're vaguely familiar exactly I was thinking it's like 11 year window
It's a daily doubles I have to guess yep
Well 32 is a magic Johnson's number and I like him from basketball I go 32
I'm sorry. It's 36
Magic Johnson's least favorite number. Yeah. No
Yep
It's me. I'll go. I don't know do random Aussie music 800 do good. No, we gotta go guys. It's a sandstorm
You're so it's so good you can do the tongue thing
Exactly
with total of
1177 studio albums Aussie rock band King gizzard and the lizard wizard released how many albums just in
11 7 2 or 5
These guys are like guided by voices
Yeah, they put out a ton of shit, but better. Oh no pop pump the brakes son
pump the brakes
I'm pretty sure this is five. I think I think I listened to five different King gizzard and the lizard wizard albums in
2017 sounds right to me
It's fine
My guesses are going well today Paul
Butterfingers for 800 in
The song yo mama at what position is yo mama on the things to do list?
Is is she on the top of that list on the bottom of that list?
After breakfast or not at all after breakfast
I'm gonna get the yo mama after breakfast
Nope on the top of that. Well, she's on top of the list. Holy shit breakfast right before breakfast. Oh
It's the most important meal of the day
Take cover everybody
Got the beards for 600 or 800. I don't care. You get the $800 when correct
No, you will still be in second. I don't care. I don't care Jacob. Just pick one
Which of these beards hits did not get a single if your dad doesn't have a beard. You've got two
All the bearded ladies, I'm growing a beard downstairs for Christmas
I'm growing a beard downstairs for Christmas and you should consider having sex with a bearded man
Which of those did not get a single Matt? These are really funny
pass
All that passes to me
Sadly sadly you should consider having sex with a bearded man did not get a single so that is that is the answer. Let's see
If your dad doesn't have a beard, you've got two moms
Perfect
And I'm closing out the category
for 800 in 2009 the beards traveled to
Where to perform for the opening ceremony of the world beard and mustache?
championships France Alaska Austria or Germany
Okay, I'm gonna take Alaska out of the running sorry Alaska
It is cold it's also a state and not a country in the other three or country each
Oh, yeah, I must say Austria. I feel like Austria
Would have some fascinating mustaches and beards
Nope, it's Alaska. Oh, I
Was exactly wrong. That is the game
I will now with only 200 points Matt's in second with minus 1200 Paul's in third with minus
2200 and that is from the scuba Tron. Thank you so much scuba Tron
If you want to send us a price of striped jock versus nerd an obelisk jock versus nerd or a scooper D
Just like the one you just saw head over to hey scoops comm right there on the home page
Make us any of those things send us some scoop mail do all the things over there at hey scoops comm do it now
Do it now get the chopper get to the get to the screen
Get to the website get to the website do it now, honey
Love the other chat you should you could consider you should consider having sex with a bearded man is still better than 90%
of my opening tinder messages we talk about this with like
Used to used to be able you used to have to call
Someone's parents before you spoke to them when you were man. That was exact. I was just thinking about that the other day
I think about that today thinking about how I called a girl to ask her out to prom and I had talked to her mom and dad
I was like, what the fuck is my wife?
And she said no
Did you did you fuck the mom and dad?
well, I asked the mom if she wanted to go to prom instead and she said I
Don't want to go to prom, but I will take you to the motel
Hotel holiday in yeah
Moveover. Oh god, you're a cow ladies
But but but people aren't taught how to start a decent conversation
So they say just rude shit
All the time on these on these websites
anyhow
That's old man still shaking fist. Okay. I want to think the following people who knew all of the answers to that that scooper
Do they knew all of them?
They know they're Australian rock. That's Laurie else Roth Lee Drummond Lee forest lemurs screamer creamer Leon Cox
Leon Kasab little red Linda Brandmeier
Lorgren see Luke Mellon M Hertz macho scoop Randy sprinkles. Oh, yeah
Much. Oh mama ninja scoop maple raisin scoop
Marble tulip scoopy tree Mark Sadowski Mario Rosa and Mark Cohen. Thank you so much
If you add the words aging panther to the beginning of these names, they're all fantastic
possible band titles
Mississippi churning scoop
Mizzoula, I was probably Mississippi churning scoop Mizzoula
Mohan Nair
Aging panther monad knock scoop. See what I did
Panther Monica day
Motor City Smitty
Aging panther mr. Head scoop. My god, it just rambles off the tongue. Miss Johnny, Australia
Natalie Wow, what happened to my fucking thing Natalie McGillatine Natalie McGillatine. I like that
Nathan clay Nathan hooten neck pubes
Neil appolitan Neil Fleisch
domestical scoop nice private parts
Nikola Petty
Nicole
Nicole busen back
Aging panther Nicole Levin Nikki Benoit
Okie scoop one fell scoop Paul Hoser scoop and
Aging panther Luxton
All right, the following people all saw the 10-minute clip from Mercedes and they have notes
That's mark Dryden mark gates mark Matson mark pickenheim mark Wilson matcha ice cream sundae
Matt scoop of fail Matt aka Stormageddon Mackle wacky Matt McKenzie max the ginger scoop McTits
Malia Melissa Arachiga
Michael Michael Calder Michael Martin Michael Shaw Michelle Yizer Mike Mike federally Mike six Mike wins and
milkleg scoop
The following people refer to their business as outdoor stage pipe and drape Paul's brother Paula
polygon PE scoop
Peb cack scoop Pete Romano
Peter bougie Peter Buford Peter Heinz Peter McDougal Peter sands own petty officer scoop
Phil Rendley Phil Tomlinson Philip Guyton pick it up. Pick it up. Pick it up proper scoop and
Proto scoop. Thank you. And the following scoops are all patient
They're not patient zero, but they're like patient 3 through 16 or so of a cow AIDS. It's true pyro
That's quite quiet scoop radioactive scoop raggedy girl Ralph Ralph Barrett Randy Randy Lin
refrigerator Perry scoop
Remember the Allah mode
Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church of the Flying Scoop Eddie monster Richard Dunn
Richard fast not Richard graffiti Richard Hill Robert Paulson robots Ahoy Rodimus scoop Roger edge Ron heck Rose Ryan Howard
Ryre Appledorn Sackett mingle salt lick scoop Sam Reed Sonya Petrovich
Sarah Boyle sax guy Jimmy D scoop scabby the rat scoop scoop Brady scoop Bucky scoop Chang Beijing bugle
Scoop Dave ill scoop Emily scoop it real good scoop de jour scoop Jesus scoop Lindsay scoop Lord Tristan
Scoop Mepha and scoop nurse. Thank you all so much
Thank you all great. If you want to be thanked on air for being a great person
Then do so by sending up over at patreon.com slash. Hey scoops. Oh, what a mouthful go to fun com
Or if you think that sweet bass playing cow and Matt should just be allowed to live their lives
Head over to farts in a bag dot biz
No, no, I was wrong get back on the bus
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm it takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as
$3 a month you can help keep this show alive you can head over there
We are supported almost entirely by our patreon
So if you go over there you will literally be helping keep this show going if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars
Preaching fun calm farts in a bag dot biz. That's where you can go
All right, well, thanks for everybody stay safe out there. We love you, and we'll see you soon
Oh
They said it would be ridiculous to build a stage in my backyard they were right
It's kind of fun though we're preaching fun
See ya your stage looks so cool though
- It does. - That's great.