[Music]
This is the part of the show where we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
I'll tell you what guys, I am going through these lists.
I am so close.
I'm really close to being able to thank each and every one of you by name this month.
And by the next episode, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna thank each and every Ice Cream Truck Driver by name this month.
At this part of the episode, don't you worry all you Ice Cream Truck Drivers out there.
Who are the Ice Cream Truck Drivers you may be asking?
Ready to buy a car, a home, or just want to take control of your money?
Your FICO score matters and 90% of top lenders use it to make decisions.
Check your FICO score for free today without hurting your credit score.
Visit MyFICO.com/free or download the MyFICO app today.
MyFICO gives you the score lenders use most plus credit reports and real-time alerts to
help keep you on top of your credit.
Visit MyFICO.com/free and take the mystery out of your FICO score.
Life you save may be your own.
Ooh, a show.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Are we on Squish taken?
We are on Squish.
Oh, hello.
Hello, Squish.
Ann advised me to raise my computers.
All the problems are solved.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social.
Sitting over there in Las Vegas, it's Matt Mattingly.
Sitting over there with a nice raised computer, it's Paul Mattingly.
I'm Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're preaching fun.
You don't want to go chin gut first to the audience, Paul?
I mean, I can do whatever is going to sell the tickets.
Whatever is going to put butts in seats.
I know some people are here for the chin gut.
I'll tell you, now I just have to find a more permanent solution.
Because right now, the computer is balanced on a big stack of DVD holder bags.
Oh, no.
Bags?
Bags.
What do you mean bags?
So these are what I got.
What's a DVD holder bag?
This is a DVD holder bag.
Oh, like a CD wallet, a big CD wallet bag thing.
Sort of.
But it holds DVDs.
I see what you mean.
I'm trying to describe it for the audience who can't see your crazy thing that you have
your computer balanced on.
It holds whole DVDs.
I've got a stack of five of these in another bag.
And then on top of that, I have precariously rested a box of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
little figure people from Fisher Price on top of that.
You don't have books?
In another box.
I do have books.
But I feel like, you know what's funny, Matt?
You know what's funny?
That was my first thought.
First of all, right next to me is where I keep my stack of--
So incredulous.
Well, I keep my stack of improv books right here next to me.
Yes.
OK?
I just happen to take all my improv books.
Should I use these books?
No.
No, I took them all.
They're in my backpack.
I took them all to class for my first class on Monday to show everybody what books to
check out if they're interested in looking up more improv stuff.
So I don't have-- but here's the other thing.
Here's the other thing.
Nice.
Stack of wires.
I do have a box of wires.
It's a box.
Just don't worry about what's in the box.
It's a box of wires.
It's the box that matters.
Well, I've got a box of wires right down here that'll work.
Matt just shifted his camera so that we could see a clear box filled with some electronic
doohickeys that he has just sitting in his office.
It's all my audio equipment for any kind of podcasting.
Yeah, I've got--
It's an excellent box to set a laptop on.
If Matt needed a box to set a laptop on, I'd be like, Matt, use that box right there.
I didn't notice what was in it.
I'll have to do that.
Unfortunately, the space here is limited.
I'll figure it out.
But I do need a box.
I'm crazy, I'm a box not bags guy when it comes to putting valuable equipment on a--
But I'm also a bags not books guy because for whatever reason, my brain goes to, oh,
but what if I need that book?
I'll send you some of my magic books that I've never cracked.
I'll send you some of those.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
I have-- do you have sentimental books that you keep in your home?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
I have several sentimental books that I keep in my home that I can't imagine ever reading,
but they were given to me by family members--
Oh, that you never read?
--or something like that.
Oh, yeah, I have something I never read.
Oh, no, I don't have any--
My uncle was an automotive expert.
Oh.
He would go to court and testify for-- I'm really not exactly sure, so I'm telling you
kind of what I understand.
Was he the one behind unsafe at any speed?
Wasn't that Ralph Nader?
Yeah, it was Ralph Nader.
Oh, OK.
No, that was Ralph Nader's fault.
Ralph Nader?
Holy shit!
Jacob Nader?
I did have an aunt-- or I guess I do-- who worked for Ralph Nader.
She used to be like his chief of staff or something.
It's all coming together.
What a tangled web we weave.
We have technical scoop port in the chat here.
It is technical scoop port for a living.
I'm wondering, do you ever have to address what people are putting their computers on
top of as a technical scoop port person?
Yeah.
He says yes.
He's nodding.
He's just nodding with-- all the time, he says in the chat.
All the time.
So people's computers just fall off of things all the time.
I've put on a series of delightful pillows, and now I'm having difficulty operating my
computer.
Oh, have you ever had the thing where they--
Perfectly balanced.
Have you ever had the thing where they stack the laptop up on pillows and everything, and
then the pillows clog up the fans and the laptop overheats?
Right.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's happened to me.
I had them--
Just blocking up the fans.
I had it stacked up on a bunch of bananas.
Yeah, there you go.
And the bananas went south of cheese, and then my laptop got infested with fruit flies.
So--
So you have a record.
Paul, say that sentence again.
Well, I--
Or the--
I stacked my-- no, I didn't really.
I was playing.
I would not stack my computer on well-stacked bananas, let them go to rot, and then let
the computer--
Bullshit.
You would not do that.
I wouldn't do that.
No, no, no.
If you came into this basement, I will tell you what you would not find.
Any food or decayable items outside of laundry detergent and a bottle or two of diet soda.
That's it.
There is nothing--
What about small rodents?
What about swirls?
Everything else in this basement is plastique, baby.
Plastique.
Plastic or pressed wood.
That's all that lives in this basement.
I'll give you some pressed wood.
When all-- when all the kids left my--
All my shelves are fucking pressed wood.
When all the kids left my birthday party, I took all the leftover balloon animals, put
them in one pile, and I put my computer right on top of the old balloon animal.
Let it heat up.
Really propped it up well.
Paul.
No, I have books about like auto accidents and stuff.
My uncle used to go testify about auto accidents and like tire marks on highways and that kind
of thing.
He was one of those types of expert witnesses.
It'd be like--
So I've got books about that kind of stuff.
Well, Your Honor--
I'm like, I'm not going to read these books, but they're cool.
They're--
Your Honor, clearly the victim in this crime was a worthless piece of shit because there
were no tire marks in front of where he was struck by the vehicle.
He was clearly not even in an automobile.
Your Honor, clearly denoting him as one of the poor.
One of the poor.
One of the worthless piece of shit poor.
One of the poor who the law does not apply to.
One of the poor.
All right, Matt.
What did you want to know?
Well, I'm just saying, Jacob's uncle was trying to get him paid.
You know, you get paid to testify in court when you're an expert.
Oh, yeah.
No.
Sometimes, yeah.
He was a paid expert witness, for sure.
Making that money.
Making that dollar.
He worked for LSU, and he was a paid expert in those types of cases.
Now, he wasn't working for the big auto people, was he?
No, no, no.
He was a university professor at LSU.
Oh, so he was standing up for the middlemen.
He was an independent expert.
He would come in and testify for, like, yeah, just testify to the facts of an auto accident.
Leon piping up in the chat that he has to pay quite a bit for his expert witnesses,
so he would know.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
So Paul.
Yes.
I'm going to tell you a story that's going to make you too messent, buddy.
I've got a feeling about what it is.
Go ahead.
Tell me.
So I was going to mail some things out yesterday to the UPS store nearby my house.
It's actually totally random.
Someone reached out and said, "Hey, this is a crazy question, but I guess this is what
Facebook is for.
I think I went to one of your comedy shows in the '90s, and I bought one of your shirts
that said possible side effects, but said free sex."
Oh, yeah, yeah, the one that says two different things depending on where you are.
Yeah.
If you look in our store, the salt pork shirt is based on ...
Yeah, we modeled it after that.
And apologies to Mike Nilsen for using UPS.
They're closer, buddy.
FedEx is all the way up on Stephanie.
Anyway, this is a side note, but yeah, yeah, so they reached out and I was like, "Oh my
gosh," and I was like, "I don't know where those shirts are," and I go, "You know what?
I have a box of old shit in my garage.
I bet I have one in there," and I looked into my box and I found my last free sex possible
side effects shirt, and I thought, "Well, it's sitting in a box for me, and this person
wants it to wear or hang up," so I went to the UPS store to mail this person the shirt.
That's very kind of you.
So a part of you decided that you didn't need to hold onto that for the future Matt Donnelly
Museum.
Yes.
Go ahead and just give that away.
Okay.
Matt at 47 looking back at the t-shirt he made when he was in his 20s is a fine length of
time to remember that time.
Yeah, I agree.
Ever since I showed Paul my rig, slowly my laptop's been sliding into my lap, so I'm
going to do this again.
Oh, and yet my DVD bags remain solidly steadfast.
How strange.
All right.
Time in scoops.
Team bag, team box, team books.
Let's go.
Paul was right.
Get more bananas.
But it wouldn't have done it unless I showed you my thing and I put everything out of my
arrangement.
It's a poor craftsman blames his tools, Matt.
I'm so happy right now.
I was so close.
I ran out of time.
I was so close to adjusting my monitor setup in my office here before we started today.
And I'm so glad I didn't be falling over right now.
I right next door to the UPS store is the comic book store.
Oh, yeah.
And I was like, man, Paul got me that absolute Batman trade.
You hit it exactly the right day.
Serendipity.
Totally.
I didn't realize it.
I walked into the complex with the day it came out, the day of volume two.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I gave absolute volume to absolute Batman.
Yeah.
Oh, crazy.
I walked in and he was like, hey, what are you here for?
I was like, you know, I got some curious about absolute Batman goes on.
That's right.
That came out today.
And I go, I didn't realize it.
I literally just happened to be mailing something next door and he's like, yo, yeah, no, it's
a great book.
Are you enjoying it?
And I want to be like, look, we can do small talk, but I am not one of you is what I really
wanted to say.
Right.
But I can't jump in, like stop him and explain to him, be like, no, no, I really didn't know
until it was coming, I was like, oh man, I don't, I was like, I was like, my kids come
here because they're in the system.
I was like, maybe because my kids come here because children buy comic books and um, uh,
and so do well educated men and women and people of indeterminate gender or whatever
they want to be.
He pulled right ahead, he was like, you closeted nerd and he just, he just dove right in.
Yeah.
Good for him.
He knows he knew you.
Yeah.
One of us.
Okay.
And, and I said, it's really my podcast partner who turned it me onto this thought bond.
He goes, oh, what's your podcast?
I gave him a chip that last time.
Well, Paul, so did I, and I, I'm just saying I went in, chipped him again.
I took him again to message Paul.
I am he as like, so I bought an absolute Batman.
He said there were two other books in the series that aren't included in the trades,
right?
Art, art cam and some other adventure.
And I bought those.
Wow.
Look at you.
You're even deeper than me right now.
Oh, he even upsold you.
He upsold me because here's what happened.
I flew on frontier and that's a hell, that's a hellscape that humans don't deserve.
Uh, among, among it being the Maury Pulvich show airlines, um, uh, uh, Jerry Springer
airlines, it's, it's, it's, uh, it's also no wifi and while you sit on those uncomfortable
lawn chairs, it's a wifi and my absolute Batman got me through a flight and I was like, oh,
I need to just have this handy for my next, uh, uh, travel.
And so, um, I bought, I bought up, I bought the thing.
So I, I, I bought, I put my name in the system and I chipped the guy and he said, do you
want to check out our podcast?
Fantastic, dude.
All right.
I am so proud of you, uh, on so many levels, uh, nerd brought this up though.
I, I, do you, cause you always do wifi on the planes.
I do.
Paul, do you do wifi when you fly or no?
Not usually.
No, I don't either.
I use, I kind of enjoy the, uh, the few hours where I'm disconnected.
I read a book or I go into airplane mode and I turn on something I've downloaded.
I usually just listen to podcasts when I'm flying.
I'm aware that you can get wifi on planes.
I just don't really think to do it.
I'll turn on my podcast and fall asleep is what I do.
That's fair.
That's, that's kind of the whole thing.
Did you have to rewind your podcast and find it and find where you left off?
No, it's usually just podcasts.
I've decided these are just my sleep podcast for the, yeah, cause I travel with just my
phone.
I'm a little bit of an ogre and don't know how to download an episode of television to
my phone.
So I usually just try to see if the wifi is strong enough.
Oh, right.
Right.
So I know like different airlines have different strengths of wifi.
Netflix is generally pretty agreeable to even the weakest wifi.
Well, Netflix is also the app that works best for downloading stuff too.
Okay.
Well now, now Netflix has the best download technology on their app.
So they are the best in airplane mode.
That's what I have to start doing.
So I'm jealous.
But now like HBO and some of those others have caught up a little bit with the app technology.
When I see them download, I'm so jealous of people who have downloaded full shows or movies
to watch on the plane.
Oh yeah.
You're ahead of the curve busting out the graphic novel, dude.
You're ahead of the curve, having the trade paperback because people can be, but plus
I'm telling you like you're on the right track.
You cannot go wrong with that absolute Batman book because Scott Snyder, who did the whole
court of owls series and a bunch of other Batman stuff that I love a lot of his work.
Yeah.
He's done some of the best Batman of the last 15 years, but this, uh, series, uh, it is
selling so well.
Like numbers keep going up her issue.
I believe they're on issue 18 and the orders are higher than when they started, which is
crazy for any.
Oh, right.
Right.
So it's increasing in popularity.
Yes.
People are buying it.
More people.
So comic books or comic shops are ordering more copies.
So it is just, it is growing, growing, growing in a way that is not, not normal, uh, because
it's that popular.
So your look, what you're reading right now in 10 years will probably be the DCU film
adaptation that that's what seems like it's headed for sure.
Oh, gotcha.
Let me ask you something simply because it's so popular.
Yes.
These, these different kinds of, uh, Batman properties, like back, back in the day there'd
be like the, the detective Batman and now there's, and now there's this, you know, all
these, all the different things.
Is that, that's just different writers or different creators all under the same corporate
umbrella or is it different people that are going to them to do this?
Or are these part, I guess what I'm asking is like, is the author of this current Batman
series that y'all are talking about here, is that somebody who's been working with the
Batman comic, uh, group, whatever, whatever they are for some time.
Uh, has he been working with DC or have they been working with DC for some time?
Yes.
Or is this like a new person that has come in to, to push things in a different direction?
No, Scott Snyder has done Batman forever.
Uh, as far as, oh, yeah, I didn't realize this was Scott Snyder comic book time.
I know that name.
Yeah.
And so he's been at it for a while and this is a new re-imagining reboot of the character,
uh, a very interesting take, which I love.
So it lets everything become kind of fresh and new and everything's under this absolute
umbrella.
So I don't know if you recall it's, it's, it's crazy to me that it was 20 years ago
when the Marvel Ultimates started, but it did.
So Ultimates is what basically inspired the MCU.
So the movies, the films that you see are essentially based off the Ultimates in a lot
of, in a lot of ways.
So, um, Ultimate Spider-Man was probably the strongest, followed very closely by the Ultimates,
which was the Avengers.
Got it.
So those are the two books that I followed really closely, but you know, every, every
little while you've got to do a reset.
And currently DC is eating Marvel's lunch, uh, as far as the success they're having with
the absolute line, which allows for these characters to be set in a new timeline, new
era, new stuff, and not say, you know, we're not throwing out the baby with the bathwater.
You still have all the other classic stuff and there are still ongoing series based more
closely on classic interpretations of the characters.
This is not the only Batman book right now.
This is not even the main Batman book.
The main Batman book, I believe, I want to say, is it Zdarsky who's got it right?
No, Zdarsky doesn't have it right now.
Okay.
Let me ask you this.
Um, whatever, whoever is writing the main Batman book and then Snyder writing, writing
this one.
Yeah.
Are those people working together in any way?
They are not having, are they having discussions?
Are they, are they like, uh, coordinating, storyboarding, anything like that?
Not there.
They're completely separate.
And they're the only way that I'm more curious about the business aspect of, of like how
these things work.
You know, like, is it like the, you mentioned the MCU and film.
Is it like that where you have kind of the whole thing story boarded out?
Now this is the thing.
And then you're trying to, hold on, hold on, you're like, you're trying to work within
that storyboard.
Yes.
Or is it, uh, several different artists working independently but kind of keeping an eye on
each other?
Within the Absolute Universe, they are just now starting to do crossovers within the Absolute
Universe.
So Absolute Wonder Woman has met Absolute Batman.
So that's, it's starting there, those characters are starting to interact within the Absolute
Universe.
How did it go?
I don't know.
I didn't read it yet.
Oh, straight to anal.
I don't vote.
Straight to anal.
I'm still waiting for my Absolute Wonder Woman volume two also, but yes, Jacob, that's kind
of been a weird thing.
They both discovered they were tops and then it got awkward.
It's been a weird thing with all the, um, uh, you know, the crossovers that these comic
book companies have become addicted to.
So when you do something like Civil War or Secret Wars or KO is the big crossover event
that's happening right now in DC.
So a lot of the mainline books do have to communicate with each other because their
main characters are interacting with each other, but a lot of times that will throw
a monkey wrench into what other creators are working on in their individual books and it'll
either completely fuck up the story in some way and they go have to rejigger everything
or they'll just be like, well, here's two issues that don't have anything to do with
the continuity we're trying to project, but this fits in with the ongoing overarching
storyline that's happening in the universe.
Like Paul, you brought up that like the, uh, Marvel just launched a thing called Secret
Wars because they thought war and secret were exciting words for kids.
Yes.
That was the thing that they did back in the eighties.
Yeah.
And that's why I think DC just launched a new series called, uh, La Boo Boo, Mr. Beast.
So wow, it's going to fly off the fucking shelves.
Yeah.
So it's, it's sold out.
That's the way to do it.
I just saw there was a, uh, George Lucas, La Boo Boo limited edition.
How big, how big is the goiter on it?
Look at it.
It doesn't, it doesn't not look like him, but he's wearing like, who else does it not
look like George Lucas?
And that is the following sponsor today's show.
Matt Manley's ice cream social is brought to you by these fine makers and providers
of products.
Uh, a single photograph of us president, Martin Van Buren.
That's right.
Today being sold to you could be a single photograph of us president, Martin Van Buren
and that's from Belgian triple scoop in 2025.
Hello.
I am a single photograph of Martin Van Buren.
I am speaking to you through the magic of picture magic.
Uh, this photograph talks.
That's why it's so expensive.
That's the only way we can keep the company afloat.
I cost $18 million and after I'm sold, that's it.
We're shutting the doors on the storefront, we're closed for business, but we'll stay
open until someone buys me the talking picture of Martin Van Buren.
That's all.
That's it.
However, I'm sorry, was that a prerecorded message or can you have conversations with
people?
I can talk to people.
Welcome.
Yeah.
Welcome to the shop.
That's why I'm so expensive.
I'm $18 million.
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
Are you, are you conscious?
Yeah, very much so and to the point where I've been giving advice to my business partners,
I've been telling them this is a stupid business plan just to sell one picture of Martin Van
Buren.
Talking or not, conscious or not, $18 million, that's great, but what are you doing?
Your overhead's got to be out of control for the rental of this space.
So I've decided that we're going into furniture as well as my picture.
So you can buy the Martin Van Bureau while you're here.
You could shop and buy one of my beautiful Martin Van Bureaus suitable to put me on top
of someday.
Yeah.
Does the, does the bureau also speak?
I'm afraid not.
Unless you put me in it, you could do that.
You could stick my picture inside and I'd be like, "I'm in this bureau, haunted or something.
I don't know."
Well, it's not really haunted though.
I'm just, I'm just a talking picture.
It's different from a haunting.
It's a good question, are you a talking picture or do you have the consciousness of Martin
Van Buren?
Not at all.
I'm just a picture that has consciousness.
Oh, you just look like Martin Van Buren.
Yes.
Well, I'm just a picture of Martin Van Buren.
I look like a two dimensional image of, yeah.
Do you know which president Martin Van Buren was?
No.
I don't even know who I am.
I don't know what I am.
I'm a picture thing.
Are you also selling a red and white wine blend from France?
Yes.
You are.
Okay, good.
I was worried someone else was trying to profit from your name and selling Martin Van Bordo.
No.
Martin Van Bordo's are being, you can get, you can buy the Martin Van Bureau stack with
Martin Van Bordo.
I actually stack my laptop on top of some Martin Van Bordo.
Just bottles?
Just bottles.
It's very sturdy.
Well, I also, I also told the guys, you know, hey, what do the kids love?
They love the vape.
Huh?
Yeah.
So we got, we got you hooked up G. We got that sticky icky, if you know what I'm saying.
So come on in and try some of Martin Van Blazen's.
420, what up G. Now you're not selling containers of just your piss, are you?
Martin Van urine, of course.
Okay.
All right.
Let me make sure this line is very diverse.
But it's not just containers of my piss.
It's in custom shoes made for skateboarders.
For Martin's Vans urine, the soggy step, Vans urine, a bird sanctuary, Martin Van Aaron.
Yeah.
I like that.
That's good.
Oh, I had a kitty cat named Martin Van Purin.
I was like, uh, Katie, Kitty, Kitty Purin, good one, Leon.
We, if, if my brain had been in a more punny place, we could have rocked that a little
bit longer.
I was, I was, I'm still pulling on the old, that's a shame.
I'm pulling on the old motor.
Oh boy.
You son of a bit too bad for the rest of this is that he had his, his, his laptop on a book
of puns so he couldn't access it.
That's right.
He needed that book.
Never stack, never stack on books.
You might need that book.
Listen to my own fucking advice.
I'm stupid matter.
Your boy's trying to buy up all the Mr. Beast jerky and whatnot.
You know, they're surprisingly not, uh, as like Uber focused like that.
So like for a second, my youngest was in the prime drinks and then, but then he's like,
after I was like, these don't taste good.
I'm going to stop buying them.
Oh, for God's sake, they're the worst shit ever.
Those Paul boys are the devil.
Now Mr. Beast does pride himself on doing ethical chocolate, which actually is like
a huge thing that we don't like to talk about because who wants to start taking pride in
their chocolate.
I thought that was only in Vegas.
Well, I'm in Vegas.
I don't know if it is anywhere else, ethylm chocolate, isn't that a Vegas company?
It is a Vegas company.
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, ethical chocolate.
Yes.
Yeah.
Ethical, ethical chocolate.
So he does.
She should call ethical chocolate.
So, so the kids will buy some feastable bars, but I'm okay with that since he is trying
to actually set a precedent of you pay a little more for your chocolate, but it's ethical.
Does he pay the cacao harvesters $2 instead of one a day?
That's right.
What a saint.
Yeah.
Hey, my question, the only thing that I care about as far as your kids are concerned, did
you show them the He-Man trailer?
I brought up at dinner and we have not had a chance.
So last night I had a corporate gig, so I wasn't home.
Tonight I'm home with the boys and I'm going to try to show them the He-Man trailer.
I did bring it up.
They showed very little interest in watching it.
Oh, of course.
Cause they don't know from He-Man.
That's right.
So, but I am, we are going to watch it tonight and I'll report to you either privately or
publicly about it.
Well, it's gotta be public.
That's what it's all about.
We're going to hear it on the, on the pod.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
Speaking of public things that people are going to hear on the pod, this is technically
scoop mail, but I want to do it now.
Lauren Shreve sent us an email and Lauren is setting up an LLC for HR consulting.
Okay.
Needs a name for the business.
Lauren is asking us to help name the business.
All right.
HR consulting business.
What's it about?
Oh, HR consulting.
HR consulting.
Not like HR stands for, it stands for human resources.
HR does stand for something, Paul.
I know.
I thought it was stands for a puff and stuff.
It's Lauren is setting up an HR puff and stuff LLC.
Okay.
Don't discuss Israel LLC.
That would be not about Israel.
I'll see.
HR is the enemy LLC fight the real enemy LLC.
Yeah.
There's still, okay.
There's still such thing as the C word LLC.
Why didn't you just tell me to my face?
I would have reacted better LLC.
We're watching you LLC.
Let's see, because you don't want to do something corny like olive branch or like peacemaking
or peacemaker.
That'd be good.
Peacemaker.
How about like humane recognition?
For HR.
How about workforce alchemy synergy?
The show.
Yeah.
Two plus two equals five.
Resourcing humanely.
Yeah.
We're getting some suggestions.
Okay.
Here in the chat.
Coca-Cola LLC.
Try that one.
Oh, lemur.
Check that one.
Martin Vroom and resources.
That's good.
Leon Casabs got hitting some dingers LLC.
It's a good one.
Scooper Nova girl.
This could have been an email LLC.
I like that.
It's really funny.
That's pretty good.
Criss Angel has a Chimera.
Why is your union rep here LLC?
I like that.
HR us from lemur screamer.
I like that one.
HR marked lemur screamer is just how about ranking them out?
How about I patch HR.
You like them the are I patch HR because I patch like I patch it up.
I'm making it better.
Right?
There's I patch pirate and then HR with the pirate are I'll just go ahead and declare
me the winner on this.
I won.
Oh, my dog is here and they're so mad that they're not getting fed right now.
Here's the question.
So like sometimes like you want like you have a regular business name, but like what you
put on the checks is funny, right?
So like my wife has like 11 jobs for the same company, but they all have a different LLC.
And every time I get the stuff for the taxes, I'm like, what is the company called?
And so like no one calls it these companies, but it's just a funny thing.
Some of the names are wild.
Yeah.
Like for this, I get paid from Penn Sunday School from preaching to the choir, LLC.
So it's just want a funny name for the LC for someone to cut the check to.
Or is this like, I need to I'm going to get a website and market my services.
I need a real name.
This is going to be that it's going to be funny.
I said, when do you think it's going to be?
No, I think it's going to be the second.
I think it's going to be the real name that she wants people to be able to see and do
business with her.
How about bat shit cross them?
What do you think?
Like a, like free beer, free beer, free beer and chicken, name it after old improv teams,
free beer and chicken.
How about, how about you call it a bear in the woods LLC, which I like uncomfortable
conversations.
We need to talk.
LLC is good too.
Yeah, something like, uh, something like hard conversations might really be on the right
path because that's, I mean, that's all anybody wants an HR consulting firm for, right?
Exit strategy.
Golden parachute final, final interview, uh, exit interview, exit interview, LLC.
You can do which exit interview, you can be a New Jersey based HR firm, which exit interview
exit only interview from the fat LLC.
One of you, one of us doesn't have a job LLC for miles around.
There you go.
It's exactly the conversations.
Oh, function the whale, uh, higher expectations, H I R E higher expectation.
I like that.
That's pretty good.
I don't like that.
Higher expectations is pretty great.
Yeah.
What I think you have to do is take your, the, the name of your first pet and the street
you grew up on.
And that's how you name a company.
As far as I know, that's a, that's right.
How about employee time of the month?
How about anonymous post it note LLC whistleblowers, whistleblowers friend whistleblowers exposed
LLC whistleblowers handled, Oh no, I think, I think you got one out of that out of that
pile.
Lauren, you're welcome.
Just one more.
Just for left field, just the hawk.
Just, I don't know.
It sounds pretty, just sounds pretty boss.
Prep that resume.
Don't worry.
We've hired the hawk and hawk HR.
Yeah.
That'll get you hired by a lot of dude, dude, dude, bro companies.
Time for people to quit, quiet quitting LLC, diversity, Terminator LLC, diversity Terminator.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah.
I work for a company who hired the diversity Terminator.
Right.
Part time.
Yeah.
Fucking shit.
But at least they're helping out ice.
I swear.
I swear to God, every day I go in there, I work a little bit less.
Yeah.
It's like, fuck this company forever.
Fuck this company forever.
That'll show him mad.
No, I got him.
I got him right there.
Even though I sweat my fucking balls off and move millions of dollars of merchandise every
goddamn week.
I got him.
Oh, fuck that company.
I can't quit you LLC.
I can't quit you without two weeks notice LLC.
If I can make you quit, this company doesn't have to pay unemployment benefits LLC.
If working here's right, I don't want to be wrong LLC.
What pension LLC?
What pension?
Indeed.
Well, that's a joke.
I was doing my shows now where, uh, uh, uh, uh, I get someone up on stage and say, what
do you do for work?
And they go, I'm retired.
I go, Oh my God, Gen Z.
Close your ears.
Right.
Yeah.
Cause it'll never happen.
That's a really good one.
That's a good one.
It'll never happen.
How about silence plebes?
Oh, I like that.
Failing upwards, LLC.
That's a good one.
Leon, the Oompa HR loompas from bossy yeah.
At will LLC from lemur creamer.
Yep.
Oh, at will L at will HR LLC is, is really good.
What's the, it's a 10, 10, nine.
Is that the, that's the form, right?
10 99.
Or is that the, what's the independent contractor form?
Yeah.
10 99.
I just, I don't know, just, uh, you're an independent contractor.
Yeah.
LLC here today.
10 99 tomorrow.
That's a, uh, you know what else has a, a really good name for their business?
That's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by, um, uh, we did a single
photograph.
Uh, yes to prop 69, that's from open body with 2021 vote.
Yes.
It's a prop 69.
Well, hey, they're hard going.
Everybody.
I'm here from the open by you and Louisiana.
We look in the past as the prop 69, huh?
Yeah.
You know that prop 69.
What are you going to do?
We're going to free up all the gators.
What living in a swamp.
Go ahead and say yes to freeing up the gators.
They don't walk across all the way to be your street.
We're going to open up bill to the gators, which is going to give it to the gators.
We took it from them.
We giving it back bill for the gators.
That's what prop 69 is all about.
Say yes to gators walking up and down bill street, sliding into jazz holes, listening
to the fine music that gets played up and down the boardwalk.
Where do you think Beale Street is?
I don't know.
Where is it?
Memphis, Memphis is where Beale Street is.
OK.
So this is why we got to pass this prop in knowledge.
To a parade, you see, all the way down to Memphis town.
We're doing a second line to Memphis, come on.
Oh, when the streets get filled with gators, oh, when the streets get filled with gators,
they're going to walk all the way down to Memphis.
Oh, when the streets get filled with gators.
Who wants to come on down to Bourbon Street, try some barbecue today?
No, no, no, Seashell, we going all the way down to Memphis, hon.
We had enough of your hey, cowpokes, welcome to Bourbon Street.
We got dry rub.
We got wet barbecue.
This my kind of place.
Now, I'll tell you what, hon, please don't be turning me into a pouch bag or some kind
of shoe.
I'm a friendly gator, don't you see?
A pouch bag?
Don't you go making me a pouch bag, befriend.
Don't make me a pouch bag perfect for putting a computer on top of you for balance.
I found my thrill as a gator on Beale.
I was like, he does not know where Beale Street is.
Of course I don't know where Beale Street is.
Nobody else brought up Beale Street, Paul.
Isn't that that cop show?
Nope.
Beale Street Blues?
Oh, Beale Street Blues.
Now y'all go on out there and be careful, this here, Memphis, we don't want nobody,
we don't want nobody getting hurt out there now.
Right here in Memphis.
Memphis, P.D.I. County, Beale Street ain't never going to be the same.
I'm going to go listen to some Dr. John playing down here in Memphis.
Come on, Dr. John, where you at?
Oh yeah, the gators are coming.
I just got a voicemail.
Oh shit.
Hello?
My glasses are ready.
Where from?
Pearl Vision.
From the Pearl Vision?
Yeah.
What'd you strip?
I'm actually not as bad as, oh did I talk about, I talked about I was going to go to
the eye doctor.
Did I talk about going to the eye doctor?
I think we were going to talk about going there and we talked about having reading glasses
around the house.
Yeah, yeah, so I have reading glasses around the house and I went there and I was like
so afraid that they were going to be like, did you drive here?
Here's these Coke bottles, you blindy.
They gave me five vision tests, I did like a round of different tests, the test for different
things on the eye.
And they said I have a very basic prescription, nothing too crazy.
That fits.
Clock that.
They said basic bitch, here's your basic bitch glasses, you basic bitch.
Basic bitch scripts.
Why don't you go have your chicken salad for lunch, you fucking basic bitch.
Get out of here.
Here's your glasses.
Are you nearsighted, farsighted, or both?
Both.
I need tough.
I need more progressives, right, so I can do the far from the top.
Let's just pour some milk in your fucking eyes, get you some lactic acid, you basic bitch.
You fucking cereal eating basic bitch.
Milk is a basic acid, right?
Or is that Beale Street?
Beale Street.
That's Beale Street.
I'm trying not to give you.
Oh shit, oh fuck, real quick, to derail everything.
Corrections time.
I'm not passionate about talking about my glasses, but that's fine.
Corrections time, and made me put in a correction.
Last episode I claimed that the interstate was designed specifically for truckers.
It was in fact specifically designed for the military industrial complex to be able to
transport military vehicles more efficiently, first and foremost.
The trucking thing.
Oh, a side effect was helping the trucking industry.
Yes, yes, yes.
And destroying the train.
And destroying the train bearing monopolies, and yeah, well I mean we have far less children
with one leg in this country thanks to that.
That's true.
More dead ones, but far less maimed kids.
Oh man.
Because they don't have as much.
But dead whole kids.
Oh yeah, dead and intact for the most part.
Dead in the car.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean well I guess how do you judge intact?
Still belted in, does that count?
Yes.
I guess.
Yeah.
Blood on the freeway.
It depends if you're a really tender chicken, you can like pull the leg out, I don't know.
It depends.
Depends.
Oh, it's done.
Oh, you just jarred another thing from me, Matt.
Let's do it.
Let's keep going.
We're on fire.
Guess what I did this week.
Yes.
What?
I made chicken and dumplings.
Out of a can that said chicken and dumplings?
Nope, nope.
I'm learning, I'm learning.
Okay.
This was-
Did you use a cooking pot?
Yes.
This was a seven, a six or a seven I would say.
Six, seven.
I did not hit it out of the park like I'd hoped, but I'm going to change up my recipe.
Your first attempt.
Huh?
First attempt, yes.
Yeah.
I'm pretty happy.
Myra wants to know, did you use a Dutch oven?
No, just a big pot.
No vegetables are added in my-
I just farted directly in Anne's face.
I didn't hold her under the covers.
No vegetables are added in my-
Paul says chicken and dumplings.
He means chicken and dumplings.
Yeah, that's it.
No vegetables.
No, no, no.
There are plenty of people who do celery and carrots and onions and shit.
Peas.
Peas is a common one, yeah.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, throw some peas in there.
Disgusting.
You don't even taste them.
No, no, no.
It's weird.
We bought a bunch of-
It's like a football in your soup.
Yeah, it's delightful.
We got a bunch of chicken from Costco, which was-
You're making a gesture with your hands like you're holding a shotgun.
What did you buy a chicken in?
What form of chicken?
It was in a sack.
It was de-boned rotisserie chicken in a sack.
Paul would show you the sack, but it's currently holding up his laptop.
Wait, that sounds-
Wait, who sells de-boned-
How does one get de-boned chicken in a sack?
At Costco.
Really?
I didn't even eat the chicken-
Yeah, it's like shredded chicken in a bag.
I didn't really get it de-boned.
Jacob knows exactly what I'm talking about.
I do.
Just because I don't doesn't mean I'm accusatory.
I can learn too.
You're learning, I'm learning.
You son of a bitch.
I bought sack chicken from the Costco.
You come on down to Beale Street, we all settle this man to man.
We're going to settle this up right here.
Who's eating who's chicken, Dr. John?
That person speaking, Aaron Burr.
Aaron Burr.
We had this chicken, and it was going to go south in about a week.
I needed to put some pedal to the metal.
It was going to go south of mustard.
I went online, and I watched several how-to videos on YouTube until I saw stuff that the
end result was consistent with visually what I recalled from my grandmother eating.
Okay.
I was like, "Okay, that's the one I'm going with."
It was very simple.
I put in an egg, flour, egg, little bit of chicken broth.
That's it.
Mushed it up into a dough.
For the dumplings.
Yeah.
Mushed it up into a dough, added flour as needed.
Rolled it out.
Oh, I was going to ask you if you rolled it out or if you did the dumpling ball.
No.
I rolled it out.
We do the flats.
I'm very impressed.
I went to a comic book shop, and Paul is rolling out his own dough.
It is a new day.
It's a shiny new day here.
We're getting old.
We're running out of things to do on the planet.
I've been sober for a day and a half.
Holy shit.
It's a weird world.
It's a weird crazy world.
This is a very weird time.
I haven't been sober for a day and a half.
I'm getting carried away.
Cut up the dumplings.
Had a whole lot of dumplings.
It was really great.
The two things that probably came up short were the chicken and the stock.
Okay.
I got just box stock.
Right?
Got you.
In the future.
Oh yeah.
You got to season up.
You can do the box stock, but you got to season up the box stock a little bit.
I seasoned it up, but I didn't season up enough.
There you go.
But I think in the future, the trick is just straight up make your own stock.
Yeah.
Boil bone-in chicken until it falls off the bone of a couple of pieces.
Clear out the bones.
Chunk up the chicken.
Take out the chicken.
Then you've got the stock.
Maybe add a bouillon.
I saw another recipe.
No, no.
Keep the bones going.
Take the chicken off the bones, and then keep the bones in there.
Let it really.
Keep them really going.
You can even break them.
Break the bones up.
Get the marrow out for a little while.
Yeah.
Or add a little bouillon.
I saw another recipe.
Added cream of chicken soup.
Eisenhower used the bones of children that died making trains.
Yeah.
That's how my grandma used to make chicken and dumplings, and it's honestly the best
way.
Train baby gravy is the primary way to eat chicken and dumplings, but I didn't have the
things available to me at hand.
I still say that's James Taylor's best song.
And I walked into my mother's house.
I could smell it on the stove.
The train baby gravy, just like she made from home.
It was supple, soft, and slippery, and it slid right in my mouth.
Fresh from the tracks at the railroad crossing, a baby went down south all the way to Beale
Street.
All the way to Beale Street.
Look out, here come them getters.
Here they come.
Looking for that baby.
That baby train gravy.
Train baby gravy.
Here comes the great strolling parlor band from Beale Street.
This is another thing, Matt, that I'm afraid the elites have stolen from us, besides our
future and our hope.
They've also stolen the ability to really make fun jokes about eating babies, because
now it's just a stark reality.
There was a time when dead baby jokes ruled the playground for kids.
Nowadays, it's just like, "Whoa, who are you trying to be?
Elon Musk?"
Yeah.
Oh boy.
Anyway.
How do you fit 10,000 dead babies into a phone booth?
You give them to the elites, they'll figure it out.
Hire Bill Gates.
That's how you do it.
He'll figure it out real fucking quick.
I also have a piece of side note business popped into my head.
We had one of our scoops right on Patreon.
I don't get the angry goose joke, can someone explain it to me?
I just thought I should maybe also explain it on air.
Yeah.
Because we're making it in reference to Fisto from Masters of the Universe.
And I didn't know this until, I guess, you can hear early episodes of us learning this
basically, but in the actual sex act of fisting, you don't actually make a fist.
You don't just punch someone's butthole.
I mean, unless they've asked for that.
I'm just saying there might be people out there making mistakes.
Making mistakes or just granting wishes.
Yeah.
Sure, sure.
Featured on a bug maybe.
The Paul Mattingly biography.
Making mistakes and granting wishes.
Yeah, making mistakes and granting wishes, the Paul Mattingly story.
A lid for every pot, a fist for every cornhole.
Now Paul, your camera went out.
Is it because your computer fell off the bags?
It's because I'm wiping my nose because it's two degrees in my goddamn basement.
My nose is running from the fucking cold.
I thought I'd spare our listening audience and viewing audience me digging for nose goblins.
Now, Bossy and Cham is a good point.
He's saying Fisting 101 by Matt Donnelly.
Yeah, don't let me be the only source on this, okay?
Please, I'm not doing, I'm not doing--
Do your own research.
I'm not doing a sarcastic Joe Rogan where I give some lunatic a platform for four hours
and then say do your own research at the end.
I mean, I really want you to not let me be the only source that you get this from.
Is that some kind of high women joke?
I don't want you to punch people in the assholes.
And I don't want you to use me as your only fisting source.
That's right.
But you actually form your fisters into a point as if you're like pinching a--
Well, if you see many of these sex toys that are sold as fisty, they are that same thing.
Right.
They are like somebody's getting ready to--
You make a cone, a cone of fingers.
It's basically prekermit.
Prekermit, yeah, yeah.
So if someone says prekermit, my butthole, we're talking about the same thing.
Pre--
You know, you can still get pregnant from prekermit.
I heard that was a myth.
No, it's not a myth, buddy.
Oh, I heard it's a myth.
That's how, look, Paul's only nine months apart from his brother.
Believe me, you can get pregnant from prekermit.
You can get pregnant from prekermit, for fucking sure.
Ten and a half months, that's right.
I thought it was eight and a half.
Ten and a half, razor close.
Eight and a half.
So, yeah, anger goose is referring to the actual shape you make when one fists another person.
Right.
I just want to make sure that we're all caught up.
It's pump at hand.
Inside joke explained.
That's a literal inside joke.
The best way that we express gratitude on the show is by saying fuck you in the face, you dick and tit farmers, of which I am the farmer.
And so that's when you get a thank you email from me for signing up for Patreon.
That's what that means on the bottom.
We have a wonderful comment here in the chat from Chris Angel has a chimera.
As an old queer man, we used to tell a joke back in the '90s.
How can you tell if a guy is gay?
Ask him to make a fist.
Oh, that's great.
I like that a lot.
That's great. That's a guy I had a friend who was a lesbian who was like, listen, the girls like to say they're bisexual.
And she goes, I just look at their fingernails and be like, no, you're not.
All good.
That's a big tell.
That's a healthy talk right there.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
What do we have?
We got some scoop mail, Jacob.
Now let's do a little jock versus nerd.
We already did.
We snuck it in.
That's right.
Like an angry goose.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
That angry goose don't speak anywhere.
Time for jock versus nerd.
The exclusion of angry geese.
Hello, fabulous face fuckers.
I wrote this scooperty on Black Friday, which made me think about a gift everyone must have received at least once in their lives, a quote of the day desk calendar.
You know the kind where there are about 365 pages and you rip them out and each page you have a new quote and you keep on tearing a sheet off every day starting on January 1st until about mid-February when you throw it away when nobody is looking.
Here is a scooperty with some famous quotes of people in the areas you three enjoy.
And this is from Psych Scoop.
The categories are comedians, magicians, comic books, and sports figures.
I'm up first.
I'll try magicians.
200 filthy magicians.
On the subject of pattern, this magician said generally magicians don't know what to say, so they say stupid and redundant crap like here I am holding a red ball.
I mean, it sounds a lot like Penn.
I'm going to say Penn Gillette.
Tell her.
Well, you were halfway there.
I was kind of close.
You were very close and that's actually that is the thing when they're talking to magicians about like the whole like once they're not doing the sarcastic teller talks thing.
But he is one of our greatest living magic minds.
And I always say that one of the things that makes him such a great magic mind.
Both men and teller are we talked about this like not sentimental.
You know if they don't they don't write they don't so they don't wax poetic or getting the things being to you know whatever and emotions in any kind of way.
So teller is remarkably practical magic advice.
That's an example of right there.
Like he's very much about like just do this.
This sucks.
This makes people go wow.
This is deceptive.
This isn't like he's very clear and bare bones about his magic advice, which is really awesome.
Yeah.
Nice.
Matt you're up.
Magicians 400 please.
This magician said there is nothing worse than good magic at the wrong time.
That's a really funny quote.
I don't know who said this.
Copperfield.
And I really want to know.
I really want to know the context of it.
Dude he is he's on his way out huh.
I don't think so.
You don't think so.
You don't think they're going to push him.
Who knows.
I guess there are no consequences for anything anymore.
I don't fucking know.
Well also if he's the only one who suffers consequences for this that'll be really weird too.
Because basically they were like.
It'll just be him and Bill Gates are the only two that are getting anything any kind of blowback.
Yeah.
I think several of them got blowback.
Oh blowback.
No.
Yikes.
This magician said there is nothing worse than good magic at the wrong time.
I'll just say this on this just to put the finer point of what I'm getting at which is that I think he's too much of a non-current celebrity to get too much shit for what's happening.
I don't.
Outside of Vegas he's not.
Outside of Vegas I don't think.
People think of as a nostalgic name that calls to their childhood.
It is not like bringing up someone who's operating right now and thriving right now.
Did he ever bring back the Statue of Liberty though?
I mean we never.
Oh it's all he does.
It's like we're like stop.
Put it away David.
It's a Statue of Liberty here.
Statue of Liberty there.
Just can you just please order.
We're waiting.
I'm going to fly across the Grand Canyon with my leg crossed.
Indian style.
Crisscross applesauce.
I'll also say I don't see too many magicians saying no to getting his private jet and go to his island right now.
So it seems like there's really no ramifications.
Wait who's private island.
David has his own private island.
Copperfields.
Of course he does.
But that's the whole point.
That's why they're like that's actually why they were mostly connected and not mostly connected through.
Oh they were island friends.
Yes.
I suppose.
Like two people with Jeeps doing the weird finger wave at each other.
Two people with Jeeps.
Yeah they go over to each other's island give each other a rubber duck every month.
No it was just a weird finger wave.
They did a weird finger wave with each other.
Anyhow pass.
Paul.
Mattingly.
Paul Mattingly.
Penn.
All right.
David Roth.
David Lee Roth.
Amazing.
Yeah.
Hey you know what.
There's nothing worse than good magic at the wrong time.
Ha ha ha.
Penn and Ma.
It's from me.
Diamond Dave.
Don't bring out magic at the good times.
Toe time to jump.
Paul you're up.
Get me a coffee and a glazed donut to go.
I'll go with comic books for 200.
This comic book figure is known for saying Excelsior.
That is none other than Stan the Man Lee.
I am wearing an Excelsior badge on my shirt right now.
I have it on my coat.
That's something that people care about.
They do.
I'm doing sports figures for 200.
Winn questioned about his work at the news conference.
Excelsior.
This sports figure responded we talk about practice.
Oh you're going to know that.
Practice.
That's true.
Yeah.
We talk about practice.
You know that.
Coach Maura baby coach Jim Maura.
Allen Iverson.
Oh that's the wrong playoff.
Something in playoffs.
Damn it.
Oh no.
Playoffs not practice.
Oh you went the wrong way.
I went to the wrong press conference.
In your defense.
Matt.
I think people mix up Jim Maura and Allen Iverson all the time.
Constantly.
All the time.
That won't even be the last time on this show where it happens.
Oh boy.
Give me comedians for 600.
Let's try it.
This gone too soon comedian said this after encountering Jacob's favorite waterfowl.
I find a duck's opinion of me is very much influenced by whether or not I have bread.
Oh shit I know who this is.
I'm picturing it in my mind.
It is not Steven Wright.
No.
You got to go outside and trim.
Mitch Hensburg.
There you go.
Yeah.
Paul.
I'll do comic books for 800.
I'm going to shoot the moon.
This superhero said there's always a way when the odds are impossible do the impossible.
Captain Planet.
No this is tricky.
The power is yours.
When the odds are impossible do the impossible.
And it sounds like Superman but it could be a lot.
It could be Captain America 2.
Out to pass.
Oh that passes to me.
That is Howard the Duck.
It definitely sounds like Cass or Supes.
Sure.
Pass.
Ultra good goodies.
That would be Fisto.
Pass.
Superman.
It's me I'll try comic books for 400.
I fell asleep.
This shield bearing comic book hero said I'm loyal to nothing general except the dream.
There you go.
That is Spider-Man.
Spider-Man Spider-Man has a web shield.
I'm loyal to nothing except the dream.
He does have a web shield.
That is the crow from the Sandman.
That is Brandon Lee's The Crow.
James O'Barr's The Crow.
That would be Captain America.
Eric Draven.
Matt.
I'll do comedians for 800.
This late comedian said cocaine is God's way of saying you make too much money.
Oh God.
Shoot.
I know that quote.
It's a very good quote.
It is.
Somebody just leapt into my head.
I have a guess but I'm not sure if I'm right or not.
I'm going to pass.
Paul.
See now I'm second guessing myself.
Who are you thinking?
Talk us through it baby.
My first thought was Carlin.
That's my first thought as well.
My second thought was Bill Hicks.
Okay.
And then my third thought was Mark Maron.
Oh wow.
I think yeah.
Mark Maron and Carlin.
Any one of those.
Richard Pryor.
Oh yeah.
I'll pass to let you take that shot bro.
No, no, no.
I'm passing as well because I'm right there with you.
Oh my God.
It was Robin Williams.
Of all the cocaine addles.
I was going to say.
So it was Richard Pryor.
Oh.
Shots fucking fired.
Stay down Robin Williams.
Too good too long.
Paid everybody for every joke he ever told.
Oop, oop, oop.
On blast.
Robin Williams on blast.
Paul you're up.
I will do comic books
for 600 please.
This super hero
said when there seems to be no chance
that's when it counts.
Oh piss.
Piss man.
Martin Van Buren
is piss man.
Seems to be
no chance.
When there seems to be no chance that's when it counts.
See this is also a very
goody two shoesy.
This could be like
Green Lantern
or
there's another
big.
No, no, this Paul, this was
a motivational
speech given by
Lex Luthor
in the big doom house
that would fly around and the super friends
would have to chase them around.
It could be
Batman. I'll have to pass.
That passes to me.
I happen to know this one. It is
the left wonder twin.
The left wonder twin.
I don't know. Pass.
Matt.
I have no idea.
Spider-Man.
Yeah.
His is, there's great
I just walked through a comic book.
I walk into one comic book shop and suddenly the
pressure's on to answer these questions.
He tested.
Oh yeah, no, that one did
come out today. You're absolutely right sir
to be here on the day that that one came out
that you just came in and asked about.
I swear it's a coincidence.
It's not. You're a nerd. You're one of us.
Well and the thing is they also
probably had 40 copies.
They did have a lot of copies.
It sounded like fucking hotcakes.
I don't know if they had 40 but they had a lot of copies.
It's my turn and I just
accidentally clicked on a question. I don't know which one I
clicked on. This hot headed coach
said when my time on Earth is gone
and my activities here are passed
I want them to bury me upside down
and my critics can kiss my ass.
Archie boy from UNLV
Is that Bobby Knight?
Is it Bobby Knight or
Tarkanian?
It's Beale Street.
Is it Bobby Knight or is it Tarkanian?
No, I don't think it's Tark.
I don't think Tark's a kiss my ass guy.
It's Bobby Knight.
Tark is the
my friend here is going to break your legs later.
Yikes.
Yeah, I'll say Bobby Knight.
Fuck yeah, it's Bobby Knight.
Which one was that?
Sports figures for
600 maybe? I don't know.
Let's see.
Matt and I are both tied at 600.
Paul has negative 200.
And I think there's still two daily doubles
left out of the six questions that are left.
So anyone's gay.
Matt, you're up. You got comedians, magicians
and sports figures. We've burned all the comic books.
I'll do sports figures
for 400 please. Let's try it.
This baseballer
said they don't think it be like
it is, but it do.
Although many falsely attribute this quote
to other players.
Oh man.
They don't think it be like it is, but it do.
Is this Reggie Jackson?
Or is this
Yogi Berra?
No, there's no irony
in it. People falsely
quote Yogi for a lot of things
but there's usually an ironic twist.
It's either Daryl
or Strawberry.
I'm going to be
Pancho Joe Pesci Bill Cosby.
I'll pass.
Paul.
Was it Pancho
Ponce de Leon?
No.
Satchel Paige.
Is that your guess?
Yeah, I'll go with Satchel Paige.
Your guess is Satchel Paige.
It's Oscar
Gamble. Oh, everyone knows
Oscar Gamble. We were just talking
about Oscar Gamble, the very well-known
baseball player. Well, I just Oscar Gamble
several points and lost.
You did. You did.
Satchel Paige. That is a deep
baseball pull, sir. Paul, you're
up.
Not deep enough. I'll go
with magicians for 800
to get back on the board.
This magician born in the 1800s said
the personality must be bigger
than the prop. Gotta be
Houdini. Who?
Houdini. Harry
Blackstone, senior.
Shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit.
My turn. I'll just try
magicians for 600
just because Houdini hasn't been an answer yet.
Shit. Daily double!
Oh, boo!
Boo, you!
There is no official
record that this magician said
anyone who believes in magic
is a fool, but
people attribute the quote to him anyway.
I'm Houdini. My name is Mr. Houdini.
Said this Houdini.
Harry
Houdini.
Houdini!
Boo on you!
Fuck you!
Houdini!
The hits keep coming.
This humorist first said in 1923
I don't drink water.
The cowboy!
It's the cowboy guy!
Will Rogers!
Will Rogers?
It's gotta be
Will Rogers!
[coughing]
Yeah, Matt!
It's gotta be Will Rogers!
I think this will be Harry Blackstone Jr.
That's it.
Is it W.C. Fields?
Ooh!
Ooh, that's a good guess.
I'll go with Fields.
Alright.
W.C.
Motherfucking
Fields is correct.
Water closet Fields himself.
My favorite
quote is, again, maybe
mis-tributed him. You can find a tribute to different people, but it's
If you want to make people laugh, dress a guy up like an old lady
and push him down the stairs.
If you want to make a comedian laugh, push an old
lady down the stairs.
My favorite Fields quote.
Paul, you have
-1400. Matt and I are both tied
at 1200. There are two questions left.
Let's get on the board with sports figures for 800, please.
Alright.
This prominent
pugilist poetically
proclaimed, "It's just a job.
Grass grows, birds fly,
waves pound the sand. I beat
people up." Okay.
Uh.
I think Matt will
agree with me. There is only one person that this could
possibly be.
I mean,
Foreman?
That's what I would have guessed.
Like, it's not
poetic enough to be Ali.
Okay.
I go Ali.
It's too cogent to be Tyson.
Yeah. Oh yeah, I don't think
it's Tyson. I think it's Ali.
Well, I'm going with Foreman.
Okay.
It's Muhammad Ali. Ah, hell!
Hell and damnation!
I gave you
the best hint I could think of giving
you, Paul.
Well, it wasn't good enough. For the win,
I am closing out the category and the game
Comedians for 200.
This sassy French
guard said, "I fart in your general
direction."
It has to be the character's name.
It's the person who put the character's name.
French guard.
French guard number one.
It's French guard number one
from Monty Python's
Quest for the Holy Grail.
That's right.
Oh, you wanted the, oh, you did want
the actor. John, please.
Oh, sorry.
With that psychological destruction
of Jacob, I win.
Man, got it! 1200 points!
Paul's got a thousand, Paul's got negative 2200.
And that's from Sykes Scoop.
Thank you, Sykes Scoop.
All the others were the comedian names,
wasn't it? That's right.
I was half joking when I said it.
And I feel bad.
Don't feel bad.
What do you feel bad about?
I felt like I accidentally
coached you into giving the wrong answer on that one.
And I didn't mean to. I was being a joke.
Joking. Oh, no, no.
I gave the answer I wanted to give.
I do enjoy, though, that you feel bad
about a joke versus nerd result,
though. Especially it was 1200
versus a thousand points of real squeaker.
Yeah, yeah.
A nail biter to the end.
Thank you, Basi. Basi thinks I should get
the points. Um, yeah.
Yeah, I
agree, Basi. He's his own judge, Basi.
He gave himself the negative. We can't, we
can, we can do it all we want. He's in
control of the points. No, no, I would like to
continue under protest.
I would like to continue
with protest over my right hand as my left
hand and I would like to get the
points. Fuck you!
Ow!
I want to thank Penn Jillette for being in this podcast.
Thanks, Penn. How is
Penn? We got a health check on Penn?
He's doing good. He's doing good. He is
really staying strict to doctors
orders, which surprises no one. So he's moving
around very little. He just
announced this week on Penn Sunday School that they will
attempt to do
basically some kind of
theatrical
presentation of Penn to resume shows
starting February 12th.
Penn will be, he doesn't
want to go on a wheelchair because it's too
like weird. Oh, no, no. He's got to do
the Axl Rose. That's it.
They're going to do the, he's got to do the throne. The throne.
They're going to do with, yeah, Axl
Rose, Ozzy. Yeah, you got to do
the throne. And so
that'll be happening there. And so
yeah.
Those will either be the best
Penn and Teller shows ever or
the worst Penn and Teller shows ever.
Those will not be
mediocre Penn and Teller shows. Those are going to be
ones that you're going to want to go see.
If you are a Penn and Teller fan,
those are the shows that you want to go check
out because that's going to be listed. I just want to hear
like three jokes that happen from
like a lack of being able to figure out
something, like seeing how many
dominoes it pushes.
Oh, right.
That's what I want to see. So, yeah, it's going to
be fun. Oh, yeah. No, it's going
to have some things. Speaking of Penn,
I want to thank you for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben. I want to thank all the people who join us
here on Zoom. If you want to join us on a Zoom
call or if you want access to
a myriad of other prizes that we offer
at different tiers, head on over to PreachingFund.com
and select a tier that fits your
budget today.
Come visit PreachingFund.com