Oh hello there, I am so glad you are here because I want to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers?
These are the folks that deliver that ice cream straight to your ear holes.
Right now I'd like to thank Travis Jagare, Thunder, Cougar, Falcon, Scoop, the lost ice cream truck driver,
Slurpee Kaey, Motherfucker, Scoop Kata, Scoop Dijor, Scoop Brady, and Sax Guy, Jimmy D. Scoop.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com.
PreachingFun.com is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows,
your life you save may be your own.
Here's a show.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Scoopfest coming up at the end of the month. We won't talk about it the whole episode, but I'm going to say it now.
Scoopfest.com, head over there, join us here in beautiful Las Vegas at the end of September. It's going to be awesome.
So soon.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social. Sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly. Also sitting in Las Vegas, me and Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
Hey everybody. That's a nice hat tonight, Jacob.
Thank you, thank you. I like that one.
Paul, you were asleep, so we had our first Scoopfest crisis, but you were asleep, so we didn't bother you.
Yeah, I appreciate that. What happened?
Well, that lineup subject to change asterisks is really coming into play this time.
Okay. Yeah, the asterisks has changed.
Alright. Just one thing. Just one of them.
Right, but we already had some stuff made up that's going to have to just be like, well...
Oh no, we've already gotten...
Lanyards and stuff, yeah.
No, we've already gotten sub people in, and yeah, we're all good.
Oh, yes.
So the lanyards weren't printed with the old info yet?
Oh, no, the lanyards are printed, the schedule on the lanyards is going to be wrong.
We're fucked.
That's fine, that's fine.
There's one event on the lanyard that's going to be a different name than what's on the lanyard. That's okay.
That's the way it goes.
In the same time slot, no problem.
I appreciate you guys letting me sleep.
I, again, like I said, been fighting a cold.
You can hear it in my chest.
My head is really hurting today.
And I slept in because I was off today.
And Ann didn't go in until late, so she was handling the dogs.
Man, I was out. I was in bed until 11.
So, yeah, it was...
P.O.
11 a.m.
Slept all day.
Yeah, I slept all day. No, no, no.
Now, does Ann factor in your sickness when she hates you for being a wuss, for not going into work because you weren't scheduled?
Smart.
I'll have you know that that all got resolved.
So, my non-schedule had...
Ranch Slunk in the chat is already blaming the microwave hot dogs for your illness, Paul.
Two components, though.
I agree.
Ranch Slunk, by the way, is correct.
I didn't have any microwave hot dogs yesterday.
We had pizza. Ann and I ordered pizza.
Fired up the oven?
No, we got Domino's.
We got Domino's. It was great fun.
We were having one of those nights.
We were really being fun with each other.
We love just hanging out on the couch being catty bitches.
We watch this show right now called...
What is it called?
Stuart's Crossing?
It's not Stuart's Crossing.
Sullivan's Crossing.
Have you guys heard of this show?
I've heard of it.
Canadian Scoop Crystals is pumping her fist.
Yeah, it's a Canuck production.
It is heavily Canadian, this show.
They got...
Sponsored by Tim Artins.
They got some folks in the show who you would refer to in Canada as Native characters.
Like Native Americans, Native North Americans.
So they got some of that.
It's sort of like Northern Exposure, but not funny.
Oh, so just like Northern Exposure.
No, it's not funny.
Stay down, Northern Exposure.
And it leans pretty heavy into stereotypical, romance-y dumb stuff.
First Nations, First People, yes.
So they have this guy, it's the guy from Gilmore Girls who was Luke, who I can't remember.
The romantic lead in Gilmore Girls.
Oh, from Gilmore...
Luke from Gilmore Girls?
Listen, buddy.
I've watched that series as well.
These are the shows that I watch with the wife.
If you just want like a time-out, Paul, to get all your facts together, we can do that.
We can figure out something.
Just saying.
Because you keep asking us for things that definitely, Jacob and I have never come close to watching.
You've never seen Gilmore Girls.
Stop yelling at me.
No, it's... that's a snappy dialogue.
Good show.
That's a good show.
Snappy dialogue?
See you later, guys.
I have to go stream the Gilmore Girls.
Matt has left the Zoom chat.
Matt will be back on the show after he's watched the Gilmore Girls.
Hey, guys, I'm back.
I just watched a preview.
I can't believe the snappiness.
So much snappiness.
Anyway, it's a good little show.
But this Sullivan's Crossing is cray-cray.
Cray-cray.
The guy is basically just an unlikable character.
He's just an old curmudgeon who runs a camp.
He's got this Sullivan's Crossing.
He goes, "Call me Sully. Blah, I'm Sully."
Name a Sullivan who wasn't called Sully.
That's what I know.
Who was like, "Call me Van."
Right.
No, he's just Sullivan.
Call me Van.
Van's Crossing.
His daughter.
There's one of them out there that I just call Goose Killer now.
Wait, does that mean the whole time it's been Sullivan?
Sullivan Halen?
Is that the way we should be?
Oh my gosh, it should have been Sullivan Halen.
Maybe it's Sylvainian Van Halen.
Sylvainian Halen.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to our show.
We are Sylvain Halen.
We are the number one tribute rock band.
We celebrate Van Halen and Sullivan's Crossings.
It is the best two things.
Sylvain Halen.
Here we are.
Sylvain Morrison.
If I had anything to reference Sullivan's Crossings,
I would do so right now for the sake of the joke.
His estranged daughter comes back to Sullivan's Crossing.
She's gone on to be a brain surgeon.
She's a literal, supposed to be a brain surgeon.
Now, Matt, how many years of education?
How dare I even reach her?
You know, I've got the hots.
Yeah, I've got the hots for teacher.
That's it.
Matt.
You've got to talk to your boys.
I know what I was going to say.
Right now.
They've got to do a couple Van Halen covers.
Yep.
Don't say anything else, Paul.
I'm done.
It's on our WhatsApp thread.
It'll be on there.
Ah, shoes burning down the avenue.
I'm hot for teacher.
What do you say?
What do you know?
I'm hot for teacher.
Eruption is what I was just thinking of.
Which one?
Yeah.
Eruption.
Just the guitar solo.
On accordion or harpsichord?
Yeah.
That's it.
Oh Lord.
That's...
Panama.
I've never been to Panama.
I've never been.
I'll never go.
Panama.
The country's quite large.
I'm stuck here.
Are there any pubs in Panama?
You know what his son was named?
Wolfgang.
Wolfgang Sullivan Halen.
All right.
I love the skip and dance.
I might just watch the show.
No.
Oh.
So the girl comes back and she's a neurosurgeon.
After all of that.
I'm so sorry.
She's a neurosurgeon.
How many years would you think would take to become a neurosurgeon?
Eight.
Study.
At least eight.
Yeah.
She's presenting around 24 tops.
Okay.
So we're already starting to do ramp jumps of logic.
Canadian Dookie Howser for those making a temporary reference.
Not even.
But she's not with it.
She misses everything.
Everything.
Her dad's a former alcoholic, recovering alcoholic.
She just misses everything.
Everything.
But one of the things that happened in this last episode that we watched.
He gets hospitalized with a heart condition.
Had a heart something go on.
And he's in the hospital.
And around all of this is the looming possibility that he's going to lose this Sullivan's crossing
campground because he can't pay the bills.
And Anne and I just looked at each other like he had a heart attack and was hospitalized.
If this was America, the show is over.
He has gone into full on.
Bankruptcy.
Forever debt.
He can't even do bankruptcy with medical debt.
He's done.
We were just like, this is amazing to see this from a Canadian perspective.
And he also got belligerent in the hospital and pushed a doctor and stuff.
And we're like, there would have been a security officer there shooting him in the head if
this was the States.
It's just so crazy to watch with a non-Canadian eye.
Oh, that's true.
Scoop Jesus in the chat is pointing out that Breaking Bad, just the concept of the show
of Breaking Bad does not work in Canada.
Because the whole impetus for the show is that he gets sick and can't afford the cancer
treatment.
That was everyone's number one takeaway from Breaking Bad.
And that's why you saw so much medical reform.
That's right.
Instead of medical reform, we have pizzas on roofs.
It is crazy.
Blue math.
That's actually what we got.
We have pizza on roofs and blue math.
You look at any hit drama.
That's exactly what we got.
Any hit drama that we've had of late.
The last, what, 20 years?
Yeah.
None of it works outside of the States because of the bullshit that we have integrated into
our society.
Well, so many movies, and then you get into the dated stuff.
So many movies in the States.
You've got the healthcare stuff.
And then the older movies, the plot goes away if anybody has a cell phone.
Right.
All these things.
It's great.
The whole movie goes away if things just aren't terrible.
Well, I mean, the show, The Wire, is one of the most celebrated shows we've made.
We don't need wires anymore.
Right.
The Wire, we don't need a wire.
And every season, that's it.
That whole show is just built on, every season was a different systematic failure of our
government bureaucracy.
Yeah.
It's just wild.
And then you get into the show that kind of started all of those back in the day on HBO.
You had Oz.
And it's just about, like, if you have any prison reform or if you have a decent justice
system, you don't have that show.
Right.
No, that show is about hot prison sex and I'm here for it.
Oh, man.
Oh, I'm not saying they're not great shows or that they don't have the amount of prison
sex that I need to get through the day.
I'm just saying they don't work outside of the U.S.
I'm happy with every other part of them.
But we're just, we're just watching that show and just mocking it at every turn and having
a good laugh here and there and really enjoys it though.
And it is kind of a nice relaxing show.
And I mean, it's honestly, it's like it's fantasy for us.
We're like, oh, man, you imagine living somewhere where people could talk to their neighbors
and then you could go and get taken care of when you had a heart attack and not lose your
fucking place of business.
Oh, God.
Not free enough.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Totally not free.
Not free enough to suffer.
Where is your freedom to pay?
Oh, well, it's a weird topic to bring up on a comedy show.
But we were on the air the other day during the Charlie Kirk stuff.
Oh, no, we can't talk about that.
We're not talking about it at all.
All I want to talk about with that is that it fucked me up for the day.
Well, sure.
Yeah.
Getting getting getting news that someone just got killed for being on shows, voicing
opinions like it fucked me up for the whole day.
I made a point to go to my comic book store, even though it was late in the day and I needed
I needed just I just picked up a few.
Oh, but here's OK.
So to shift topics completely.
Yeah, do it.
Do it.
I just wanted to say because we were on the air when it came out and then the show came
out and everything.
It feels weird to not say something about it.
But that's that's kind of what it was.
We don't need to go.
I mean, it happened right when we were on.
And then yes, the last couple of days have been not so weird, not so weird.
Yeah.
Bad news, Matt.
I get over guys.
Guys, guys, I got it.
I was reading up on on Israel and Gaza.
Should we just go there?
Should we?
No, let's just let's shift over to a fun topic at at the comic book shop.
I got to pick this up.
It's a brand new arc, brand new start of a new run of powers.
Oh, Matt's kids are going to be so.
So I'm so sorry that your son is probably going to find more of these books now and just
go to whackety jackety town for everybody on Twitch.
Just open up the centerfold.
Show everybody the centerfold.
Let's see.
Let's see what the centerfold is.
Don't do it on Twitch.
Look at the next issue.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, wow.
That's just that's just a jizz.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on there.
Yeah, it's not even drawn on there.
That's just all just showed us his jisms on a comic book.
Well, I'll take this.
I will show you.
That's just him.
Speaking of those laminated, speaking of a dialogue, this is Bendis dialogue right here.
That's what that that's what Bendis is known for.
Just talking, talking, talking, talking, talking, talking, talking.
For those of you who can't see the video, Paul just held up a comic book to the camera.
It was a full panel.
Just chuck a block with word.
It looked like a lot of speech bubbles.
A lot of word balloons.
Yes.
That's some that's a that's a Bendis hallmark right there.
And I'm pleased to see that again.
I'm looking forward to reading this new arc and seeing where it goes.
So yay.
New powers is out, everybody.
New powers, new powers, new powers.
Yeah, dead last celebrating as well.
That's good.
And what else?
Oh, and then and then I got this too.
This is for those other super nerds out there.
Transformers issue 24.
This is the culmination of the two year arc done by Daniel Warren Johnson and Jorge Corona.
This is the end of this story.
And this book has been incredibly successful.
What's his name?
Kirkman from Walking Dead.
This is one of his side project things.
He's taking over the main writing.
So that's going to be really interesting.
I would love to see the possibility of a Kirkman Transformers storyline that could be made.
Yes.
Television or film thing.
Preach.
Right.
No, no.
Do you know what Kirkman would add to that to that comic, Paul?
What would he add?
Snappy dialogue.
He's my dad.
Get some snappy dialogue in there.
So much snappy dialogue.
He's the guy behind.
You would open the comic.
It would snap right back close.
That's how snappy the dialogue would be.
Oh, it's so snappy.
Couldn't read it.
He does have some pretty good dialogue.
I mean, he's the guy behind Walking Dead.
He's the guy behind Invincible.
And I would love to see an Invincible style cartoon helmed by Robert Kirkman for Transformers.
I think that'd be awesome.
Are you watching any of the Peacemaker, Paul?
Peacemaker, Peacemaker.
Oh, I haven't watched the new season yet.
Yeah, I haven't either.
The first season was so good.
I really like the first season.
It was so funny.
Is it good?
Okay.
Yes.
How many episodes are we in now?
I think three.
I haven't watched two, but I think I have one on the hopper.
Scoop Jesus in the chat.
I'm with you.
We're letting it get a little ahead.
Yes.
And we'll probably binge a couple episodes at a time.
That's kind of my thing.
Yeah, I always want to give it a little.
That's what I'm doing with Task.
Oh.
Oh, how is that?
We tried to watch it.
I've heard it's good, but I'm not trying it yet.
I'm waiting for three or four or five episodes before I get into it.
We tried to watch it yesterday during all the, "Ugh," and we're watching it.
And Ann's like, "I'm already just a bundle of nerves and nothing's even happened in this
thing."
Nothing happens in the first 20 minutes or so that we watched, and she's just like, "Ugh."
And I was like, "Fine, I'll turn it off."
And I'm like, "We just watched that 'Evil Lives Here' latest episode with that horrible
kid that ended up going crazy and killed his mom and all that nutty stuff."
And she's like, "Yeah, but that's true.
This is made up.
Let's just watch what's already actually happened.
Why do we have to keep making up horrible stuff?"
I'm like, "Okay, you're right.
You're right.
We should focus on the reality of the horror show that is existent and not the fictional
horror show."
Also, we are going to talk about Gaza.
Oh, my God.
This is outrageous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one I stopped watching.
Did you ever get into Nerdcore rap?
MC Chris.
Yes, I love MC Chris.
And who's the other one that I like?
Well, there's a couple, but there's another guy that used to do PAX every year.
He was a mainstay.
But yeah, MC Chris is still my Nerdcore rap guy.
Why?
What's that?
I like a band that was Nerdcore rap without me knowing it was Nerdcore rap.
When I looked them up recently, I was literally on the plane and I was like, "I want to listen
to something."
I'm like, "Why?"
I would say I have nothing to listen to, and I used to listen to a ton of music, and I'm
always at a loss of what to listen to.
I do the same things, right?
I go into David Bowie or Tom Waits, Jag, or something like that, and then it's predictable.
I'm on a good music kick right now.
I'll tell you about it when you're done.
Was it?
I was like, "Oh, there was this band that crushed ... I saw them multiple times because
they just were always in lineups.
They were never the headliner.
They were always in lineups.
A band called Two Skinny Jays.
Are you familiar with them?
I have heard of them.
I am not familiar with their oeuvre.
They have one major album called Volumizer, and I put it on and I was like ... I thought
I was going to basically put it on and maybe be embarrassed or just nostalgic.
Uh-huh.
It is still a really good album.
It's a bang, huh?
It has some crazy, well-written lyrics, really good hooks.
They're very good musicians.
It's not constructed hooks.
They were a live band.
They got crushed at ... within a year and a half in college, somebody saw them twice
in concert at two different locations.
They must have been based out in the East Coast.
East Coast somewhere, yeah, yeah.
That's why Madden didn't finish college.
He was too busy following around the Two Skinny Jays.
Here's another person I saw too much of without being a huge fan.
G-Love and the Special Sauce.
Have you heard of them at all?
G-Love and the Special Sauce?
Yes, I remember them.
No.
Oh, they had a couple of hits.
They were more mainstream than Two Skinny Jays.
They actually had a couple of legit hits.
They were out of Philadelphia, and lyrically it's inescapable that they are from Philadelphia.
I say that as a Springsteen fan.
He never sings about Jersey.
That's one of the jams that Two Skinny Jays does that's very rare.
Grown Up is a good one to check it out.
I think I may know this song.
You've rattled something in my head from way back.
Yeah.
Grown Ups is the movie that they wrote starring Adam Sandler?
That's right.
Themed song.
Yep.
Yeah.
The opening song of Horns of Destruction is really great.
Horns of Destruction is really funny.
Lemon Drop is a good one.
But yeah, I was just going through it and I was really like, "Oh man, I'm usually embarrassed
about my music taste."
There was actually one band I thought of that I cannot go back, but I laughed when I thought
of their name.
So I won't even go back and listen to it.
It's too embarrassing.
I know it's bad.
Oh no.
I remember because I remember this really, really cringy incident of when I was on the
team bus for the basketball team and our team was basically half white and half black at
my JV squad when I was playing basketball.
And spoiler alert, the black guys were better at basketball.
Oh, that's where that rumor started.
Honestly, the cooler black kids would go sit in the back of the bus.
That's the way it works.
And they would all be putting their headphones on listening to different discs on their disc
bands.
Sure.
And I got turned into like one song by a rapper called MeFi Me.
Okay.
I can't even.
I won't.
If I listen to them now, I'll just vomit out of embarrassment.
I had MeFi Me on and I was like, oh, I might know a really awesome rapper that maybe they're
not familiar with.
And so I remember like bobbing my head and like really showing that you were doing some
hip hopping.
Yeah.
You were signaling that you were enjoying the hip hop.
I want the cooler black kids to know that I'm listening to hip hop and they're going
to ask me who and I'm going to say MeFi Me and they're going to go what?
And that's exactly what happened with the exception of the positive reaction.
Okay.
They were like, get that trash out of here.
I never heard of that.
One guy's like, yeah, I heard one.
He's got one trick that's okay.
And then the guy was like, oh.
I'm like.
Well, that's all right.
That's a start.
And then they just made fun of me for being into it.
They're like, but you were really into it.
Oh, man.
See.
It's Donnelly's worst nightmare.
This is our difference in age.
This is our difference in age showing.
And I was just lucky.
I was just lucky because I was a few years ahead of you and into the hip hop stuff, which
I'm just going to argue was a golden age of hip hop that I came up in.
And so you would talk about someone who never gets embarrassed.
I don't get embarrassed.
I don't give a shit.
I've always put my freak flag very high and not giving a fuck what people think I would
be in the back of the bus with my boombox on field trips and my two deck cassette player.
I would vacillate between body count, public enemy, fear of a black planet, the Disney
afternoon soundtrack, and they might be giants.
I mean, what?
All over the place.
Crazy shit.
You know what I mean?
I ain't give a fuck.
All the hits, all the hits, all over the place.
And then I really lucked out.
I really scored some points at Governor's Scholars.
Yes.
Paul definitely had the over the shoulder boombox at Governor's Scholars Program.
Don't think anything else for a moment.
No, it was too wide for, I mean, you could, but it had a handle.
But Governor's Scholars Program, we had a field trip out to a mall one day.
Paul put that double decker right on his lap like a villain with a cat.
That's exactly how I rocked it.
What I did have was a 60 cassette case that I held over my, I had all my ammunition belt.
I was a straight up, no, not an amp, but it was a padded case, a padded case that held
30 cassettes.
What?
Well, it was like the movie poster for Commando with just cassette decks all over them.
There's Chewbacca with tapes on my bandolier.
I was ready at any time.
Whatever the, whatever the thing I had, I had everything, man.
I had it all.
Scoop Jesus says you look like John Popper.
I had, I had Pantera, I had fucking, what's his name, the Harry Connick dude.
I had it all.
I would go between Pantera and Harry Connick in the drop of a hat.
At Governor's Scholars, we went to this mall field trip and we bought some stuff.
I bought Tribe Called Quest's Low End Theory album.
It had just come out.
Oh, that's a good album.
That's a good album.
It came out that week.
Yeah.
Getting on the bus, some of the other kids and some of the other hip hop heads were like,
"Oh, let's listen to that."
They played it on the bus speakers.
The whole bus was listening to Low End Theory on the ride, thanks to my purchasing finesse
of making sure that I got that new Tribe album, which was just, that's just a fantastic album.
It's a masterpiece.
Paul Mattingly, everyone.
You're welcome, everyone.
Hero.
Paul Mattingly.
Ten Scoop is showing exactly how Spock would have handled me back then, but it was a different
time before the rise of headphones like that.
You know who else listened to a whole bunch of Mattingly's cassettes in the back of a
school bus?
Mattingly didn't know they were there, though.
That's the following sponsor.
I would have been popped in my head so hard.
Yeah.
I know you were.
Pop.
Today's show is brought to you by Women, brought to you by Tom Cruise.
That's from MLK in 2025.
Today's sponsor is Women, brought to you by Tom Cruise.
Hey, everybody.
It's me, Tom Cruise.
I'd like to present Women.
I'd like to, but I can't.
Yeah.
Oh, I got to run.
I got to run to my next-- shoot.
Oh, boy.
I'd also have trouble presenting Women, because my good friend David Miscavige misplaces his,
and we don't try to find them.
That's just how it goes.
Allegedly.
Who knows?
Enter eight scoops of checkout.
Yeah.
I was thinking about Tom Cruise this morning, and then everyone makes fun of him for running,
and he always likes to run in his films, and he always runs full speed.
And then I was like, oh, I couldn't do that.
If I booked a part, and they're like, this is where you run full speed to the airport
for like 30 seconds, I'd be like, oh, this is going to look terrible.
I don't think anybody makes fun of Tom Cruise, though.
We don't make fun of his running because he's an older gentleman and is bad at running.
We make fun of it because he does it so often.
I don't think there's any question that Tom Cruise is in great shape for a man of his
age.
Yeah.
It's not like he's like, oh, I have to do this.
He's coming to the producers and being like, can I dangle from a plane, please?
This is the part where I run.
Yeah.
He's making it happen, Matt.
Don't feel bad that way.
You're going to be fine.
Also, in today's modern age, what sense does it make not to be on roller skates or some
sort of ambulatory device that could make you go even faster than running?
I was thinking, they'd have to ride in like an electric scooter for me to be like, and
I was like, oh, that'd be really fun just to actually see an electric scooter chase.
Yeah.
It's like really fucking like born identity level, but just pushing that little thumb
button.
It'd be fun.
Yeah.
It'd be good.
Man, I am a sucker for those.
I treated myself in San Antonio.
I always go try to get my steps in, right, so try to get my 10,000 steps in.
Yeah.
And so I kept telling myself that I'd rather have electric scooters, but every time I just
had...
It was hot, so I had to get my steps in close at night, close to midnight, or whatever.
But the last night, I go, oh, I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to walk.
I only had to walk for like 15 minutes.
I go, I'm going to walk 15 minutes straight out of town and I'm going to find one of those
scooters and ride it back.
Yeah.
And that's what I did my last night.
And man, I know it's so dumb they go like whatever, 15 miles an hour, but bopping and
zipping through the streets at night and you're just going all over it because it was a Sunday
night, right?
That whole week, whenever I'm there, it's like a show because the river walks the center
of attention and it builds during the week and then it's crazy in the weekends.
And then Sunday, it's like you feel like it's great receding.
I remember the Sunday night bar shit.
It's probably busier than Vegas right now.
Probably.
Although I guess the reports come from people who worked with that company or that tourism
is down in a lot of places, not just Vegas.
No.
Yeah, sure.
What?
Yeah.
Probably unrelated to anything else.
In the United States of America?
Yeah.
The land of dreams?
Where the rivers flow with milk and honey?
Because if people pick up the news, there's nothing but sunshine and rainbows here.
Right.
This is just like the Garden of Eden out here on the good ship, lollipop.
But no, so Sunday night it was dead.
And so I basically had the streets of San Antonio to myself.
That's right.
I want to say it very romantically like that.
I just zipped around.
I was loving it.
I probably look like a big idiot, but I had loved it.
I had my Mi Fi Mi on my headphones and...
Great.
Before you listening to Streets of Philadelphia and replacing it, "San Antonio."
San Antonio.
I was just singing that loudly to myself.
"The streets of San Antonio."
It almost fits the meter.
It means red stick, I'd yell as I drove down the street.
That's right.
Have you had a show since, since you've modified your language yet?
No, not yet.
Not yet.
My next magic show will be at ScoopFest.
Okay.
Where I'm only doing things they haven't seen.
Sweet.
New, new stuff.
Bunch of, a bunch of feet stuff.
Yeah.
A lot of feet stuff.
A lot of feet.
A lot of bare feet.
Magic.
Yeah.
Borrowed, borrowed, and returned feet.
Oh my God.
Foot to impossible location.
Matt.
You know.
Foot tip.
I use a foot tip in this trick.
So we have yet to actually implement with PNT the, the, the magic that is magic Wanda.
That's true.
How about we have magic Wanda and your bare foot with googly eyes on it.
Yeah.
And we call him Presto.
Presto.
Magic Wanda and Presto.
Huh?
Somebody just laying underneath the curtain with their foot up in the air.
Dude, that's a YouTube channel if I've ever heard one right there.
I know.
That is, that's gold.
It's also in 12 years the best idea that Paul has come up with.
And he's like, pitch this to pin, Matt.
They did sled a foot.
This is by far.
Did they?
Three seasons ago.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, they did on Fool Us, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was one where I helped work on that trick and I gave Penn a button on it.
Okay.
Where after the whole thing was over, he says like, oh, you can put those cards back together
or whatever.
And then she, the volunteer goes to do it, I go, no, with your feet.
And they like that.
And that was always there.
They're out.
And then I went to record at Penn Sunday School and Penn said, Matt, you are a genius.
And then Teller wrote me an email saying, you are a genius.
Wow.
And I didn't know why.
And then Penn told me at Penn Sunday School is that basically like this very hammered
girl came up to do a sleight of feet.
And when they yell no with your feet, she was like, oh, okay.
And she just flipped herself upside down and started moving with her feet and she wasn't
wearing any underwear.
So she just was flashing Penn and Teller.
Yeah.
That sounds like they're out there with a private show and they were like, what a great
profession we have.
What an odd job we have chosen for ourselves.
So they both wrote me privately to let me know I was a genius.
Great job, buddy.
Oh, I got to tell you my music thing.
I've been on a kick lately, full albums.
So all I do when I run through an album now is I do a Google search or a chat GPT search,
whatever search engine I've got, kind of most handy.
And I ask like, what is the best album from, and I just pick a random decade or year or
whatever.
And then I listen to that full album.
But it's always an album that was made to be a complete album.
So like this week, I've listened to Elton John, Yellow Brick Road, and yesterday I just
finished Purple Rain.
I just finished the Purple Rain album.
And holy fuck, Prince is really good.
What?
Breaking news?
Yeah.
Prince is really good at this.
I knew it.
I knew what he was doing.
Like when doves cry, go listen to when doves cry, do yourself a favor, listen to when doves
cry, and it's a perfect song.
The reason it's so ubiquitous is it's just fucking perfect.
Yeah, he's really, really good.
It is one of those things where it is worth a re-listen for those things.
And you're right, Jacob, I will take you up on that because he was so popular that like
you understood music to be that.
Like for instance, that my kids started listening to Michael Jackson's music, which is just
no inner conflict there.
But the thing is like, you're like, oh, he really just had like, his voice honestly is
like it's unique and it's okay.
It's not amazing, right?
But he had two superpowers that he could dance his face off, really believe in dancing, and
his ear for sounds is just the actual composition of sounds and music is that.
So I think like I got distracted because someone put my website in the chat.
I don't know why.
Oh, that was me, sorry.
In the chat, somebody was asking where they could find dates for your show, so I put your
website up.
Oh yeah, I haven't updated it.
You got to go to my Instagram for the updated dates, but I got to update it.
My next dates are, and this is really important, Scoopfest, then we're going on a bunch of
cruise ships, and then I'm going to be in Sparta, New Jersey.
Sparta.
On October 17th, doing two shows there, and then yeah, and then after that, there'll be
a special show in October that we haven't announced yet, but I'll announce after Scoopfest.
Yes.
Because it evolves palmatically.
And what else?
I think, I think, I'm about to enter cruise ship season, which is why I'm being, this
is, I'm going to do a bunch of cruise ships through the holidays.
Cruise ships through the holidays?
I'll be back in San Antonio.
Okay.
The third, November 3rd through the 8th.
But the big thing, I've been making a big stick, because then come the turn of the year,
Jokers of Magic is going back out on tour, and when all those dates are locked in, that's
going to be at the start of the new year.
There'll be two different tours, one in January and one in March, and we'll be all over the
place, and I will be pumping those dates a ton, because that's the show I want to be
doing.
Right.
Yes.
That show is awesome.
If you didn't get to see the first run, it is such a fun show.
Anyhow, I want to go back and listen to those Prince albums, because I actually want to
understand that these sounds didn't really exist, because I just, I grew up with those
being music, and so you're like, "Yeah, yeah, it's pretty good," but I think it's so cool
to go back and really hear the sounds and the tones of the instrumentation of those
songs.
So I'm listening to the Purple Rain album, and Darling Nikki is one of the songs on there,
and it's all about a woman masturbating in a hotel lobby, and then has sex with her,
and then she invites him to come back, and it's all this stuff.
He's Shakespeare, right?
You find the core stories of the American Dream.
It was revolutionary at the time, because it was very female-forward, very woman-empowered.
She's taking control of her own sexuality.
She has him come up for a one-night stand.
Oh, yeah.
No, she's in charge.
In the song, she is fully in charge.
She rocks him with everything in the book.
She's got the whips, the chains, the whole secret room thing, and then she's out the
door before he's even awake and just leaves a note, "Kissy, kissy, you want to do it
again sometime?
Let me know."
"Hit me up next time you want to grind."
Yeah, and she's just like, she's out.
So it was very female-forward and very empowering.
The end of that song has some of the backwards stuff on there, so if you listen to Darling
Nikki, at the end of it, it is something being played in reverse on the track.
So I was out walking, listening to Darling Nikki, and I texted a buddy of mine, Andy,
who is previously the president of the official Prince fan club.
He has every piece of music that Prince has ever released, and then every piece of music
that he can get his hands on, bootlegs, all that kind of stuff.
So I texted him and said, "Hey, I'm listening to Purple Rain, listening to Darling Nikki.
What is the backwards part at the end of Darling Nikki?"
Because I knew he would just
I was like, "Andy will just know this.
He'll know it off the top of his head.
He won't even have to look it up."
So he texts me back.
He said
I have this in my head.
You know what?
What is it, Paul?
Do you know what it is?
It's something to the effect of, "Thank you, friends, for listening to this.
We hope you enjoyed the song," kind of thing.
It's weirder than that.
What does it say?
It is, "Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine, 'cause I know the Lord is coming soon."
Oh, Lord?
"Coming soon."
Oh, no.
Well, he was deep in that
Because remember, Prince was super religious as well.
He was.
Yeah.
I would
I'm still
There's a ton of stuff at the end of a bunch of these songs, including like Purple
Rain, When Doves Cry, all this stuff.
There's a lot of really Jesus-y stuff in there too, and it is
It's a little weird, but it's also kind of like a glimpse into Prince, and I'm kind
of enjoying that part as well.
I wish we could have gotten that Kevin Smith documentary.
Yeah, and then the other one is on the shelf too, right?
Yeah.
And then there was another one that anyone who's seen it says is amazing, but it got
held up by the dumbest legal technicality.
Right.
Yeah.
They said they were going to make a six
They signed the contracts for a six-episode documentary, and the guy who made it said,
"No, it needs a seventh episode," and because I went to a seventh episode, the Prince part
of the production team got to say, "You broke contract.
No one gets to see it."
Awful.
Yeah.
Well, this would be my recommendation, Matt, for you, MC Chris Friends.
Okay.
It's an EP, so it's a quick listen, and it's all Batman and Robin, so I think you'll
like it.
All right.
I will give it a listen.
Cool.
All right, friends, it is me, Guillermo del Toro, I have tried my best to make a Evangelion
live-action film, but of course, many things got in the way of my production, not the least
of which, just trying to make giant robots.
It's tough.
So what I decided to do, take a much of the pre-production material from that and go ahead
and make my own Kaiju film, and I did, and what I have created is the Pacific Rim, but
now I have the two of the films under the belt.
I had the guy doing the thing from Lost in the Gang of Mean People, Dangerous People
Show.
Lost in the Gang of Mean People, yeah.
The Gang of Mean People Show.
So I got the Gang of Dangerous People Show, man, who do the movie, and I'm like, "Ah,
that's okay."
But now I realize the money is in the pornography.
So I say, "Okay, let's go," and I want to do this the right way, so I am bringing
Yena Yemisin out of retirement, yes, and Yena Yemisin.
Who?
Yena Yemisin.
Yeah.
No, it's all right.
Who?
Her name is Yena Yemisin.
You say Yena?
Yena Yemisin.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
I hear, "Yes, I am a saint."
Is that what you hear?
Hold on, hold on.
Let me look this up.
Oh, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I have a pronunciation all messed up.
I may say, "Beladonna."
Okay, so Beladonna is going to do this new movie, and she is going to do what is going
to be called, "Specific Rim."
Yeah.
One specific rim that she wants to get her tongue on, and it's the Charlie Mann from
the, "I Got the Gang of Bean People" movie, and so the whole movie about her in a haunted
house trying to find one specific rim.
And you see-
Enter eight scopes of check-out.
Yeah, no robots.
Oh, there's a robot, a double-headed robot.
Well, okay.
Tell me what I did.
I guess some of these new dildos do have AI.
That has to be true, right?
There have to be sex toys with AI by now, right?
No, but I guess technically, you can't call it a dildo if it has technical parts, right?
I think so.
Yes.
Yes, Mr. Deltoro.
I believe that is true.
Look, I am not a dildo expert.
It seems like you are.
Wink.
No, no.
My name is Jacob.
I am of course a dildo expert.
Benicio Deltoro.
Dildo expert.
I mean, look at Benicio Deltoro.
Guillermo Deltoro.
Look up the definition of Guillermo Deltoro.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry.
Guillermo.
Benicio Deltoro.
Not that hack.
Not that dildo expert.
Scoop Jesus's artificial intelligence.
Yes.
Mmm.
The AI inside.
Guillermo Deltoro.
Say that again?
He's selling a bunch of his old movie props.
Is he really?
Yes.
I don't know if it's an existential thing or he's just trying to make some room for
stuff.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's an existential thing or he's just trying to make some room for
stuff.
Because he's got a lot of shit.
Right.
Have you seen anything that you want?
Oh my God.
I mean, not really because horror collectibles aren't my thing.
All right.
But, you know, one or two pieces would be kind of cool.
No, I mean, I'm really happy.
I actually already bought something from his.
Oh, really, man?
What did you get?
I got a case of snappy dialogue.
Oh, it's so snappy.
Yeah.
Guillermo del Toro's snappy dialogue.
I tried to open up the case and it was snap, snap, right shut.
Too snappy.
You know, is there a horror memorabilia thing that either of you would really want from
old horror films or either of you old horror hits?
I'd want the giant pot of boiling water from sleepaway camp.
That's what I would guess.
Oh, really?
Oh.
That got the big fat guy?
They got the big fat guy and he holds up his burning arms.
Yeah.
That's where the whole.
It's all jellied out?
Yeah.
Oh, that movie's something else.
There was, there was a time when I was a teenager, I was probably like 15, 16 years old, where
I was so over horror movies.
I was just a kid.
I was like fucking horror movies.
They're not scary at all, but I would go see them because they would have naked teenagers
in them.
Oh, yeah.
And like after the first, what, half hour of the movie, I'd be like, well, they probably
aren't going to be any more naked teenagers.
I'm kind of done with this movie.
That.
Yes.
I mean, that's sort of the formula, right?
Yeah.
But I was not interested in watching the horror movie part at all.
It was just like the horror movie part, which to me was just boring and stupid.
Jacob, have you seen any of the "Terrifier" films?
I saw the first one.
Okay.
Yeah.
I watched it with Matt's kids.
I was going to say, I still want to do a "Terrifier 3" with Matt's kids.
They loved it.
"Terrifier 3" with Matt's kids would be like a big Patreon level.
I just, I just bid on eBay for a cracked sidewalk that was the path of death's design.
So when it was, when it was cracking through the streets, I got, I got that crack there.
Someone has to have Freddy Krueger's, Freddy Krueger's glove, right?
Oh, there's, that has to be.
Yeah.
There's a couple of those.
Cause they, they did it different for a couple of the movies, right?
Yeah.
The movies went on long enough that there's a Freddy Krueger, and I bet Robert England
has one in his personal collection.
Probably a few.
Yeah.
Like the classic stuff, uh, like, like Freddy Krueger's stuff, uh, I'm talking like even
for like, he's collecting all the hammer horror stuff.
Like he's got like old Wolfman and Bella Lugosi shit.
I would love any of that stuff, like the, like the classic horror stuff.
Any of that stuff would, would, I'd, I'd display that very happily in my house.
Uh, like the pinhead stuff.
Hellraiser, I was a big Hellraiser fan of those early movies and everything.
Yeah.
There's probably some stuff that I'd like.
I, uh, yeah, they had a replica.
Um, that's actually when you watch Penn and Teller do needles, it's actually pulling the
pins from pinhead out of Teller's mouth.
Oh God.
Oh, that's, it is though.
Those are pinheads.
I've always wondered.
I, yeah.
Oh, good old pinhead.
Yeah.
That's right.
Cause he takes the pins, he takes the needles out and puts them in like a, I think I might
be conflating Teller's version of this with a bunch of other people's versions of this,
but does he take, does he take the needles out and put them in like a lemon or something
or a pincushion?
He takes them out of an apple to start.
That's what it is.
It's an apple.
Yeah.
He eats them from the apple and then he pulls them out.
Uh, so he could have like a little, instead of an apple, he could just have a little pinhead
prop and then he could just be taking the needles out of pinhead's head, I guess.
That would be, yeah.
That's nice.
I'm a, I'm going to send him a DM right now.
Teller, I have a note, I have a note on needles for you.
What's that thing called?
I have a note on your oldest, best, whatever.
What's the name of the puzzle box for the Hellraiser?
It's got a name.
Oh, it does.
Nepronomicon.
It's something like, it's something like the paint, the, the paint-a-cron or something
like that, the Lament Configuration.
Thank you, Steve Jasper.
Uh, Teller's street show, by the way, that, I don't think he's performed a trick more
than needles.
Uh, uh.
Has to be.
His most, his most performed trick.
Yeah.
That's what, he has a little, he had a little mat and he says, the show will begin when
all the needles are in the apple and he put out his mat and his little table and he just
starts sticking needles into an apple and that's when people, that's how people would
gather around him when he's a street performer.
Right.
When he's out gathering.
Yeah.
Just, who's this guy putting needles into an apple and what's going, what's about to
happen here?
Yes.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
Andy Cheek asking if I have any movie props.
I don't have any official movie props.
I've got a lightsaber, but it's not, you know, a real lightsaber exactly.
So I would like to have a real lightsaber.
Do you have any?
Director's cut.
So you know, so you do have some actual screen used, uh, movie props.
Yeah.
That's cool.
Somewhere.
Yeah.
It counts.
Oh, some big stuff.
I don't know.
I've got some stuff around here somewhere.
I just don't know what I have.
I don't know.
I have Judy Gau's ruby slippers.
Oh, that's nice.
I think I have, uh, in my house somewhere, I think I have a cane that FDR used.
That's probably my best prop is that.
That's definitely your best one.
It's right where it is.
FDR's cane.
I'm going to go with that.
For people who don't know, Matt does actually have a cane that FDR used.
After it was in a show in the episodes where we joked that it was FDR's cane, we found
out after the fact that it was FDR's cane.
That's really weird.
That's a really weird series of events.
And it was used in the show as FDR's cane.
Yes.
That's some weird shit.
It was an old cane from "Grandma Ruby's House."
That's the funniest thing.
We just talked about this for what?
Five minutes?
Yeah.
I am surrounded by Ruby Keeler stuff.
Of course.
Yeah.
You've got tons of film use props.
I'm lousy with Ruby Keeler stuff.
So yeah.
You have a Hollywood Walk of Fame on your wife's family tree.
Yeah.
You know what happened to that giant typewriter she danced on?
No.
Oh, I've got that.
I'm using it right now.
That is something.
I should have pitched this to the people who work behind the scenes at Spiegel World because
they put these different events and shows together, but I thought that Spiegel World
should get Sean and John together with my wife and reenact the tap dancing on the typewriter
bit.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
That typewriter prop was ... If you don't know what we're talking about, you can YouTube
Ruby Keeler dancing on a typewriter, and it's a famous movie musical bit.
It's from the movie, the 1937 film, "Ready, Willing, and Able."
After its use in the film, the typewriter became part of the film's production design
and is now considered a piece of movie memorabilia, even though its current location is not known.
Yeah.
I bet that just got-
I mean, back in those days, it was-
I'm assuming it got taken apart in these projects.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even just recently, even through the '90s, stuff just got trashed, man.
Oh, yeah.
Well, a lot of stuff gets reused, broken down and reused for different things.
Right.
Sometimes, yeah, but-
Yeah, if you can reuse it, they're breaking it down and reusing it for the next thing.
A lot of times, people just throw shit away, man.
Especially in the movie, the studio era.
Yes.
Is it true or is it false that the Falkor is the animal skin in "Dumb and Dumber"?
That was a rumor.
I don't know if that was actually true.
I don't think that was actually the- But they might have repurposed part of him for the
mutthut truck.
Yeah.
That's what I kept hearing as a rumor.
It might have been.
It might have been repurposed and-
I don't think it was.
It feels too good to be true.
Yeah.
It's not quite the same fur either.
Right.
Yeah.
Google says, "No.
Not used there."
Yeah.
But, yeah, it was a good thing because it wasn't close in time, was it?
The never-ending story-
No.
It was a long way off.
Was much earlier, right?
In fact, I do believe, I remember just a couple years ago, someone actually still has Falkor
in their barn somewhere.
Like kind of rotting away.
Half-rotten.
Oh.
Yeah.
Slower fall.
That's too sexy.
Yeah.
Like, the way that-
Show me that half-rotten Falkor.
Have you seen those fucking Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle heads from the Henson designs?
Oh, yeah.
Nowadays?
Yes.
They look-
I have a friend who worked on the construction of those.
Oh, wow.
They look crazy now.
Yeah.
That's insane.
Right.
NECA made a line of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles cross-universal monsters because they had both
those licenses.
Mm-hmm.
This was like two years ago.
They made, you know, figures of the turtles as monsters.
They had like Leo as Frankenstein and I think Raphael was a vampire.
They made Michelangelo a mummy, right?
Okay.
And they based his head sculpt design off of the rotting mask of the one that was used
in the movies.
Oh, jeez.
It looks very much like-
It's really cool.
It looks kind of skeletal.
It's wild.
If you look up, you know, rotten Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle head-
The people on the Zoom, we're about to see it right now.
Yeah.
No, I know.
We're talking with a puppeteer, Tim Lagasse, who is big in the puppet world.
He's the one who taught that puppet workshop to my kids.
And he basically says that like, you know, all the material that goes into puppets eventually
rots.
Yes.
Right.
Even like sponge and stuff like that, like sponge will just dry out and become dust.
Exactly.
Yep.
So you always have to update stuff.
And Jacob just showed me some pictures that looked horrible.
That looked really scary.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And you're just running away and then you have the teeth in there and they don't run
away.
And if you look up NECA Michelangelo mummy figure-
My search history is already weird enough, I'm fine.
It's basically that same head.
Also leading up to ScoopFest, boy do my Amazon recommendations get weird fast.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
As I buy things on Amazon for ScoopFest, my recommendations get real weird real quick.
But most of the time you're just searching on the site jackable.com, right?
That's right, that's right.
Cookies un-gaged.
Turn them cookies on, time to jack it.
Speaking of jacking it, it's time for Jock Versus Nerd.
Winner gets the jacket.
Right here on Switch.
Jock Versus Nerd action.
Who am I?
Oh boy.
It's exactly, it's exactly that Rotten Smash.
On the hunt for balls.
No, Rotten Michelangelo.
We got a Scooperty today from Scoopy Logic, Scoopy Logic sent this one in a couple of
years ago.
I've gone back into the old Wayback machine here and found this Scooperty that Scoopy
Logic sent in I think in 2023.
Anyway, the categories are not only a Fruit, Deals of a Lifetime, TMNT, very coincidental
there, and Hodgepodge.
Oh neat, I love it.
I'm up first.
We got some TMNT.
I'll try TMNT for 200, let's see.
This actor voiced Shredder in the original cartoon series will accept his best known
role.
Oh cool.
Oh, I have zero idea.
I have to pass.
This is Philip Seymour Hoffman.
No.
Famously Philip Seymour Hoffman.
Paul, who is it?
It's the guy who played Uncle Phil on The Fresh Prince.
Oh, interesting.
That's right.
I did know that.
James Avery.
Yes.
Matt.
If that's the $200 question, forget about it.
I know, right?
I will do not only a Fruit for 200.
A berry.
This tropical fruit naturally grows in bundles.
It's better than naturally growing in bindles.
Right, right, right.
Only hobos eat this berry.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul.
Bananas.
It's a banana.
It's technically a berry.
That's right.
Paul is technically in the lead.
Paul, you're up.
TMNT, please.
For 400.
The multicolored masks were established in the original cartoon.
What color did they all wear previously in the comics?
Red.
Damn it.
I knew that one.
Red.
I should have done.
I should have gone there.
Paul out with a commanding lead right now.
800 to 0 to 0.
Baton Rouge.
Baton Red.
I'm just getting the basics, though.
We got, you know, just getting the simple questions.
All right.
You have to smack talk with your lead, buddy.
Yeah.
We'll see.
I'll try TMNT.
Try to steal one from Paul for 600.
Here we go.
This TV producer is credited with writing the classic theme song.
I don't fucking know.
Matt.
God damn it.
Stevie Wonder.
No.
I don't know.
Stevie Wonder.
Paul.
Fred Wolf.
Chuck Lorre.
Oh, it's Chuck Lorre.
Okay.
Chuck Lorre.
Yeah.
And Paul's points are gone.
Matt.
I've got 200.
Hodgepodge.
James Bond creator Ian Fleming wrote this book that in 1968 was turned into a children's
movie starring Dick Van Dyke.
Hmm.
Deep Throat.
God.
Does it say, would you say Mary Poppins was starring Dick Van Dyke?
Probably not.
It was.
I mean, he was the...
Yeah.
He was one of the leads in that.
It was like the actual timeframe.
Yeah.
Oh, it's not it though, I don't think.
I think I know.
Passes to Paul.
Shitty, shitty, bang, bang.
Shitty, shitty, bang, bang is correct.
Cool.
Shitty, shitty, bad, bad.
Paul.
TMNT, please.
For 800.
According to Internet Conspiracy, what band was created after touring in a live action
TMNT concert series?
Oh man.
I don't know.
But I do know...
Come on, Paul.
You know this one.
Michael Ian Black was part of the promo team for The Turtle's Way back in the day.
I feel of great kinship with him doing costume work.
I'll pass.
I don't know.
You don't know about The Turtle's?
What band would you guess?
It's probably a boy band.
Probably...
No, it's The Turtle's.
No.
NKOTB, I bet.
I have no idea.
I'm passing.
Matt.
I bet the guess is New Kids.
Black Eyed Peas.
Oh, wow.
The Black Eyed Peas.
"Tonight's Gonna Be a Good Fight" was the original lyric.
Oh, yeah.
Let's get some pizza in here.
Let's get some pizza.
I'll try not only a fruit, a gourd.
The season is almost upon us.
Prepare for the olfactory overload.
Ah, yes.
Wait, what?
Oh, is it pumpkin or pumpkin spice or all those things?
Pumpkin.
Yeah, pumpkin.
It's pumpkin, pumpkin.
I don't know anything, huh?
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself.
You know some things.
Let's go with Hodgepodge for 400.
This American actor accidentally killed two people while driving in Ireland in 1987.
This definitely tickles something in my brain.
I think it's in there somewhere.
I know, I'm trying to think, is it Robert Downey Jr.?
He got in a lot of trouble.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul!
Um, his name is flying out of my head right now.
And into two people walking.
No, it's fucking Ferris Bueller.
Matthew, Matthew...
Damon.
Fuck, what is his name?
Matthew...
Sully.
Matthew Sullivan's Crossing.
Fuck, why can't I get his name?
It's going to be really funny if Paul's just doing a gamesmanship here to try to get me
to say his name.
I can't get his name.
I can't, it won't come to me.
Matthew...shit.
Harry.
No, pass.
I can't get his name.
Matthew Broderick, Paul?
There you go.
That's it.
I'll try Matthew Broderick.
I could not get it.
No, you could not get his name.
Paul!
Uh, Hodgepodge for $600, please.
Children's book author Roald Dahl wrote the screenplay for which James Bond movie?
Oh, boy.
James and the Giant Spy.
That's a...
I'll pass.
I don't know.
Pass this to me.
I'm trying to think of like, what are the weirder James Bond movies?
Like Octopussy is a weird one.
That one's all set with like a circus troupe and stuff.
Yeah.
There are some weird ones out there.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt?
That is James Bond, of course, Sleeping Foot to Face.
I bet it was Dr. No, but I don't know.
I don't know at all.
Dr. No was the first Bond movie.
Was it?
You Only Live Twice.
I think that's the one where...
I think You Only Live Twice is the Sean Connery one where he does Yellow Face.
Yes.
I think he dresses up as a Japanese man in that movie.
It's me.
It's my Deals of a Lifetime, 200.
It's a B.
In 2007, this creative team negotiated for 50% of all digital rights for their show and
have made almost $1 billion since.
Wow.
Creative team negotiated for 50% of all digital rights of their show.
What was this category?
Deal of a Lifetime.
Oh.
So these are smart people who made a really smart deal.
Yeah.
I have no idea.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt.
I think this is Trey Parker and Matt Stone.
Oh, that would make sense.
I think you're right.
Good call.
It is Trey Parker and Matt Stone.
Well done.
Matt.
I knew a thing.
Look at you go.
Boy, they must be.
They are cleaning up.
Clearly.
Yeah.
You heard it here first, folks.
Trey Parker and Matt Stone doing fine.
The reference to that, if you watched them, they're funny.
They are.
Deals of a Lifetime, 400, please.
Outside of the small pittance of merchandising and sequel rights, how much was George Lucas
paid to direct the Star Wars, the original Star Wars film, within $50,000?
Everyone knows he was paid with candy.
That's right.
I don't know.
Pass.
Paul.
How much was George Lucas paid?
It wasn't.
I don't even know if it was $100,000.
I'll pass.
I don't remember.
Yeah.
I mean, he can't have been paid much.
Do I need to guess?
Oh, no.
I'm in the lead.
I don't want to guess.
Pass.
$150,000.
Wow.
Paul would have gotten points if he had said $100,000.
I would direct Star Wars now for that money, just so you know.
Oh, OK.
I need $160,000 minimum.
I'm going to stand fast on that.
Paul.
I'll close out Hodgepodge.
For $800,000.
Daily double.
Here we go.
We finally found one.
Oh, now it's for the real deal.
Volkswagen's top selling product is not a vehicle, but iconically German food.
Wolf brand chili.
Well it's either a pretzel or a bratwurst.
Two bits.
I'll go pretzel.
A pretzel?
A currywurst sausage.
Oh.
A currywurst sauce-age.
Who would have accepted bratwurst?
If you had said currywurst, I would have accepted currywurst.
Yeah.
Currywurst.
I might have even accepted sausage.
It's me.
I'll try Deals of a Lifetime 600.
We got four questions left.
One daily double left.
In a 1986 antitrust lawsuit, the USFL, Donald Trump successfully sued the NFL, winning how
much money?
Hint.
Pick a number.
1 through 10.
I don't remember.
Next map.
A dollar.
$1.
$3.
Oh shoot.
I was ready to guess $1 too.
I watched the documentary.
They presented him with the check.
This is back when he wasn't who he is now, and so it was a very embarrassing moment.
Later on he would go on to prove that he wasn't capable of embarrassment, so there you go.
But very capable of vengeance, it turns out.
Yeah.
Holds a grudge for a while.
I'll go with Deals of a Lifetime to close it out.
Oh no, it's Matt's turn.
Great.
It's Matt's turn.
I need to make up some ground here, so I will steal Paul's question and do Deals of a Lifetime
for 800.
Daily double.
There you go.
Now you got it, Matt.
Paul with the gamesmanship.
Retired in 2001, this former NYMET receives a little over $1 million annually for every
July 1st until 2035.
Bobby Bonilla, baby.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
How did he do that?
Bobby Bonilla.
I have friends, my Mets friends, the day that it pays, they go, "It's happy Bobby Bonilla
Day," and it's the day that Bobby Bonilla is still being paid by the Mets.
What happened?
So basically they gave him a crazy contract to play baseball, which happens at baseball
more than any other sport, and then he ended up being so terrible, they wanted him to stop
playing, and there was no rules yet on stretch provisions, and so they basically, to not
hurt their salary cap or not hurt their bottom line or whatever, they asked if they could
stretch his contract out for whatever it was, like 27 years or something like that.
Anyone who got paid now is not even considered ridiculous, but back then it was a ridiculous
amount of money to play horribly for the Mets.
It's a ridiculous amount of money to not do anything.
Well, ask Kawhi Leonard.
Who's that?
Oh, you don't know about this one?
He's the man who's getting paid a ridiculous amount of money right now for not doing anything.
Made a really, really good ... If we did old school jock versus nerd, this would have been
the question of the week for sure, but Kawhi Leonard was paid $28 million to not show up
or do anything for this company that was a sponsor of the L.A. Clippers.
Oh, this was the way they got his ... It was like phantom salary.
Yes, it was to get around the salary cap, to give him an extra bonus money inside the
salary cap.
At least that's being investigated right now.
It's just blowing up now, right?
But it was supposed to be an environmental company, worried about reducing people's carbon
footprint.
The joke is that Kawhi Leonard never even tweeted or did anything, but what is Kawhi's
stance on people's carbon footprints?
Is he even passionate about it?
Who knows?
It's a weird, weird thing.
That's really funny.
It was first exposed nationally by Pablo Torre, which has a great podcast, Pablo Torre Explains
It All.
Yes.
Then Mark Cuban, I guess current part owner, but former majority owner of Mavericks, started
hitting up on Twitter.
He said, "Why don't you come on my show?"
They debated about who's at fault for this for two and a half hours.
They put an hour and 10 of it on air, and there's two people passionately arguing about
something, and there's no name calling.
No one gets called Hitler.
No one gets called the child molester.
No one is insulted.
It was an earnest debate where people kept their cool.
It's worth listening to just for that miracle, just because I didn't think people could still
do that.
Matt, just to be clear, you mean they edited all that stuff out, and that's in the full
version, but not in the part that they aired version, right?
They wouldn't have done all that arguing without calling each other Hitler and child molesters.
I know.
It's against the rules of basic conversation these days.
That's right.
I'm glad you didn't disagree with me right there, because I would have had to call you
Hitler.
Here's the craziest thing.
We've done so much crazy shit because of bullshit child molestation rumors that aren't true.
It's all because calling someone Hitler stopped working.
That used to be the worst thing you could do, and someone figured out that calling someone
child molester is worse than Hitler, and then that took over, and that really has created
a bunch of extra conspiracy theories that wouldn't have been otherwise.
Do you think that if it were released today, like if new evidence came out today that Hitler
himself was a child molester, do you think the pendulum would swing back to just calling
people Hitlers again?
Then I'd be like, "Life is a herald.
That's a perfect third beat of conspiracy theories."
That would be it right there.
Paul, you got not only a fruit for 600 or 800, you have negative 400 points, Matt has
400 points.
I have 800 points.
It's a very high-scoring game.
I'll try 800, please.
Not only a fruit for 800, according to the US Supreme Court, Nix V. Headon in 1993, it's
a vegetable.
1893.
Sorry, 1893.
Tomato.
So the US Supreme Court ruled that a tomato is a vegetable?
That's it.
It is.
It's a tax case.
Vegetables are not a botanical classification.
It's technically a fruit.
Yeah, you're technically a fruit, Hitler.
I'm not technically a fruit.
I'm just a fruit.
Okay.
La-dee-dah.
I'm closing out the category and the game, not only a fruit for 600, a composite fruit.
This misnamed fruit actually consists of many tiny individual fruits embedded in a fleshy
receptacle.
Oh.
I like me a composite fruit.
Let's go.
I like me a fleshy receptacle.
A composite fruit, this misnamed fruit actually consists of many tiny individual fruits embedded
in a fleshy receptacle.
Fleshy receptacle is really just not where I want to be in the day.
We are different people.
That was my high school band.
That was our number one single.
We open for the meat puppets.
And I mean that literally.
I guess I'll pass.
Matt, you can win with this.
Man, I don't even know if I have a guess for what a fleshy receptacle would be.
Fleshy receptacle, doo-doo-doo-doo.
I have a guess.
All right.
I'll pass to Paul.
Pass to Paul.
Pomegranate.
I bet you're right.
There we go.
No, it's a strawberry, raspberry, or blackberry.
Boo.
Boo earns.
I thought about strawberry, but I didn't think fleshy receptacle.
Fleshy receptacle threw me off.
That's the game I win today with 800 points.
Matt has 400.
Paul has a negative 200 after his fleshy receptacle mishap, and that is a scooperty from Scoopy
Logic.
Thank you, Scoopy Logic.
Like I said, Scoopy Logic sent that to us a couple of years ago, so if you want to send
us a scooperty, send us a Price is Skripe Jack vs. Nerd, send us an Obelisk Jack vs. Nerd,
send us some scoop mail.
You can do all those things over there at heyscoops.com, and today is evidence.
If I don't get to your scooperty when you send it in at first, I'll probably get to
it later.
Eventually.
It's coming.
I want to thank my favorite fleshy receptacle, Penn Jillette, for creating this podcast.
Yeah.
Thanks, Penn.
Of course, I want to thank all the people that make this show possible, who support
us on our Patreon.
These people all are writing on the new Powers comic book coming out next year.
Fantastic.
Circles and Circles.
Signature Curl Scoop, the micro scoop for shaping.
We all scream for Mark McLean, Unbanned Scoop, One Small Scoop for Man, a Ranch Slunk, a
Scoop of Root Canal, Aaron, Aaron Boyd, Aaron Wendling, Adam Goff, Adam Stickney, AJB,
Akshay Mysore, Ala Scoop 6666, All Star Scoop, Amera Scott Scoop, Andrea Anderson, and Andrew
J Hughes.
The following individuals all bob their heads vigorously while they listen to the podcast
in the hopes that someone will inquire as to what it might be that's causing them the
jam so hard and they try and get a successful obelisk off of it.
Bearded Scoop 3, Bear Scoop, BJ Joyer, Belgian Triple Scoop, Ben, Ben Dennis, Ben Gow, Ben
Smith, Ben Sherman Scoop, Big Lodo Scoop, Big Sexy Digital Nomad, Bike Scoop, Bill Beatty,
Blue Line Scoop, Boss Wayne Scoop, B.O.B., Bobby Becerra, Brad Martin, Brendan Light,
Brendan Allen, and Brian Maddox aka Anarcho Scoop.
The following people can be seen dancing in the video Jigging with the Devil by Sella
Van Halen.
And that would be Andrew Koenig, Andrew Ossichuk, Andy Cheek, Angela Chan, Angry Face Scoop,
Ant Foods, Anton Jernberg, Apple Scoop, Ameris Saar, Avin Zarlez, AWOL Scoop, Bad Pirate
Scoop, Bertie, Bert Vonk, Base Camp Scoops, and BB Hermit.
Sorry, yeah, I did, I said Boats and Scoop wrong again.
So Boats and Scoop, thank you Boats and Scoop.
Also, all of these people have realized, hey, Prince was incredibly good at what he did.
Brian Richard, Brooks Lyle, Brian McLeod, Brian Traves, Buster Kamikaze, Sea Wick,
Kali Ghost, Cameron Hall, Canadian Scoop, Crystal, Captain James T. Scoop, Cargo Van
Killa, Carolyn Albert, Cassie Rice, Charles Eaton, and Charles Jashacky.
And the following scoops were all featured in several Roald Dahl books.
That is Charlie Thompson, Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Chelsea Farr, Chris Barsky, Chris
Ellis, Chris Fisher, Chris Jackson, Chris Jorg, Chris Kay, Chris Meloncon, Christine
Alsasser, Christine Starr, Christopher Hayworth, Christopher Huff, Kristy Salinas, Chronicler
Scoop, CJ Magnetta, Clayton Shoney, Clown in a Brothel, Coach Rat Bastard, Coconut Time
Travel, Coffee Bean Scoop, Colleen Fisher, Colton Stettenberry, Cone's Photo Scoopter,
Brianna Jemora, Corny Scoop, Counselor Matt, Country Scoop, Court Myers, Craig De Farmer,
Craig Little, Cream City Scoop, Chris Bear, Cup a Scoop, and Dan, Dan Thirsty Three.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do love you and appreciate you.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air, if you want to be invited out to our Zoom episodes, Twitch
episodes, get yourself over to preachingfund.com and sign up today.
Or if you, like me, are surprised that we got through an episode today without me having
a weird bathroom story, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with preachingfund.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We are here because of you Patreon supporters, so we thank you so much every show because
we couldn't do the show without you.
So if you want to be one of those Patreon supporters, preachingfund.com, fartsinabag.biz,
those are the places that you can go over to and sign up.
Honestly, just be part of the family.
We're just one big happy group here.
We all have so much fun doing this show all the time.
It's all about the family.
That's right, Bing.
Fast and Furious Family.
All of his Bing Crosby impersonation are just perfect.
We're doing a heist just to show how much family matters to us.
How much family matters.
We rob people for the love of family.
That's right, come on out.
Look, Scoopfest is two weeks away, but we've got room for you.
You can still make that choice.
We do.
Go to scoopfest.com.
We're selling tickets every day right now, so yeah, we definitely have space for you.
Come on out.
It's going to be awesome.
Yeah, it's going to be really fun.
We just added a thing that's going to make people very happy.
It is.
Make a road trip of it.
Do what you got to do.
I don't know if you guys saw this in the chat of our Scoop group stuff, but we had a pair
of Scoops who are coming to Scoopfest who ran into a little financial hiccup as far
as return tickets went for their flights back out of Vegas.
Our community stepped up and already helped them out, got them some GoFundMe coin to get
them a flight back home.
Wow.
I mean, I'm telling you, we got the best listeners on the freaking planet.
I love every one of you guys and it just makes my heart swell every time I come to this podcast
to record and see all your lovely faces and people that message me.
I don't get mean messages.
I just get nice stuff.
The occasional, "Paul, you didn't get this right thing," but that's about it.
Right, right.
That's about it.
Most of the time, I get, "Paul was right," so I like that too.
I hardly ever get mean messages, but when I do, several people make sure to forward
them to me.
So I do have that going for me.
Yes, Winterscoop pointing out that only my heart is swollen when I come.
Yes, that's what happens.
Just my heart swells.
It's a condition.
Yeah, yeah.
I saw it in the comic.
It depicted like a circle in a circle.
Hey.
Yeah, that's right.
Some people out there might be looking for another podcast.
You can participate in our Abla scheme by selecting one person and one person only to
check out our podcast.
I say, promise them all the snappy dialogue.
That's a lot of snappy dialogue.
God damn.
Very snappy.
I got snapped on.
I snapped on for my Gilmore appreciation.
But the dialogue, it's so snappy.
Out of them, we are the Gilmore girls of dudes podcasting.
I'm sure we tackled a lot of the same issues.
Thanks, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you.
Paul is Jesse from the Gilmore girls.
Jesse.
Yeah.
Jesse is a character in the Gilmore Girls, I think.
Marble Tulip Scooby Tree over at Twitch is team Jesse for life.
Oh, oh, yes.
Jesse is Luke's son.
So Rory, the daughter, is torn.
Paul, I didn't care.
Oh, no.
But she's torn between Jesse and this rich kid.
What's his name?
Logan.
Logan Huntsberger.
I happen to be team Logan Huntsberger.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the stage, Logan Huntsberger.
He calls her ace.
It's the cutest thing in the world and she should have stuck with him, but she was conflicted
and dumb and young.
What are you going to do?
That's how it is.
Well, I got to go.
You don't want to stick around for the snappy dialogue?
There's so much snappy dialogue though, man.
See ya.
I can't believe Logan Huntsberger occupies a bunch of hunk of my brain.