It's that time, it's my favorite part of the show, this is the part of the show where
we thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers, thank you Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
I want to thank Scoop Brady, Scoop Dijor, Scoop Cotta, Slippery Caye Motherfucker, The
Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop, and Travis Jaguare.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks, deliver that fucking
ice cream straight to people's fucking ear holes, head over to PreachingFun.com, PreachingFun.com
is where you can go to sign up, and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
And now, a program.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
I confirmed that my wife's band that we talked about on the last episode is in fact not a
secret.
So I am not in trouble.
Okay, great.
That's good.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social, sitting in Pittsburgh.
That's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt Donnelly, and in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio
Guy.
We're PreachingFun.
Yeah, my wife's band.
Next year, 2026, is the 250th anniversary of the United States of America.
And so all of the-
Are you sure we're going to make it to that?
No, I'm not.
We're prepping just in case.
But yeah, next year is the 250th anniversary of the United States of America, which also
means a bunch of cities and towns across the country are also turning 250 years old.
So this coming summer, there's just going to be an assload of town festivals and city
festivals and fairs and all this stuff.
And so SJ and one of her agents had this idea, like, let's put together just an American
rock band.
And I just kind of do, yeah, so that's the style.
My favorite band name that I've come up with so far is Imminent Domain.
It's not quite right, but we do really like that name.
That's beautiful American stuff though.
That's right there.
Really ties in.
With us in studio, we have Dr. Mike is here.
Dr. Mike.
Thank you guys.
In studio, I mean, we're on zoom and you're in Australia.
Right.
Yes.
As close as I could get.
In a room, it's Dr. Mike.
Now how old is your country?
What birthday are you guys celebrating?
Depends on who you ask.
If you ask the indigenous population who have been there for 65,000 years, I would say that
the country is many, many, many thousands of years old.
But if we're talking about colonial, 1788.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
So what does that make it?
Not that old.
Not as old as the US.
Just a little behind us.
Not far.
Yeah.
We're 1776.
Oh, there you go.
Is that a number, is that, is that year a number that Australians just know?
Like I think, I think most citizens of the US know the, know the name or they don't know
the date 1776.
Is that a, is that something?
You know what?
The reason why I know it is because there is a part of Australia called 1788, which
is where they landed.
And that's the only way that I remember it's despite history, you guys don't agree on what
your oldest bar is.
Don't you have three bars that argue that's their oldest bar?
That's the oldest bar.
Oh, there's one down the road for me, which is supposed to be the oldest bar in Australia.
Yeah.
And then you go for a drive down the road again and there's another one.
I like this, but you wrote a book.
I did.
Yes.
The Body A to Z.
You've sent me a blurb to, to preview it and I read none of it.
I read none, not a single part of it.
And I appreciate it.
I think it's, I think, I think it's a, it's fine.
I only sent you the blurb with 24 hours ago, so that's not your fault.
And I was like, I said, now the procrastinating is on my end.
But I know you've been working on this book for a while.
So tell us what went into the book is you always know the title.
What motivated it?
The book's called The Body A to Z, I'm a professor of medicine in Australia.
I've got a YouTube channel where I teach people how the human body works.
I've got a podcast where we do the same thing.
And I'm on social media talking about, you know, this and that in regards to people's
anatomy and physiology.
And in all honesty, the only medium I hadn't touched yet was book form.
And Matt, who I do all my YouTube and podcast stuff with, likes to joke that the people
who watch my TikToks, probably the Venn diagram of those that watch my TikToks and read, it
doesn't overlap significantly.
So let's reach two distinct circles, two very distinct circles with a big gap in between.
I've got bad news for you if you think you're finding readers on our show.
Hey, hold on.
So, yeah, and the book came out a couple of weeks ago.
It's an alphabetized, it's not a textbook, obviously, it's an alphabetized journey through
some of the lesser known structures and functions of the body.
It's for anyone from 12 to 112.
We go through topics like the external anal sphincter.
We talk about why, for example.
That is important for 12 year olds to talk about, I'm glad you said the age thing before
talking about that.
Yes.
There's a lot of interesting topics.
I think the Scrotox topic, have you guys heard of Scrotox?
I have, sadly, I know what it is.
So I believe I know exactly what it is.
I can't wait to hear you describe it.
And Matt, if you are worried that your ball sack looks older than it should, all you got
to do is put a little Botox in that bad boy to de-wrinkle it.
Smooth it right out.
Yeah.
Man, who is that for?
Smooth it, smooth it, a baby's ball sack.
I met a guy who actually had Scrotox and I was like, run away.
I mean, it's true that one third of the ICS hosts have had it done.
Dr. Mike, regarding Scrotox, is that something you would advise or recommend?
No, I wouldn't for a couple of, I mean, one, I'm not sure.
I mean, the aesthetics, I don't know who is staring, who is staring at that part of the
body.
I don't know who is that.
That's a common misperception.
It's a common misperception that people do it for vanity.
It's for aerodynamics.
Well, okay, Jacob, if it is for aerodynamics, I'll give you, if it's for aerodynamics, because
then that means you're already shaving.
Right.
But if you do that without the intent of shaving every day, you're just wasting your time because
you can't see the non-wrinkle with the hair in the way.
That's why I started putting Botox in my chin.
Frozen cusser is right though.
It helps with some people who have excessive sweating of their balls.
They will do that as well because Botox paralyzes the muscles in that area.
So one, the aesthetics, two, the sweating, but the ass sweatings, three, the aerodynamics.
So you have a very informative YouTube videos, you have over a million subscribers.
You must get some strange questions to answer as a doctor from YouTube.
What are some of the strangest questions you've been asked?
I would say the strangest questions, I did call back radio for three years on our ABC
radio station and the people that would call and the questions that were asked, I mean,
there was one guy that said he could smell snakes so he could walk into a shed and know
where a snake was in the shed by his nose and he wanted me to explain how he could do
it.
He doesn't know why?
He just said, I knew where it was and I said, what did it smell like?
I said, I had a musky, musky smell and I could pinpoint exactly where in the shed this snake
was.
Did you just tell him he's clearly house-slytherin?
There was another guy that said, he wasted a genie's wish, like what'd you do for the
other two?
Right.
I know.
It was the oddest superpower I've ever heard.
I'm getting a thing.
I'll be back.
Paul has announced that he was getting a thing and left.
Hope is okay.
Paul's scrotal Botox person has arrived to the house.
He's got to let them in.
They have a lot of setup.
Paul's going into his garage, maybe he'll smell a snake while he's in there.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Maybe he can locate one for us.
In Australia though, isn't it, I mean, isn't that kind of a bullshit trick to be able to
be like, this shed has a snake in it?
That's just a safe bet, right?
Like, yeah, yeah, there's a snake in that shed.
Point, point in the corner and there's a snake.
It's not even 50/50, it's just, it's likely there's a snake.
Now I've got a lot of strange calls.
One guy that was trying to argue with me about, for some reason, sunglasses don't protect
your eyes in any way.
I didn't understand his point.
And he kept referring to his, his Turkish friend as evidence and saying that I've got
a Turkish friend who's never worn sunglasses and his eyes are okay.
So explain that, which I found difficult.
I cannot, I can't explain that.
So he had, he had a one person case study.
Yeah, he just called up, he called up and he goes, I've got one for you.
I've got a Turkish mate, never worn sunglasses and his eyes are totally fine.
Explain that.
Did he believe it was tied to his friend being Turkish?
Was that part of the deal?
Did the Turkish have heartier eyeballs?
He did refer to him as a Turk at least a dozen times in the question.
I don't know why he was so focused on the fact that his friend is a quote unquote Turk.
How long have you been working on the book?
So the book took us about 12 months to write.
God, I have to say, writing a book is not an enjoyable process.
Many people refer to it as like, like, like, like in like surgical ways, like it was like
losing a limb or like, like they basically just all talk, most authors talk about writing
a book as if it's torture.
Yeah.
I would say it was.
It was like losing every limb and then getting pushed down a hill and try to keep your, keep
your balance.
It was, it was just trying to find the time to write a book and then, you know, you've
got to, you need a lot of intense time.
You can't write 30 minutes of a book.
You've got to sit down and get into it and, and figure out how you're going to present
it.
And Matt and I aren't writers, so we have to learn how to write during this process.
We're academics.
We can't write academic papers, but to write something that is fun and enjoyable for everybody
to read was not easy.
Now Paul helped you a little bit with, with, with jokes.
Is that right?
Yeah.
So we're writing a second book at the moment and Paul, which is going to be A to Z of Diseases
and Paul is helping us punch it up.
So we're throwing him some of our draft chapters and he's sending back some of his, so, you
know, he's got some very good, very funny quips, but he's also got his typical obscure,
you know, metal lyrics from a band that nobody's ever heard of.
We might not necessarily keep that particular reference.
That's your mistake.
That's good.
I actually wanted you to talk to you about Paul when he wasn't on air and then you did.
So it's good.
This is a, this is what now he's coming back.
No, no, he's been, he's, Paul has been.
Paul has been fantastic, which is definitely all that was said.
Dr. Mike said that you've, you're, you're, you're, you're doing some additional writing
for A to Z diseases.
I am working on some a punch up, uh, editing for, uh, the chapters.
Yeah.
It's been a lot.
How do you think that's going?
I think it's going great.
Um, I mean, I can only say they've been very kind, uh, in their responses to my, uh, silly
stuff.
You've been fantastic.
So all has been silly.
Yeah.
You've been absolutely fantastic.
It's been great.
It's been wonderful.
Uh, I can, what, what's fun for me is having this, this, uh, opportunity with Dr. Mike
allows me to now proudly say I am juggling basically four jobs at once, which is awesome.
Uh, welcome to America 2025.
Well, you've been, it's, it's been super helpful for us.
Um, you know, Matt and I, we think we're funny.
We're by no means funny.
And when we get into that mindset of writing something about the body, we tend to lose.
I'm worried that we lose humor because we're trying to get facts and you're pulling us
back in with the humor, which is brilliant.
Uh, it's been, it's been really fascinating for me.
I'm learning a ton of stuff.
This latest chapter that you just sent me, can I speak on that at all?
Yeah, go for it.
Absolutely.
So it's all about the dancing sickness, which I am actually familiar with.
So what I'll do is Michael send me this stuff and I'll, I'll read it and then I'll just
let it go for a day or two and let it percolate and then come back to it.
Um, but yeah, the, the dancing sickness, I don't know if you guys are familiar with this,
but it was a, uh, mold in the bread.
You remember this, Jacob?
Well, it's shaking like you got the St. Vitus dance.
That was it.
It's the same thing.
That's exactly the town that it happened in.
And so, yeah, people, uh, people got affected by this and they've just danced themselves
to death.
Uh, many people did because it gave them these weird, uh, brain conditions from ingesting
this bad mold that came from, what kind of grain was it, Mike?
Oh, that's a good question.
I can't remember.
I think it was oat grain.
I'm actually wrong.
Someone should write a book about this.
I think it, I think it was oat grain, but anyway, it was moldy and that's what it was
and it, and it caused people to get sick.
Nobody knew what it was.
You know, of course everybody thought it was possession or some kind of, or something wrong
with the water.
A million different theories came up, but then it spread to a bunch of different places.
It's crazy, but they finally figured it out.
God, our FDA is rolling back protections on shit so we can get this dancing going again.
That's right.
You're that, that is a bit frightening that last point because I mean, well, we said,
we said Paul, a chapter on, um, lead poisoning and the potential link between lead poisoning
and mass murders.
Um, you know, the, the way things can become contaminated quite easily and without oversight,
that can lead to huge amount of issues.
I think one of my favorite chapters with the new book that that Paul's helping us with
at the moment, um, is, uh, a disease called Monday disease in which, so, uh, this is great.
This was great.
I've got a case of the Monday.
You think, but this is awful.
Yeah.
It's a, so Alfred Nobel, he basically created nitroglycerin, the explosive and felt bad
for the amount of lives he potentially has have lost because of that.
So he decided to put money into, you know, the Nobel peace prize and so forth.
And that's where that's gone from there.
But, uh, nitroglycerin and, and, uh, nitro or nitrous oxide, nitrous oxide is a vasodilator
tells your blood vessels to relax, but very chemically similar to the explosive.
And the people that were working in the factories making the explosives were exposed to this
chemical and it would dilate or relax their blood vessels very easily absorbed through
the skin.
Exactly.
And the, when you get a headache or a migraine, that's because your blood vessels are suddenly
relaxing too quickly.
And so they'll get headaches coming back to work on Monday, but because it relaxed their
blood vessels, those who had heart disease got relief while they were at work because
their blood vessels were relaxed.
And then they'll finish work on a Friday, go home for the weekend, start to get chest
pain over the weekend again, potentially suffer angina or even heart attacks, and then come
back to work on the Monday and then get the headaches all over again.
And that was the Monday disease, but the Monday disease was a temporary relief for people
with a heart condition.
Yeah, exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
And that was through that.
They discovered how that could be utilized for the alleviation of vein type problems
in the body.
But can you guess?
That happened to me when I had that scary incident before I was put on blood pressure
medication where I came in.
Oh, really?
I came in to just get it.
What happened?
I came in, I talked about this a long time ago on the show, this was, I went in to get
a sign-off because I was going to get sinus surgery to remove polyps from my nose, which
I still never had.
And my-
You never had the polyps or you never had the surgery?
I never had the surgery.
Okay.
No, I was convinced by a hypnotist, a stage hypnotist, that I had nose polyps and he never
snapped his fingers.
That's horrible.
Anthony Cools played a terrible prank on Matt Noddely.
What a bastard.
Anthony Cools, come on, man.
Give me back my sinuses, Cools, uncool, Cools.
And my blood pressure was like through the roof.
And they literally were like, and then so I was like, so I can't get surgery tomorrow?
They're like, you can't leave this office.
And I was like, oh.
And they took a big nitroglycerin, I don't know, they took a big clear gel and just put
it right on my, all across my chest.
And it was awesome.
And I was like, I, cause I take pills now to keep it regulated, but that gel thing was
so cool.
I was like, I would like to do the gel, but apparently it's like, it's like, you can't
control it or whatever.
Yes.
It's only done.
It's hard to, it's hard to get dosage right when you're smothering someone in a gel.
Say it again, but slower, Dr. Mike.
But that's exactly what happened with the, with the stuff they've, you know, they found
all these different uses for this, for this heart condition medicine.
And they had a controlled test, a controlled experiment with these miners who were coming
in and they kept giving all these miners, these blood pressure.
No children.
Wait, how old were they?
No, they were actually in the hole digging miners.
Still not children.
Cause that's coming back into America as well.
We're letting 12 and 14 year olds dig holes.
No.
They're smaller.
You don't have to dig as big a hole.
You're right.
And hey, they haven't lived a life.
They don't care.
Exactly.
Yeah.
They don't count.
So, but all these miners come in and finally, after months of these tests, one guy goes,
Hey, uh, I don't know if this is anything, but I had a raging boner at night.
And the other guy's like, Oh, well yeah, me too.
Yeah.
I did also.
We all had raging boners all the time.
And so finally they go, Oh, fuck.
Now we can make some money.
That's how they discovered.
That's how they discovered my Ankara.
It's amazing.
I have a boner over over four hours last night.
That's just it.
But they're so embarrassed to even talk about it.
They almost missed it.
God damn it.
We need sex ed everywhere.
No, I looked up, uh, Dr. Mike, I looked up the St Vitus dance and this one's talking
about being a neurological disorder, not that was, that was thought to be caused by mold
and it's something else.
Is that something different?
Yeah.
There's, there's another condition, which is St Vitus disease, um, which is a neurological
and it affects the way that the body moves.
So the person moves rhythmically because of the way that the motor system is being affected.
So that's a different condition.
Oh, but that's not, that's not like a life threatening disease.
Yeah.
Richard in the chat was mentioning it was ergot.
That was the specific mold that caused the problem.
Oh, gotcha.
Yeah.
Oh, neat.
Ergot the rhythm, ergot the music, ergot my brain exploding on the floor.
Yeah.
Uh, I'll tell you what else ergot and that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by of course, dr Mike and dr Matt's book, the body eight
is ed, which you can get somewhere.
Yep.
And that's correct.
You can't get it somewhere.
It's your local Walden books.
Is it available in America yet or no?
Well I, I don't know if you guys know this, but there's these things called tariffs that
are happening in the U S but is it affecting the economy at all?
Um, well, I don't know again, Matt, you might not be aware, but um, yes, significantly.
Um, and it's affecting my book sales in the U S because it costs, if somebody in the U
S, uh, well, if my publisher wanted to make the book and sell it in the U S people would
have to pay about 60 U S dollars for the book and my book's not worth 60.
What is your MSRP on that bad boy?
What is it normally going for?
Uh, well in Australia, I think what Paul's trying to ask is how much for raw book?
Right.
I'm asking for raw book.
I'll rule book you Paul.
Okay.
Don't worry about that.
I appreciate it.
You can get it in Australia for $37, uh, which is Australia, which is a little more three,
three U S dollars probably, but yeah, but, but you can order it, uh, and they can share
it to the U S through ratings.
It's, it's, it's a publisher, a distributor called ratings and they will ship it to you
or you can get it as a Kindle through the, uh, U S Amazon.
Okay.
So there are options.
There are options.
All right.
Yeah.
The body A to Z, uh, Dr. Matt and Dr. Mike, uh, they are the authors on there and yeah,
it's on Amazon, uh, for a Kindle and get the physical one in all those ways.
Also $37 Australia is about $24 U S there you go.
And now I've answered all the questions that today's show is also brought to you by the
hemorrhoid razor, a razor to cut your hemorrhoids.
That's from Nola school in 2021.
I'm glad this is a doctor present tells us about how well this works.
The hemorrhoid razor.
Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm the hemorrhoid razor cutter.
That's right.
Looks like you've got a polyp on your bottom bud time for the hemorrhoid razor.
This sharp one's going to slice you clean.
Come on over, spread those cheeky weakies and let me get a slice in I've cut you to
the quick I have slippery slice.
No preparation needed for this H E double hockey sticks.
That's right.
I'm taking you to hell as first with my hemorrhoid razor.
It's a simple slice right around your colon, but just before it, your GI will never be
the same.
Look here.
When you clench that sphincter, I'm going to make it pink to when I slice with my hemorrhoid
razor slice, your little chocolate starfish better make its last wish as I come in with
my hemorrhoid razor.
Your eye of Sauron is going to be a power on blood when I get my hemorrhoid razor slice.
Please do not shit for four to six weeks after the use of the hemorrhoid razor.
It's smart and it scoops a checkout.
So Dr. Mike, let's, let's talk hemorrhoids for a second.
There are several different causes, right?
Yeah.
What's the ultimate, what let's describe.
What is the hemorrhoid?
So there are veins that sit around the anus and they can basically enlarge
cause they're lazy and don't want to get a job.
My hemorrhoids sit around the anus all day.
They sit around the anus.
So it's an, and why should we, and why should we razor blade them?
You know what?
I've been a listener for 10 years and I had to be part of the episode where it was the
like Geo said, it's the worst, most disturbing ad I've heard so far, putting a razor blade
to a hemorrhoid makes me feel sick.
That would do a lot of damage.
That would really not help, right?
That would exacerbate the problem.
I mean, if you think about how much blood can come from a hemorrhoid, just from excoriation,
and I do often, and Jacob often does putting a razor blade to it wouldn't be good.
I mean, some of the ways they get rid of it, banded surgery.
So they band it up to get rid of a sheep's tail.
Oh my God.
Nice.
That's gotta be a big hemorrhoid.
Yeah.
So some people will have challenge accepted Paul external.
Okay.
All right.
Ben, have you ever met anyone with a prehensile hemorrhoid?
Use it to climb a tree when I'm scared.
I could hang from a branch by my hemorrhoid.
Oh my God.
There's a new way that they're doing it, which is they sonicate it.
They actually use sound and what the sound does is, I actually don't know what the mechanism
is.
I don't know if many of the colorectal surgeons.
It's a guided by voices album.
Look man, not a lot of hemorrhoids here.
So thank you.
That's right.
Now we have a very specific follow-up coming from a listener here, Jacob, can you also
highlight Jessica Jane Peterson, please?
Jessica Jane is in chat there.
Oh, where is, where is J.J.?
Oh, there she is.
Hey, J.J.'s here.
Hey.
I was trying to get J.J. to join us in our first episode, but she's here for the second
episode and she just texted me with a question that has to go directly to Dr. Mike.
Did you want to ask her J.J.?
Ah, good.
You know, I feel like, okay, I should say I escaped from a straight jacket eight times
a week hanging upside down on 35 feet in the air.
But if you know about straight jackets, which I'm sure you do, you know, it has that special
crotch strap.
Can that strap cause these hemorrhoids?
So how is this strap wrapped around the back, but then I'm hanging upside down.
I was like, it hasn't happened yet, but I'm wondering if like there's preventative acts
to prevent the hemorrhoids that could be caused by the straight jacket.
You think you need to do like a water tank?
Is it like a G-string bungee?
Okay.
It is.
It's like a G-string bungee made of canvas through Spanx with fishnet.
Okay.
I think your hemorrhoids are safe.
You think the Spanx and the fishnets probably do enough cushioning to prevent the...
There's no preventative measures that I need to take because I just, this sounds terrifying.
There aren't any stretches?
I didn't know any of these things.
I texted Matt.
I'm like, I am learning so much about hemorrhoids.
My Lord.
Well, the fact that you're upside down means that the pressure is probably reduced in that
area.
And it's all going to your...
Right.
Or at least going to your head.
Sorry.
Where's my...
Your hemorrhoids are...
My tight wire act where I just taint myself across, where I just keep shaking my legs
until I inch myself across...
Oh God.
That's maybe a bad idea.
Keep going, Matt.
Keep doing it.
Taint.
Taint shaking.
Matt's raking his asshole across a tightrope.
Look, man.
It's the only way Popov will let me into his pet circus.
So I have to do that act.
Damn you, Anthony Kuhls.
Ouch.
So when can we expect the diseases A through Z?
Do you expect it to sell more or less than the body A through Z?
I think the diseases A to Z is going to be really fun because Paul's helping us punch
this up.
I think it's also going to be very funny.
It's coming out same time as this book.
So this time next year, a Christmas book.
I just got to get it done by...
We've got to get it done, Paul, by June.
Oh, easy peasy.
Yeah.
Cool.
I'm stepping it up.
Paul will not be done by June.
Now I'm going to tell you that right now.
He's killing it.
We send it to him.
He's back in a couple of days.
He's killing it.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get faster on it now.
I've got a much more full schedule, so that allows me more...
Funny, I allocate time better now, so that's good.
Thanks.
And where do you want to send people, Dr. Mike, to check out where your stuff is?
If you, I think, go to our YouTube page, Dr. Matt and Dr. Mike, have a look.
There's videos there for everybody or our podcast.
And yeah, if you want to consider buying the book, go for it.
Otherwise, hit us a subscribe and a like, and I'll be happy.
All right.
Well, thanks for coming by.
Thanks for waking up early.
You woke up at like four o'clock in the morning to be on the show at your time.
So thank you.
I appreciate it.
I did.
But it's all good.
All good.
Thank you, guys.
You've been with us for a decade now and I will continue to be a listener.
Please clear up anything we misquote medically.
Please always fact check us.
I'll be too busy if I did that.
And I can tell you, honestly, the new book that we're working on is fascinating.
And I'm sure A to Z with the body is just as fascinating.
You're going to learn a ton.
So check it out.
Give it a read.
I've already learned a ton of stuff just in my editing of this new book.
So I can't wait to pick up the other one.
Paul, bad news is that now you have to become a doctor by June as well.
You have to also because good news, good news, Matt.
Those kind of degrees in the states are now not professional any longer.
So I I'm technically a doctor already.
I'm technically a doctor.
I have only come at me, bro.
I've only seen the reactions to this.
I don't know the core event that happened that has caused talk about medicine not being
professional.
I can tell you what's going on.
You want me to break it down for you?
What the way they're doing this bullshit because it's always some bullshit loophole.
What they're doing is they're using this formula wherein if a degree's income, if when you
graduate college, the money you make from your income is not significantly greater than
what a high school graduate would make, then it is rendered as though it is null and void
beyond a high school diploma.
By who?
Right.
Who?
What are you saying?
Who renders it null and void?
Yeah.
What's left of the goddamn Department of Education that's being systematically dismantled.
Okay.
So what they're saying is that degrees that do not provide a significant monetary payout
can be compared to the money that a high school graduate makes in its first year.
Now that does not take into account that as you go through the ranks of these things,
you make more money and of course, especially with nurses and internships and that kind
of thing, it is a gradual progression, especially with education.
A lot of that early education is being pulled out from this stuff too because it takes a
little while to get your feet under you and make actual money and tenuring and all that
kind of thing.
So that's the loophole that they're using to undermine many of these degrees as being
anything more than what would essentially be a high school diploma equivalence.
And so they're labeling them as unprofessional or nonprofessional through that loophole.
Does that mean the government does have to fund things?
Does that mean the government has to do things?
It means that you don't get recognized as professional.
The biggest thing about it and shock of all, this giant pedophile ring is deciding that
these specific careers that also happen to be mandatory reporting careers, which means
that if they are informed of any kind of sexual abuse from a minor, they have to report it
to the authorities.
These are also being undercut as nonprofessionals anymore.
So that's going away too.
What do you know?
Shock and surprise.
So that's what's really at the heart of it, is making it so it's harder for crimes against
children to be systematically reported and cataloged.
Guess what is not being systematically eradicated through this?
Degrees such as fucking religious studies, which are not having to be reporting because
that's where it's happening.
I'll tell you what else they're not paying attention to, the body A to Z and you should
be paying attention to it.
You should be paying attention to that.
Can we move to Australia, please?
I know, right?
Do you have room?
Come, come to Australia.
I've been trying to get the boys to Australia for a long time and they refuse.
We want to go, we want to go.
We want to go.
At this point, I think all of our visas would be flagged, but what are you going to do?
Who the fuck knows?
Arms wide open.
Well, thank you, Dr. Mike.
Thank you, Dr. Mike.
Thanks for your time, Dr. Mike.
Appreciate it, man.
Thank you all.
Have a great day.
You too, buddy.
Hey, you too, buddy.
You rock, dude.
All right.
I'll tell you who else is punching up Dr. Mike's next book and that's the following sponsor.
Today is brought to you by 19th Deck Handjobs from Captain Scooper in 2025.
It's 19th Deck Handjobs because sometimes I'm tired of just walking up there.
Well, I was born one day shuffling spades.
I finally decided to change up trades.
I went ahead and I jacked off 18 dudes and the next one showed up.
He was already nudes.
You got 19 decks.
What do you get?
A whole bunch of slop and stuff on your neck.
You can't escape all the jizz that comes and goes.
I owe my soul to these jacked off hoes.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Well, after 19, I thought, where do I go?
I went back out and found another hoe.
Number 20 came and number 20 went, but number 21 was already spent.
You jacked 19 decks.
What do you get?
Your face covered in jizz and soaking wet.
Saint Peter, don't you call me unless you are the actual Saint Peter who has Peters
by far.
Yeah.
Give me those Saint Peters.
Saint Peter's got Peters by far.
Me her.
And her hate scoops are jacked out.
There you go.
Oh, you know what that horn means.
Matt Dolly's heading up to old 19.
I can only listen to books on tape for so long.
I'm about to head out to the-
Board.
Yeah.
Right after Thanksgiving, I head back out to the old Sun Princess.
Miss the old gal.
Going to be there.
How long are you going to be out?
Just a week, which is good.
Nice.
Jessica Jane, are you at sea?
Yeah.
I think so.
I joined the Disney Destiny in, oh God, in three days and I still have to write two more
routines.
Crap.
They work you hard on that ship.
But then I go to Star Princess.
So wait, when are you on Sun?
I'm on the Sun in December and then I don't go to the Star until March and then I'm on
the Star in May and June.
Okay.
Well, you don't know whether you're booked there or you're already booked out.
Disney's got stuff till like 20 to 27 because they don't want me to have a life, so they
own me.
I am owned by the mouse.
I was just saying, I'm even on the Star in August.
I'm on the Star a ton, but I won't run into you.
You won't get booked as a, because Jessica Jane gets booked as a stage magician.
I get booked in Little Magic Castle Experience, so I could be on this ship.
And then we can do a show together in the pavilion thing.
Yeah.
No, I do have two Star Princess dates in March, so we'll see.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yay.
I miss you guys though.
Hi, JJ.
You were supposed to come to Scoop Fest and you bailed on it because we were working on
a project together.
I was going to say, yeah.
Yeah.
We need you to block out some dates on the next Scoop Fest, so yeah.
Yes.
Yes, we can, JJ.
We can definitely talk about whose fault that was.
Vinnie Grasso.
Can we talk about Vinnie Grasso?
Fucking Vinnie Grasso.
Yup.
Because who got sent to the Virgin Cruise thing because Matt wasn't available and what
Mike had what?
His daughter's dance recital or something and Vinnie's like, "I don't want to do it,
so send JJ."
That's right.
But we missed you.
You recently-
Vinnie came by though.
Vinnie came by Scoop Fest.
He was there for all of it.
He came by and really hug out.
He was there?
Yeah, yeah.
He came by and hug out for a lot of Scoop Fest.
Are you freaking kidding me?
Vinnie went to Scoop Fest?
You're freaking kidding me.
Matt Foster.
I knew that'd make her mad.
I believe Jacob is kidding you.
I believe he's kidding you.
Vinnie was not there.
Oh, he's kidding.
I was so mad.
Vinnie was in Italy.
That's why you had to go on.
Oh, okay.
It was all just not available.
I can't accept that.
You weren't at Scoop Fest because I was supposed to be on the ship during Scoop Fest and I
said no because of Scoop Fest.
So you were there.
JJ, Vinnie-
When I was near in spirit, just a lot taller.
You talking about Michael Elsroth dressing up like you for the Scoop Fest?
Can we please, for the next Scoop Fest, Mike, can we wear the exact same outfit and walk
around together arm in arm?
It would make me so happy.
You do not need to ask Elsroth twice to do an elaborate bit.
I'll tell you that much later.
No, he will very quickly commit to that.
He'll run with it.
Yeah.
He'll do it immediately.
You should both be mermaids.
Oh my God.
Wait a minute.
He was there.
That bastard.
I'm texting him.
You were at Scoop Fest?
You told me that you were in Italy.
I just saw a picture of you at Scoop Fest to go to the ship, to do the Virgin gig.
So let's talk about that, Vinnie Grasso.
I love it.
Drama.
I'm just there to ruin J.J. and Vinnie's relationship.
I believe in truth.
I believe he came by for about five minutes one day.
I think he came through on his way to the airport.
He was there just in time to grab a Fez and run.
Yeah.
Okay.
We got to get you a Fez, J.J.
Oh, I would love a Fez.
Yeah.
That would be awesome.
J.J. is now our neighbor, Jacob.
Yeah.
I knew you were in town.
Where are you?
I'm on Bracken, so I'm really close to the downtown arts district area.
Wow.
I think I'm a 10 minute walk from the Haunted Museum.
Oh, how nice.
Have you been yet?
No, I have not.
That was one of my gigs.
I worked at the Haunted Museum.
Really?
Yes.
Before they opened and during the opening months, I was there for just about three
months.
Yeah.
Vinnie Grasso got Paul the job there.
Vinnie got everybody who he really liked jobs at the Haunted Museum.
He did not.
I got that job myself.
No, but I worked with Zach on, I helped write a lot of the pattern that the guides use throughout
the entire museum and I worked there for several months.
I was there for, we had to postpone our opening because October 1 happened, so the next Monday
we were going to open and we had to postpone it until Tuesday because it was too crazy.
We had to just chill.
Mass shooting in Las Vegas, that's what October 1 is.
So then I was there for Friday the 13th and for Halloween and it was in fucking sane.
Yeah, Halloween was nuts.
We had some crazy shit go down during Halloween.
Yeah, I never had anything too crazy happen to myself, but it's an interesting place at
the least to check out.
There's a lot of really cool stuff to see.
Did you ever have any moments though where you got freaked out?
I actually had to go turn off lights at the end of the night because I was like a mid-level
manager type.
So I did always say hi and bye to Peggy, Peggy the doll.
So I didn't even fuck with that.
The only weird thing, there's a couple of weird things.
There was a latch on this gate that opens and closes for the basement and I would constantly
have to relatch that basement gate.
That latch was always coming loose.
then upstairs in the room that held the Dibbock's, which was right next to Peggy's room. That's
the golf thing, right? Yeah. Dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip,
dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip,
dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip, dip. So the Dibbock's, which is basically
based around the conjuring stuff, the Dibbock's room, I had to go in there to turn on lights
one morning, and I went to try the doorknob, and you know, did you ever grow up with siblings
of any kind? Yeah. I felt that feeling, and I couldn't get the door to open, and I tried
it again, and it was the same kind of thing, and I just had to let it go, and I was like,
"Okay, I'm going on." Paul's brother was on the other side of that door holding it. You
never know. Those were the only really weird things that happened to me, but plenty of
other stuff happened to people that were around, but a lot of it is because he doesn't let
people have drinks in the place, and they all get dehydrated and pass out. That's really
a lot of it, yeah. A lot of it is just people suffering from Vegas and just passing out
because it's a lot to take in. Pass out saltines and espresso on your way in, and then you
can't drink water. Honestly, yeah. Spraying you with salt. Well, there's a lot of fog
machines and stuff in there, too, so that can affect people, too. Can we have a scoop
group visit to the museum? An excursion to the museum would be really, really fun. Yeah.
That would be really fun. I know somebody had contacted me from over there about some
of my Houdini stuff, because I was like, "Well, I live close by, and it'd be safe there."
You should chat him up. Drop my name. I mean, he'll remember me. I left on good terms. They
said, "Come back any time," so it's all good. Yeah. Bacon was his right-hand man while I
was there. He might still be his right-hand man. I don't know. No, I think Vinnie Grasso
is just running the place now. Could be. Vinnie Grasso just texted back. He goes, "I stopped
by on the way to the airport to give Matt a magnified for Oscar. Nothing to discuss,
Ms. Peterson." Oh, boy. Giving you the business. Ms. Peterson. He was only there for two and
a half days. But seriously, JJ, your routines would be a huge hit there. He is a mega circus
fanatic. He has an entire area dedicated to classic circus memorabilia, and he has a giant
circus diorama built out with little tiny pieces that move and little elephants that
jump through hoops and stuff like that. He's a sideshow fan and stuff, too, because this
shit I have in my house. Big time into that. Oh, my God. You're right next door. You should
absolutely stop by sometime and say, "Hey, if you've got special events happening anytime,
I'd love to come by as a performer," because he's always looking for that kind of stuff.
Paul, some of the stuff I have here is hardcore, because I lived in Gibsonton, Florida when
we would winter with a sideshow. I lived in the trailer outside Ward Hall, the king of
the sideshow's house. Holy shit. He had all the stuff from the early 1900s. I have jars
of things where I don't even know what they are. You got pickled punks and shit back there.
Oh, yeah. I know where all the pickled punks are buried in Gibsonton, Florida. Get the
fuck out. Yeah, they made it illegal to put actual dead bodies on display. It used to
be the blow off of the sideshow. You go through the sideshow, and at the end, you pay an extra
dollar to see what's behind the curtain. Then they open it, and there's these babies in
jars that were real. Right. They would talk about, "This is why you don't do drugs, people.
Cha cha cha." Then you leave them. Apparently, when it was made illegal, they were worth
too much money. All the people that live in Gibsonton, it's a law that you can have anything
on your property as long as it has to do with circus. Government can't do anything about
it. There's freaking half set up rides and a tiger over here. It's insane. There's a
field where all the pickled punks are buried, hundreds of them. Oh, Jesus. Wow. Now see,
that's the kind of stuff he would- This is why you don't let circus people make the rules.
No, but that's the kind of stuff he would buy. He went out and bought David Koresh's
hot rod a couple years ago and stuff like that. Yeah, I don't think Zack should be in
charge either. He's always looking for that kind of stuff. You guys would hit it off.
You should definitely look him up. I feel like we'd be friends. You would. You guys
would be. Paul, you can vouch. Zack pays really well, right, Paul? Here's the thing. I was
just about to say, whatever you're thinking of charging, just charge double and you'll
be good. Yeah. Okay. He's classic sideshow in every way. Classic sideshow is GTFM. Get
the fucking money. He loves Barnum. He loves P.T. Barnum. That's his whole, that's his
ideological guru. And that's why he's got all that- Oh, I've got a Barnum letter in
the back room that's written by Barnum. I've got like- Hey, you looking to make some quick
cash? Honestly, that's the kind of shit he will buy in a fucking heartbeat for his museum.
Well, you've got me wondering. Yeah, I've got, there was a murder in Gibsonton, Florida.
There was this guy called the Lobster Man and the Lobster Man abused his family. So
they hired a hit on him. His name was Grady Styles. And I have an impression of his hand,
like in like the actual impression of his hand. He was the one that was murdered. And
there was this crazy story around it. You've got Circus Freak and Murder Mystery Story and
Murder Mobilia all connected. He will pay you crazy money for this shit. This is exactly
the kind of stuff he loves to have in his place. Wow. Yeah, you guys will hit it off.
Yeah, if you guys don't know that story, look up Grady Styles, the lobster boy. It's been
a long time since I've heard that, but he had hands kind of like the penguin in the
Batman Returns. Yeah, yeah. The pincers. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Oh, fucking shit. You guys
absolutely have to chat at some point. We got to figure that out. Yeah. A pickled graveyard.
Yes, Andy. It's a pickled graveyard. All right. Shout out to Richard Bruins for doubling his
Patreon while we were on air. I'll keep doing this if people keep doing it. So I'll just
keep doing it. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you, Richard. This is great. Yeah. We love you guys so much.
Thank you so much for sending us. Coach Rat Bastard just became an ice cream truck driver,
buddy. Yeah, Coach Rat Bastard. Yeah, baby. That's what I'm talking about. Welcome to the
feed. Is Mike technically an ice cream truck driver all the time since he's actually driving
his truck? Yes. Hi, Mike. Kind of. Yeah. Oh, yes. Yeah. And he was kind enough to say that
he's going to up his Patreon as soon as stuff gets squared away from the holidays. So yeah.
The people who are doing it can fit it with their budget. Obviously, we do not want people
to take any financial risks to up their Patreon. No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no. But we desperately
appreciate everything that everybody does for us. So yeah. There's still the experiment
that we're going to run after we get $3 billion. That's right. We're going to give each of
us a billion dollars and see how we spend it. We're going to see if we can be better people
than the billionaires that we have today. So we'll see how that goes. I know I could.
My guess is no. I could. Well, once JJ sells all of her memorabilia to Zach, she'll be a
billionaire as well. I'm telling you, you got some money. Well, at the very least, yeah,
you guys would actually hit it off. Yeah. First of all, JJ hits it off with every single
person on the planet. Yeah, I know. I know. I'm not like breaking news here. JJ gets along
with someone. Yeah, but we've got sawdust in our blood. Yes. Yes. No, I think you guys
because of the circus thing. Yeah. For the Zach Bagenstern, I was trying to get to the
lead of why we had you on here is you just did a concert with Alice Cooper in Arizona.
Oh, you did that one. Yeah, that was interesting. That was very interesting. What happened?
Well, here's the thing. I'll just tell you what I saw. I saw that you were at one point
you're eating fire. And at one point there's a picture of you eating fire and you're and
normally when you fire your head is back, your neck is up. There's a picture of you
eating fire and your face is forward and you're just shoving a ball of fire into your face.
I hurt my neck. I couldn't put my head back. And then I just did it. And I had no eyelashes
afterwards. They said I looked like a badass. There's no doubt. No doubt. So sorry. Tell
us all about the gig. So David Menken was the one that got it because he's been friends
with like Alice and his wife for years and they are the nicest human beings in the world.
And the gig was for this thing they do called Alice Cooper solid rock. Basically in Arizona,
any kid that wants to learn an instrument, learn an art, anything, they can stay after
school till 10pm at their facilities. They get their instrument for free. They get training
for Alice. Oh, that's awesome. It's insanely cool. And so they had the winners of like
their annual like School of Rock type thing in this concert. And then it was me, David
and Chris Mitchell, Collective Soul, Don Felder, his guitarist that was insane. I forget what
her name was. Nina, I think something. And then Alice Cooper performed at the original
band. Whoa. Oh, cool. Badass. But so I got there and obviously I'm like, we're the magicians.
We're not going to get a dressing room or anything, which I was right. So we go downstairs.
I'm trying to find a place. I was like, I gotta curl my hair. I just got off a cruise
ship on a plane and I said, is there any place with a plug? And they, they pulled me down
the hallway and he said, oh, and here's fine. I was like, oh, this is nice. There's nobody
in it right now. So I curled my hair for like 20 minutes and you guys know I shed like a
Siberian husky in summer, like there's red hair everywhere all over the floor. And so
I'm trying to collect some, like I could make another JJ out of actually Mike, I should
just give you my hair for eight years. That's what I should do for your next. Else Roth
for Else Roth to get JJ's hair. Well, I got, so I, I, I finished and I just had a feeling
like I need to get out of here. I leave, I leave the dressing room and my shoulder brushes
somebody going into it. They have put me in Alice Cooper's dressing room thinking he wouldn't
be there yet. And I literally just made a mess of his dressing room with my hair. It
was so embarrassing. And I saw David Lincoln and Chris Mitchell on the other side of the
room going, Oh no. And then my other fail moment. Have you guys ever misquoted lyrics
to a person who wrote them? Oh no. Something I'm very capable of. So Jacob, what, what
was your misheard lyric that you quoted to that person? It was, it was an Ozzy Osbourne
lyric. Uh, not, not too Ozzy, but to the person that had written this song. Uh, I, I don't
know what the lyric was, but I was definitely just like singing part of it with, uh, like
through with this guy and he was like, that is not the lyric at all. It was, it was embarrassing.
Oh shit dude. So collective soul. I love collective soul and Ed Rowland, like the lead singer
for it. And you know that song that, Whoa, I thought it was never let your light shine
doll. Oh my God. And I didn't know what the real lyrics were until yesterday when I told
the friend this story and they're like, they didn't correct you. And I went, no. And then
the other one, Ed Rowland filmed on his phone to send his family cause he loved it. You
know that song that, that dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, I thought it was turn
your head now, baby. Just say meow.
Turn your hair now, baby. Just say meow and, and he laughed so hard during the show when
he sang whatever the real lyrics. Oh, it was bad, but no one corrected me. Like my wife
thought the collective soul was, Oh, physical attraction is what she thought it was. What
do you guys, what is wrong? Everybody just got hearing problems. What's happening? Baby.
Just physical. No, Jacob, not everyone has hearing problems. I used to think the boots
are made for walking. I thought it was one of these days. These boots are gonna walk
on over to you.
Wow. It's much harder than that, JJ. It's much harder. Oh God. As a kid, I thought jump
and drive was drink and drive a beautiful anthem to drunk driving. Like this wonderful
party song. My favorite, my favorite song is manslaughter three. Oh man. Good parents.
You genuinely believed the lyric was now baby. Just say meow. Yeah. I didn't, you know, when
you hear something and you just sing it that way and you never even think about what you're
actually singing, it never occurred to you to even think about it. And this is, and this
is all like these songs all came out when we were younger and this is before the Shazam
and iPhones and stuff. You couldn't look up this was dentist jargon though. It's dentist
jargon. What's dentist jargon? Turn your head and spit me out. That's what it is. Turn your
head and baby now baby. Just spit me out. Yeah. But it's talking like a dentist, but
like who's given head in a dentist's office. I mean, I mean, you gotta go to the right
place. I guess I can tell you right now. It took me forever to find one of those covered
by insurance. Yeah. But turn your head and spit is a, is a dentist thing. But if you
break that down, turn your head and baby just spit me out. I hear it now that you're saying
it. JJ, I get it. Turn your head now, baby. Just say meow. Yeah. But he sings with a very
affected way. I, I'm going to be, I'm, I want, I don't like collective soul, but I know a
ton of collective soul songs because when I was coming up as a young man, that was on
the radio 24 fucking seven, their stuff was huge. You couldn't escape their songs. Yeah.
It's very funny that I thought, I think it's funny that you think it was turn your head
now baby. I want to, I want an all JJ cover band that just sings her lyrics, the wrong
lyrics. Yeah. Jacob, the wrong lyrics. That's a band name. The wrong lyrics is a good band
name, right? Yeah. Speaking of all these bands, I saw bowling for soup. They had a free concert
on Fremont street the other night. They are great live. Oh, they're so good live. They're
so good. A friend of ours was opening for them. And so we went down and saw our friend
open and then we hung out and watched bowling for soup a little bit. They were so good live.
They were so funny. They talk, you know, they, they, they do the songs and everything. Uh,
Cooper Nova girl in the chat saying 1985. Uh, so that's one of their big songs. It was
so goddamn funny. They're up there. They're playing and we're kind of on the, on the side
of the stage and uh, we, we, we see them, we see all the signs and you know, people
are holding up signs. This is 1985 between every song that they do. People are yelling
for 1985. They, they want to play it. And finally the front man chefs fucking kiss to
this guy. He goes, Hey, Hey, how many hits do you think we have? We've been doing this
a long time. We're going to play our big hit last 1985. Now we're going to play it. It's
going to be last. When I saw them, they were playing the small room. It was still the hard
rock instead of Virgin. It was still the hard rock and they were playing the smaller room
and they vinyl, they they were playing vinyl and they go like, uh, we're going to play.
Um, uh, this is a song we wrote for Katy Perry and they played, uh, you're hot. Then you're
cold. You're yes. Then you're no. And they played it awesome. They played it fast as hell.
They just rocked it out. And then when they finished, they go, we didn't write that for
Katy Perry. They go, do you think we'd be playing this room if we wrote that song for
Katy Perry? We just be at home swimming in our money. We wouldn't be here. That's great.
I love so hard at that bit. They wrote a song for Katy Perry. So smart. Uh, it was just
the funniest bit, but they were great. They were so great to see. I could hear them from
where I live because Fremont street is so close. So like there's a lot of times I can't
go to bed early because there's stuff going on. Oh yeah. It's so confusing because I heard
that concert and then I look out and I see Disney drones and I'm like, God, I thought
I got away from them. Fantasmic. Freaking Belatio was like, they found me. He gads.
Well, if you ever, if you're ever downtown again, you hear bowling for soup playing just
come on over. Cause I'll probably be there. We're going to play that one last. It's our
big song. Let me explain to you how show business works. That's very funny. You're going to
be on Disney for Thanksgiving. You'd be on Disney for Christmas. I'm traveling to Disney
on Thanksgiving and I will be on Disney for Christmas. Yes. And New Year's Eve. What's
the point of us becoming neighbors? If you spend all your holidays doing cruise ships,
JJ, but I'm here. I'm here December 3rd to December 13th. And then for next year, I've
taken off two weeks of every month because my body, apparently I, my cortisol levels
are 42 and they're supposed to be not higher than 28. And, and they're like, it's burnout
and stress. So I'm, Oh, where's Dr. Mike? We should let Dr. Mike go. We should've talked
about your cortisol level. I need Dr. Mike. What is, what is a cortisol level? What does
that do? It's basically what regulates stress. I think, right? Okay. Yeah. I hear people
talking about it. I don't know what it is though. It's, I gotta tell you, you don't
want a high cortisol level. Instagram says I need to treat it like crazy. Um, in terms
of a targeted ads. Yeah. No, every targeted ads. It is all BS. Oh, the Instagram medical
advice is, is not a solid. Not to be trusted. Not at all. Nope. It's very hard to treat
your cortisol levels with an herbal supplement. Um, I don't think we need Dr. Mike back on
to tell you that's true. Um, but I did switch to actually, it was a quarter. There's after
it was a cortisol, cortisol supplement, but it was advertised to me as like, if you're
taking melatonin, you should maybe switch to this. And I've been taking melatonin since
the pandemic and then, and then the study came out that was like, Hey, taking melatonin
every day might not be good for your heart. And so I would, I forget what the name of
the study is, but the study is the placebo's work. Even if you know the placebo's, do you
know the study? I mean, I know of studies like that. I don't know what the, uh, with
melatonin, it wasn't a melatonin based study, but there's a particular study that just basically
said we're giving you placebos for the symptoms and people would knowingly take the placebo
and still report improvement in their conditions. So I've switched to this herbal thing and
stop taking melatonin and it, and I've been falling asleep, uh, better on this herbal
supplements than this. And I'm, and I'm positive. It's just the placebo effect. I can't, I cannot
positively endorse this product. I just simply am happier that I'm not taking melatonin.
So I'll do it. I'll take it. It's called Ambien. Yeah. Matt's going to sleep really well on
this new supplement Ambien. It's, it's, it's a, it's actually, it's, it comes in a rock
form and you hit your head with it until it absorbs the bus. Oh yeah. On the bus, I was
always so tired on the bus. I was actually ended up taking Advil PMs, which I knew is
something you shouldn't take longterm, but I was taking, I was doing, I was doing anything
to fall asleep on that bus. Uh, yeah, I was not, I was never falling asleep on that, but
Matt, here's a trick that I've tried and it's worked for me that I just heard about. Uh,
get yourself a cooling pad. Do you have like, um, little ice pack type things? I do. Okay.
Uh, and you've got it where you can either wrap it in a cloth or something where it could
be safe for skin contact. Okay. All right. And before you go to bed, once you're in bed,
you put it on your forehead for 20 minutes and that will chill out your frontal cortex,
your frontal lobe and seriously send messages to like, go to sleep. And so it really, really
helps. So try it. This is what you need. I was just about to say, I know JJ invested
in some old timey ice bag and she, here it is. There it is. Here's the thing. Here's
the thing. So if you're at a hotel, you can fill it with ice. If you buy a drink at the
airport before I get on a plane, I buy a fountain soda, fill it with ice. There you go. Use
it on the back everywhere. Yeah. Cruise ship, fill it with ice. This is, I live by this.
That's a genius idea. To be accurate, how much soda do you pour into that ice bag? It's
not none soda. No, but that's great. It has happened once when I was very tired. But that's
great. And yes, I did drink it out of the bag. I assume you drank it. Yeah, that's awesome.
Oh yeah. So I get water as soon as the ice melts. I'm like, I'm not paying $6 for water.
I'm just drinking out of a plastic ice bag. Genius. It works. That's how you get that
sawdust in your veins. You absolutely could. There you go. Yep. Yep. Yep. Genius. Genius.
You say that like you drink. You don't really drink. No, not much, but I could. She just
wants to have the option. Yeah. Guys. Guys, I'm icing down my knees every night with old
fashions. It really works. It absorbs through the skin. Natural medicine, baby. Natural
medicine. Oh, you don't know nothing about no natural medicine and you don't know nothing
about nothing because it's Jack versus nerd. All right. You're going to find out who knows
nothing about something. Ladies and gentlemen, it is time. Time for Jack versus Nerd. Explosion
me accidentally deleting the scooperty before I got to it. We got a scooperty coming to
us today from ML Kennedy. The categories are how it started dot dot dot. What's their number?
Turkeys and potpourri. Oh yeah, it's the Thanksgiving one. Happy Thanksgiving everybody. JJ, what's
your Instagram? Wait, my Instagram? Yeah. At Jessica Jane Magic. Jessica Jane Magic.
Leave JJ a follow. She always does. Oh yay. I'll follow you back. I put weird stuff up.
You document your weird life on ships all the time. It's a good follow. It's good adventures
of someone. I'm very honest. That's what I don't like about her. That's how I knew about
the old timey ice bag. I do post that on my Instagram like you guys, but I'm going to
mention the alcohol thing now. That's going to be fun. Life hack! Matt, you're up first.
What category do you want? Oh, I have to put it back on the screen, don't I? How it started.
What's the number? Turkeys or potpourri are the categories. Matt, what you want? How it
started please. For 200. This 1996 Tim Burton movie was based on a series of tops trading
cards from the 1960s. I feel like this is obvious, but I'm trying to think of tops trading
cards. A league of their own. I know. It's like major league, but that wasn't a Tim Burton
movie. That'd be a weird Tim Burton movie. That'd be a great Tim Burton movie. I'll pass.
Oh, that passes to me. I have no idea. Pass. Mars attacks. Oh, sure. Mars attacks. Good
call. That's from a trading card game. Oh, it's me. I'll try, what's their number? 200.
The King of England during the American Revolution was King George the... Infallible. I want
to say fifth. King George the fifth is what I'm saying. Third. Oh, you overshot it. Overshot
it by two, Jacob. So close. Yep, yep. Wrong George. My bad, George. Paul. I'll try potpourri
for six. For 600. How tall is Hello Kitty? Please give the answer in apples. Oh man.
So Smurfs are three apples high. Famously. Okay. I'm going to guess Hello Kitty is also
three apples high. Okay, let's try it. Five apples. Of course she's bigger than a Smurf.
Fucking shit. What are you thinking, Paul? At F1 there was a Hello Kitty booth this year
because it's so funny because they added this Formula One Academy, which is all about training
up women racers. So they had a big Formula One Academy race and they had all women drivers.
And so one of the sponsors is Hello Kitty. So all these people who weren't aware of this
new thing were just like, what the hell is this Hello Kitty thing doing here? Oh, that's
great. They didn't like Hello Kitty? They're just confused by it. A lot of basically car
dealers who won some contests that their dealership sent them to F1 did not appreciate the Hello
Kitty thing. Yeah. Well then they're idiots. Mickey Mouse and the gang and Hello Kitty.
They're absolute idiots because any car dealer, no seriously, if you were lucky enough to
be like, let's just say a Toyota dealership and you were lucky enough to get like a Hello
Kitty limited edition Avalon made, holy fuck, those would not stay in stock for five minutes.
Good point. They have no idea what they're doing. Fuck those idiots. From your mouth
to Theodore Toyota's ears. Theodore Toyota, send me a message. We'll talk. It's weird
to have Paul cursing out because I feel like Paul would get along with all of the opulent
people that go to F1 normally. I would get along with the rich people? No, I'm being
sarcastic. He'd be so mad the whole time. Yeah, I would be throwing shit in their face.
You'd just be furious. I'd be throwing shit in their faces. Matt, you're up. JJ, where
should I go? What's your gut? Turkeys for $400. All right. Turkeys for $400. The budget
of this Gina Davis pirate movie was around $100 million. It grossed about $18 million
at the box office. You know this, Matt. You know this, Matt. I do? What is it? I don't
know. What is it? I know this one. JJ, you can tell me. You can just tell me. It's Matthew
Modine. Gina Davis is a hot pirate? And Matthew Modine? Where do pirates hang out, Matt? On
a ship in a harbor. Yeah, and that ship takes them to a piece of land that's in the middle
of the ocean called a? Island. It's an island. Yeah. What do they do on that island? Look
for treasure? Nope, they kill each other in a very specific way. Murder Island. Close.
Getting closer. Who are you? JJ, you're a horrible lifeline. Just tell me the answer.
We can move on. Actually, I forget. I was just hoping you'd get to it. Matt. Shipwreck?
It's a good movie. Imagine you had to go down on a sword. Okay. What would happen? Cutthroat
Island. There you go. Cutthroat Island is it. All you have to do with these clues to
get Matt to figure them out is reference fellatio. That's right. Got it. It is a good movie though.
Come on now, JJ. I believe Cutthroat Island was the reason that movie studio had to fold.
Yeah, it's a terrible movie. It destroyed a movie studio. It's damn near unwatchable.
It was hot. Oh my God. Yeah, everyone's attractive. The movie's terrible. What were you for when
that fucking thing hit the theaters? And you were like, wow, of course it was cool to a
four-year-old. JJ watches that shit on mute. She sips from her ice pack. All right. Fair
enough. I mean, I ain't taking nothing away from Gina Davis and big old pirate boots. Good
stuff there, but you know. I'll try turkeys for 600. You would. This film developed in
part by the four-year-old son of the president of Paramount grossed $65 million on a budget
of $125 million. It's about trucks with hive mind creatures living under the hoods. Oh,
is that though? Oh, what was the, the, the, it was like the, the Loch Ness monster looking
thing. What does your, what did your wife work for, for a minute there? Uh, pimp. Okay.
After she got done being turned out on the street, she decided to go get turned out on
the tracks with those machines. Was it just called monster truck? It sure was. We just
called monster trucks. Yeah, there you go. Monster trucks. Yep. Yep. There you go. Uh,
Paul, you're up. I'm going to go, I'm going to take Turkey 800 please. I got to get back
on the board. This 1999 movie based on Michael Crichton's novel Eaters of the Dead grossed
about $62 million worldwide on a bigger than $100 million budget. I guess that was an unlucky
number. I'm going to tell you what this movie should have made way more money. This is not
a Turkey. This is an exceptional film. Antonio Bandara's puts in a superstar performance
in the 13th warrior. The 13th warrior is correct. It is such a good movie. It is good. I have
that on DVD. That is one of my favorite movies. It's great. JJ was just talking about how
good cutthroat Island is Paul. Don't be too excited to be on her team. I'm on, I'm on
team 13th warrior. I don't give a shit. Cutthroat Island, whatever. But yeah, 13th movie all
time is the Phantom with Billy Zane though. So stop it. Stop it. He was the bomb in Phantom's
yo anyone who's like absolutely repping Billy Zane first. Yeah. It's an insane person. No,
that's just, that was just, uh, JJ, I know somebody else in town that that is their favorite
movie. I'm going to make sure the two of you meet. Holy shit. I'm going to introduce you.
You don't know them yet. God. You're going to, you're going to, you're going to be better
be careful, Jacob. You don't want to get too zaniacs in the same room together. Like a
little too zany. It's, it's Matt Franco. It's always been Matt Franco. He's got it on a
loop in his dressing room. Uh, Frank and I literally can talk to each other in quotes
from nineties magic specials and only quotes from nineties magic specials. All right. Raise
your hand if you're surprised. Okay. Raise your hand if you want to be in that room.
No hands free. JJ, where do we go? Where do we go? Um, um, maybe a how it started. How
brave are you? Let's do it. How it started for 400. This six film franchise originated
from an unused spec script for an episode of the X-Files. It's latest entry grossed
over $300 million this year. Six films, aliens or conspiracies guy, girl, guy, girl investigators.
Paul, you know this one? Uh, it could be something like the nun, you know, they have those one
off kind of ghosty stuff, you know, monster of the week kind of thing. But I'm thinking
six films. When was this, when was this, uh, scooperty? Uh, it's recent. It's a, it's
a Thanksgiving. It's a Thanksgiving scooperty for 300 million this year. So it's a film
that came out this year. It's part of a horror movie. Uh, is what he called up to six movies
now. Um, Oh, you know what? I think it might be paranormal activity. Oh, that gives that
come out this year. I think there was another parent. I don't know activity or the, I'm
definitely passing Paul. What is it? I mean, paranormal activity or the conjuring is the
conjuring up to six. I'm going to get, I'm going to guess conjuring. I'm guessing conjuring.
Let's see. Final destination. I eat my own butt fart on a shit. Okay. I should have known
wait. All right. My first thing was found as a nation, but it initially bombed. So the
fact that said it reached over 300 million, I'm surprised because yeah, this latest reboot
was really hot. People were really, I think this, I think it got like a cult following
thing with the sequels and all. I think it's just one of those. And it also got real viral.
I thought it was opening weekend this week and so I didn't guess that millennials are
desperate to get killed by a log carrying truck. Who is it? Oh man, sign me up. I'll
try potpourri for 800 right back to zero fart. This is the only current flag of a sovereign
country without elements in white, red, or blue. I got this white, red, or blue. Is it,
I'll take a guess on this one. Brazil. Is it, is it Brazil? Maybe Jamaica. Y'all think
it's Brazil. Oh, I think you might be right. It is Jamaica. You were right. Yeah. Got that
one wrong. Wait, can I get it right? What the hell? He didn't pass you jerk. I didn't
pass. I just got it wrong. I don't give a shit. I still want the points. I lost points.
That's how the game works. Fair enough. Paul, you're up. Potpourri. 200. This name later
shared with Star Wars characters was given to the Mohawk steelworkers who helped build
modern New York City. Ewoks. Ugnaughts? Sure. Wait. Yeah. I'll go with Ugnaughts. All right.
Skywalkers. Right, right, right. That makes a lot of sense. See Paul, since that was your
turn, I'm going to address your points with that question. Thank you. Matt. JJ. JJ controls
me. What's their number? 600. What's their number for 600? Daily Double. Oh shit. Yeah,
it's on the line now. The current Pope. Oh Jesus. Is Pope Leo the what? Oh shit. I don't
give a shit about the popes. The American from Chicago. The popiest pope that ever poked.
Oh, I love it. Richard. Pope Leo to Bears. I would rather be locked in a Scottish basement
than figure out whose pope is whose. I will. If you would ask for his name, I could not
have given you Leo. Right. Like I said, I know he's from Chicago. I know he's Chicago.
That's all I know. Yeah, I know. We're so. He literally had a rave at the Vatican like
last week. I get it, JJ. I hate people trying to make these popes hip and likable. It's
like, okay, okay. Yeah. Yeah, but this pope has really good drugs. And good pizza. All
right. Six. Two. Let's try six. 14. Oh, missed it by that much. Close. There's been a lot
of Leos. Good Lord. It's me. I'll try. How it started. 600. This 1992 movie turned Tony
winning musical was originally conceived as an entry of Tales from the Crypt. Ooh. 1992
movie turned Tony winning musical. Tales from the Crypt. That is, of course, The Lion King.
The Lion King. Really? Huh? No, I don't know. Well, what do we suppose? What do we got?
92. 92 musical. I think I know. I think I got it. I think I got it. I mean, I got to
pass. Paul, it passes to you. What do you think? I got to guess Beetlejuice. Yeah, that's got
to be it. Yeah. Oh no. Death Becomes Her. Death Becomes Her. I lost more points. Paul,
he lost the point. I heard that show's amazing though. SJ saw it right before it got nominated
for the Tony. She saw it like with a half empty audience with the original cast and
was like, oh, this is just spectacular. She was so mad that I didn't see it with her.
Oh wow. Paul, you're up. I'll do how it started for eight to try and get back into negative
nothing. Get in there. This four-time Golden Globe nominee was originally cast as Sonya
Blade in 1995's Mortal Kombat. Unfortunately, or fortunately, she broke her wrist while
training for the role and was replaced by that lady who married Pete Sampras. Right.
This was Kate Winslet. Her name was Carmen in that fucking thing. Carmen Electra? No,
it's Cameron Diaz. Cameron Diaz. Cameron Diaz is correct. I know my Mortal Kombat Trilogy
trivia. You do. Yeah. That gets Matt all the way back to zero, which puts him in the lead
with zero points. Matt is at negative 200 and I am at negative 400. Thanks a lot, ML
Kennedy. Matt, you're up. You got four questions left. It's anyone's game. I think there's
a daily double left too. Let's go with potpourri for 400. The roots of this ice cream come
from Greek words meaning new and city. The roots of this ice cream name? Huh. Ben and
Jerry. Haagen-Dazs. JJ, you don't need Greek words for new? Nope. Moose tracks. So I'm
just repeating everybody in the chat. What's my yogurt? What's on my yogurt container?
What do all the captains say? You probably know some Greek. All the captains are Greek.
That's true. Is it Haagen-Dazs? Haagen-Dazs is a made up name. No, it's not a daily double.
Oh, then what am I doing? Pass. I don't give a shit. Yeah, I passed too. Paul. No, I passed.
I have no idea. Neapolitan. Oh man. We're so dumb. If only any of us had thought about
the show that we're currently on. Let's see. I'll try to get some points. What's their
number for 800? The youngest of George Foreman's sons is named what? I believe it's George.
I think they're just all named George. It's George the sixth, little Joey. Little Joey.
Wait, do I get credit for George? Wait, no. It was in the category of what's the number?
I don't know. Was it? If it was what's the number then I got it wrong. I did not answer
a number. Oh, how it started. Oh no, it was what's their number. Yeah. So no, I didn't
deserve those points and I didn't get them. Paul, you're up. You got what's their number
for 400 or turkeys for 200. I'll try turkeys for two. This 2012 Disney movie based off
a princess of Mars managed to lose somewhere around $200 million for the studio. The movie
isn't bad. John Carter. Paul has other thoughts. John Carter of Mars. John Carter of Mars.
Oh, it was just John Carter. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So you got that wrong. You said of Mars. I
did say of Mars. And that is incorrect. And Matt closing out the category and the game.
Going for the tie. Going for the tie. High stakes. What's their number? And it's a daily
double. Oh shit. It doesn't increase anything. Oh, that's right. It doesn't. The current
King of England is King Charles the what? The gracious. The King. Charles's have there
been. Boy, if there was ever a time to start up a new Charles in charge. Let's see, Elizabeth
was Elizabeth the second. So that would make King Charles got bail is King Charles. Daily
double. So I have to guess. The good thing is you know that it's a number. So it's not
like there are infinite wrong answers. I'll go with third King Charles. The third is correct.
Wow. Well done, Matt. That is the game. Matt and Paul are tied at negative or at 200 points
apiece. I have negative 1200 points. But since of course, Matt and Paul tied, cat's game.
I win. Jacob wins. Jacob wins. Congratulations, Jacob. I know that's from ML Kennedy. Thank
you. Thank you. I hope I hope when they because we get we get updates over who writes them.
They score them right. But I hope they get it right. They score your win for Paul and
I tie. I hope that was you guys get the points. Yeah, you get the points in the points totals.
But yeah, yeah, but I should get credit for the win. That was a really good one. ML Kennedy.
Thank you. That was an excellent scooperty. That was if you want to send us a scooperty
just like ML Kennedy did. Hey scoops dot com is reading. Go go over to hey scoops dot com.
You can make a scooperty. You can make the price of scryte jock versus nerd. You can
make us an obelisk jock versus nerd. You can do all those things over there at hey scoops
dot com. You can also send us an email over there. We'll we read emails on the show from
time to time. Matt, I have a piece of physical scoop mail here for you that that a house
guest of mine brought for you. Oh, well, there you go. Our friend Scott Burrell from Natchitoches
is in town right now. Oh, and he brought you a Bruce Springsteen and the East Street band
tour hat from their from their 1999 tour. That's 1990. Yeah, 1999 tour. Wow. That was a reunite.
That was when they reunited. Yeah. So I've got I've got a hat here for you. Freaking
awesome. Yes, I'm very excited about that hat. I want to thank Dr. Mike for stopping
by today. Yes, absolutely. Thank you, Dr. Mike. He and I've been texting since he got
off air. Next time we do a double episode because because when we do two episodes, he
can wake up at a reasonable hour and join us. We're going to do a Dr. Mike answers all
of our medical questions episode. We'll tell the scoops in advance. Oh, good. Yes. All
the scoops. That's a great idea. That's a brilliant idea. Yeah. We should do that sooner
than later. Yeah. I don't know. I mean, I feel like most of the scoops questions involved
hemorrhoids and I feel like we covered most of that today. We did cover a lot of hemorrhoids.
There's no doubt that's going to be hashtag butt stuff. That's there's no doubt. Well,
I mean, it's Dr. Mike's personal hashtag. Did we did we where did we come down on the
razor in your hemorrhoids or no? That's a bad idea. Okay. Okay. Yeah. You're saying
like it was up in the air. It wasn't 100%. I wasn't 100%. I also want to thank JJ, Jessica
Jane for stopping by. Thank you, JJ. I love you guys. Thanks for coming by. Magic over
on Instagram. Go check her out. Give her a follow. Don't follow her in real life. Just
follow her on Instagram. Follow her in real life. She's going to follow. You're going
to follow her down alleys. You're going to find single shoes. It's going to be a whole
thing. Listen, I am so lonely. I was just going to say if you think you're going to
follow her physically, you get in line. There's at least there's at least four other people
trying to do that. They're all magicians. Well, they're not trying hard enough because
I'm lonely. Please talk and visit me. And for me, as your friend, the best I can promise
you, I think December 8th or 9th, we can hang out is the next time we can hang. Maybe come
over to you. You want to do a game night with the boys. We should do that. Yes, that will
be awesome. I miss those little dudes. Yeah. They're not little, but yeah, yeah. They're
big dudes. They're just dudes. They're taller than me now, I think. I think one has got
you. I do think one has got you. Oh, chaotic clumsy. The American health care system equals
showing a doctor from Australia, your hemorrhoids and rashes on a group zoom filled with other
people yelling salt pork at the screen. You're not wrong. Absolutely right. You're not wrong.
It hurts how right you are. It's true. I will go to Europe. Who wants me to go to Europe?
Nobody wants you to go to Europe. I will go. Yes. And Andy, I am recruiting stalkers. Don't
get me mixed up with Mike. Or Dr. Mike. And we got to get our castle show together. All
right. Thanks for listening, everybody. No, we got to thank people. No, sorry. Yeah, we
got Patreons to thank. There are people here that supported us all these years. All of
these people know that you cannot get hemorrhoids as long as you're wearing Spanx. That's a
scoop of salt water, scoop Skywalker, scoop tea, scoopaholic, scoopa troopa, scoop Paul's
drag race, scoop to mids, scoopa Luga, scooper Metroid, scooper Nova girl, scooper Loren,
scooper Jupiter ascending, scoop JD, scoop Kada, scoop knack patty whack, scoop lock
Kisa, scoop neon black, scoop Nick, scoopometrics, scoops a hazard, scoop Trek the experience
and scoopy and the beast. The following people learned the hard way that you should not raise
your your hemorrhoids. Six foot scoop, scully wall scoop, slightly slutty scoop, slurpee
Kaiei motherfucker, Smitty scoop, solar powered scoop, soulless scoop, sound man scoop, spring
loaded scoop, stab and dash scoop, Stacey Coleman, Streets McGreets, Stephanie Young,
Steven Clively, Steven Landon, Steven Biggs, Stuart Wilson, Strange Uncle's podcast, strap
a chicken on scoop, Sugar Rush Socio, Supergeek13579, Swedish scoop, Take it Evie podcast, Tamara
Hamilton, Technical Scoop Hort, temporary dart dot reality, Pierce, Turn the Page, That
Thing in the Attic, The Bad Humor Man, The Sincy Scoop. The following people all have
a pickled graveyard in their backyard because it's allowed by the law. That's a scoopy doobie
do, Scoopy Ramone, Scoopy Bartfast, Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess, Scott A, Scott Andrew, Scott
Ashlock, Scott Headington, Scott Mulderig, Scott Schofeld, Sean Kelner, Seanathan P,
Sebastian Robbins, SF, Sean, Shula Scoop, Silicone Scoop, Silverfist Scoop, and Sir
Scoopy McScooperton the third Esquire. The following individuals all have an elaborate
shrine to Billy Zane in their attic. The Sincy Scoop, the Civic Crew Scoop, the Damsels of
Dorkington, the Devil's Lettuce Scoop, the Didgeridoo, the Famous Ball, the Going Over
Our Fred's podcast, the Ice Cream Headache, the Ice Cream Headache again, the Lapis Lagomorf,
the Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver, the Nano Scoop, the SCOOP, Turn the Page, That Thing in the
Attic, and the Bad Humor Man. And of course I want to thank all of these people who have
prehensile hemorrhoids. That is the Salty Squid, the Scoop Lockian, the Spirit of the
Latin Club, the Upside Down Under Scoop, the Dirty Scoop, the Man, the Myth, the Scoop,
Thomas Beach, Thunder, Cougar Falcon, Scoop, Timothy Sutton, TK421, Scoop Please, Tom
Kreiger, Tom Mankerdy, Tom Stott, Tony Cowley, Tony Scoprano, Travis Jurguri, Travis Murray,
Tristan Guevara, Troy Anthony Tanzer, Tuba Scoop, Tyler Bartlett, Tyler Scoop McDuck,
Udo Gearhards, Uncle Don's Woodshop, Warren Breaux, Water Ice Scoop, Wendy Cooper, Wendy
Bumgarner, Wes Coughlin, What Was Like When Scoop, Who Dat Scoop, Will Beardydan, Will
Kellner, William McDonald, and Wind Walker Scoop 23. Thank you all so much. You are all
jewels in my eyes.
Thank you all so much. If you want to be thanked on air, if you want all kinds of other rewards,
we have monthly and yearly options. Yearly will save you some money by committing to
the year. You get a discount.
That's right.
So, anything that fits your budget, we can use your support right now over at PreachingFun.com.
Or if you don't want to physically follow Jessica Jane around town all the time, just
send her a nice gift. What should you send her? Send her a Fart in a Bag. Fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts, fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz. Not along with, what's the other one? PreachingFun.com.
JJ's all faster.
JJ distracted me with her farts in a bag. Not along with PreachingFun.com. It takes
you to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show
on the air. Of course, we are funded by our Patreons, so head over there, fartsinabag.biz,
PreachingFun.com. Go over and do it now. Another thing you can do after you have gone over
and given us most of your money at PreachingFun.com and fartsinabag.biz, if you have any of it
left over, you can go over to GoFundMe and they are funding the last of the Hey Scoops
the Movie. Help finish Hey Scoops the Movie. If you look up Hey Scoops GoFundMe on Google,
it takes you right to the page. The page is actually called Help Finish Hey Scoops the
Movie. They are currently 70% on their way to the goal.
We want to push it past the goal.
And we want to go past the goal, of course. Because there's going to be more expenses
and everything. It's going to be a bit of a moving target, but it's going to be all
reasonable and great. So if you're interested at all in the Hey Scoops Movie, go over there.
How big of a role does Vinnie have in the documentary?
I was going to ask if he's in that day movie. The day that they were filming the movie,
I'm sure he did.
I think he's the narrator, right? He's the Jiminy Cricket, I think, of the movie.
No, no, no, no. Not okay.
Yeah. Happy Thanksgiving. Oh, yeah. And just a shout out to all of those. Well, I guess
it's too late now. But I'm hosting the Hangout tomorrow at seven o'clock. Oh, yeah, it's
too late. Last episode, you would have heard it, but whatever. Yeah. Good job. Put a button
on that one. Thanks, guys. Glad we circled back. Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, I'm on top of
it.
Oh, right. Does anyone else have any announcements? Yeah. Tomorrow, Hangout, 7 p.m. But that's
Wednesday. That was last week, Paul. That was last week. And this is going out Thanksgiving,
right? Monday. This technically our Thanksgiving episode, yeah? Okay, great. This is our post
Thanksgiving episode. This is our Monday after Thanksgiving episode. Oh. We're all so full.
This is our tryptophan episode. Yeah. Yeah. So we hope that you use some song lyrics if
you got challenged to say grace at your table. Yeah, don't forget to do the... Bermuda Bahama,
come on, pretty mama. Yeah. The Kokomo challenge. The Kokomo challenge. How much Kokomo can
you fake for grace? That's always... If you didn't do it at Thanksgiving, Christmas is
right around the corner. That's right. They always get a chance. I want somebody to get
through it 100% one of these days. It's going to be awesome. I think the Kokomo challenge
is one of the funniest things we've ever done. It is. It really is. It really is. We should
have stopped there. Because a lot of it sounds like a prayer. Yeah. All right. Thanks for
everybody. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon. We'll see you soon.
That dreamy look in your eyes gives me a tropical contact high. Thank you, Jesus. Pass the gravy.
We're preaching fun. See ya.