oh hello there I am so happy you're here because it is time to thank you the
ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers these are
the folks that bring that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear
holes right now I'd like to thank Jonathan Joshua Bartles L'Oreal's rough
Leon Casab, Mary Norbury Glazer, Malia and a random admiral admiral yeah it's a
random admiral if you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like those fine
people and that one naval officer head over to preaching fun calm preaching
fun calm is where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who
knows the life you save may be your own
here's a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love
to great let's go
sitting over there in Pittsburgh PA that's Paul Mattingly sitting over in
Las Vegas it's Matt Donnelly in Las Vegas as well as me Jacob the audio guy we're
preaching fun I like Taskmaster it's a huge fan of how did this get made the
podcast with Paul Scheer and Jason Manzoukas who has done Taskmaster in the
past I don't know if he's on this season or not that well just imagine and I
haven't got it I just informed by a friend but just imagine because basically
wrote them being like why aren't I on this show and like barge this way on it
got us himself invited onto the show yeah but it's an English show and you
have English comedians or British comedians on there and it's the snarky
hosts co-hosts and they put people through like random tasks would have to
be very creative or justify their answers it's all very like very funny
and I didn't know about the show and turned out a friend of ours their
daughter was I'm being informed that's that's not snarky it's just British fair
enough and their daughter was totally into this show and so we decided they're
going to throw a Taskmaster themed birthday party so what happened was they
need a taskmaster coach out to California and and they couldn't come
without bringing a gift because every on the show every community has to bring a
gift with a certain theme ah and the theme had to be rain and sticky was the
was the theme of the of the so everybody brought her a rain stick and a press on
a press of Audrey there was rain and sticky and someone could have you could
have done that but the problem is if you watch the show if you something
predictable then the snarky slash just British hosts will slam you and not give
you points so you have to surprise they'll be British at you and give
points and so at first I was like I cannot believe that I'm driving my kids
out to California and I'm giving them homework right but I start watching the
show with my kids and they haven't seen it either the prep and the show is
really great like it's really funny I'm gonna have to check it out it's it's
really great and Jacob what gift would you bring under the restrictions of
rain oh I glad you asked I already thought about it I would bring a bottle
of pancake syrup that's exactly what I was gonna do I was gonna do a mrs.
Butterworth dressed up like a queen oh no no I'm going to have somebody else
sit in a chair I'm going to do a sticky rain on them oh I was gonna have the
queen the queen mrs. Butterworth she would have the rain of sticky oh that's
good too I like that there's a bit of a pun what about you Matt what did you
end up bringing her so help my kids out with two different ones my one kid
decided to make a fortune-telling jar of answers to any questions that he had
with a with a fishing pole with a and this the hook was sticky it was a ball
of sticky tape so great he basically wrote like yes no maybe ask again fill
in the blank hell no oh he didn't write a whole bunch of like really super
specific answers and just drop it in there I know you should not invest in
that property yeah and then my other kid took an umbrella wrote the most
impressive thing on the umbrella with sticky notes and dropped glue sticks
from strings from each prong on the on the umbrella so he opened up the great
with an umbrella of glue sticks he won he won the challenge with the really
with the glue stick umbrella yeah he's he's good at a lot of things this was a
like 24-hour event this was my friend went way the fuck overboard so they were
throwing a birthday party for their child with all the kids the next day
but the chosen five were to be contestants in in the in the contest for
the whole day the day before they're doing all of that and then having a
birthday party after that yes I was like that is crazy that's too much you need
to have an intervention with these people like no one loves their child as
much no one no so we had our objects I load up with all the stuff they needed
for their sleepover and they were tasks waiting at the door before you enter the
house so it's like they have these like little ornate envelopes with like the
red wax kind of sticky on them or whatever uh-huh and I my two children's
they've been given two different assignments one was told to enter the
house in the most annoying way please I don't even know I don't even want to
know which kid that was that go on and then the other kid was told enter the
house in the smartest way mm-hmm both kids instantly had an idea great so one
kid who had the annoying assignment just opens door and goes hey six seven six
seven six seven six seven six seven six seven and this does it and my other kid
just threw his stuff at me and ran around the house like went to find
another way in to the house yeah and so I entered behind the kid who got the
annoying assignment and said you got to go find my other kiddies coming in some
other part of your house probably good luck to everyone involved uh you know
they were given like all kinds of crazy tasks and the birthday girl was the
hosts and the my co-hosts and they literally ran the whole afternoon with
games and tasks for five of her friends to compete in in the contest that took
place all day you know I'm thinking about I think this is a girl parent
versus boy parent difference you say that Jacob just but I had just a
demonstration of how much harder it is to be a girl parent it is to be a boy
definitely is it definitely is different challenges for sure I I would say though
too like some people birthdays are way more of a thing like yeah with my yes
wife's family birthdays are big big deal you get to eat wherever you want everybody
has to go along like it's a it's a it's a thing yes my my family wasn't that big
of a oh it means occasionally it would be a big thing when we were little
little littler but you know it wasn't it was in our house it was able to be
shuffled around like we still would do like a dinner yes where or event but it
was like hey this brother has a basketball game this brother is a
football game this is like we need to do it next Saturday especially you got that
many siblings - yeah yeah so it was always just a movable thing right we're
gonna go have dinner we're gonna we're gonna have a cake and candles or
something like that some kind of celebration thing and we're gonna do it
at some point did you have a heavy month Matt was there a triple sibling with my
period yeah yeah did you have to you know really contain your birthday flow
no we were pretty we're pretty spread out actually with my fam oh that can be
a trouble with the period - yeah June July we have a June and July August three
month period see a doctor see a doctor yeah April December my sister and I are
well we're nine years apart but we're five days apart that was with the only
similar birthday okay that's why I was wondering yeah yeah but now like when my
you know all of your siblings birthdays I do yeah well it's why I know no one
else's right but people go like I suppose I got shit for like not
remembering when someone's birthdays and I'm like man I just have my family and
that's enough but my when my when my second son was born just two days after
my birthday I was relieved I was like great we don't have to work on birthday
ever again and then just be his birthday yes I really thought we so cool to have
the same birthday but didn't work out right probably for the best for his own
thing but I thought it was awesome nice yeah when he's little you just don't
mention it right you're like you're at his birthday party or whatever like you
you know like it's also my birthday kids or just a room full of eight-year-olds
and no one has told me happy birthday today I think I'll be taking this toy
thank you very much just be like I thought it'd be cool with it you know
what now it's not cool what a cake I did not sign up for this you know who else
thought they were gonna be okay with not being the center of attention for a few
minutes but they were just wrong about it it's the following sponsor today's
show Matt Manley's ice cream social is brought to you by Marcus McGillicuddy's
luxury abandoned homes that's right that's right that's from George
Scoop Stanza it's a good scoop it's 2024 that's Marcus McGillicuddy's luxury
abandoned homes hey Marcus McGillicuddy here and got some luxury abandoned homes
and I'm willing to sell you on the cheap how can I afford to sell this so cheap
two words black mold yep it is the kind that invades and permeates every area of
the house and your body cancer-causing baby-killing diarrhea and zooin black
mold Texas tea as they call it yeah the first two examples were much worse than
the third one you think cancer baby death diarrhea well but it's constant
diarrhea oh that is bad that's right it's not like just oh well I don't feel so
great today no it's it's I am I am I just ate four bags of olestra chips
every moment of your day it's it's like you never stopped eating olestra chips
do they still sell olestra chips I wonder many a business many a business
was sunk on the term anal leakage well add me to the ranks because that's what
you're gonna get you're gonna have a seep and weep and be all if you come and
buy one of my homes filled to burst in with black mold Texas tea enter hey
scoops a checkout I have an eye doctor's appointment today guys well I hope your
eye isn't exploding like mine is I know I know the funny thing was is that I I've
had I insurance been paying for our insurance for the last three years and I
haven't gone yet never used it and it was only because I went to the Verizon
store for my ordeal don't worry I will not get into it again we don't have the
time and they did they did they call you out on your giant font old man I'd love
to read the terms and services here but it's one letter per scroll here Jesus
Christ I broke my thumb trying to get to the bottom to agree to continue your your
TOS took me 18 years to scroll through like I'm so stupid about I stuff like
I was like I don't know the difference between like person who gives you
glasses for someone who gives you an eye exam like I just was like there's
glasses thing optometrist versus optician maybe optician and then I look
ophthalmologist pearl vision was right next to the Verizon store there and then
as I walked by it for like the third time because I went back and forth so
many times I noticed there were doctors names listed on the door oh I was like
oh so they got I doctors in there mmm doctor places it's I walked in as I can
help you I said I I bet yes
how can I have an issue with myself are you in network I go apparently I've had
very good I doctor insurance for a long time like the basic okay it's VSP they
take it everywhere is basically what I was told oh great and so I said I have
this insurance and I had it on my phone and I said Jesus that font I got a
dial at your eyes you have V scroll s scroll insurance that was Matt realizing
you couldn't spell insurance bail bail on bit insurance insurance and I said I
have this insurance I've never been doing I anything before my eyes are
terrible please help oh god wait now are you wearing contacts or anything yet
I've never worn contacts I I have readers hit me all over my house like
like Easter eggs on Easter okay every room has like a pair of readers I've
just thrown there just in case and what what number reader are you purchasing
and hiding around your house that's the round one with a big stick at the end of
it and it's like that's it that's a real big you know one seven five once that's
not too bad okay okay good good yeah I've recently started hiding readers
around my house as well that just go along with my contacts because now my
farsightedness is is thinking about starting to catch up with my
nearsightedness fine which is going real real bad for Jacob seeing any hit the
to Jacob let's hit the to middle-aged white guy let's do it because I need I
need I've added one to the kitchen so I used to have one wherever I'd sit and
look at my phone there's a pair of glasses I look at my phone and then I
started for directions on stuff to cook I had a pair I have a pair next to my
chair and having a pair next to my bed I just have to just just a two around the
house well at first my and this is really fascinating for listeners but at
first like you know obviously reading tiny things was was where it started
just not being able to look at look at small things so so did you have the same
did you have the same reaction that I did when I started to not be able to
read my comic books I was like what the fuck is wrong with this printing and the
same with like macaroni and cheese instructions and things like that I'd be
like who is this font for what yeah what Lilliputians are picking up these boxes
this is ridiculous yes yeah and now the problem might be me you see the TV above
my head that's the bet that's the TV in my bedroom so my I'm further away from
the TV than like a regular TV viewing kind of thing uh-huh now I'm having hard
time seeing the subtitles on shows I'm watching from there so now the other
side's going too so yeah it's time that's both ends it's time but I would
right after yeah right after this episode I'm running over to Pearl Vision
oh nice yeah so they said yes we can't help but not today that's right yeah
that was let's do it let's do a whole appointment we'll do the whole thing
which gave me some time you know give me some time to think about it and so I
started buying a lot of supplements off of Amazon and I think I spent this I'm
trying to cure my eyesight train your eyes train your eyes in three days so I
called back never mind I'm fine right as rain click I saw some tic-tocker he's
like problem solved when I tell you about where these glasses he's got these
glasses that just have nothing but little pinholes in them I wear these and
that fixes my eyes I'm like fuck you do fuck it does you lying at the you hope
it does yeah I understand that you would like it too it doesn't know the idea
like look I know medical costs and medical care in this country is
complicated annoying and expensive everything else but the idea that it's a
constant just like no we don't want anyone to know that the simple blank
exists so that we can just rake in the dough on every single ailment that we've
come up with it's just a little much sometimes yes it is I don't want to sit
around defend the medical industry but I don't think that the whole eye doctor
industry is like shit hope they don't figure out pinhole glasses that we're
doing like yeah my eyes here's how bad the the medical insurance here is my
eyes are terrible we've talked about that in show before my eyes are horrible
you've never seen me without contacts or glasses I can't function without at
least one of those things and like if this weren't this century if this were
just a few hundred years ago I would just be dead in the woods somewhere
right remember there's an old like back like a decade ago an old Netflix show I
think it's called yeah it was a Western show and it had a guy his glasses broke
on like a on the terrain and he's yeah and he spent the rest of the series like
not able to see and I was like holy shit yes I was like oh my god you don't think
about that like my worst fear on vacation is like if I leave town if my
contacts or glasses get fucked up yeah I can't do anything yeah I'm just done
no you will cut pinholes and two pieces I would fashion a mask out of it like a
placemat you would tape it to your head just pinhole your way around Portugal
and I'd be fine then I'd be fine but no our insurance is so bad like I have good
I have good insurance I have good health insurance I've good medical and vision
insurance all that kind of stuff there is a surgery that could fix my eyes my
eyes are so bad I can't do like the LASIK thing and so the surgery is
basically a cataract surgery where they they take that lens out and they put a
corrective lens in in its place and then it's just an implanted contact lenses is
basically all it is probably safer than LASIK maybe I have no idea who knows but
I do know what it does is is it keeps you from getting cataracts later in life
it's also it's also a preemptive surgery for cataracts preventative because you're
doing the cataract surgery before you have cataracts smart with my
astigmatism I'm very likely to have cataracts they will not pay for that
surgery now until they will pay for cataract surgery until you get they will
not it's not they will not pay for the surgery that would also correct my
vision because that's that's an elective surgery even though I will almost
certainly get cataracts in the future and then I'll have to have the surgery
anyway yeah it's fucked it's really stupid it is it's stupid it's awful I
mean one and this is the kind of obstacles I faced as a man of size
trying to address my hip issue for years you know and just being basically you
know dismissed out of hand by the first guy I went to because the doctor didn't
have the appropriate eye prescription and couldn't see you well he could see
me and he was like he was like look here fatty and I was like put these put these
pinhole glasses on and you can only eat things that fit in this pinhole I just
I'll never get over I'll never get over the glory hole diet the the the actual
guy that actually helped help me and fix my leg and the fact that when they got
in into my hip socket they were like it was basically deteriorated into fragments
and dust yeah well we're really surprised how you were walking on that
as am I I told you this for you it's fucked if y'all listen to him bitch
about it for the whole time you wouldn't be that surprised your buddy yeah Jacob
and I were not it was better than what we thought it was gonna be but this is
the same thing like why the fuck don't I just you know and it's it's worse for
women I know that too like it's one thing to be a heavy dude but it but if
you're a woman forget it my god the shit the fucking race the only aspect where
it's hard to be a woman than a man but thank goodness only applies in the
medical field oh yeah yeah just well well everybody has a good day I'll keep
you posted well Jacob do you think there's any way that you could possibly
rectify this because I know that there has recently been a kerfuffle on
tik-tok I don't know what other social media sites you frequent or our party to
but there was a guy on tik-tok I'm pretty much just I'm pretty much just
tick-tock Paul I just do lots and lots of tick-tock well he needed he needed a
liver transplant right okay and the the insurance would not cover it they would
not go through with it he was ready to do it and you know he was gonna die and
so he raised a bit of a stink on on his tik-tok page and it went very viral and
what do you know sure enough they turned around and they did the surgery and he's
gonna live but it takes a couple of million strangers screaming at these
mega corporations to say hey help this person it's fucked up I'm the same way I
won't do that I won't help anyone until there's millions of people experiencing
intermittent or outrage I would also like a liver though so if everyone could
please raise a lot of outrage get Jacob a liver I don't want it I don't want any
surgery I just want the liver put it on ice by the way it's a little update on
the old duo lingo I've after when I was suggested to be friends with my dead
friend I since I've got a lot of scoops and other people follow me on duo lingo
I'm following everybody back I think it's gonna be really funny if my most
popular social media outlet is duo lingo I am eating apples I am drinking water I
am you know eating pan I'm asking people they speak English or Espanol I'm on a
roll I'm on a roll yeah but but in terms of like hey do does your phone listen to
do apps listen to other topics and try to compete with each other my Instagram
apparently was very jealous of duo lingo uh-huh so that they gave me not one but
two friend suggestions for two people who are dead they two dead friends they
offer me to follow back two dead friends just one and two right there first two
many dead friends follow why would you compete with this I think actually Matt
you have inadvertently subscribed to cul-de-sac which is the new app that
just has you trapped in a dead friends and escape I have a lot of friends on
seance have you guys downloaded seance you wanted to say Spanish you got the
seance you wanted to say Spanish yeah that's right that's right
chaotic points out in chat that my duolingo streak is better than my dead
friends so there you go you got that going for me those are wins or wins might
not have made the Myler's Club but goddamn it that streak is on no problem
what are we getting buried with our phones what's the plan here what are we
doing with our phones I don't know what the hypothesis that made that what's
that how does that answer a question I don't know I'm just thinking like maybe
you keep it plugged in throw some kind of bullshit AI on it and let it keep
chirping and chipping away at people long after you're dead me like hey man
what's up you know it's like wait I thought you're fucking dead yeah I'm dead
so what my it's just Paul having weird dark thoughts over here I'm doing fine
that's precisely like that's it I can't think of a more tech bro idea they'd be
like I want to be great when you as your AI self can let other people know you're
dead so to find out from anyone else yeah I mean I mean your brain knows for
like six minutes or something like that they say so hey yeah great yeah phones
are waterproof now so it doesn't that doesn't take Throshen off the table you
know right gates Throshen still there and I can still it's basically I'd be
talking to you from the grave and a submarine it's like the same time well
now the only the only challenge is keeping it powered that's the challenge
is how do you keep the battery going hey how you doing this is the AI Jacob how
are you I hope you're doing well Jacob is not doing well at all he has passed
away I am really sorry to be the one to tell you about this I am 100% sorry that
Jacob has passed away and I am 200% sorry to have to be the one to tell you
about haha yes of course you said yeah you're a good friend and Jacob was you
to know that really good job would you like me to break down three different
ways for you to pay homage to Jacob by the way that might fit your comfortable
lifestyle I know you don't like my firms wait wait I like it I like it yeah this
is gonna be a new thing it's definitely gonna be a new thing yeah yeah well I
mean there's plenty of gravestones with QR codes and shit on them and that
stuff's not gonna stay around forever it's just weird I don't know grave
gravestone QR code is actually that sounds better to me than what we just
came up with that seems like oh how so the idea of just strolling through a
graveyard and scanning QR codes is both beautiful and horrifying you can do it
right now there's plenty of graves with QR codes you can scan it up to bring up
a little memorial and pictures and videos and stuff yeah yeah that's what I
want I want people on their phones you know like I really want people just be
in tech just in their day-to-day shit grieve through the screen put these VR
glasses on and grieve give me your grief in AI AI grief so my oldest kids a spoiled
brat he's this this this week ends with him going thank God you figured it out
first this this week ends with him going to the
sphere with his schoolmates to see Wizard of Oz which we still haven't seen
uh-huh and then the next day they go to Disneyland with the show choir that's
that's his Thursday Friday this week tough tough days but the message we got
for the sphere was hysterical okay so like one is that we have to fill out
photo and press releases for our children in order for them to go you
can't go unless you fill out a photo release because both the sphere and the
school need to put bus to publicize the event they're having school kids visit
the sphere okay what's what's gonna be shown is I got a show in the big nature
film Wizard of Oz yeah no one cares about nature anymore Paul that was when
the sphere opened I don't think they even do the nature film anymore
and then Lauren Shreve is it sounds expensive it is we fundraised throughout
the year you know it's it's death by a thousand donations with schools they
just keep beating you with the same fundraisers I have no idea how much
money we gave to make this happen but I know that it happened in like several
several increments of time do you think that you gave more money to this than
you would have given if you just paid for the kids to go to these events well
certainly Disneyland because their grandmother has a pass so yeah so more
than free more than free you should be like yeah you can take my kid to
Disneyland hold on I'll set up his ticket then the sphere had a breakdown
that was like hey there'll be no book bags or any kind of carrying permitted
into the sphere not even water bottles you can't bring water bottles or
anything into the sphere nothing your children will come in as they are
dressed that's it okay and we will not sell any food or beverage to anyone while
they're in the sphere this is the second no this is no this is I get this
because you get one peanut allergy and it's all downhill bottles of water no
you don't want nothing it's the desert look give them some water go get your
own camel back or where's our camel fuck that's the first line of the sand I've
seen with anyone with school kids and their access to water there's one thing
the kids have just been able to be fucking nuts with is that they must have
access to these oh my god they're so hydrated these children now so hydrated
Mark Gates is no peanut water there's a market salty and delicious peanut water
hey look at that is that official Waffle House merch it's official Waffle House
bunk yeah did you buy that at a Waffle House I bought it off the Waffle House
website because I was waving about Waffle House website send me Waffle House stuff
and I was like what there's nothing here oh we're usable coffee mug yeah look at
that I like that it wasn't the yellows this is the blue one that is a subtle
Waffle House and but yeah so so the kids didn't go there they're they may starve
while they are in there but that's what's gonna happen go in there and then
have no evidence that they were ever there ninjas they must come in right
without a trace there's just gonna be a whole sphere filled with starved and
desiccated children stuck like mummies to all the little chairs just I just want
to know what the sphere is gonna do when a busload of kids shows up and they're
all carrying water bottles like yeah what are you gonna do it really feels
like like whoever's running the actual like boots on the grounds part of the
sphere doesn't have kids and like for like eight meetings they're like and
there's a we have another request from school they're like Jesus Christ with
these school kids want to come here god yeah yeah so I was like well might be
good PR all right they better sign fine this is they better have no evidence
they were ever fucking here they better not fucking pee or eat or drink or not
like I want to it's like we pulled the bathrooms out there aren't bathrooms
anymore we will bring them in through a series of locked chambers it's a bad
idea idea to bring him there yeah any of it yeah yeah I think that I think the
sphere is making a drastic error how about that do your kids are your kids
familiar with the Wizard of Oz yes okay I wonder at what point well what part
will we get to the point where people haven't seen the original Wizard of Oz
enough to get what's going on at the sphere yeah I don't know I mean you know
the whole thing is that the wicked wicked creates this extra more current
right a city for the original that's true Oz yeah who wrote that book in a
minute couldn't couldn't have thought that this was that this was gonna happen
with that of all the you know quote-unquote IP the Wizard of Oz like
you know that's a crazy it's a crazy ass weird psychedelic the guy who wrote
wicked or the guy who wrote Wizard of Oz Wizard of Oz yeah the person who wrote
the original yeah the wonderful world of Oz and all that stuff yeah that that's a
Frank Baum right I think so bomb sounds right yeah so what's fascinating about
him that Ann has continued to educate me on is that his wife is a woman of some
renown who's now flying out of my head one of the suffragettes you can fly no
no no I'll fucking find it but uh yeah his whole family situation was really
really interesting and that's a big part of why he put women forward in much of
his work because he he and his family especially his wife in the forefront of
feminism in that time oh wow oh and it works women have it so easy though no
good job everybody no but it's great I didn't realize that and it's good it's
good that it's good that it just puts women forward and I don't necessarily
make it like oh it's a pro-woman thing so it's good oh pro-women oh bro all right
yeah so I still haven't got anything in the sphere so my kids will like it will
beat me to the sphere experience there do you have a desire to do anything you
want to go see at the sphere I don't have like an eight hundred dollar desire
yeah it's just the price point thing like even even the movies like yeah
because because I'm not gonna see was advised by myself so I think that's like
two hundred something dollars right right but it's still a hundred dollar day if I
take the fam right sure so that's like it's just it just it just doesn't add up
or whatever yeah our pal Lewis was looking out for me for a little while
for first few years stuff that was popping up he runs that liquor
distribution company all right okay but still the spheres tight tight ticket
it's pricey it's a tight it's a tight ticket well it's a nine-inch nails ever
plays a sphere that will prop that that could very well get me to Vegas they did
right now Metallica the Metallica thing is like that's that but that's pretty
great that's gonna be so much money so much money it'll be I think it's gonna
be a lot of money and and but if I ever get the opportunity to I would go see
the Metallica sphere that's for sure yeah are people making films of these
concerts yes several of them yes okay I know there were films of the u2 one well
I know see that's thing like Trent Reznor was working very closely with
James Cameron at one point to put together a toured film and it just fell
apart at the eleventh hour but I would love to love to see all that I still
have I just realized I still haven't sat down and watched Ozzy Osbourne's last
concert that that big huge concert they did shortly before he died that he
actually performed at so two things from that you guys are really kind of
contemplating or beat yourselves up for not seeing stuff it's really Kelly has
turned into a scarecrow and Jack was just on TV talking about how the
benefit money was way overinflated I guess they they had claimed like a
hundred ninety million dollars or something like that remember Ozzy's
concert yeah remember how giant time money that was supposed to be coming in
I don't remember hearing anything about the money but I believe it yeah this
latest interview Jack was like no it was like ten million dollars yeah it wasn't
190 million dollars but then part of me goes oh wasn't it check oh really mr.
runs the till yeah as far as I know we donated I don't think we got any money
our way a lot of expenses here if somebody could reimburse me that'd be
really great exactly exactly so I don't know yeah so my kill my kid will do that
and then I'll go I should take all of the school to Metallica that's what I'll
do good man that would be hip as shit well for your for your next kid's
birthday you could have five of their friends show up Oh could learn to play
all of the Metallica music on real instruments and then you could book the
sphere for them to open for Metallica before Metallica sphere concert you
could do that and then the next day you could throw a birthday party for your
kids and wanted me to tell you Matt and wanted me to tell you I don't know if
you know this map but there is a thing you could do for your kids and their
friends relatively inexpensively if you wanted to show up like a boss Starbucks
has just unveiled a mr. beast drink oh yeah that's you take our bucks you could
take the kids to Starbucks for a mr. mr. beast pick me up I think that would be
like number one on the kids list like if I if I if they could meet a celebrity I
believe both my kids would choose mr. beast really really damn that's sad huh
I know I started watching much less obtainable for them than audio guy for a
podcast I yeah I mean they we just started watching beast games to the
second alright of beast games came out this is admittedly not as
psychologically torturous as the first season so far I've only watched the
first two episodes lessons I learned this lawsuits have been settled not just
a bunch of people being terrible right off the bat and just making everyone
cry there's been a lot less tears in this first two seasons and actually much
more of like competition stuff which is what you feel like legit things happen
with winners and losers so I do think they've learned something from the first
season like go to room one of you yeah psychological breakdown and then you
lose it would have been difficult for them to how hard would it have been for
them to just recreate that first season oh if you were just like do exactly the
same thing here's the new people yeah you would have been like fuck no yeah I
can't be if they did it again it'd be a felony no I thought it was so funny
because he's he is remarkably not empathetic and he hosts like his his
authentic reactions of what he laughs at or like what gets him like a little a
little stirring is always like wow he just has no room for another human heart
in there just not right in there and there's one game where they had to wear
circles on the colored circles on the back of their head and there was
different circle colors on the floor and within 10 seconds you had to run and be
in the proper color okay that mass about your head so it means you had to ask the
person next to you what colors in the back of your head or whatever it's a
you quickly looked around to see who you had alliances with it would be truthful
to you and in this particular round everyone was truthful with one another no
one wanted to fuck anyone over oh nice and so everyone kept going to the proper
colored circles and he kept being like if this is supposed to be a bluffing
game and if no one plays the game then we have to find another way to live by
people and you will not like it and he had to like admonish them for not
fucking each other over and sure enough I did this is sort of drawing people at
random and eliminating people because everyone's being truthful and even after
the first rounds of that happening it never got the bluff game going they just
eliminated people arbitrarily until it got down so that game was just people
well you know that gives me a little hope that creeping fascism might have
some speed bumps along the way oh no I think I think that is a I'm not even
terribly surprised to hear it hear that honestly I've seen several things now
like reality TV games I go down weird rabbit holes on these reality TV game
shows especially foreign-made ones yeah and I just got done with a Korean one
called something like the it translates to something like the devil's game yeah
and it is not a well-made show but the game that they that they built to build
to film the show around is a fascinating game and it was there were people who
were doing kind of what you're talking about Matt there was one guy
specifically he was like I'm gonna try and play this game where nobody gets
eliminated until the final episode which I want to play this game where no one
gets eliminated and we just play for the prize at the end and that's it Wow and
it didn't work out that way but like he had real momentum going and just like
kindness and working together is definitely something that is in the
face of shitty people doing shitty things is definitely something that is
making a resurgence I mean I think people recognize that it's a needed
commodity and and they're filling a void I think yes and I mean it's a good point
that should be represented in those kinds of more exciting or mainstream or
attractive kind of media ways people are generally good good like like the
problem yes the problem is that what makes the news is very right now we're
living in an unprecedented era of blatant power grabs by very powerful
people right right and it used to be that even the power grabbers would have
to pretend to be altruistic or pretend to be you know caring in some way they
had to do at least one press conference where it wasn't just about the oil right
like could you imagine if you know as Elon Musk is winning court cases of
anyone trying to be in the way of him becoming the most obscenely rich person
on earth right he keeps winning these court cases and Tesla keeps battling to
pay him the most amount of money possible and the thing that I find
generally baffling if I were a major Tesla shareholder I would just be
furious yeah all the time and it's this it's this tech bro like Messiah culture
where they just make anyone who's come up with a good idea and got fucking
really lucky yeah become the most you know worship person on earth and
therefore these things can't exist without the worship person being a part
of it right and it's really strange but could you imagine if he said hey if you
if since everyone's making all this money I've decided to make dedicate
blank of my income to go to these other things but he doesn't right I mean look
there are plenty of examples of people who have you know like right Bloomberg
Soros there are plenty of people who have made sure that Bill Gates has spent
a lot of his money and influenced with altruistic endeavors so it's not it's
not without examples that that exists but it's just not the culture it's a
simply not the way it's it's going and so right now we have an era where very
few people are being blatantly greedy for both money and power and going out
of their way to affect people's lives that have nothing to do with it right
and this is yeah that's a thing and those people are inviting other
people's kids to come to these weirdly elaborate birthday parties for their
kids it's not it's not free for the other parents I mean they have to do they
have to spend the time and the money and everything and then they have to go do
all these all these crazy tasks with their children the parent did offer to
reimburse anyone for expenses for any supplies and beg them not to spend more
than $20 so but it's interesting the thought did cross the mind obviously for
that yes of course oh well I think the majority of people are still good and
the majority people are empathetic and look out for each other and I do too and
we see it with people putting the other resources like for example even the
crazy-ass liver story that you told Paul millions of people did rally right like
you know like yeah you know it's like we we do look out for people all the time
did you see the doctor pepper thing I have a lot of friends in Minneapolis so
I'm happy now donating to numerous couples who are trying to get their
loved one out of detention from I say although they are citizens so yeah well
Matt I'm glad that this has I'm glad that all these people's discomfort has
provided a way for you to feel a little bit better about yourself I'm a good
person so yeah yeah no you're doing great Matt yeah I mean you can't have my
liver but other than that I'm you're good part of it all right let's talk all
right all right it grows back what's the doctor do that I had a friend do a live
donation live liver donation oh wow cuz you look cuz your liver is one of your
only organs that does grow back yeah it regenerates yeah yeah I mean yours is a
strong term for you Jacob but like the general ones liver can grow back yeah
a liver can grow back there's this creator on tik-tok who she was like hey
I got a jingle for dr. pepper she's like dr. pepper baby it's good and nice do to
do and people just glommed on to it kept sharing it and doing remixes of it and
full instrumentation everything dr. pepper finally ponied up some dough to
her and they've used it in a national commercial oh nice it's probably gonna be
a Super Bowl ad yeah yeah it's a very viral fun and I would like to take this
moment to encourage that person to go over to preaching fun comm with your new
windfall of cash over to preaching fun comm yeah get us closer to that three
billion dollar mark that's right that's right get us up there yeah yeah and you
know who else would like to get us closer that three billion dollar mark
that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by oh it's over
here guys Marcus McGillicott oh no we did that one luxury abandoned homes
janky Steve's fruit cups that's right it's from dead last though in 2026 who
went for 2026 I think janky Steve's fruit cups janky Steve yeah janky Steve
janky Steve's fruit cups yeah oh oh man oh I got them what you hungry oh man you
want snack oh boy I got over here Del Monte Del Monte oh yeah oh what's left
of a something what's left I mean yeah yeah I saw janky Steve what you can't
see you can't be another people's root cups a little bit fruit cocktail still
left go ahead have some I don't want to have enough you've already all I did was
drink that syrup I leave the nuggets I leave the parts fruit I leave the
nuggets in there I just drink the syrup and I don't even I don't even break the
whole thing I just vampire bite the plastic wrap on the top and I'm looking
through each piece of fruit through the pinhole you've left with your tooth and
I can see it perfectly and that's right are better yeah well now you could now
you're improving your vision and getting some fruit cup and why why janky Steve
janky Steve selling you leftover fruit janky Steve janky Steve come on and get
your leftover fruit I know you're hungry and you're thirsty and you want some
fruit but you won't get a drink of the fruit it's scooted out of the thing when
I put my mouth on the fruit cup of sock did out yeah janky Steve janky Steve only
a little bit of disease janky Steve janky Steve only a little bit of mouth
disease I don't think you could get all my canka sores from where I suck the
drink out from the fruit I don't know for sure but I can't be 100% good luck
with the fruit that I leave you no no no no no no no Jackie Steve Jackie Steve I
should do want some delicious fruit juice I just want the juice from the cup
all I do is drink the juice from the cup every time someone offers me fruit I say
how's can you just juice it for me and they do and they do and they put it in a
cup for me who janky Steve janky Steve janky Steve sucking all your fruit drink
when he wants to sucking it sucking it and drinking it all day long sucky suck
suck that fruit juice give me that fruit cocktail when they said fruit cocktail I
envisioned a cup like a Cosmo and only settle for beverages I want my fruit in
beverage form that's all I like I want to drink it I just want to drink fruit
fruit juice fruit juice fruit juice give me all that fruity juice give it to me
slow through a straw and let me tell you one more thing yes janky Steve also sell
it to you for a discount how how how Jackie Steve Jackie Steve I sell stuff a
little cheaper than I should I'm just losing money that's the way I play the
game I don't have any kind of discount except to lose my own investment so go
ahead and take advantage of janky Steve like the world has the world's fucking
taking advantage of Jackie Steve Jackie Steve shouldn't change things now fuck
it keep on keep on we're taking advantage of Jackie Steve and the deals
you get you get some slurped on fruit mm-hmm have it go ahead have it go ahead
I'll deliver to you I'll deliver it right to your house I actually bought a bunch
of janky Steve firewood from yeah yeah and I delivered it to you didn't I you
did how bye bye I got a broke down bike that I used to deliver stuff I also have
a wagon on the back of the bike it doesn't go very fast very far that's how
I go I get in my old fucking bike and I take my shit where I can't give you what
you need mmm go ahead and call me anytime day or night I'm ready to deliver
with my bike in my wagon mm-hmm sucking on fruit all the way to your house
cuz that's what I'm giving you the sucked on fruit you only get sucked on
fruit delivered straight to your house through my wire rusty old wagon on the
back of my bike that's right that's right and it's discounted which we already
talked about that before you lose I lose my money on the discount mm-hmm that's
just how I go anybody need a special order of a very special fruit hey janky
Steve sorry we didn't hit record the beginning of the ad we just have to go back to
the top yeah all right yeah all right all right yeah great go ahead today show
is brought to you by janky Steve's fruit cups what you might not know is janky
Steve is also an audio engineer how I didn't know that
I just go ahead and push the button on my computer I make it record when I wanted to record and then I take the
thing and I said that on down the road janky Steve janky Steve janky Steve what
down the road your audio files manually absolutely what do you think I'm a
millionaire I lose money on every fruit deal I do this is a problem this is not a
good business plan at all not at all also it turns out all I'm doing is
stealing fruit cups from the local grocery store it or hasten how
janky Steve janky Steve I wear a really big coat put it up my sleeve janky Steve
janky Steve I wear oversized clothes and put it up my sleeve janky Steve I'm a
robber janky Steve I'm a thief janky Steve
what what I should be what I want to confessing to crime yeah whatever the
devil does it all day it doesn't matter anymore there's no rules I have a lawyer
how how how janky Steve janky Steve I went to law school for 15 years
janky Steve was actually a lawyer 15 years of law study I am a lawyer I'm barred in seven
states I have the bar in seven states I am an official lawyer but my practice is
mostly in accidents accident lawyer janky Steve janky Steve the accident lawyer
doesn't do a lot of good when I'm trying to protect my business rights and my
fruit cup business it doesn't really apply cuz I haven't caused a lot of
injury or had any injury to me yeah
janky Steve advertisement I think we've heard the last of janky Steve I can't
wait to see that tapestry he might be Center Square on the next Hollywood
Square usurping Paul Lin janky Steve use oh I don't know I don't know maybe all
right we'll see another important square another important square they're all
important after the resounding success of my 80s movie scooper D trilogy I went
back to the drawing board for a completely original idea that however
proved to be a whole thing so I'm with plan B a reboot please enjoy this
completely fresh take on a stale concept that I'll keep rehashing long past its
overstayed welcome and that is from keester Sunday the categories are 90s
comedy 90s horror 90s action and 90s sci-fi me first I'm hyped for this all
right I'll take a I'll take a 90s sci-fi I'll take that for two hundo after
uncle Fester falls in love with the mom from stepbrothers he says fuck it and
gives up time traveling to stay in the Old West leaving Teen Wolf to go back
home and do nothing notable for nine years until Stuart little came out that
would be back to the future part three that's right future three
Paul hmm I will try 90s horror for 800 Oh Robert Rodriguez's 1996 horror action
classic starring everyone's favorite Batman and everyone's favorite creepy
foot fetishist suddenly becomes a vampire film halfway through when they
end up at titty twister an all-night Mexican bar from dusk till dawn from
dusk till dawn of course that's the $800 one wow that's a great movie oh yeah
Matt and that was also a perfect explanation of it too I need to watch
that again 90s comedy 200 please future stars of the critically acclaimed smash
hits the master of the skies and the love guru co-star in this 1992 skit
turned feature film about two Illinois losers doing a public access show out of
one of their parents basement well-written Wayne's world that is
Wayne's world of course the master of disguise and love guru I want to be a
master of disguise turtle turtle turtle I'll try 90s action 200 you can think
this overrated pseudo-psychological 1999 film where Ted Theodore Logan and Clark
Kent's boss save humanity from enslavement inside a computer-generated
dream world for a decade of annoying parodies and the term red pill that of
course is the lawnmower man matrix matrix 90 sci-fi for 800 where is that
over here daily double here's where it all turns around everything's coming up
Paul mm-hmm this 1994 film has a pyramid and a portal on the poster I made it the
$800 question because I never saw the film so that's the only clue I have for
you I bet Paul knows what it is from that vague description though yeah that's
gonna be Stargate mother fucker that is Stargate isn't it what else could it be
the only way would be what's his name the guy spader spader spader spader
would have put it over the edge I'll do 90s action for 800 mace Windu helps the
singer from the critically acclaimed the return of Bruno solve Alfred's fun
puzzles around the Big Apple 1995 action thriller it was the third in the series
and they never made another one I don't know the singer oh shit
I'm and I'm not even trying to give you a hint on this one I think I think this
movie was difficult tedious arduous hard day's night close close close if you're
if you're if you're rolling in the back alley what are you using a garbage truck
no I'll pass you're shooting passes to me oh it's diehard but which it's the
what's the subtitle yeah that's the thing and I knew Paul already knew the
diehard one is this I'm not I'm not confident in what it's called either yeah
yeah no I knew you knew the diehard part though is it it's not it's not is it die
hard I think it's the third one it's a third one but is it die harder is or is
that with a vengeance diehard with a very hard with a vengeance diehard with a
vengeance maybe it is diehard with a vengeance it might be diehard with I'll
try that I'll try diehard with a vengeance okay diehard yes definitely
not have gotten that one kudos it's me I'll try a 90s comedy for 800 in this
comedy Rudy and Mitzi Shores idiot son befriend a prehistoric George of the
jungle humor is supposed to follow instead what actually followed was son
in law and bio dough son-in-law is pretty good movie son lies but son-in-law I
believe my wife unironically really enjoys it's a good movie this movie
though mm-hmm has that guy in it and my wife is screaming in the car and just
coincidentally or because of this question I mean coincidentally she's
always screaming in the car but she loves this movie she loves this movie
it's one of her fuck it's Brendan Frazier come on pass it to me baby give
me the rock toss me the pill come on Jacob you got diehard with one of and
you can get this one and see no man oh you got it mother fucker you got it I
knew it was a place you got it Paul uh 90 sci-fi for 600 please let's see here
in the middle of his Johnny Depp phase Monica Bellucci's future ex-husband
directed this somehow depletes star-studded bomb in 1996 about hilariously
sarcastic spacemen attacking the United States it was based on a series of
1960s tops trading cards Mars attacks no I'm sorry it's also in Cino man I wish
that was such a strange film oh I love that movie Matt I will do 90s comedy for
600 word association time Amish fake hand comb-over oh fuck it's the bowling
movie with Bill Murray yeah and Woody Harrelson yeah Woody Harrelson's that's
a funny fucking movie - yeah it is that is a good movie he'll pick that spare up
when my hair falls out I'm afraid that they pass I wonder how that holds up
it passes to me fuck
throw me to rock now I can't think of it Paul go ahead Kingpin Kingpin that's it
it's me I'll do 90s action for 600 and this globally celebrated action
blockbuster president Lone Star and the guy who tried to cook Chris Rock's face
like chicken lead America and saving all the non-america countries from aliens
running windows 95 on their mothership hilarious hilarious I believe this is
Independence Day yeah those are some great clues oh yeah well I go to the
night when I go without a fight case oh that speech killing it Paul 90s horror
for 600 oh here we go cracking it out for cracking it 800 wow I'm getting my ass
kicked huh you are getting your ass I just noticed that I was like holy shit
Matt is losing badly subterranean creatures are from are closer than six
degrees from footloose and Joe dirt's dad who are fighting for survival in a
small Nevada town but the monsters are no match for Reba McIntyre's comically
large artillery stash Tremors Tremors of course I knew that one guys you did know
that one thanks guys Paul now has a lead with 5600 points has 200 points the only
questions left are all 400 and 200 so there we go that's right we burned all
the hardwoods there is a daily double out there though no need Paul again I
think I got both of them did you already get both of them yeah oh shit all right
never mind I think Matt you're up well I'll do I guess we'll find out for 400
the dad from the conjuring falls for Rachel Green and begins to take his
cubicle job in stride after an occupational hypnotherapist dies before
he can end the trace he put him under in this 1999 bomb turned cult hit office
space huh office space is correct best I saw that in the theater hey I got one
guys fuck nice thanks thanks for having me fantastic Matt Donnelly everyone Matt
Donnelly love that movie I'll close out 90s action for 400 yeah that's right
deuce bigelow I don't know how to use the three seashells who in the fuck knows
how to wipe their ass with three seashells fuck you oh sorry I misread the
first part yeah that's right deuce bigelow sorry was at deuce bigelow not
about deuce bigelow that would be the the 90s classic demolition man yeah
Paul you got 90s horror or 90s sci-fi what do you want mmm let's go sci-fi
for 400 Paul Verhoeven rounds out a trilogy of unrelated violent satires
with this 1997 film starring Tarzan Christmas Jones and Doogie Howser about
a future fascist government false flagging a war with space bugs to prop
up their war-based economy oh that is oh why is it going away from me I can see
it oh yeah soldier fight soldier fight that's
a bugs starship troopers that's it starship troopers no I'm sorry it's
soldier fight bugs soldier fight bugs soldier fight you should have gone with
your first instinct Paul soldier fight I was close
Dickie Steve 90s horror for 200 or 400 Matt directed soldier fight soldier fight
bugs on MTV I will take these horror for 400 just see if I can at least make it
get some extra points there 12 years before she filmed the sexiest hot tub
scene of all time reboot matlock saves Sonny Corleone from a car accident and
then infects one of the most ball retractingly painful acts ever filmed
for an Academy Award winning movie RIP Rob Reiner misery yes reboot matlock
matlock is great that's pretty good I'm closing out the category and the game
90s horror for 200 Wes Craven revived the whodunit slasher subgenre with this
1996 film starring that girl from party of five Monica and the guy that owns
bozo the clown spoiler alert it was shaggy and that weirdo from the craft
was that scream that's it or was the other one it was scream alright scream
I'm gonna go with Paul's hint and go with scream scream is my hands are always
pretty good your hands are always pretty good you didn't need to save it that
time because Paul crushed us with 6,000 points I got second with 3,200 and Matt
got a respectable third place with 1,000 points well done Matt and well done
keister Sunday for that really yeah that was great is on my magic podcast we were
making fun of like basically a telltale sign you haven't written your trick well
enough as if you are the only one go like wait what what's this over here
right I was laughing at jakey steve going like how how Paul should just
lecture with jakey steve at magic magic just toss it to me be like wait what why
why I want to thank the following people who all got herpes from jakey steve
or hey Masalo Joseph Foster Joseph Paul rero Joseph pen Grazio just Joshua
Wilson Judy Schneider Kai McMillan keister Sunday Keith Corning Kenny
Colin Tony Craig Ruth Kristen Kledek Kurt Egner Kurt Hendrickson Kyle Wells Kylie
cones Larry Goodale Lee McGarrel I think Lee popsicle and Leon Cox the
following people have all died from dehydration inside the sphere
Morgan see they weren't allowed to bring in their drinks Luke Mellon M hurts mama
ninja scoop mark sadowski Mario Rosa Mark Madison Matt's Lindgren Matt
Daugherty Matt Glowacki Matt Mackenzie Matthew Dugan Matthew Smiel Melissa
Archiga Merlin's barn podcast Michael Calder Michael Ellsroth Michael Shaw
Mike J. Nielsen Mike six and Mike Wentz and the following scoops all know that we
recorded this sometime in the past that's me for me for revia me for
revia I think so Mitch Hedberg lives bit Zula Mohan Nair monotonic scoop Monica
day Myra Nate Taylor Nicholas Newman Nick Dingman Nikki Benoit oh knee knee
okie knee okie knee maybe oh yeah I like it okey scoop one fell scoop Patrick
Michelle Paul Clayton Paula Pete mortis Pete Romano Peter bougie and Peter
Heinz thank you so much everybody mm-hmm thank you so much if you want to be
thanked on air with your name perfectly pronounced then the hell over to
preaching fun commas like the tear that fits your
or if you think Matt's friends need to put a little more effort into their kids
birthday parties head over to farts in a bag that means that along with preaching
fun calm it takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as three
dollars a month you can upkeep this show on the air we are dependent on our paid
patreon subscribers so please if you think this show is worth more than zero
dollars preaching fun comm farts in a bag dot biz head over there you can
subscribe on a monthly basis you can subscribe on a yearly basis that saves
you a little bit of money it also helps us out because we can see what our
yearly budget is a little bit better and you can also gift subscriptions to a
friend I still stand by gifting someone a paid subscription to a podcast is the
most hilarious way to get them to listen to that podcast I agree yeah right well
thanks for listening everybody stay safe out there we love you and we'll see you
soon
oh yeah I did learn today that Waffle House has a merch page on their website
very happy to know that