There aren't many guarantees in life, but there are in life insurance.
If you're 50 to 85 years old, call ColonialPen now, 1-800-757-4488.
With ColonialPen's guaranteed acceptance, there are no physicals, no health questions,
just permanent, whole life insurance designed to help cover final expenses and medical costs.
And as long as you pay your premiums, your policy can never be canceled.
That's right, all those worries you have, how your family will manage the bills when you're gone,
will they be okay financially? ColonialPen is the answer.
Plans are available to fit almost any budget,
because cost should never be the reason you can't protect your family.
So again, if you're 50 to 85, call 1-800-757-4488 now for your free
beneficiary planner from ColonialPen. There's absolutely no obligation.
That's 1-800-757-4488. 1-800-757-4488.
Two-year limited benefit period. Ages vary by state.
Once insured, your rate will never go up. You choose an option that's best for you.
Premium is based on the option you choose. Benefit amount based on age and gender.
As long as you pay your premiums, coverage can never be canceled.
That's right, all those worries you have, how your family will manage the bills when you're gone,
will they be okay financially? ColonialPen is the answer.
Plans are available to fit almost any budget, because cost should never be the reason you can't
protect your family. That's 1-800-757-4488.
Plans are available to fit any budget, because cost should never be canceled.
It's the key to building the future you've been working toward.
Visit MyFICO.com/free or download the MyFICO app and take the mystery out of your FICO score.
I'll get on here and apologize right away.
Patreon's switch is default, so when I put up a Zoom link to our Patreon members,
it only went to free members and not to anyone else, and that's my bad.
You'd think the paid members would be the default.
It's time for Matt and Maddly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in Port, it's Matt Donnelly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Maddly.
Sitting in Vegas, it's me, Jake and the Audio Guy.
We're preaching fun.
Oh yeah, ScooperNovaGirl was just mentioning YouTube doesn't care about swearing anymore,
and that does seem to be the case.
They have arbitrarily just changed up the whole thing, and you say,
"Fuckity, fuck, fuck, fuck, as much as you want."
Right at the top, doesn't hurt a damn thing.
Well, then they deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Yeah, baby, that's what I'm talking about.
I'll go back in and edit that.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yeah, no problem, no problem.
Yeah, yeah.
Paul, how's your eyeball doing?
Okay, so eyeball update.
Hold on, I'll play the theme.
Eyeball update, eyeball update.
It's a ball in Paul's head that he sees through.
Hey.
So, left eye.
I'm left eye Lisa Lopez, and I went into the...
So, optometrist is the one to get you your glasses.
Ophthalmologist is the one that actually looks at your eyes, right?
Uh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, let's say yeah.
Anyway.
I mean, optometrist also looks at your eyes, I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
For the sake of this, yeah, let's go.
Do we really know the answer to this question like in our hearts?
Optomologist is the one that knows how to really get in there and do the thing.
Yeah.
Larry in the chat is saying, "Optomology is surgery."
Yeah, so I went to the ophthalmologist.
According to R.F.K. Jr., you're supposed to see a shaman.
I don't think your eyes can ever heal until you start having more.
You need to have a worm in your eye.
R.F.K. Jr., I wasn't going to bring you in until later.
In the guest segment of the show, but it's good to have you.
Yeah, well, I've been watching you guys.
You got a real, you got really a show here.
Oh boy, oh boy, what a show.
I have to say some of your information seems to be
outdated from what I understand.
Medical accuracy.
How many bloodlettings did you do today?
I personally have 18 leeches on my scrotum right now.
Yeah, but not for health reasons.
Well, no, of course not, personal pleasure.
The Kennedy curse is bald leeches.
I have misunderstood what the Kennedy curse was for years.
Ever since Chappaquiddick, that's what actually, it's a curse.
The Chappaquiddick leech, the cat Chappaquiddick ball leech has just come.
So how's your eye?
Okay, so it hadn't gotten any worse, which is good.
Good, good, good.
Over two days or whatever, the guy looked at it very intently.
Right eye is fine still.
The fact that it's only in the one eye,
it is possible that I have some back and forth blood flow issues.
So just to be on the safe side, we're going to get that.
My whole neck looked at for the veins going back and forth there.
Just see if there's any kind of...
Well, you've always had a great neck.
It's any kind of occlusion.
Anyway, we'll see.
But he doesn't think that's it either.
He seemed to be very, very positive about it's just probably,
it's probably just the stress of scoop fest, the extra work, the extra travel,
all the extra lack of sleep, all that shit, and dehydration, et cetera.
Then, yeah, and then that's it.
So it's probably just on its way to Wellsville.
It's healing up, hopefully.
But I had all the blood work in the world done.
I don't have AIDS.
I don't have syphilis.
That you know of.
And I'm not...
Not yet.
You don't have them yet.
I'm not diabetic.
Well, that's the case with all those things.
I'm not diabetic yet.
I'm not syphilis yet.
I'm not AIDS yet.
Yeah.
We should start to go fund me for Paul to get syphilis.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that doesn't cost that much.
Couple hundred bucks, right?
Oh, you're paying a couple of hundred bucks.
Who's your syphilis guy?
I can get it for you for half the price.
You know, it depends on where, what kind of syphilis you want.
Several different versions.
I got bear syphilis when I was...
Bear syphilis, simple bear syphilis.
The disease that comes from a bear.
I have misunderstood what the candy first was for years.
I need the bear syphilis.
Get it from a grizzles.
Who fucks you and me as you'll get it there.
All right.
I'm going to write a musical about RFK Jr. getting bear syphilis.
That's good.
Good. Another one.
You can write another song about getting bear syphilis.
I got the bear syphilis from carrying a bear carcass.
I thought it would be funny as a joke.
What an asshole.
All right.
So, yeah, I go to get my thing looked at in a couple of weeks
and then I go back to him in like five weeks.
Oh, but the one thing that was kind of rough during the whole exam,
the second exam, the follow up.
Anne was there with me the whole time again.
She's great as far as follow up.
Even she got a little squeamish because at the very end,
he's like, okay, I'm going to press on your eye now.
It might be a little discomfort.
Because you don't you've never worn contacts or anything.
No, no, no.
So, yeah, so I was like, you know, just jamming on there
and looking with the thing.
So that didn't feel wonderful.
An optometrist told me something when I was a young kid
first getting contact lenses.
And it is something that has stuck with me
and weirdly made me feel better for decades of my life.
Yeah.
Which is your eyeball doesn't really feel pain.
So whatever you're doing, like everything around it,
there are nerves around it that feel pain and everything.
Right.
They're like, yeah, yeah, your eyeball is fine.
So mess with your eyeball, like touch it, do all the stuff.
It's just weird and icky, but it is fun.
It doesn't hurt.
Yeah.
So.
Matt's out.
But my eyes.
Thank you.
My eyes definitely.
Not having stick your finger right in there.
I'm good.
So I had him dilated.
What's the patron level for Matt to poke himself in the eye?
I had him dilated on Friday twice.
Scoop pink guy.
And then I had him dilated again yesterday early in the morning.
So dilating motherfucker.
I'm definitely like, I'm feeling like, oh, geez.
So I think the, I don't know.
Can you, my eyes just feel tired.
Yeah.
My eyes just feel tired.
I slept as much as I could today.
And yeah, let me look to do some more sleep as soon as I can.
But, uh, otherwise rock and roll, uh, Viatola, everything seems to be okay.
So that's good.
I appreciate everyone's, uh, concern and, uh, I'll keep you updated.
But, uh, so far, so good.
Hopefully it's just a, a symptom of a lot of travel and whatnot.
And I've got a little wheeze going on now.
I'm, I'm laying down, reading my comic books last night before I go to sleep.
And I, and I hear this little squeak and I'm like, what is that squeak?
And it's me.
That is, and it's coming from your eye.
That's my life, man.
That is my tiny little, a tiny little squeak coming out of me.
Every, at the end of the night, I'm like, what the hell is going on?
So just a little squeak at the end of my, my breathing.
There's a small dog trapped inside of you.
No, at home, I like sleep with my head facing away so that I don't let my like weird,
weird throat organ, uh, keep my, keep my wife awake.
It happens all the time.
I've never thought your throat organ was weird.
Oh man.
I mean, and I, my throat organs, but you know,
best throat organ in the business.
Yeah.
So, but, uh, yeah.
So there's, there's the update.
How's the boats treating you, Matt?
Oh man.
Well, the streak had to come to an end sometime.
I got on board and was immediately demanded to hand over my knife to security.
It did happen.
Holy shit.
This is one for the books.
Virgin nicer cabins, stricter about not talking about your creeping fascism.
And then, uh, that's what I said.
I thought this boat was about freedom.
I yelled, no, it's not, it's, it's buffets.
This boat is about buffets.
I mean, anything for those passion fruit meringue tarts.
Here, take my knife.
There he is.
Uh, yeah.
So what happened?
That's a, that's a key part of your act.
No, no, they give it, they gave it to me for my show.
So they keep it checked somewhere before, when you're not performing.
They keep it in the, the, uh, the, the arms, the arms safe, but whatever.
Do they really lock it up?
They lock it up.
Yeah.
And then some from security brings it to my show and as soon as my show was over,
I was like, Hey, I'm here to collect your knife.
I said, Oh, there you go.
Is it possible that they are worried about, uh, pirates and boarding parties?
And they're like, we have to do this.
It's just the captain's general order.
Like get, get all of the weapons in case we have to repel boarders.
They actually said, they said, it's not a policy across the board.
I said, we ran a background check on you specifically, and we're taking the knife
away from you is what they said.
Stop it.
They did not.
I don't know what to believe anymore.
We're through the looking glass here, people.
I don't know.
I agree.
Everything's fucking crazy.
Have you seen all these fucking AI things that are coming faster?
Furious now?
It was coming out of my mouth.
I was like, wait, this is, this isn't as extreme as this is too real.
It's too real.
It's too real, Roy.
Yeah.
Very good.
That's right.
Born in Jersey, hand the knife over pal.
Yeah.
Oh, that makes sense.
That's a, yeah.
A cursory background check.
Born in Jersey.
Get the first red flag right away.
First item, first item on the, on the background check.
They didn't even have to read down the list.
No.
And I had a, uh, we have other magicians here on board, uh, uh, early foolish,
Kyle and Misty night, a little magic duo.
Uh, this guy, Tom, follow them on the Insta.
This guy, Tom Crosby, who fooled Penn and Teller with his Rubik's cube routine.
Nice.
Uh, he has a, he, it's one of those things where like, if you knew anything about him
before he went up, he has a Rubik's cube Twitch channel that's very popular.
So in terms of guessing whether it was a gimmicked cube or skill,
had you known about his Twitch channel, you would have guessed skill.
But he fooled them.
I remember that.
He was, he was one of the, he, he went on and fooled them, uh, by just doing it.
Ultraviolet.
Yeah.
He had someone else next to the cube.
It was ultraviolet.
He took a flash ultraviolet flashlight to it and then saw the behind his back.
Yeah.
And so with the, with the cube, they thought they guessed that basically the cube can light
up whichever way it wants.
It can light since, since, since it's the UV thing, you can light it up.
Therefore it's a right thing.
So, uh, yeah, technically puzzle cube.
Good job.
Scoot shooter.
Uh, Rubik's cube is a brand name.
Puzzle cube is the, is the term, although most cube people still say Rubik's cube,
even though almost none of them use an actual Rubik's cube.
Right.
Yeah. Actual Rubik's cubes are junky clunky cube.
Uh, there are so many, uh, more well-made cubes by different companies that people use.
Yeah.
Anytime you see somebody like holding it with one hand and like spinning
just a single plate of it or something like that with their, with their finger real fast,
that is not a Rubik's brand cube.
Yeah.
I remember way back in the day, we got one from rice checks, uh, proofs of purchases.
Did you ever have a rice checks cube?
Rice checks cube.
Yeah.
No.
What?
Rice checks.
Like the cereal?
Rice checks did a rice check.
Yeah.
The cereal that, uh, that we did a mail away rice checks cube and it had like
rice checks on the stickers and stuff.
Yeah.
It was interesting.
Um, huh.
Rice checks really got into it, man.
They even had a doom clone towards the end of their, uh, well, I guess they're still out there,
but they did a doom clone.
Uh, for cereal clone.
Yeah.
You know, you remember doom, the hot, the hot, hotness, the game.
Yes.
Oh, the video game.
Okay.
Yeah.
The PC game.
Yes.
Yeah.
I remember doom.
Okay.
They included a disc on there.
Uh, there it is.
Oh, yep.
It's in the chat now.
There's the, that's the checks, the checks.
Uh, oh, you beat me to it.
Yep.
And, um, there was a doom clone that they came out with checks quest.
Checks quest.
And, uh, that came as like a CD on the packaging.
There it is.
There's checks quest.
Wait, someone in chat is saying my uncle made that game.
Get out of here.
What is happening?
James T.
Scoop.
Scoop is saying that, uh, get out of that for real that your uncle worked on checks quest.
That's captain James T.
Scoop.
Could you unmute yourself?
Hey, sorry.
One second.
We got to get out of my office.
Oh.
If she talks about her uncle in her office, she gets, she had to call the cops.
Yeah.
I just, they put her right down.
Um, but yeah, yeah.
He's uh, well, he's not my uncle anymore.
He divorced my aunt.
Um, don't bring up his name at a family reunion.
I'll just say that.
I will not.
Okay.
But yeah, thank you for the heads up.
Once he invented the checks game, you know, all the power and fame went to his head.
Even though that's right, that's right.
He's a little nutty, um, according to my dad, but yeah, no, he's my, um, my cousins,
he's their dad and his son is a big game developer now.
And yeah, pretty cool.
That always got me a lot of points with the boys in elementary school.
So, you know, sure.
Well, yeah, cause all those, all those boys in elementary school, they were all just hard
for rice checks all the time.
They were like, God damn it.
Give me that rice checks.
Freeware was over to have my dad coming back to me up and be like, yeah, she's down the truth.
Wow.
Did you ever get like a special copy or anything?
Um, no, I don't think so.
I'll have to ask.
I'll have to ask my dad, but I don't think so.
Listen, uh, James D Scoop, don't give away where you keep your private checks,
memorabilia collection on air.
No, no, do not.
It might get robbed by those NFL players.
Yeah.
Yeah, fair point.
I'll have to add my security, you know?
Well, that's really cool.
What a small world, huh?
Yeah.
It's pretty neat.
How, how, how often have you ever bring that up in conversation with people?
You know, I wish I could say not often, but I have so little that I can brag about.
Also, I wish I could say I brought it up last, Jack's quest was monumental.
Monumental, I say.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
Tall enough people do, um, to have people on related to the guy that made doom.
I mean, like I said, a lot of people think that's pretty cool.
So yeah, I'm fairly certain.
I'm 90% sure that might've been the very first free video game
ever given with a product.
Oh, interesting.
Certainly the first free video game given with a cereal.
I got to believe.
Well, apparently he wrote a, he wrote a book.
His name's John Romero.
And, um, my aunt is.
Stop it.
Wait a minute.
I didn't know who you were talking about.
John Romero is your uncle?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Former uncle.
Oh fucking look, hold on.
Oh my God.
Paul is leaving.
It'd be great.
Like if like Paul's chair just backed up like into a wall and like through a wall,
like Kool-Aid man and then just kept going.
Paul keeps his ball.
It's coming.
Paul keeps his another room.
He also has a hidden Romero vault.
Holy crap.
Don't tell anyone where it is.
Do you guys have any idea?
John Romero is the number two guy.
It's John Carmack and John Romero.
Wait, John Romero, John Romero is the guy that did the rice checks.
He did the Rice Checks Tube.
The Rice Checks thing isn't even.
He, that's not even, that's not even.
No, this is, okay.
This is, this is the book.
Masters of Doom.
Oh yeah, that's his book.
Yeah, my aunt's in there.
So Masters of Doom is all about the incredible success of Romero and Carmack.
Motherfuckers.
You guys, fuck you guys.
Fuck you guys.
John Romero is a seminal, he is a seminal character in video game history at large.
Oh yeah.
How do you feel about my first date with my husband?
Yeah, that's right.
He is.
He's incredibly important.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He's still.
Oh yeah, you know.
No, he's one of the more important video game guys that I talk about ever.
So he finally left Id.
He left Id kind of early.
And, um.
Seems like he has a leaving.
Am I right, James T. Scoop?
It does seem to be.
Well, he started his own thing and he fucked up because his big game,
Daikatana, was a massive failure.
They put tons of money into the advertising and everything.
Even the song.
Hey, Daikatana, I.
So the, but the big advertising push in many of the print ads was in, you know, in September
or whenever the game was coming out, John Romero is about to make you his bitch.
That was, that was, that was the tagline.
Because he had such cache among first person shooter fans.
But then the game, the game tanked.
So were you around when Daikatana came out?
Was that part of why he left?
Because the failure of Daikatana, everything went to shit in a relationship
after he lost all that money.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he, oh gosh, I don't want to speak out of school here.
I don't want to get like quoted on like BuzzFeed or something.
Yeah, a lot of national press checking out social.
I think, yeah, the first time he lost all his money is about the time they split.
So pretty early on.
Yeah.
My dad always was, he's just one of those guys who'll lose his money,
but then he always finds a way to make it back.
He's out living in Ireland right now with his new wife and kid.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's still, he's still very wealthy guy.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
He's doing all right.
Yeah, but you're right, he's gained and lost fortunes over the years.
Oh yes.
We got a, I almost said email, but we got a mail mail,
an invitation to a wedding in Ireland from Sarah Buren,
who has been a longtime listener and apparently is getting married in Ireland.
So we should go get married and see Sarah in Ireland
and go visit with your previous uncle.
Yeah, that sounds great.
Yeah, why not?
Oh, the wedding is in, oh, it's coming up.
It's at the end of November.
Okay.
Probably too late to rally it out.
We could have stayed at John Romero's house.
Ridiculous.
Well, that is absolutely fascinating.
I had no idea, I had no idea.
Yeah, no, it's really fascinating.
Yeah, and so, and my husband, he's a software engineer and he,
you know, works on the side, makes the games.
He's developing an app right now.
And so he and my cousin, Michael, John's son,
you know, they, yeah, they talk about stuff and, you know, anyway.
So they're pals.
So, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Oh, that's wonderful.
Did the same guy make the game Quake?
Yeah.
I don't know if, I don't know if Romero, I guess, I think he was,
yeah, he was on with Quake.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just, I mean, I just looked him up and it says, it says Quake.
Yeah, yeah, he was on with Quake.
Yeah. Great.
I mean, yeah, full disclosure, like, I mean, I don't know John,
very like really at all, but mostly his sons, you know, but yeah, yeah, it's fun.
But that's so funny though that you're related to the guy who made the Chex Cube.
Yeah.
So even though he's not actually part of the family anymore,
I assume that you're going to get that sweet Chex Cube money
passed down to you when he dies.
I guess it's time to come clean.
I'm not here as a cruise ship entertainer.
This is my cruise ship.
I'm on my own ship.
Which makes the knife thing even weirder.
Excuse me.
Yeah, I took it.
Oh, Matt and I sound exactly the same.
No, I just coughed all the time.
It's miserable here.
I'm in St. John, New Brunswick and it is just.
Overcast, dreary.
It's dreary.
Oh yeah.
This is the storm because we're sitting right on top of everything.
And so it just makes my whole face blow up.
Captain James D. Scoop, thank you for telling us about your previous family.
Thank you, Captain.
That was awesome.
Yeah, thanks guys.
Next time I see you in person, I can tell you some stories
I don't want to say while being recorded.
Fantastic.
That's awesome.
Thank you.
I'll tell you who else Captain James D. Scoop is going to tell stories about
next time she sees us in person.
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Madeline's Ice Cream Social is brought to you by...
Come on, internet machine.
Go, go, buddy.
Oh no.
Brought to you by Dirty Diana's New Jersey Diner.
That's right.
That's Dirty Diana's New Jersey Diner from Ranch Ham in 2022.
Do, do, do.
She wants some french fries with cheese but she ain't willing to pay.
She's pretty hungry, you know.
She ain't ain't nothing today.
She's gonna step right on in and get herself a plate.
She's really hungry, you know.
This girl, she will not wait.
She says, "What pies do you have?"
They say, "Apple and peach."
She says, "That will do."
"Give me one slice of each."
"Can I also get an order of fries and cheese?"
They say, "We don't serve that."
"And she got on her knees."
"Dirty Diner Diana."
"Yuck."
"This floor is gross."
"Ick."
"This floor's disgusting."
"Gross."
"Why did I kneel down?"
"Get it clean."
And her hay scoop's a check out.
Yeah, I'm not gonna be able to rhyme that better again.
The worst part of that song is the end of that song when she realizes that even after
she did all that, they don't have any other flavors of pie.
No, that was it.
She got her two flavors though.
She got one slice of each.
She got those two, yeah.
Yeah, that was good.
That turned out good.
"Dirty Diner Diana."
That was good.
I made those rhymes.
It ended well.
I'm very happy.
Very happy, yeah.
Good.
And you killed it before I could ruin it, which is good.
Yeah, 'cause if I went further, it would have gotten weird.
But it's still good.
Speaking of throat organs, I went and saw Paul McCartney this week.
Oh my God.
I went and saw Beetle perform this week.
It is a whole fucking thing.
How did he do?
He is really good at that.
He's still really good at doing the whole thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the whole putting on a show and singing and talking and doing the whole thing.
He's had a minute or two.
It's like he has practiced, and he's very, very good.
Did you get graced with the double Beetle shot?
Did Ringo pop in "Secret" on this one?
No, Ringo wasn't in town.
He was in town the week before, and I was hoping that he would stick around and make
an appearance, but it didn't look like he did.
So yeah, no special guest, but holy fuck was the show good.
They had audience cameras and everything.
At one point, the camera stopped on somebody in the audience, and Paul was talking to them,
and they had a sign that said that they had seen the Beatles at Shea Stadium in 1965.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
He's like, "Wait, you really saw us in 1965 at Shea Stadium?"
And she's like, "Yeah, I fucking well did."
It was so crazy, the number of people that were there, what it meant to everyone.
I took my mom.
My mom came in town, and so she came in town to see the Beatles.
Yeah, I mean, it meant a lot to her.
It meant a lot to me.
It meant a lot to everybody around us.
Yeah, it was so fucking cool.
It'd be like John Romero showing up to my house.
It would be exactly like that.
Hey, Dicatana, hi.
Hey, Paul McCartney Singh, hey, Dicatana.
I mean, you talk about...
I kept yelling it out.
I kept yelling it out as a request.
McCartney's version of Dicatana.
No, but you talk about a seminal creator.
There you go.
Dicam, how big was your "I have cancer" sign, will you please say, "Oh, blah dee, oh, blah da."
It was roughly the size of a Sherry's Berry.
It was enormous.
A Sherry's Berry.
Holy shit.
Paul McCartney did...
Because there were signs in the audience, and he, I thought, did something very smart,
which was he addressed the signs and then people would put them down.
That's nice.
Yeah, that's smart.
Yeah, so he did like five minutes between two songs early on.
He was like, "Oh, we got some signs out here.
Let's see what they say."
And he'd go through a couple of them.
And then when he was done with them, they'd put them down.
There was one person towards the front holding up a large piece of cardboard.
And all it said was, "Paul McCartney saved my life.
Can I have a hug?"
Oh, my God.
And that was one that he did not acknowledge.
Of course, because no, because no, buddy, sorry.
Because the answer, I'm sorry, is just probably not.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Was there one song that he performed that really put you over the moon
or one that you were surprised that he was belting out?
Oh, you know, he's 83, I think.
Before we move on, I'm skeptical, by the way.
I don't think that Paul McCartney saved that guy's life at all.
I don't think he did anything.
What do you mean?
I mean, I think he just was, by coincidence, this song maybe meant something to the guy
before he maybe was going to jump off a bridge or something.
But I don't think Paul McCartney specifically...
You don't think that renowned neurosurgeon Paul McCartney might have saved that guy's life?
You're close.
You're close, Paul.
Actually, the guy in the audience I did, I got to speak to him, he was confused.
It turned out John Lennon jumped in front of a bullet mitt for that guy.
And then he thought it was Paul McCartney this whole time.
And I was like, "No, that actually killed John Lennon."
The bullet mitt for you did kill John Lennon.
It'd be really funny if he really did have a doctor named Paul McCartney who helped his brain,
but then he mistakenly thought it was the other guy.
Like halfway through the concert, he maybe puts a sign down.
I was like, "Wait, it can't be the same Paul McCartney."
This guy doesn't look anything like the guy that saved my life.
This is a different guy.
I paid so much money for these tickets.
I don't think this is the same guy at all.
I feel foolish, this piece of cardboard.
I feel foolish.
I mean, this is a nice song and everything, but this is not what I'm here for.
I was here to give thanks to the person that saved my life.
Who cut a brain tumor out of my skull.
And I wanted to give that person a hug.
This person doesn't want to hug me at all.
If anybody has a chance to go see this McCartney tour now, you would highly recommend them?
Oh, yes.
Oh yeah, it's the Got Back Tour.
There was so much going on.
Is Sir Mix-A-Lot opening for him?
Sir Mix-A-Lot is not opening for him.
That's a missed opportunity.
That is, I agree.
Baby got back.
Yes!
You can do side bends or sit-ups.
Please do actually.
Keep your body active as he gets older if you want to keep that blood flow going.
You are an octogenarian.
You should do side bends and sit-ups.
I engage in a lot of Tai Chi.
I got an afternoon over at the park.
I got pool aerobics.
It's pretty great.
Keeps my ass in shape.
I walk every day.
4,000 steps a day.
I know that isn't 10,000, but it's still pretty good.
Baby does bends.
Baby's got steps.
I'm in the barbers club.
So I think I mentioned to you guys that on my greatest day ever last week,
I ended up buying that Rock Band 360 controller that I've been looking for.
So I finally got a chance to test it and, Jacob, you'll be happy to know,
my first game I wanted to test it with was Rock Band Beatles.
Yeah, you talked about that last week.
Because I love that game and I love the art style of it and everything.
So I get my old 360 going.
Hadn't turned it on in probably a year.
Turned on my 360.
Opened it up.
Put a disc in the tray.
Closed it up.
It goes, man, man, man.
And then it just says open tray.
And I'm like, oh, no, that seems like a bad sign.
It was a bad sign.
So I pressed it and opened it up and I tried it again.
And man, man, man, nothing.
So my 360 isn't reading discs.
And I'm like, fuck, I got like 200 discs sitting here for my 360.
That's the one system I've kept.
I would like my games to still be able to run.
So I'm like, oh, shit.
So I started getting really sad because not only was I like, well, you know, all my 360
games aren't working, but now I'm going to have to go through all the hassle of returning
this guitar.
I don't really know if it doesn't work or what, but I don't know how people existed
before the advent of YouTube, honestly.
So I go on YouTube and I look up this very specific malady going on with my 360.
And a short pops up and a guy does exactly what I did, gets that same error message,
open tray.
He puts it back in as the disc is going back in.
He just reaches up on the top of the system, goes back, back, back.
Oh, and then sure enough, sure enough, he just hit the top of the thing on the top
of the system.
And then sure enough, it reads the disc and he plays the game.
And I'm like, well, I don't know.
I don't want to be beaten on my system necessarily.
But I, but I do know like PS ones, old PS one models, you had to flip them over and
run them upside down to actually get them to read after a while.
And when they got old, huh, that was a fix.
So I was like, all right.
Well, so I looked again, the next one that came up, same error message, same thing.
Guy goes back, back, back and starts to read it.
I'm like, all right, fuck it.
What have I got to lose?
I do the thing.
I put it in back, back, back.
Fires it right up.
My fucking controller works with it.
I played a perfect round.
So the controller is very responsive for a, you know, 15 year old piece of plastic
hardware that could easily get fucked up.
I'm like, yeah, this fucking works.
This is great.
I was really happy.
Got to watch my, uh, you know, the Beatles animation and all that, which is really,
really cool.
So I played a couple of Beatles songs with my new Fender Stratocaster and, uh, I was
just, uh, I was just over the moon.
But, uh, yeah, I had to fucking Fonz my 360.
Just bam, bam, bam.
Yeah, got it.
Yeah, uh, time to mod it up and get those discs.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, if your dog starts feeling bad and, uh, you're going to take it to the vet to
have it put down, try to hit it on top of the head a few times.
I tried that with pirate.
Maybe that was what, uh, brought up.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh, no, dog dogs are doing really good.
Thankfully.
Although I don't know what the fuck happened last night and gets up.
She has to go in early every, every fucking day.
It's something new with this place with her.
She's getting called in early.
So she goes to let the dogs out at like four in the morning.
It was Ann.
Well, no one had yet.
That was why she had to do it.
I don't know what the fuck was in the yard, but it ran over the fence.
She heard crazy commotion.
It had knocked over and bent the bird feeder.
I think it was a big fat raccoon, but Ann thinks it might've been a bear.
Who the fuck knows?
Bear?
A raccoon did not bend the bird feeder.
Then it could have been.
You have like a metal pole on the.
It has a big metal pole, right?
Big metal pole.
A raccoon didn't bend that.
So yeah, it might've been.
Bear is what I was thinking.
It might've been a bear, but the dogs went and chased the bear.
Oh, hello.
I love this yard.
Yeah.
You know, if you invited him over, he'd have been probably nice enough to give you the syphilis.
If you ask him, you know, just say, please, can I have your bear syphilis?
He'll do it.
I would've given it to.
I want that bear syphilis.
Give me your bear syphilis.
So anyway, yeah, who the fuck knows?
Or it could have been a deer.
Maybe.
I don't think a deer though, because deer would have really had to jump over our big fences.
It's possible.
Who knows?
But it was probably.
It could have been a bear.
But yeah, so a little, little crazy.
We had some wildlife activity in the, in the yard.
Unhoused drug addicts who wanted to eat bird feed.
Not completely out of the realm, but I don't think he would have bent it over like he did.
To get at the bird food.
But I fixed it.
I fixed the pole today.
So it wasn't that it wasn't that strong.
I was able to straighten it out with my hands.
Just kind of, you know, so maybe then maybe I think it could have just been a big fat possum.
Big old fat raccoon.
Yeah, I think it could have been.
Or tiny raccoons in a raccoon costume.
I might've been, it might've been stranger things.
My God.
Or a lot of tiny raccoons in a bear costume.
You guys experiencing these full moons right now?
There was a big one last night.
Yeah.
These big harvest moons.
So as the moon got fuller and fuller when I'd go into work in the morning, good gravy.
Are there deer out at four in the morning?
They're everywhere.
I must've passed 16 years last time I was driving to work.
No three mile radius.
Crazy.
Do you think maybe they're choosing you as a leader?
I hope so.
I usually drive with my window down and I, and I call out to them.
I say, Hey, gorgeous.
Hey, beautiful.
Just to make sure they don't run into the road.
Looking good out there.
I do.
I compliment you.
Look, you look incredible.
I don't know what you're doing, but don't stop.
You're amazing.
I mean, his whole life complimenting women has kept them away.
He figures it'll work for deer too.
I don't do it to women, just deer.
That's how I get my, that's how I get my cat call fix.
I just can't call the tears.
I'm driving off.
Hey, that's at least a 10 point rack you're sporting.
You're amazing.
That is fabulous.
Oh yes, girl.
You've had, well, it looks like you've got two little does with you.
Beautiful.
Go mama.
Do it.
Work mama.
I'll tell you who else gets horny watching Paul's deer.
That's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by dog made doggy dentures for cats.
That's dog made doggy dentures for cats.
That's from the New Hampshire caveman in 2023.
Oh, roof for roof, roof, a roof for roof, roof.
We're tired of the kitties with their fangs so itty bitties.
So we made some dentures to stop their shit.
Hey, it's me, the dog dentist, dentist D dog dentist.
I know it's, I'm working on the name.
Dentist, dentist D dog dentist.
My last name is D D E E.
My first name is Dennis.
I happen to be a dentist, a DDS.
Dentist D dog dentist DDS.
Don't let it get it to it.
Don't get it twisted.
Dentist D dog dentist DDS has come up with a really great solution for kitties fangs.
Fuck these cats trying to claw our eyes and bite our balls.
I got these special made crowns that are very dull and thick.
And not only does it prevent biting, but it also impedes eating.
So the cats get thin and weak around us.
Roof, roof, roof.
So come see me.
Dennis D dog dentist DDS at your local earliest convenience.
And I will fix your cat's mouth.
So it won't bite your dog anymore.
A roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof, roof.
That's my dentist D dog dentist DDS guarantee.
It's the hey scoops of check out the list.
That's simple.
Oh, hello.
Uh, at the McCartney show, they had a lot of, you know, there was video of old Beatles
performances and things like that.
And one of the things that was in there, uh, Matt made me think of, uh, you and your kids.
Okay.
And like specifically kids, like more specifically just kids in general today.
But, uh, but especially your kids.
You felt called child predictive services during the concert?
I think that often.
I, you know, I probably, it probably popped into my head at some point during the concert.
Yeah.
Uh, how would you feel okay about things if your children, uh, while, while attending
a concert or, you know, a big, a big event for, for somebody that they liked,
if they were screaming in a way that seemed like they were in pain,
just because the person was on stage, you know what I mean?
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, it, it kind of struck me.
I don't have kids.
I don't think about things from the point of view of having kids very often.
And for some reason it just struck me at that concert.
That is a weird thing for, you know, fairly young children
to just be screaming at someone because they are so overwhelmed with emotion.
That was the children at the Paul McCartney concert screaming.
No, no, no.
This was, this was videos of old Beatles footage when this was happening.
It is really hard.
Like, uh, there were children at the Paul McCartney concert, uh,
several of the, uh, we saw several of them with their parents and their parents were
trying to keep them awake because boy, the 13 year olds that have been brought by their
parents to the Paul McCartney concert, not give a shit.
This is a thing of kids and their parents going to concerts.
I never thought to go to a concert with my dad.
I don't think my dad ever thought to go to a concert with me.
I guess we would go to like a show or musical or something.
So maybe, I don't know how different that is, but it is, it is a thing that I'm hearing
a lot more of, which is like, but he didn't take you to something that he liked and just
to be like, you should like this too.
Willie Nelson buckle up.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, they called it Beatle mania for a reason.
It was straight up.
Right.
That's what I mean.
Yeah.
It was insanity.
It was.
And I think, you know, it just goes to the repression of the society at that time.
You know, it was one of the few times people were
allowed to really let their emotions fly.
And I mean, if you haven't been able to be free, you know, that's a chance to really
get it out.
It's not dissimilar from, you know, going to like a church revival, speaking in tongues
and shit, you know?
Yeah.
You're probably right.
I also think like, you know, like it's really hard to relate in a non-internet era where
like there is no fix, right?
Like you like Paul McCartney and he's not in this country that read this year.
Right.
And you can't go on any internet outlet to do it.
You have to try to find a magazine or something, do an article and just to kind of
keep scratching that itch.
And then finally, you have to, you know, have her, you're probably only going to see
him once in your life and you're there and you're going to scream your guts out.
I definitely think that's a crazy thing.
I remember when Penn was filming Apprentice, One Direction was staying at Trump Tower for
their Madison Square Garden concert.
And the amount of fans that were just sitting there all day, just packed around that building.
Oh, yeah.
One member of One Direction to walk out of the apartment was crazy.
They were all waiting for Harry Styles.
Taylor Swift is about as famous as it gets right now.
Yeah.
I think people go wild seeing her and screaming for her.
Definitely.
Yeah.
But I think it's more rare.
I don't think it's completely gone, but it is.
Yeah, it is rare.
Yeah, I don't know.
I was sitting there, I was standing there during the concert trying to like appreciate
the gravity of what this was in the 60s and 70s.
And yeah, I don't think I can do it.
I couldn't really wrap my head around what that must have been.
I mean, at ScoopFest, I don't think people even move to applaud at all, right?
That's at least half on us if you do something to warrant the applause.
I don't know.
Is it kind of like a bell curve where the raw sexual chemistry just gets too profound
and then the applause dies down?
It's like they're just shocked into silence when they see us on the stage.
They're like, "Dear God, my libido is in a state of frenzy that I can't even articulate.
I just have to sit here calmly or I may explode from just observation."
That's what several Scoops came up to me during ScoopFest and told me.
Said their libido is in a state of frenzy from observing me?
That's right.
Is it, "Sorry, we're not applauding.
My libido is in a state of frenzy."
Frenzy!
Never gonna clap, never gonna give it up.
Because of my libido.
It's in a state of frenzy.
Lindsay said, "Paralyzed by horniness."
That's exactly it.
No, that's crazy.
Hard to applaud with two hands full of cotton.
Tell them, Scoop Shooter.
How old is McCarty?
83, I believe.
It's crazy that he's still out there and delivering.
He's kicking ass.
Oh, yeah.
And putting on a good show, putting on such a good show.
How much stuff was new?
How much stuff was Beatles?
How much was Wings?
Oh, that was, there was some Wings.
There was a fair amount.
He made a joke at one point.
He was like, "Oh, we're gonna play some of the new stuff right now."
Well, I guess it's 20 years old, but it's still newish.
And then they went into it.
That's funny.
There wasn't much that they played that I didn't know.
There were a couple of Wings songs that he played.
But he played for a long time, too.
He played for, it was well over three hours.
That's crazy.
Oh, Laurie Elsroth in the chat saying, "Not Wings."
One of the best moments of the night was a Wings song
when they played "Live and Let Die."
And the whole place just exploded.
This was crazy.
It was so crazy how prolific he is, right?
Because we can bring up like four Wings songs
that are just gigantic smash hits.
Post-Beatles, really, it's crazy.
Have you, Jacob, delved into the
simply having a wonderful Christmas time conspiracies?
I've heard a little bit about these.
Of course I haven't delved into these.
So why not?
I am vaguely familiar with what you're talking about.
So apparently, simply having a wonderful Christmas time
is actually about someone interrupting a Wiccan ceremony.
Okay. We're in there having like pagan rites.
And somebody is interrupting them.
I'm skeptical about this one.
Well, as you should be, as you should be.
I think it's really funny to have that song be a song
of interrupting is very funny.
Like people are just like, "The moon is up."
See, that's where it starts.
The moon is up.
So it's like, it's the beginning of a pagan setup.
That's right. You say that like it's A to B, and that's A to Z.
Because I've just done a search for it.
It's simply having a wonderful Christmas time about witchcraft
is the auto-film that came in when I searched for it.
That's right. Of course.
And it says, "No, it's not."
You know what? Interestingly enough, no.
Oh, oh, did you ask Siri about that?
She's notoriously truthful, that Siri.
The moon is up.
Wiccan, Wiccan ceremony.
No other human would look up at the sky, see the moon,
and think that'd be a good first line of the song.
Nope.
See the moon, I get Wiccan.
Oh, apparently this is all based on just a misunderstood lyric.
Oh, right. Okay, sure.
So the lyric that people hear and thought was Wiccan.
Paul's such a staunch defender of this Wiccan ceremony conspiracy.
Fine, let's hear the lyric, Mr. Smarty Pants.
Yeah, so the lyric that Paul is referring to is, "The moon is right."
That is the lyric that people glommed onto, is that this is Wiccan.
According to Paul McCartney, when interviewed about this, I said,
"No, the lyric is about the mood, M-O-O-D, not M-O-O-N.
The mood is right, not the moon is right, the mood."
Paul, I want you and R.F.K. Jr. say one side of the conspiracy theory
and then say which one the other side of the conspiracy theory is
and see which one seems more natural in R.F.K. Jr.'s throat.
Well, when you watch and listen to Simply Having a Wonderful Christmas Time,
what you'll find is there are moments when they're talking about sharing drinks,
and those could be tainted with adrenochrome that they have obtained from babies.
That's how they do it, drink babies.
Simply Having a Wonderful Christmas Time, that translates to,
"I'm drinking adrenochrome from babies." You play it backwards.
We're drinking adrenochrome.
And now what's the other side, that it's just a Christmas song?
Yeah, yeah, that's just a Christmas song.
I know that for me and my family, it's not Christmas until someone brings a dead bear in there.
[laughter]
I'm not dead yet.
You will be.
No!
We're gonna roast you up like you're...
Who bent this pole? Who bent my Christmas pole?
Oh, God.
Sorry.
What do you call that pole at Christmas? Not the Yule log.
What is it called?
The Yule log, yes.
Oh, and someone bent the Yule log, it was a bear.
[laughter]
You're right. The regular Christmas sounds more believable.
The only way to win is to force you to agree with RFK Jr., and then I figured you would maybe not.
[laughter]
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
Maybe that'll bring you back.
The moon is right.
If he is a fucking AI character, the moon is right, the moon is left.
Ah, man, there were so many good moments in that concert.
Completely full, it was Allegiant Stadium, Raider Stadium in Vegas, totally full.
But I'm looking at the set list now, they did Band on the Run from Wings, they did Get Back,
and then they had a little moment, and he would talk a couple of times between some
of these little moments, and then they went into Let It Be, and they started Let It Be
in a very interesting way, and then they filled out the song, and then they did the whole thing.
By the end of it, there were a couple of times in the concert, by the end of it,
you had about 50,000 people really nicely singing along, not singing at the top of their voices,
not screaming, but just pleasantly singing along.
Well, they didn't want to wake up their children.
That's right, that's right.
[laughter]
Now, this was at Allegiant, was that where this was?
Yeah, this is Allegiant Stadium.
That makes sense.
And at the end of Let It Be-
Anything three years old, still filling up Allegiant Stadium is crazy.
That's insane, that is insane.
Yeah, and seemingly just effortlessly, and also moving around, playing a lot of different
instruments. He played his bass, his famous-
He still had his bass.
Yeah, his famous violin-style bass. He played a couple of different guitars,
he played two different pianos, he played a mandolin, and he played a ukulele that had
been given to him by George Harrison, and he told a little story about how George had given him this
ukulele. So he plays a lot of different instruments, like he's all over it.
But the end of Let It Be, you asked if there was anything that kind of hit me.
And the end of Let It Be definitely was one of the two times in the night that I tiered
up a little bit, just standing there.
Sure.
And Let It Be, yeah, there will be an answer, let it be.
And the whole audience was singing that, and at the end of it, he did something that I thought
was fucking brilliant and perfect. He just let that last note hit, and as the audience applauded,
they just stood there. They just didn't say anything.
And you could tell that everybody was definitely a little moved, like the energy in the room was a
little moved. And he just said, "There will be tomorrow, just let it be."
I said, "Man, this guy fucking knows how to do this." Like he knows how to tap into the energy,
he knows how to tap into the room. Everybody in this room was seemingly listening to this song
and thinking about the way the world is right now, and thinking about our brothers and sisters all
over the place that are having a hard time because of a great many things, because of
war in different places of the world, because of the insane political climate that is in
the United States right now and in different places around the world as well. I know, I know.
It's an old guy thing. You have to be 83 to really see the whole pattern in all of it.
The average age of MSNBC watcher?
Yeah, that's it. And I mean, man, he hits the end of that. And he knows what the whole room is
thinking. He knows what the whole room is doing. And he just lets everybody sit in it. And he
doesn't have to say it. He doesn't even have to come out and point an arrow at it. He just says,
like, "Yeah, this is a thing. And it's shitty right now. And it's going to be okay."
And then the concert ended, or the main part of the concert ended before the encore. And the
last song of the main concert was Hey Jude, which was another big, of course, sing-along moment. I
got a good 360 video of the whole crowd. Exactly. Yeah. And I finished that. And then they came out
for the encore a couple of minutes later. And here comes Paul carrying an American flag.
And then some members of the band are coming out behind him. One of them has the Union Jack. They
have the English flag there. And one of them comes out with the Nevada flag, because that's
where they were. And then the fourth band member comes out with the, oh, I just forgot the name of
it, the Pride flag with the newer extra stuff on the one end of it. I don't remember the name
of that flag. But it's the inclusion flag, the Pride Progress flag. There you go.
Make you a Latter Day Scoop. And they just stood there and waved these flags around for a few
seconds and let everyone just kind of think about that. And then they went into I've Got a Feeling,
The Beatles' I've Got a Feeling. They played some of that. They played some Sgt. Pepper's.
Did Fergie come out? Will.i.am? What's that? Did Fergie and Will.i.am come out for that one?
They did not. They did not, weirdly. That's weird, yeah. They also did Helter Skelter live,
which was pretty great. See them do Helter Skelter was pretty awesome. That's pretty cool.
Yeah. Man, it was just, it was good. It was touching. It was entertaining. Fuck me,
Paul McCartney is good at what he does. Where were you in the stadium? Oh, we were on the floor.
My mom, my mom had never seen any of the Beatles before. And so I wanted to do some good tickets.
So we were in the 16th row on the floor of our house, right? Yeah. Did they pull out the Raider?
We could see him. Did they pull out the Raider grass for you or did they just pull the tray away?
Did you get to ride? They put the tray away for some reason. I was so mad that the grass wasn't
there. Yeah. Oh, okay. Pandora is absolutely listening to me just right now. It came up with
a thing that says, "A notification just hit my phone." It says, "All of the Beatles, every Beatles
song." Yeah. I've been getting a lot of Beatles recommendations the last few days. Oh no, that's
terrifying. It's really exciting, Jacob. And it's good to know that something successful can happen
inside that stadium. So that's very nice. That's right. It can actually happen, right? Something
that ends with everyone just feeling good and like they spent an evening out doing something
worthwhile. It can happen in that stadium. That's good to know. Amazing. Yeah. Oh, it was so fucking
good. Let's move into some little Scoop Mail here. Yes. Physical Scoop Mail. Physical Scoop Mail.
Zip-a-dee-doo. We got mail in a box. I love it. Oh, it's Physical Scoop Mail. Great for Jacob.
Bad for Paul and Matt because they're not here. Oh, we got one from the Coffee Bean Scoop. Matt,
we got some coffee from our friend the Coffee Bean Scoop. Gentlemen, the Stars did not align
this year for me to make Scoop Fest, but I hope I'll make it next year. I hope everything is lining
up well or that it went well, depending on when you get this. That's Paul, the Coffee Bean Scoop.
He also sent the second letter here. The summer seems to be flying. I hope it's treating you all
well. I forgot to send you a package last month, so I upped your shipment this time. That's right,
we got extra coffee this time. Nice. I've also included a little extra something for Jacob.
I like bourbon and Jacob likes bourbon. A big part of bourbon for me is sharing what you're
enjoying with friends. I can't be there to share a bottle with Jacob, so I'm sending you
some of what I'm enjoying this month. This month is Penelope Estate 10-year single barrel
at 105 proof. Paul also sent me a little tiny bottle of bourbon here for me to enjoy on my own,
so that'll be very nice. Lovely. Thank you very much. I already mentioned Sarah and Mayer, M-A-Y-O-U,
getting married in Ireland. Congratulations. They're coming up here in November. Yes, absolutely.
That's fantastic. Then we got something here from the OG Scoop. We got Andy, the OG Scoop,
who is in the chat with us right now. Hey gang, I have some small gifts sent by Amazon to the
Vegas address and also to Paul's place. I just wanted to send you this note. They are small
tokens of my appreciation to you for all the laughs that you have given me in the past and
continue to do so. Thanks to all of our wonderful community for all of the love that you have shown
to each other over the years. I love you all mentally and sexually. Fucking you in the face,
that's Andy, the OG Scoop. Oh, thank you, Andy. Andy sent two books along with us here. Oh,
what you got there, Paul? This is what Andy sent me. He sent me a cool bird of prey,
wood printout 3D model that I can put together. Oh, cool. Moving forward, we're going to be,
specifically me, I'm going to be hosting some extra Zoom chats as a Patreon reward. This is
going to be one of the projects I'm going to be working on during one of those Zoom chats for
sure. Thank you, Andy. Very nice. Yeah, this will give me some more fun stuff. This and LEGO type
stuff will be some of the things I'll be engaged in while I'm chatting to you guys during some of
those meetups. Very cool. Well, I might be drinking some of the whiskey that I learned about in this
book, A Field Guide to Whiskey, which is what Andy sent to me, which looks like a very informative
whiskey book here. And Matt, don't worry, he sent you something as well. And it is fantastic. He
sent you a little golden book. You remember the little golden books from our childhood? Yes. He
sent you a little golden book all about Bruce Springsteen. It is a Bruce Springsteen biography
as a little golden book. That's really cool. I just got this. Are you excited about the movie,
Matt? I just got this note slipped under my door and it's telling me I should check out some Beatles
on my music player. So there we go. Oh, the boat is listening. The boat is listening. Oh my God.
No, no, I'm not excited about the movie coming. What do you heard? What's the scuttlebutt? I don't
know. Is it a Jared Leto and Skeletor kind of situation? Because that's got me in a fucking
tizzy. Jared Leto is playing Skeletor in the new Bruce Springsteen movie. Oh, well, I would be out
of it too. Yeah. It's got the dude from succession taking very big swings. The bear playing Bruce is
like a really weird melancholy thing. And I love Bruce so much. I've read multiple biographies on
him. His autobiography as well as other biographies. I will see that man in concert as long as he's
playing. I'll see when he's 83 playing playing. Oh, yeah. He can't fill up a legion, by the way.
That's the thing. It's like that's why I'm so impressed by Paul McCartney. I don't think Bruce
could fill up a legion. Yeah, I think Paul, I think Paul plays less than Bruce, though. Yeah.
I think Paul gives audience less opportunity to say. Yeah. Also, he just does the big ones.
Arguably one of the most popular people in the last in the 20th century.
Yeah. I think he's got a little more fame than Bruce. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anyhow, I just don't. I
just don't know what the I don't know what the story is. You're just worried. You're just worried.
I don't know. Matt has concerns about the film. I get it. When Ray came out. I do like Ray. Oh,
yeah. Sure. Really great biopic. And then they kept making other ones that weren't as good
afterwards. Right. Still about Ray Charles. No, no, just like then they just started a bevy of.
Yeah, right, right, right. A bunch of others that came after it. Well, we did get Walk Hard from all
that. So that I was going to say you have the John C. Reilly Walk Hard that came out of that whole
love walk hard. Yeah, we say like we I don't I think one is very hard to make a really good
biopic. And then two, I don't think we have it like in our in our in our in our, you know,
artistic hearts take in a lot of biopics, you know, like, I think one comes around that we
really just kind of like it for what it is. Right. And so I this is coming right on the heels of that
really well done Dylan movie. And yeah, I just don't know if you get to do that twice. That was
good. That was a good movie. And I agree. Let's cancel Bruce Springsteen. Jeremy Allen White's
not singing. Right. He's lip syncing or doing whatever. Oh, that's that's rough, too. Yeah.
Because that was actually our boy doing the songs. Right. Yeah. Timothy Chalamet just straight up
became like a channel. That was ding dong. Don't play, man. Same with Jamie. What's his last name?
We played Fox. Jamie Foxx. Jamie Foxx. Oh, yeah, you're right. Jamie Foxx went straight up,
went to like Ray Charles School, just straight up. Oh, yeah. Charles. I mean, doing Ray almost
turned Jamie Foxx into a full time musician. Yeah. Was Ray Charles still alive at that time?
Yes, I think so. I think so. He had some he had some actual direct firsthand, too. Yeah,
it was definitely. Yes, there was definitely footage of Jamie Foxx learning from Ray Charles.
That's cool. And in the behind the scenes. Oh, yeah. Ray Charles died in 2004.
So I hope I'm close. I hope I'm wrong. But everything about everything I'm seeing makes
me go like you. Sure. Sure. Well, I mean, Tron Aries is getting in the 50s for scores right now. Oh,
no. Yeah, it's it's also not a good Bruce Springsteen movie at all. And not great.
But again, it's hardly there's hardly any Bruce Springsteen in it. You could barely call it a
Bruce Springsteen movie. I don't get the Jared Leto thing. The only thing I think is honestly,
Jared Leto must have dirt on a lot of Hollywood. The place like, you know, to place like an
interplanetary, you know, neon motorcycle race based solely on the Ghost of Tom Joed album is
a mistake. It's just a mistake. You know, when I heard about that, I was really excited. I'll be
very honest with you. I thought that was going to be it. But yeah, just it didn't work out.
Or it's because they had so many of them there. First, there were two, then there were three,
there were four. No, it's all about soon. I think I have to try to see it right away because I think
for the sake of this podcast, I just have to. I think as a podcast, I have to. But yeah,
we'll see how it goes. Same thing with me and Tron Aries. I really want to see those visuals
with that Nine Inch Nails music. I want to go see it in IMAX because the soundtrack is exquisite.
Right. It's it's some of the best Nine Inch Nails music in the last 10 years.
Yeah. So I don't know. I watched. It's really, really good. I watched F1 last night.
OK. The new Brad Pitt movie. This is the Brad Pitt. Right. Yeah. You did a great job with the
soundtrack on that. It's really like felt like old school. Like it was really a lot of scorpion
songs. Yeah. Very old school sports movie that like the soundtrack was really pumping you up.
Nice. I liked it. It was it was it was, you know, I think we figured out so much with
movies now. It was it was a it's a sports movie. It's a it's a sports movie traditionally done
well executed. It was really fun to watch. And yeah, I just I'm looking forward to it.
It looks like it's a good watch for me. So last night did my first shows on the ship. So it was
like I was staying. I was a little wired. So I just watched it to the end. So then I went to sleep.
It was fun. How did the first shows on the ship go? Good. Good, good, good.
It was it's a big enough room where I basically couldn't get like I did. I did the show as written
and so it went over well. A lot of people laughed. You know me. I like to get like
something spontaneous happening in the show. I want like another character to emerge
that kind of stuff. And I didn't get any characters out of the show. And so everyone else
like, you know, good show. Really funny. I was like, yeah, yeah, yeah, I was fine. It was a fine
show. It was a solid B B minus is good. I mean, they have an awesome crew here is also neat. They
have seven movable giant LED screens that you can arrange in whatever order you want.
Well, that's a that's a nice plus. It is. Yeah. And so I created like a V with six LED screens
and put one all the way back. Nice. And it was really nice to create intimacy with the audience
to kind of focus that V right there. And so I got to perform kind of center stage and not feel too
small in the giant theater. Okay. And it was and so that part super fun. Their crew is just
unbelievable. They just follow every direction to a hill. You tell everybody everything once
everybody's remarkably calm. Nobody's there. There's no crew. That's what you want. That's
the juice right there. The ship is next level. It has no cruise director. They have different
people in different positions that handle things, but no one's job is to talk to or host to the
audience. So you just come out and do your show and your show ends. There's no extra, hey, this
is what's happening tomorrow. Here's what's going on later on tonight on deck seven, blah, blah, blah.
That's that's cool. This whole ship is so different. It's so it's like it's like it's
honestly with the cosmopolitan at sea. It's it's a there's no fake opulence. Like there's no like
grand ballroom type feel to stuff. Like it's all very hip hotel. Nice little niche. Nice things.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's really, it's a different design from what I can see in there. It looks
pretty cool. Oh, it's the nicest room I've been put in as a guest entertainer by far. Well, that
was the thing. As soon as I, as soon as I asked you how the boat life's going, I thought, wait a
minute, is he just in a regular hotel room? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then it has like different light
settings as an IP the whole thing. So the whole room is controlled by an iPad.
I got as different moods, including get it on. Every room has its own iPad. Yeah. Every room has
its own iPad where I can turn on the TV, open the curtains, turn the lights on and off everything,
temperature, order room service. It's all right here. Is there a Patreon level where we could give
a scoop control of the lights in your room on the ship? We're just going to keep hitting, get it on,
get it on. Exactly. You hit get it on and all the lights turn purple and then music comes on.
Is it, is there a setting for real? Yeah. That's amazing. Show us. Can you show us?
Yeah. Let's see, Matt, this is going to hit. This is why we broadcast with this. Why you went,
oh my God. Oh, there was just a large button on the iPad that says, get it on. There he goes.
Matt has hit the button. Oh my God. Yes. Oh my God. It's just close. Just a love machine.
And I won't wait for nobody but you. Wow. Look at this. It's like that moment straight out of an
eighties movie where somebody bumps into the record player. Yes. Instant sweat house. I'll hit photo
shoot. And then that's going to turn the lights super bright. Yeah. Look at that. Wow. It doesn't
have a refractory period button. Just go to like a nice dark blue and some soft music starts playing.
You can't read it because it's too bright. It says zen. Is that close enough?
That's pretty close. It's pretty good. It goes to blue and the curtains do close again. Yeah.
Look at that shit. Holy smokes. All right. Go back to the get it on look real quick.
Oh, there it is. I need to. Oh, wait. There you go. This is pumped up.
I don't know what that means. Lights go up in this kind of purple and blue. Okay. You want to
get it on? Okay. Yeah. Give me that get it on look again. I just need to get a quick shot of
something here. I don't do it. There we go. Maybe. Oh, dammit. My screen capture isn't working.
Wow. That is something else right there. Yeah. That's amazing. I think I got it. Well, technology
is better every day. Clearly. Yeah. Oh, yeah. This place just like it's really like about. Yeah.
There's not like Excuse me. There's not like a pageant to the cruise ship. Do you know what
I mean? Like there's not like this kind of someone marching you along through the cruise. It's very
you do your own thing kind of thing. And even the showrooms are all hold like 300 400 they don't
there's not like a giant theater. So like it's just you're not going to do the same thing as
everyone do their own thing. And it's just totally it's the restaurants that crazy amazing
restaurants. Oh, yeah, I went to the test kitchen where they bring out all this experimental food
to you and courses. They just bring it out. And that was Yeah, it was just nuts. This has
been a crazy crazy trip. Every. Oh, cool. I put a picture of me working Virgin and like every,
every entertainer who hasn't worked is like seeding. Like, I'm trying to get there. And
everyone who has played Virgin is like, Oh, so you're here now. Like, it's very like,
everybody, everybody just wants to play here. Everybody wants to get the call all the time to
play here. Like, it's definitely like the number one. It is the spot. Yeah, I get it. I totally get
it. Like I before I leave want to be like, I will do anything to be here again. Thank you.
I will leave my family for any period of time. I will come sit on your ship and your purple neon
light in my room. Let's do a little jock versus nerd action. Oh, am I? Yeah, I'm on the hunt for
balls on the hunt for balls. Oh, we got a scooper to come in as today from ML Kennedy. The categories
are that was remade this time in English, good remakes and confusion remakes. Oh, it's me first.
I'll try. I'll try that was remade for 200. This 1984 Ivan Reitman film was remade by Paul Fieg,
I think in 2016. But nevermind that one. We're trying again with a soft reboot next March.
This is a this is an older scooper. Oh, yes, I guess it is. But thank you. This is great to have
is this not next March? Is this is this like a previous March that happened? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is 2017 or 2018. Yeah. Oh, well, that's that explains why I don't know this. I pass Matt. Yes.
Paul Ghostbusters. Oh, oh, yeah. That that that. Oh, okay. Matt. This time in English, please.
For 200. Based on a play 1978, Lacanje  Follets was titled this when it was remade with Robin
Williams in 1996. The Birdcage. The Birdcage is correct. Let's see. I'll try. Oh, no, it's Paul.
Paul, you're up. I will try. That was remade for 400.
This 1987 Paul Verhoeven classic was remade in 2014. The remake made 243 million dollars
despite no one remembering it. I guess crime's new enemy didn't make an impression. RoboCop.
RoboCop is correct. Ah, boy, I'm not doing well on this one at all. I'll try good remakes for 200.
Be afraid to be very afraid. This 1986 Cronenberg remake starring Jeff Goldblum and Gina Davis
is much better than the original 1958 version. Help me. That would be Jurassic Park. Jurassic
Park starring Gina Davis. She was the T-Rex. She was the T-Rex. Big old lady. That'd be the fly.
The fly. Yes. Good. She was the pilot. No, it's Gina Davis. Matt. Good remakes, 400.
That'd be category number three. There we go. Yes. This film was awesome in 1956, arguably better
when remade in 1978. Still pretty good when remade in 1993 and pretty terrible when remade in 2007.
As the film is about duplicate replacement copies, it makes sense that another remake is in the works.
Oh. I don't know. Pass. That's Paul. Paul, do you know what that is? Invasion of the Body Snatchers.
Invasion of the Body Snatchers is correct. Paul is fucking rolling with ML Kennedy's game today.
Paul, you're up. That was remade for 600, please. This 1990 Paul Verhoeven film starring Arnold
Schwarzenegger was not based on a Stephen King work. It was remade with Colin Farrell in 2012.
You'd probably need a perfect memory to recollect that. That would be Get Your Ass to Mouth.
Total Recall. Total Recall is correct. There we go. I forgot that Colin Farrell had made a
total recall. Was that any good? It couldn't have been, right? I don't know. I didn't see it.
Let's see. I'll try a good remake, 600. Daily Double.
This 1960 killer plant film was made for about $28,000 and all its interior shots were done in
two days. Naturally, the more popular 1986 version is a $25 million musical, I believe.
Oh, wait. Oh, it's a Daily Double. I can say it all out loud. I think it is A Little Shop of Horrors,
but it could be Attack of the Killer Tomatoes. In 1960? Yeah, I don't think it's that. Yeah,
yeah. Yeah, it's A Little Shop of Horrors. Yeah. Yeah, there it is. You got it. Matt?
I will take good remakes for 800. Jeff Bridges replaced John Wayne when the Coen Brothers remade
this 1969 film in 2010. True Grit. True Grit is correct. Paul? I'll close out. That was remade for
eight. Schwarzenegger was replaced by Jason Momoa when they tried to revive this film franchise in
2011. The 2011 remake made less money than the 1982 film, even before adjusting for inflation.
Tell me what is good in the box office. That hurts. Not this. That hurts. Conan. Conan? The
Barbarian. I had no idea Jason Momoa did a Conan remake. Oh, yeah, it's terrible. And I love Conan.
I'm sitting here with the whole classic run of Conan. I got this. I got these brand new ones.
This is the brand new. Show of hands. Anybody surprised that Paul has Conan toys at his
fingertips? No hands. No hands. Look, they definitely didn't inspire each other. That's
all I want you to know. OK, Master's Universe is not a rip off of Conan. That's for sure.
Good. This Momoa should just be a comedian. Who? Momoa? Yeah, he should.
He's so much better in comedic roles than he is in action roles. Yep. Yep. Well, he's getting there.
Well, it's if they do pull off that third Dune movie, which I guess they are moving forward with
some production stuff, he might that might be really interesting to see him turn that because
that's a crazy character arc for that character that he's playing. Oh, really? Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, because he is good in the he's one of the parts of the Dune movies that I like so far.
So do you know what happens to his character? No, no, I don't know anything about it. So it's
Duncan, Idaho is his character he plays and Paul Atreides love Duncan, Idaho. You saw how, you know,
they captured that relationship of how he idolized him and everything is a who was that second name
you said? Paul Atreides, the main character. Oh, OK. That's oh, that's Timmy. Timmy. Yeah.
OK, so they were, you know, best buds. Well, he ends up cloning him over and over and over again.
And he gets Duncan, Idaho gets real weird and philosophical about shit being a clone. It's
interesting. So, yeah, just like Michael Keaton in multiplicity. Just like that. Exactly. It's me.
I'll try this time in English for 400. Spike Lee directed the 2013 version of this 2003 Korean
film, the second installment of the Vengeance trilogy, preceded by sympathy for Mr. Vengeance
and followed by Lady Vengeance. What? You heard it? I have I have no idea.
I don't think I do. I think I'm going to pass to Matt.
Matt, do you have a guess? Me? No. Yes. Paul. I believe this is old boy. All right, let's try it.
It's it's old boy. Yes, that's just what it is. Yeah, I didn't know we did a score check.
Yes, the original version of Old Boy is legendary. Yeah, yeah, the Korean version.
Yeah, it's fucking crazy. Yeah, I never saw that. That another one was the what's his name? Yeah,
I didn't see that one. Matt, you're up. I'll do with Confusion Remakes 200.
Rob Zombie remade this 1978 movie in 2007. Then he made a sequel. Then we ignored both those movies
and all the other films in the franchise to make a sequel to the original 1978 version in 2018,
which shares the same name as the 1978 and 2007 movies. I don't know this, but that's very funny.
Pass. Paul. Halloween. Halloween is correct. Oh, I wasn't against Halloween, but yeah,
you would have got it. Yeah. If you had, you would have gotten more points. Paul. Shit.
Confusion Remakes for four. The Thing from Another World was remade by John Carpenter in 1982 and
called this. Then in 2011, they made a prequel to the 1982 movie and gave it the same name as the
1982 film. The Thing. The Thing is correct. This category specifically just bread and butter to
Paul here. It really is. Score check with four questions left. I have 800 points. Matt has a
thousand points. Paul has 3,400 points and none of those are off a daily double for Paul. There's
still a daily double out there. Could bring me to my knees real quick. I'll try Confusion Remakes
for 600. In 1998, Gus Van Santen made a shot for shot remake of this 1960 Hitchcock film for reasons.
It had, oh, what's that guy's name that's in a bunch of stuff? Vince Vaughn. I can't think of
his name. Vince Vaughn. Vince Vaughn. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. This was the remake of Psycho. Yeah. There
you go. Yep. Matt. This time in English, 600. The Austrian film Funny Games was made in 1997 by
Michael Hankney. Hankney. Hanky, I think. The 2007 American version was also directed by Michael
Hanky and was called this. Funny Games. I don't know. Is it the game? I think it's the same title,
Matt. Do you think it's the same title? I think so. I'll pass. Paul. How much does he think it's
the same title? I'll go for it. Funny Games. What is Funny Games? It was also called Funny Games.
Okay. Yep. Boy, this really is just made for Paul. Have you seen that one? I've seen the English one.
Yeah. No, I saw it and then didn't get the question right, Paul. Yeah. Oh, no. Yeah, I saw the whole
thing. Funny Games is awful. I mean, it's great. Matt just watched it this morning. Funny Games is
really good, but it's horrific. I never did. Yes, this time in English or Confusion remakes,
one of them is a daily double. God, here we go. Here we go into zero town.
I'll go Confusion remakes. Oh, if Paul loses now, it's going to be amazing. Yep. Here it comes.
Either I'm the king of all or crushed to nothing. This 1988 film series about murderer Charles Lee
Ray comprised seven films, the most recent of which came out in 2017. Then in 2019, it was
remade without Charles Lee Ray. But now in 2020, the original version of the franchise is getting
a 10 episode TV series. That is Chucky. Is that your answer? Let's see if Chucky is correct.
Oh, wait. Give me a minute. You did not give me a minute. You did not give me a minute to ask what
the thing was. Come on. Come on. You got it. Relax. And I'm closing out the game and the
category this time in English for 800. The American version of this film came out in 2010,
despite the original also being in English and coming out in 2007. Peter Dinklage plays the main
antagonist in both films. Huh? American version of this film came out in 2010.
Was this the station agent? Gotta be right. I'll say the station agent.
Oh, it's death at a funeral. No, I think the station is just older than that.
Yeah, I didn't remember when I saw the station agent. Oh, well. Oh, I got that wrong. Yes.
And that is the game. Paul eked out a victory with 8,000 points. Matt is in second with 1,000
points. And again, thanks to Peter Dinklage. I am in third with 600 points. And that's from M.L.
Kennedy. Thank you, M.L. Kennedy. If you want to send us a scooper to your appraisal, Scryte,
Jack vs. Nerd or Annapolis, Jack vs. Nerd, head on over to HayScoops.com. HayScoops.com right there
on the home page. You can send us any of those things. Go do it. It's awesome. All I was doing
is trying to find the category of Blade Runner and I thought Blade Runner was going to be an answer
and I couldn't find it. Nope. I just answered true grit and then sat back and rested on my laurels.
Thank you, M.L. Kennedy. I also want to thank Pengeleff for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben. I also want to thank. Did you send the list, Jacob?
I did. We don't have a new list yet, but we will get one before the month is over.
It's early October. Yeah. So we'll thank all the people who get to join us on Patreon all the time.
I can also get discounts. No, that's not true. I was going to say discounts at the shop. So I think
we explained it before, but I'll explain it again. We had to stop giving out discounts at the shop
because they wouldn't give us codes that lasted long. There are too many bots out there that comb
the internet for codes and offer it to people. I'm sure you all have an app on one of your computers
that offers you to run a bunch of discount codes through and that's why we can't offer discount
codes at our shop anymore. I thought about that today. I ordered something last night and I got
the thing today and as I was ordering it, they had a little like, "Oh, here's where you enter
the discount code." I was like, "Oh, this never works. I might as well try it." And I looked up
one and got a 40% off discount code. Whoa. I was like, "Oh, this is why our shop can't do this."
You're better off with those bots. Yeah. Anyway, but we still have a shop available
with all kinds of really cool stuff for sale. Check that out over at storejingle.com.
Oh, I wasn't ready. Store jingle, a big store song. We got a store.
It just makes people so happy, that song. It does. Yeah. But basically, this podcast is awesome.
Your podcast is helping pay for very expensive internet here as I'm out in the ocean,
just so I could do Zoom calls. Literally, this podcast would not be possible.
The support that we get over at preachingfun.com. Head over there now and support us.
That is absolutely correct.
Or if you also didn't know they had remade Conan, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts in a bag dot biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with preachingfun.com. It takes you over to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. It's like Matt said,
we can't do it without you. It pays for everything that we are able to do here. So if you like the
show, if you think it's worth more than $0, preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz. Those are
the places you need to go right now to help keep this show doing what you like doing. And hopefully,
hopefully you like it, because we like it. I hope you do too.
Stay tuned, because we didn't even get into our very passionate and well-thought opinions
about Bad Bunny being the halftime show. So we didn't get into that.
Very passionate. A lot of opinions.
Anything you should get tricked into a debate on online is whether or not you have very strong
opinions about who's going to play for 20 minutes in between the Super Bowl.
A football game. A football game being played by teams that are as of yet unknown.
I've started asking people who do say bad things about Bad Bunny if they know where the Super Bowl
is actually being played this year. And so far, the answer to that question has been no, they don't.
There you go.
It's as if they already know who's going to watch the Super Bowl and want other people to watch too,
so they get people who bring in a different audience than someone who's already going to
watch the Super Bowl. Yeah.
It is almost like that. What do you know?
Oh, winner scoop in the chat says, I guess JD Vance said the NFL should drop Bad Bunny
and hire Lee Greenwood. As someone who has seen Lee Greenwood play live a couple of times,
I'm just going to tell you, nobody wants that. Nobody wants that to happen, including Lee Greenwood.
No, no. He doesn't want to have to play live in front of those people. Oh man.
That ain't Paul McCartney. He's like, fuck this, I'm retired.
Yeah, it costs money to do. Like you lose so much money in the Super Bowl halftime show.
And I don't think Lee Greenwood has that money. I don't think he's got that kind of jingle.
He ain't liquid like that.
All right. Well, anyhow, thanks for listening. Stay safe out there. We love you all and we'll
see you soon.
Oh, apologies to JD Vance, JD Vance. I am so sorry. See ya!