Oh hello there. I would love to thank you. The Ice Cream Truck Drivers. Thank you so much
Ice Cream Truck Drivers. I'd like to thank right now Richard Dunn, Sarah Boyle, Sax Guy
Jimmy D, Scoop, Scoop Brady, Scoop DeJure, Scoop Kata, Slurpee K.A. Motherfucker, Thunder
Cougar Falcon, Scoop, and Travis Jagare. If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just
like these fine folks, head over to preachingfun.com. Preachingfun.com is where you can go to sign
up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
And now, a show. Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social? Yeah I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Here we are. So you're in some alien jag right now? You know I'm always into aliens. You
know I'm always, I'm always interested in the alien stuff. So Anne, Anne brought this
up to me yesterday and I don't know if you guys have heard about this, but. Matt, any
bets? I bet I haven't. I bet I haven't. Any bets on what you think this might be? Aliens.
Well, who knows? The Senate is made up of lizard people? Nothing so, nothing so gauche.
No. Oh, how great would that be? Do you have any idea how nice it would be to just find
out that they were all lizard people the whole time? We'd all be like, ow, at least they
were just lizard people. It would make more sense. Would you rather discover that the entirety
of the Epstein List is just lizard people and not pedos? I, it would, it would weirdly
I think make me feel better. Technically, yes. About life in general. I guess, right? Less
pedophiles on the earth. I don't know. Anyway. Pedophile lizards, I guess that's a new problem
we have to deal with. Anne brought this up to me and I was like, what? And I haven't
really looked into it too much, but I just, I've just seen a couple of these headlines
and it just popped up against me, my feed. And it says, uh, breaking a new study suggests
that a potentially hostile seven mile long alien spacecraft may be headed towards earth.
Scientists say. Scientists say. And what I love is that this was tagged by, this was tagged
by a account I follow and their, their headline over this is what did Trump do in those Epstein
files? It's like the kind of shit that people are coming up with for excuses. It's just
ridiculous. Uh, but yeah. Anne was telling me about that. Do you guys remember Moa Moa
a couple of years back? Yeah. The song Moa Moa. That's right. That's right. That's right.
And that song is all about the cigar shaped turd looking thing that came flying through.
I do remember the cigar shaped, uh, uh, asteroid or whatever. Yeah. Do you remember it? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And, and folks are still torn as to whether or not it had any kind
of intelligence behind it or what it might be, if it was just the dead probe or what
it was, but it was a very uniquely shaped space object and, uh, passed close enough
to us, uh, to be an interesting thing. So, uh, we'll see. Yeah. Uh, Bazzie says, yeah,
it makes a lot of sense that a species capable of traveling over light speed has no stealth
capabilities, right? I mean, things fall apart when you look at it too quick. Don't start
looking at stuff. You, you're part of the problem by the, you're asking questions. Uh,
no, I, I honestly, I don't know. Wayne in the chat just says, sometimes the cigar is
just a cigar. You'll get no argument from me, Dr. Freed. I'm afraid not, but, uh, that,
that makes me laugh and who knows, uh, maybe, maybe the spaceman's are coming. Maybe that's,
that's the big take. That's the first one. That's the first one. Maybe they're coming.
Maybe they're coming. I, uh, I went to, uh, I just got back from Saratoga Springs, New
York. Oh, I'm sorry, Matt. You don't want to talk about the space bands anymore. I was
looking for an in and, uh, just that it's, it's seven miles long and it's a common just
didn't give me too much. I mean, right. I, I, I need to go find the article. There's
really not a whole lot more. I don't think. Why start now? It's too late. You should have
found the article before we went on air. Oh, it just popped up in my feet again. And the
fact that it hit again reminded me that Anne brought it to my attention. When Anne brings
something to my attention, I find it newsworthy. It's go time. I'll look it up. I'll look
it up. Oh, good. Good. Yeah. But, uh, but you were in Saratoga Springs for the horsies.
Yeah. When saw the ponies and, uh, Nicholas Newman, uh, once again cemented himself as
an honorary Donnelly child by writing up very hilarious pink sheets for betting sheets,
uh, for it. Um, I do have to break the news to Nick via this podcast that as my older
brothers were losing more and more bets, they became less and less interested in the comedic
bits of Nick Newman. They weren't interested in laughing, losing money at the same time.
Was Nick giving them tips? Nick has a hilarious breakdown. He breaks down every race in Saratoga
and, uh, does things like highlights, uh, which, which horses are from Ireland since
we're Irish. Um, he'll give me a gossip, uh, by the horse's owners. He'll, uh, make fun
of, uh, the whole race as a whole. Like the, we were there Friday and Saturday. The Friday
slate was the oddest slate of races. Cause the, uh, Saturday of course was the Jim Dandy.
It's called Jim Dandy. It's a big horse race, but it's called the Jim Dandy. And I was like,
what a finer isn't a finer race. It's like the Jim, but it's dandier. I've never understood
that fucking song. Have you guys ever understood that fucking song? Break it down for us, Paul.
That go Jim Dandy go Jim Dandy to the rescue Jim Dandy to the rescue. Do you know that
song? Yeah. It's about a fella named Jim Dandy. I guess he was going to come to the rescue.
What the fuck is unclear about this? So I'll tell you what's unclear. What's with Johnny
be good. What's, what are we asking him to do there? I understand everything about Johnny
be good. Wait down in Louisiana, close to new Orleans. That's where he lived in a cabin.
It was a cabin made of earth and wood. Yeah. He played his guitar there. He could play
it very well. Almost like he was just ringing a bell. He had that much skill with the guitar.
I know about Johnny be good, but the Jim Dandy song explains fucking nothing. It's just like,
Hey, Jim Dandy, go, go Jim Dandy. Jim Dandy to the rescue to rescue who being helpful
from what? Why anything bullshit? Jim Dandy is a traveling do good. Jim Dandy is a crisis
actor. How dare you? Jim Dandy is seven miles long and one light year away from earth. Hey,
look, it's like a cigar. I typed in seven miles and it went right to seven mile spaceship.
So shit is real y'all. But right to it. The word is there at the interstellar object that
I was referring to. It is known as 31 slash Atlas. It has been observed. It's quite large.
Oh, 31 Atlas. Oh yeah. Yeah. It's been observed. It's quite large. Confirmed not to be a comet.
It is confirmed to be a comet, not a spaceship and significantly further away from earth than
a spaceship would be. Uh, the idea of constructing such a massive structure in space is a topic
of ongoing research and discussion of field of aerospace. Well, they fucking just pooh
poohed it all. Okay. So it's just an interstellar object. It's not a threat. Here's the thing.
I have never been happier about an article that Paul looked up. The person poohing it.
Are they a scientist? Cause the scientists said it was, it was an alien ship, seven miles
long on its way to earth. They are, and they're clearly weighted. It starts off with the concept
of a seven mile long spaceship is currently hypothetical though there is an interstellar
object called 31 Atlas. Uh, it is a comet. So I guess people 31 Atlas, what do you get
another galaxy older and deeper in debt? Still get that debt. So, uh, every summer my brothers
and I get together with my dad and we go to Saratoga and spend a couple of days betting
on the ponies. And, uh, usually it's right after foolish. And so, uh, me affording my
own one person vacation on top of, uh, uh, you know, a family getaway, no problem. Thanks
to the generous coffers of CW. Uh, but not this year. And so, uh, I've been a traveling
magician man. And so I used points to try to get there cheap. And I used points to try
to get me a rental car. Cause basically my points wouldn't fly me into Albany, the closest
airport to Saratoga. Was there, there was a restriction. It just, it just wasn't. Yeah.
I tried to use my points and there was no flights to Albany from Las Vegas, but it would
fly me to Connecticut. Just about just under just a hair under two hours away. How's that
bad? So I was like, Oh, I'll do that. And I'll run a car and I'll drive. I don't care
about driving two hours. No, it'll be the wiser. No problem. And, um, I'm a fancy, I'm
a fancy traveler guys, right? Yeah. I got the clear, you know, I'm, I'm a global entry
member. Sure. Pre-check nailed it. I walk into the airport and I'm not, you know, I'm
not checking any bags. I'm not doing magic now. And so I walk up. How does that feel?
Does that, you, you, you, do you get a whole body vibe when you're like, Oh man, I have
to worry about like shit, tons of trunks and stuff. Yes. Love. Yes. Yeah. Very happy to
travel without checking two giant bags that I know to the pound, how much each weighs.
I'm very happy. Um, uh, so I, uh, zip right through scan my eyeballs in the thing, fly
land myself, uh, in, uh, in Connecticut, walk right up to the rental car counter, which
is right across the street from the, uh, thing. And they say, uh, give me your license. And
I go through my wallet and I cannot find my license down down down down. I am having a
panic attacks. I've never, I don't, I'm not the kind of person that misplaces those things.
You don't take your license out of your wallet. No, no, no, no, no. And I am going like, Oh,
I don't have it. I go, I do have a picture of it. I always keep a backup picture of my
license and my phone. And they took that and let you ride onto the plane, right? He's going
for a car. I'm already, I'm already through the, I'm already landing in Connecticut. I'm
already through the, through the, through the, through Las Vegas landed. No problem. I didn't
have to get my ID out once. Oh, right. We're right. Okay. I didn't have to get my ID out
once to get through the airport. And so I'm in Connecticut, two hours away from my family.
And uh, I say, uh, and they go, uh, we can't, we can't rent you the car without the physical
license. Oh man. And I was like, I have, I have a global entry card. This is my idea.
I have a passport. I have a photo of my ID. Yeah, it's definitely you. They definitely
run it up the pipe, get on the phone and they pretended to talk to someone like a car dealer
does. Uh, they really pled my case and they're like, ah, we can't rent it to you. Yeah. And
I was like, I, I'm not going here. I'm going to Albany and my whole family's like, what
do I do? Like I had a total meltdown of like what I'm in Connecticut. I don't plan on being
in Connecticut. I said, are you familiar with a show called Fool Us? Good, good. You tried
to hire, you're dropping out. If you ever laughed at a, at a toss to commercial or welcome
back to commercial on the, on the show, fool us. No, you fast forward those parts. Um,
interesting. Outrageous. Outrageous. Those are arguably the best parts. Now that's not
a winning argument, but it's arguable, arguable. Did you watch VH1 20 years ago? Do you know
who I am? Uh, no, I just literally like look at them. Like I, like basically it's like,
and now I'm just like, you know, I can't, I can't rent another car. I can't, I can't,
I can't do this. And I am like, I guess I can look at them. If they didn't rent you
a car that you were just going to stay there with them. I was kind of doing that by like
sweating and mumbling and going like, what am I going to do? Uh, you're like, wouldn't
you like me to leave? They definitely was like a team of three of them by the end. And
they're like, yeah, we're so sorry. We got to get this guy out of here. I was like, I'm
going to sit in that chair over there and look sad all day. Um, and so I call my brother
hoping I catch them on the way to Albany where it's not too far out of his way to come pick
me up. Got it. Uh, I, I'm wrong. It's way out of his way. Wayne Geo said I dropped.
Did you, have you ever heard of the Donnelly Harold? Um, uh, he's already there. He's in
Albany. Oh shoot. Well, and he goes, well, I don't know what else I'm going to do tonight.
So he just gets in the car and he drives two hours. Oh wow. I'm going to pick up my brother
to come get me. And then my other brothers jokingly said, boy, did you call the right
brother? Cause we would not have got right in the car and come and go. Shout out. Which
brother was willing to come Brian. Shout out to Brian, my hero. Thank you, Brian. Well
done Brian. Um, and then I, I, I fronted the money for the tickets to the Saratoga and
I was like, well, now I can't ask him for that money. I can't ask her to pay me back
for that. No way. That's right. He's paid you back already. I'm done on that. I'm up
paid in full that. Um, so, so it ended up costing me a little bit of money, but still
nonetheless. Hey, but you got to, now did you have to pay, you didn't have to pay for
the rental car, right? I didn't. Right. So it's all in points. There's a savings. Oh,
you were going to do it in points anyway. I was doing all the points anyway. And then,
and so I said to my brother when he drove here, I said, okay, either we can put the
rental in your name so we can get it out of here and, and, uh, or you have to drive me
back here on Sunday. Oh, right. Right. And so they let me, even with points, they'd let
me, uh, switch him as the driver. Okay. That's nice to that. And then we had to pretend like
he was going to drive the car the whole time, even though everyone, everyone knew the circumstances
he drove here. And so we had to do the theater of him driving out of the lot. Oh, I've decided
to leave my car that I just drove here, take this rental car. I can pay for my car to be
parked here while I drive my new rental. Now, uh, for some reason, the cheapest rental,
uh, from, uh, uh, enterprise was a Toyota Tacoma. It was not, it was not a tiny, not
a tiny little, little pretty big coupe car, right? Right. That is that's happened to us
in Texas. That has not happened to us outside of the state of Texas and Connecticut. I was
not expecting the Toyota Tacoma to be the, the, the, the, this one. And so we get out
into the lot and the, and the person helping us with cars says, I don't have any Tacomas.
Uh, you can take one of the, one of the, one of the Ford F one fifties. You can get bigger.
And I was like, I drive a Corolla, right? So I was happily, you happily drive a Corolla.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I, yes. As my first car was a little, little Volkswagen golf, I've
always enjoyed just being a guy who darts around town. Not big, not big on a, not big
on a big space. We share, we share that. I do not like a vehicle that takes up much room.
So I go, well, I don't have to take a big Ford over 50. I can, I mean, if you're going
to give me, I'll take, I'll take one of the SUV trucks or whatever. He goes, no, those
are an upgrade. Oh my God. I go, but the truck isn't, by the way, I'm talking for my brother.
He's be driving. I'm just the one talking. Hilarious. I am the mouthpiece. He is the
driver. It's my opinion that counts, but, uh, he's ultimately the one behind the beat.
I'm the negotiator. He's the muscle. He's the silent muscle. So they're like, Nope.
That's the only car you can get. Uh, like they won't even give me like a tiny car. They're
like, no, that's the only, the only car you can leave this lot in is, is either a black
or a white Ford F 150. What did you go with a white? You'll be leaving this lot in an
F 150 or at a box. Or you don't leave at all. Now, did you go with the white one? Drive
an F 150 off this lot or we will murder you. Did you pick the white one as just a kind
of a knee jerk instinctual move because of Vegas training? Correct. I was just thinking,
I was like, it's summer, it's hot. I'm going to take the white car. Also, I was like modern
political sensibilities. We're limiting DEI. I should take the white car. Um, smart. Was
this, was this rental place at otherwise, otherwise I'm going to get collected by ice
for being a trader and they're going to go through my phone and find all, all my damn
it all. Damn it. Damn everything. Already would leaving Connecticut. You're going to
have to go through the border checkpoint anyway. I was like, I'm in Connecticut, right? They're
like, yeah, I was like white. Yeah. This is a white town. Oh God. Uh, so Jacob, you live
this life. I live the, uh, the truck life regularly. I drove around in a Ford F 150.
It is different living. All I kept thinking the whole time was like, this is what Jacob
does all the time. Yep. Yep. So really honestly, we were just having this conversation last
night. SJ has become a very happy truck girl lately. Yeah. Yeah. Cause SJ has been driving
the truck around a lot over the summer with a, with gigs. So I've been in the electric
sports car most of the summer and she's been the truck gal all summer. But yeah, the driving
a truck around is a different experience than driving a little car around town. Oh my, my
sons are with me. They would have flipped out cause they love going in your truck. They
would have loved going around in a truck for the weekend or whatever. But, uh, um, you,
so every time you pull into a parking lot, you have to go like, oh shit. Every time you
go like, all right, where do I fit? There's a spot. I was just pulling out of the parking
lot this morning, this morning, leaving work. I was pulling out of the parking lot, driving
normally in my lane, headed to a stop sign. A truck is coming in. The truck had to stop
and wait for me to go around. So we could physically get into the parking lot because
there just wasn't enough room in the two lanes made for the parking lot. That happens from
time to time. Yeah. So that is something that just occasionally happens. So, uh, yeah. Like
we were going to dinner and I just go like, all right, I let it go. Like, I'm, I dropped
everyone out. I'm like, everyone go in. I'm going to need a minute to figure out what
I'm going to do. I'm going to, can you just, can you order for me the thing? Just smash
three cars and park there. Well, so this is it. Cause we went to, um, we, cause we went
to, you know, the first, we went to two days of races. The first day we took my brother's
car. He drives a hybrid Accord, like the, okay, like the woke hippie jerk that he is.
You know, they just signed the hybrid Accords over in Scotland. Yeah. Yeah. Finally. But
I don't think the hybrid Accords will stand, but my dad, you know, we're celebrating his
birthday 87. He, he, he certainly enjoyed getting into the truck more than a hunching
down into the old, the old Accords. So that's interesting. Interesting. So that's why my,
my mother-in-law, whenever she comes out to visit, uh, her, her knees are bad enough that
she doesn't enjoy climbing up into the truck. So I was going to ask what your dad getting
up in there. Oh, he was like, he's got those new knees though. Nice. Yeah. He's got those
new knees. He's got those robot knees. He don't give shit. He's 87. Those knees are
like two or three. Right? Those are baby knees. Yeah. Don't fuck those knees. They are not
of age. Those knees are in the Epstein files. Um, you could fuck every other part of Dave
Donnelly, but not his knees. Don't do it. Oh my God. So we were taking the truck everywhere.
So the second day we go to the races, you know, it's the Jim Dandy. Go ahead, Paul.
Go Jim Dandy. Go Jim Dandy to the rescue. What the fuck is he rescuing from whom and
why? No one tells you. No one tells you. And so, uh, and so, you know, it's, it's, it's
Saratoga is a tiny little town. So when the races come up, it's like all these small businesses
just open up and let you park in their little parking lots. And sometimes there are lawns
and that kind of stuff or whatever. Right. So we're driving around and all the lots are,
uh, are a little full cause everybody got, some people got there earlier. We went out,
we went out for a lovely brunch where I literally was like saw a thing that said valet and I
was like, should we go there for brunch? It's like, get this out of my hands. I can only
shop and eat at places with valet. And so, uh, uh, we go and, uh, we pull up to this
lot and all the lots, a lot full of the guy who's wearing a tie-dye shirt and he just
stand there and he goes, and he kind of looks and he, and he points at me and I nod like,
yeah, I'm looking to park, even though this is full and he, and he, and he kind of hustles
up to my car and he goes, uh, you're looking to park. Yeah. I go, yeah. I goes, you're
a lot full. He goes, I'm going to give you some VIP parking. Whoa. I said, okay. And
he goes, uh, I'm right next to like the front of this little tiny storefront business next
to the, the, the larger lot that's full. He goes, you're going to park right there in
the lawn in front of that, in front of that business right there. I said, what? And he
goes, yeah, yeah. VIP parking, man. And, and I go, okay. He goes, uh, $20 because that's
how much it was to park in the lot. It's $20 in the chat. It says best case scenario and
I can't agree more. And, and I'm letting my dad whips out the 20s. I got you. And I was
like, yeah, dad, sure. But I don't know if this guy works here. Yeah. He's like, you're
going to park on that lawn. I don't know if he hates that business and wants to just fuck
with them by putting a big truck in front of it. He's just out there causing havoc.
You are overthinking this. I already would have been gone. I'm going to give you some
VIP parking. Yeah. So we give him 20 bucks. He helps us guide us in. And then he's looking
at me. Cause at first I go about it like the wrong angle. And he said to me like, what
an asshole. And I'm like, this isn't my truck. I don't know how to park trucks on lawns.
Of course. This is your first truck on lawn experience. And so, uh, uh, we finally get
it in and as soon as I'm parked right. Yeah. He literally takes off, just runs. He just
runs away. And that, that made you feel better. I was like, what am I? Does anyone know that
I'm supposed to be? Am I committing a crime? Yeah. So I'm looking for the food for right
now just to show you guys that I can, I can, I can, uh, put it on social media when the,
when the episode comes out. Um, God damn it. Where is it? I was only gone for a few days.
Was there anything else on this guy's tie-dyed t-shirt? Was it just tie-dyed? Just tie-dyed.
So no, was he had to have a hat? Grateful dead shirt. It was just a hat. Did he have
any like, uh, what are those things that the, uh, airline guys use? Oh, that is just like
a front lawn with a pickup truck. You just parked on somebody's lawn. Like filling up
the front lawn. Yeah. And that's a business. And that's a business in front of there. What
do they call those things? I don't know. Semaphore flags. I don't know. And there's a business
there. And that business was not like the guy didn't go inside that business. He just
ran away. So I was like, wonder if a guy was going to come out the door and be like, God
damn it. Yeah. Parking on my lawn. No, nothing. Maybe somebody park on my lawn. It's probably
his business and he's just going to go get a drink. It's probably fine. It was like 20.
I don't think it was his business, but oh shit. Okay. I was thinking it was an old guy.
And you know what? I will say maybe because you know what we owe people bitch about other
generations lately as old man, uh, on the, you know, on the front lawn, um, the amount
of young people that I've run into working lately are crushing it, are doing great jobs
working. Like the super young people in the early twenties and the thought that popped
in my head and I could be totally, I'm totally out of pocket on this and I'll happily be
corrected. But I was wondering, I was like, Oh, the young people working now weren't working
during the pandemic. That's true. They didn't, they didn't have that weird bowling ball wrecking
ball come and smash the way they were getting by or anything like that. Yeah, that's probably
true. And I feel like the people who were covering for the pandemic and working and
working in like these, you know, food industry and like in hotels and low service industry,
you know, kind of things really had a hard time coming back and like getting back to
the grind. And so we were like bitching about it as people who were using these services,
right? Right. The young people are lately, I've just run into young people who are just
crushing it, just doing awesome. And so they're just doing it. Yeah. And so I was like, I
was wondering if it was just like, it's still like, I think it's still like a, a pandemic
versus non-pandemic thing, but maybe that's just my theory. That's my theory. Or just
some generations are better than others. I don't know. One or the other. Those are the
only two. You know, it could be both. It could be both. Maybe you're just running into good
young people. There are a few out there. Maybe everyone knows like the singularities around
the corner. So they're like, let's just work now. It doesn't matter. We're going to be
just goo in five years. It's fine. I have heard from several sources. I'll tell you
who else like Matt Donnelly really admires a lot of very, very, very young people. And
that's the breaks. Pump the breaks. Like my dad's knees. Today's show is brought to you
by country Gators, Gator country country tours. That's right. Country Gators, Gator country
country tours. Hey y'all, I'm an alligator and I'm going to take you on tour. If you're
ready to go. What I do is I take you through my swamp. What I like. It's out in the country.
It's a country swamp. And what you're going to find is a lot of these here trees. They
got knot holes in them. What looks like vaginas. So I call them countries. So you can fuck
me if you want to. I ain't saying don't, but I mean, you know, splinters and whatnot, but
you know, and some of them knot holes got critters in them. You might find your wiener
up against the squirrely squirrel. So just be careful when you're doing it. But most
of the trees I have in my swamp got big old vagina looking knot holes on them countries,
as I was saying. And uh, yeah, that's what I do. And uh, and also I'll eat the smallest
member of your tour. Cause that's part of my Gator ring ways. I am still a Gator country
Gator. What? What? I'm supposed to not be a Gator? Huh? Yeah. What? I'm supposed to
be nice, not eat you. Yeah. I got you. I y'all come up in here and fuck my trees and I ain't
getting allowed to eat one of you at least leaving a bunch of nut leavens in my trees
vaginas and I can't have a little snackety snack. Please. Now come on. And her hay scoops
to check out. I just went back. I just got back from a Portugal. Yeah. Did you see Bazzy?
Did you actually have an encounter? No, we didn't have an encounter. Portugal made me
like New Jersey less. Oh shit. I was, you know, I can be offended except that I know
what happened. You know, part of what happened. No, like I literally have to fly back to dream.
My sister's coming in from Paris. She's staying at like a shore house and I'm, and I am thinking
of not to not to get too far ahead of the story here, but I'm thinking of flying into
Maryland and driving up my brother to fly out of Maryland because flying into Newark
has been a disaster all summer. Yeah, we, we lost an entire day from our vacation because
of Newark. I'll tell you, my, my wife would not recover from that. If we were on a family
vacation and lost the day and got stuck in Northern New Jersey for a day instead of instead
of Portugal, my, that would not be, did you have to stay overnight somewhere in New Jersey?
No, we, uh, we stayed an extra night in Las Vegas. So we, we were able to come back home.
We had a flight to Newark and then from Newark to Faro, uh, Portugal on the, on the Southern
end of Portugal there. And our flight to Newark got delayed, delayed, delayed, delayed, delayed.
And then finally got delayed enough that we were going to miss our connecting flight on
the only flight, uh, to, uh, to Faro. And, uh, so we ended up just coming back home on
Sunday morning and we try to get on Monday morning. Wait, it was morning at work. It
was, it was going to overshoot your destination. No, we were going to get there too late for
the, uh, connection. I thought you said too far. Oh, I was confused. Okay, trees with
vaginas in them and shit. I eat the smallest number to fly into Newark was because they
did not have adequate air traffic controllers in the tower there because fuck our government.
They fire everybody and then don't hire the, I, whatever. No, I read one, only read one
article about it, but apparently it's crazy, but they are actually are actively trying
to recruit people to work in the air traffic control industry. And it is so, um, it has
gotten so basically fratty. Like people are so kind of like hard on the new people and
like, and like really break it down that people quit left and right and don't stick with it.
Oh, it's super clicky to be a, uh, air traffic. Well, I think we need, I mean it's a, it's
super difficult. And then it's like all of this other shit on top of it. Yeah. I mean,
it's, it is a strange thing. And this is the, this is like one of those weird things to
keep hearing about. Like all these jobs are going away. But then, and then you, then you
hear about things where like, we can't get enough people to do this job that we definitely
want to hire people for. And those things are, it's always so strange to kind of figure
that all out, but I guess it's super hard hours and it's, and then, and there are so
many, of course, super stressful, super stressful, right? You gigantic planes filled. Yeah, I
was, I was going to say, uh, Carolyn Albert has a scoop. She has talked to us a couple
times about her air traffic controller stuff a little bit. And yeah, air traffic controller
stuff is nuts. Right. That's, that's nuts too. Uh, but, uh, we don't have to worry about
that here in Vegas because no one's coming. No one's coming here. That's right. No problem
with that. And for some reason we're talking about building a new $20 billion airport.
Now I keep seeing conflicting reports here because I keep seeing posts from vital Vegas
and he just put one up yesterday or maybe even today it was like, uh, you know, the
locals are like, like you guys, nobody's coming. It's the ring, ring the death now. Yeah. Um,
and then I'm not there, but okay, right. But then, but then, uh, other Jacob started, uh,
doing, uh, doing weird, weird, weird pillow art on Etsy as a backup for, right. Yeah.
And you know, okay, you say weird, it's hurtful, but okay. Restaurants or whatever are like,
okay, yeah, we're not going to make, make as much this, this time around. But then he's
like, but then also like Bally's just posted like, yeah, our, uh, our room rates, our room,
uh, occupancy went from 99 to 97. We're still going to have a banner year. Who cares? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So it's weird. Like there's conflicting stuff, I guess. I don't know. Vegas is just
changing, uh, as it has done a couple of times in the times that Vegas change. I can't believe
it. It's just doing its change thing and going crazy about it the same way they do every
time. Yeah. I think like, uh, like, uh, I actually see in our chat in our, in our zoom,
we have Canadian scoop. Crystal labeled Canadian. So crystal, if you feel like unmuting to talk
for a moment, we can actually check in with self identifies as Canadian because one of
the storylines is Canadians don't feel like coming to know we're not getting this. You're
not getting snowbirds, but, uh, um, yeah, our Canadian tourism is way down. Our international
tourism in general is down. So can you, can you scoop crystal? Is that the sentiment?
Is that true from where you're neck of the woods? A lot of people don't want to go down
to the States and they're kind of avoiding it. I'm still coming to scoop fast, but it
took some of my arm to get my partner to come with me. Well, I don't blame them. That's
and we appreciate you guys going for it. Yeah. It's a little scary. You think we're going
to be taken at the border? Like that they could like cold us and, and, uh, we, we've
already spoken to ice and everybody to show them your scoop fest ticket and you'll be
fine. Just be, just be like here. I'm going to scoop fest. I'll be, oh, right this way.
I wish I could completely allay your fears, but I cannot. Uh, I don't know. It was pack
a fake tip sheet of where aliens are hiding out. Illegal aliens are hiding. And then like,
here you go. I'm doing my part. No, it's no, I've had multiple scoops, right? Saying they
don't want to be stopped, uh, in airports. They don't want, they don't want, uh, people
going through their text messages and the, or, or checking their social media and that
kind of stuff. And I, in my, my guts say like, that's very unlikely to happen, but I can't,
I also can't go, no. I mean, I just, I just came in through customs the other day in Philadelphia
and it sure seemed like everybody was having a very easy time, but that's, that's one time
and I don't know. Yeah. And, uh, Chris Gasman, uh, checking in the chat saying, of course
she's wanting anyone going through his picks. And, uh, that's for multiple reasons. Uh,
Mr. Mr. October, Mr. November, Chris, the plumber just, it's because he keeps assigning
himself as Mr. That month. Yeah. They don't call gas man calendar. They don't call him
nice pipe because of his job as a plumber. Do you know what I mean? No, no, no. Those,
those crystals got a kitty on, on the video there. What's the kiddies name? She's already
muted. She's done with us. Uh, we couldn't agree on names. Okay. What? And I have a boy.
It's got two names. No. So, so this is girl and then I have another cat named boy. That's
great. That's I, you know what? That's how, that's how couples stay together. Unlike how
we named our cats growing up, we would name them a black kitty and white kitty and, uh,
mama kitty, et cetera. I like to be original, but I haven't been so much lately. Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's original name Sonic. Oh, that's lovely. But also not original. I don't know
how to tell you this. What neck of the woods are you in Canada? I live in Toronto, Toronto.
And is there people, do you hear like around like general sentiment that people don't want
to come to America right now? Um, I feel like it's mostly from my partner being like, Oh,
no, people don't want to go. But, uh, like people aren't walking around saying, Oh, we're
not going to the U S really weird if they were the first topic or whatever. Uh, well,
thank you. Uh, uh, thank you for chiming in. I appreciate it. Yes, Crystal. Thank you.
We appreciate boots on the ground reporting like that. We do. No, I mean, I think right
now it's specifically in the summertime. So in the summertime we used to get a lot of
European travelers that would come here, uh, division and they're not coming. Uh, also
LA, right? LA is, uh, right now currently on tsunami watch, uh, still recovering from
the fires and obviously had like honestly like been fighting, uh, political stuff in
their own front yards. Right? And so those people are not blowing off steam to make sure
they come out to, to spend some money at Vegas and hit the, hit the pools and the day clubs
and all that stuff. And so, and that's, I think that's what it really is more than,
more than people not wanting to travel and everything. It's nobody's in that mood to
blow off steam. Everybody's got shit going on wherever they are. Yeah. Nobody's trying
to come here and put a 20 in a slot machine. And, and, and sure. And I get it. Maybe, maybe
occupancy is only slightly down, but I can tell you if people who are in shows that the
show attendance is way down. Now show attendance goes down in these months anyway, but they're,
they're, uh, they're going away. I also anecdotally traveling around talking to people who would
come to Vegas. Um, my brother said it best Vegas has become spirit airlines. Uh, uh,
uh, uh, Mark, not Brian, not my hero, but my asshole brother who would not come and
get me. He said, uh, better than to call it. I'm interested in this, uh, analogy here.
So why is Vegas now spirit airlines? I think I know right where this is going. It seems
like it's cheap to come, but as soon as you come, you get charged for everything left
and right. And as soon as you turn anywhere, suddenly you're just nickels and dimes and
charged for every single fucking thing you do. And you leave feeling like, Holy shit.
I thought I was going to spend a lot of money and I did, and I didn't even gamble and I
didn't even see even, I only saw one thing and I'm, and I'm leaving, uh, uh, like broke.
And so it is, uh, it's, it's becoming a real buzzkill for the town. And I, it seems like
some places are kind of starting to combat that. It seems like people are, are people
here seem to be realizing that. And some people seem to be going the other direction on that,
but it hasn't caught on in the big time yet. No, there's like I said, these are small temporary
measures that people are taking just for the summer. They're waving. Some people are waving
resort fees, some people waving parking fees, and that's exactly what this whole town needs
to get back to doing as a whole. Yeah. Free parking. Well, I think also it's, uh, a comment
on the fact that gambling has just become so ubiquitous. Like you can just gamble on
your phone. And it's funny cause it's, it's, it's these companies that spearheaded it.
That's the weird thing. Like you think, you think Vegas would be protectionist, but these
companies are protectionist, the Vegas, they're simply saying, if anyone's going to gamble
anywhere, it should be through our company. Right. And so they, and there still is a Vegas
element connected to it all. You know, like the bed in G MGM is like, that's their whole
tag lines. Like the casino created in Vegas, that, that, that, that, but it's simply not
as exciting to sit in front of a slot machine at Monmouth racetrack in ocean, New Jersey
and spend a day pulling levers there. Like it's just not, that's just not going to create
the same deal. Right. Well, I can tell you out here, we got these fucking skill games.
You ever heard of these fucking things? Oh yeah. What are skill games? Skill games. I'd,
I put a fiver and was like, you gotta go try the skill game. I'm like, all right, whatever.
I put a fiver in, I didn't know what the fuck I was doing. It is confusing and weird. I
didn't understand it. It had a bunch of symbols. You press stuff, you lose your $5. It takes
a little longer. It doesn't make any damn sense. Didn't make any damn sense to me whatsoever.
I was like, what am I doing with this thing? I need a lesson on the skill games, but I
don't know. It just seemed really, really dumb. I don't have the skill. That's true,
Wayne. Yeah. I think that's up. You went into a skill game unskilled. What did you expect
buddy? No, it's what I don't know. I don't understand. I didn't understand what I was
even doing. Well, the good news is that we're protected from the aliens that are coming
because they can't afford all the resort fees and no, no, no, no. And the cocktails. Well,
apparently it's not even aliens. It's just a theoretical thing about seven mile wide
comet. It passed the comet test. It took a test. There's a little box at the bottom said,
check if you are a comet. And it checked it. So it said, Oh, I checked it. I am a comet.
And Ranch Slunk is asking, what is the part that is skill? I don't know. I played it for
like 15 minutes. I'm like, I don't understand what's going on here. Paul has never known
what part of it was. I take it back. I take it back. I take it back. Now my memory is
getting jogged. I do remember once you get to the bonus round, I basically was playing
Simon. The bonus round was Simon. Okay. And I made it through like five things and then
I fucking messed up the pattern. So yeah, there, that's the skill, but it still made
no fucking sense. So yeah. All right. This is all a big buildup by next year. It will
be fuck Mary skill. That's right. Yeah. I'll tell you who else is going to fuck Marion
skill. And that's the following sponsor, a new service that helps Paul buy back all his
toys when he feels sellers remorse. That's from the red Baron in 2021. Oh, the last one,
by the way, is from country scoop. Uh, this is a service that helps Paul buy back all
of his toys when he feels sellers remorse. Hey, what's going on? It's me country Gator.
Uh, I actually also run an Etsy shop and, uh, ideally in secondhand toys and collectibles.
But I'll tell you what, if you in the market for an original teenage mutant, Ninja turtle,
or maybe an old school transformer, I got you covered. But, but, but really it's a front
and I sell logs. I sell logs that have the vagina part, not holes in them. And I can
get them across country lines. So you can, you can look up, you can say, I'm buying me
a toy. It's a toy. All right. But it's a special toy. Yeah. It's a not hole tree that you can
put your Willy in. And I can't guarantee it ain't going to be no squirrely's in there
still. I can't say for sure. But also if you do just want to go to trip down nostalgia
lane, buy yourself an old toy that you used to have, you can get it. Just come on on my
Etsy shop. It's country Gators, country toys. Uh, yeah, but as well, wow. So it's country
toys, huh? Yeah. It, it's one of those things where, you know, you, you do your advertisements
and you make them real controversial. And then people like, Oh, did you say country
virtual? Country virtual. Yeah. And so it's kind of like, uh, it's like a schmuckers.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, country toys. They must have something on the ball calling themselves
that shit. Sure enough. Now are the toys country or they for country? They can be anything's
a dildo if you're brave enough friend. Guys, I just got a text. I'm so glad it's Amazon
looking out for me. They texted me and 19 other people who happen to have a North Jersey
area code phone number, but more convenient. They're looking at for safety and quality
issues of product that I bought. They won't say which one until I click on the link. Safety
is their top priority. So there we go. I don't want to, I don't know. That shit was on the
rise for a while, but it seems a little more prevalent in the last couple of months. Am
I crazy? I don't know. I get it. I get it. I get it. I don't know either, but I'm getting
a lot of these fucking spammy things. Yeah. In my day. Yeah. All I know is that Democrats
are feeling more confident because in the recent days I've gotten a ton of different
people asking me for money. And I think that's hilarious. And I always hate when it's like,
Oh, did you see Pete Buddha judge just top roped Trump into submission with this. I swear
to God breathing every time I am so done. I don't know who thinks that messaging is
working anymore, but it is fucking not. It is not working for anyone. Cause nothing's
changing. Nothing's changing. Nothing's happening. Now someone sends me a things like this motherfucker
ran off the Senate floor with a can of Barbasa and a razor blade and shave that motherfucker's
eyebrows off. I'd be like, here's $20. Thank you. Here's $20. I appreciate your fucking
service, but nobody's doing anything of any meaning or merit. So it's preposterous. Yeah.
I did see they made me laugh. It showed a, there was an AI image. It showed Trump using
a comb over and his hair is covering the Epstein files on top of his head. It really, it really
made me laugh. It is the strangest. Oh, that's really funny. It is the strangest fucking
thing at this point, right? Yeah. It's just, I mean, we are, we are through the looking
glass here, people. I mean, it's, it's bizarre, right? There's no defense for any of this.
And I think that's the other crazy thing is there's a lot of folks like us who, you know,
we hear these talking points of like, Oh, Bill Clinton might be on that list. Fuck that
asshole. Get them all. Bury him under the jail. I don't give a rat's dick. Put them
all in the cemetery. Yes. Everything should be collapsed. The whole government at this
point. I don't give a good goddamn. Oh, and I, I'm going to steer off from that, from
the, uh, from the government conversation in a very, uh, easy way. I'm going to tell
you about my trip to Portugal this last week. Yeah, it's just, yeah, it's just, yeah, there
you go. Scully. Thank you very much. Scully's Scully's on point. That's all you need. That
meme is what we're living right now. Absolutely. We're all looking for the guy who did this.
So we get down to Portugal. Uh, we fly into Faro in the south end of Portugal. Yeah. It's
fantastic. We stayed in, uh, Gia or Gaia, depending on, uh, on how you say it, different
people said it different ways. Derived from mother earth. Uh, yes. Well, I mean, it sounds
like that. Yeah. I didn't name it. Did you find out what Portugal means? In America,
we pronounce it grapes, Jacob. Grapes. Yeah. Yeah. Like bossy, the Portuguese scoop in
the chat here says Gaia. Okay. And then another friend of mine, uh, says Gaia and then people
there, uh, some people there said Gia, some people there said Gaia. I think, I just stopped,
I stopped saying the name entirely just to be safe. I bet you it's a bit to just correct
tourists no matter what they say. Fine. If it was good bit, uh, Jacob, it's pronounced
Chimera, but go on. Uh, so we, we hung around down there. It was just wonderful. Our friends
Scott and Paula, uh, we, we hung out with them and, uh, boy, we had great food. We had
all kinds of just wonderful experiences there. A couple of different beaches. What was your
favorite meal, Jacob? Oh boy. We had a, we had a meal at a winery, uh, that was just
fantastic. Uh, we also had this, uh, spicy chicken at one place. Yeah. That was, uh,
it's a main dish of the region and, uh, it was so fucking good. It's, it's like a hot
oil, uh, that gets poured over the chicken. It gets cooked at a really high temperature
for a short amount of time. It's just quick. I assume it's not fried. It's not fried at
all. It's like roasted. Oh, uh, and I mean, it is, I, I assume that there is some kind
of, um, preparation to it as well. I don't know if they soak it in the spicy oil or whatever
marinate first. Uh, yeah, I don't know if they, if they do any kind of like the marinade
or whatever, uh, but it is slap it. So fucking good. It is so slap it. The slap cook it.
Remember, that's right. They give a good old slap. Period. Period. That's it. Uh, winter
scoop. Thank you. Period. Period. Chicken. That slap cooking chicken is the wildest fucking
thing. That chicken. Those, those videos are awesome. Those were forever. Stay in my brain.
Cooking the chicken. Well, that's cool. Um, so we did that for a few days and then we
took the train, uh, north to Lisbon and, uh, I'll tell you about the part in Lisbon because
it was everything in the south was very relaxed. We had just a wonderful time, so much beautiful
scenery. Uh, it was a wonderful week. It doesn't make for the best stories on the comedy podcast.
So I'm going to tell you about Lisbon instead. We got on the train to Lisbon. First of all,
we got off the train earlier than we were planning to. We had, we had booked a, a booked
passage to this, uh, one station and we decided to get off a couple of stations earlier. Once
we got to Lisbon because we were like, Oh, it's a little closer for a hotel. It's in
the area that we want to be in. We're just going to get off here. So we get off the train.
It's pronounced Lebanon. Sorry. We get off the train in Lebanon, Kentucky. It was a very
long train ride, very wet. And, uh, so we got off the train. The fact that my hometown
was called Lebanon. I know the fuck Lebanon is fucking crazy. Life is crazy. Don't forget.
Uh, SJ went to high school in Palestine. Don't forget it's not just Kentucky. No, it's not.
They're all. So we get into an Uber and the Uber driver that we got in, in, in Lisbon
spoke the least amount of English of anyone that we had interacted with the entire time.
Perfect. Everybody, everybody spoke English at least to a passable degree. No problem
at all. Uh, we get in the car and, uh, you know, first thing to say to this guy is that
do you speak any English? And he goes, he holds up his fingers very close together and
goes very, very little. All right. No big deal. Now, did you think I can use Google
translator? One of these automatic. Oh, we had been doing, we had been doing that to
some degree, but like he, he spoke enough English and you know, it's an Uber. So he's
already got the destination. We don't have to have a conversation. Did you think about just
yelling English slowly at him? That does seem to work, right? Overpronouncing English words
loudly. The winery please. Turn left here. Oh boy.
But it's no big deal. He doesn't speak a lot of English. No big deal. He's got, he knows where
we're going. He's going to drive it. It's, you know, a 20 minute drive. Uh, so he says
in, in broken English, he says, get comfortable. Uh, it's going to be a little bit of a drive,
uh, no big deal. We go great. And so we sit back. We're having a little conversation between
ourselves. Uh, we're kind of figuring out what we're going to do that evening. How many are in
the car and then a small, the small pane of glass comes up separating him from the group
and then gas just fuels into the back of us. You all wake up in bathtubs with a phone next to you.
Your kidneys have been taken. We ride in silence for about 10 minutes and then he started talking
and his lack of English did not stop him for long. How strange. Yeah. So he initiates a new
conversation and he just starts talking to us in English, in English, in as much English as he,
as he could. Uh, and so we're, we're having a bit of a conversation with him and then he starts
talking about the blacks. Oh no. Quote unquote. Oh no. No, no, no, no, no, no.
And he starts selling us how the blacks are taking his, are taking his jobs. Oh my God.
And we are sitting there going like, what the actual fuck? Why is this guy telling us about
the blacks? And he talked about the blacks for about five minutes. Yeah. And then he said
something about Uber, right? He went, Oh, Oh, motherfucker. He's talking about Uber black
language barrier. He's talking about cause he drove an Uber comfort. Okay. And so he was saying
there's more and more Uber blacks now and they're taking business away from the Uber comforts.
Don't let, don't let these people know about the Uber blacks. That's, that's the last thing they
need. That's the last talking point. This guy's back seat. It is, it is very nice Tesla that he's
driving us around and I am just laughing to myself, relieved. Right. He was talking about
the Uber blacks and not the black. Goodness sakes. And then he pointed at a black person on the side
of the street and said, Oh, I don't pick them up. No, no, he did not. He did. Oh, for God sakes.
It was like, Oh, God damn it. So he was actually talking about it. No, he wasn't. He wasn't. He
was talking about Uber blacks. You rode the full roller coaster of racism, right? But this guy's
clearly an idiot. So maybe he thinks Uber blacks is just for black people. Maybe, maybe what a dim
wit. And so he, he then tells us, he says, he's, he's taking us to an area. Uh, our hotel in Lisbon
is in an area, kind of at a downtown area and right, right nearby there, there's an area called
pink street and pink street used to be, I guess, the, the red light district. It was the brothels
and all that kind of stuff. Yeah. And now it's restaurants and bars and there's a lot of live
music there, which is why SJ and I were, uh, you know, heading in that direction. We're going to,
we're going to go hang out in the, in the, in the pink street area that evening and listen to some
live music. It's going to be great. We're really looking forward to it. And then he starts telling
us that this is after the conversation about the blacks. And then he starts telling us that, uh,
Oh, by the way, don't go to pink street tonight. And we had not said that we were going to pink
street, but the hotel was just nearby. And so he goes, don't go to pink street under no circumstances,
go to pink street. That's all we say. Why? And he goes, uh, and then he goes on his second racist
tirade of the ride, but this time it's about the Roma. Oh, and so, and so then he said selling,
telling us how the Roma are in town and they are shooting each other on, on pink street.
And, uh, but that's a festival tradition, the shooting of each other.
Right. You ever been to a San Gennaro? Come on. What are we talking about?
Roma the bulls and Pamplona. The Roma just shoot each other on pink street. That's just,
and at this point I really am just sitting there going like, I'm ready for this ride.
Of the patron, the patron saint of ammunition. You celebrate him. Um, yeah, bossy bossy in the chat is,
is hurrying the story log and tell it saying that of course that's not true. And of course bossy is
100% correct. Right. Spoiler alert. There was no shooting of anyone. And yes, we hung out everywhere.
We wanted to hang out. This guy is just a racist asshole. That's it. And honestly, the entire ride
and still right now, I think he was being racist, but I'm not entirely sure because it really may
have just been a language barrier. No, I'm telling you, I'm still, I'm, I'm pretty sure he was being
at least racist some of the time, but I'm not, I'm still, I, yeah. Oh, about the Roma. He was
definitely being racist. He was deaf. Sorry. Let me be very clear. He was definitely being racist
about the Roma. I'm not sure if he was being racist towards people who were dark in skin color as
well. Jason has a great question for you in the chat, Jacob. Oh, what is it? Did you give them five
stars? I honestly don't think that I ever got back around to reviewing and doing all the stuff. Yeah.
You're too stupefied. So he tells us like, Oh yeah, don't, don't go down there. It's dangerous.
Whatever. We finally get out of the car and we're like, our hotel was literally above pink street.
Like you had to walk out of our hotel and walk down like a ramped alley and you were on pink
street. So I mean, we were directly above it. We were in such a party area of this, of this place
here that our very nice hotel gave us earplugs to sleep in. Oh my gosh. And rightly so. Really?
Absolutely correct. How long, how, how late into the night did the, the party go? I mean, by the
time I fell asleep, it was still going. Which was? In Portuguese, how do you say to the bric-a-bric-a
dawn it's on? Oh, that's a bric-a-dawn. Oh, okay. That's actually, that's actually Portuguese.
Universal. Yeah. That sounds right. Did you understand that you were going to be staying
in that type of an area when you shopped for your vacation? Yes. Okay. Well, we were only staying
there overnight because we were flying out the next morning. So we were only in that hotel one
night. Well, and, and you coming from New Orleans, you've done your share of Mardi Gras. And we
understood what we were getting into. You know what it's about. Right, right, right. We, we were not,
we were not upset by this. We were just, we understood what we were getting into when we,
when we stayed in that area. It's actually funny because I was on my flight back from Connecticut
to Vegas. There was, there was some Roma on my flight and they just shot each other right there,
right there in the aisles. Just right there. Just dead, just two, two shot dead people. Oh yeah. And
he went into all this stuff. He was like, he went into all this stuff about how you can identify
aroma if we, if we see them. Oh, we're not identifying aroma. This is getting weird.
He was telling us how they all wear white t-shirts, which I thought was very vague.
I was like, okay, that's weird. And then he started telling us about how they all had,
he didn't say the words meth teeth, but he was saying meth teeth.
Summer teeth. Yeah. Yeah. That's it. He was saying their teeth are a little meth-y.
So we went to pink street though, and we had a wonderful time. We went and saw some musicians.
It was great. We had some, we had some cocktails. It was really wonderful. We walked, well, we went
and had a nice dinner in Lisbon first and walked all over and looked at some, some different statues
and walked down by the pier. It was all great. We got to pink street and literally, I don't want
to overstate this. I don't want to make it clear that this is not me exaggerating for the show.
Within the first five minutes of us just walking around on pink street, I was offered cocaine three
times, not drugs, not party favors, specifically cocaine. I was offered that, uh, just walking out
at Cozumel at like noon. So I don't think that's a, I just like, I turn and walk onto the street and
the first person I see literally makes eye contact with me, puts his finger to the side of his nose
to gesture for cocaine and then says, want some cocaine? Are you sure that wasn't Santa Claus?
Cause that's his move. There must've been some magic in that old white powder he found.
I was like, why did you gesture for the cocaine if you're then going to explicitly offer me the
cocaine? Well, there are other ways to take it. Sure. As Paul takes it, you can take it
intravenously. Or he could, you know, he might've, you don't want to go up to the drug dealer who's
like pointing to his asshole. Cocaine? Do you want some Bolivian gunpowder? Bolivian marching
powder in your shorts? Do you want Bolivian marching powder, which is slang for cocaine? Would
you like some of that? Do you skewer? Insert penalty. And by ski, I mean, do you, do you do
mountains of cocaine? So we've got three, three offers of cocaine in the first five minutes,
two offers, two, two more offers. Nose candy where the candy is cocaine for your nose.
So it's not made of cocaine, but cocaine. Not even a whole lot of cocaine. It was great.
There were traffic circles in the area that we were in, especially there were traffic
circles everywhere. Not a lot of streetlights, which I kind of enjoyed. Roundabouts, you mean?
Yep. Yeah. Roundabout traffic circles. We saw one fella at a large traffic circle, you know,
in the city, big roundabout, you know, huge statue in the middle of the whole deal.
And anyhow, you get on a roundabout and you get on a roundabout, it might have four entry exit
points and it'll say like, oh, you, you get off on the second exit or you get off on the third exit
in the roundabout. And that's how you, that's how you do the roundabouts. We saw one guy in the
middle of Lisbon, uh, turned the wrong way onto the roundabout and, uh, he was, uh, yelling and
it looked like crying all at the same time while, while they were trying to figure it out. I just
wanted a can of Coke, an actual can. That's it. He just, he was just trying to get somewhere and
he, he didn't know how to drive in Lisbon and he was very stressed. Oh my God. Basi says there's a
city with 32 roundabouts there. Oh yeah. I would lose my fucking mind. In the South, especially we,
we saw like two traffic lights the whole, the whole time we were in the South of Portugal.
They are building, they're building more and more of those out here in Pennsylvania. Oh yeah. And
nobody knows how to use them. And I am also in that club and I do not like them and I do not like
them building all these roundabouts. They are more efficient. You're right. People in, in, uh,
people in the chat are talking about how they are much more efficient than, uh, treat street lights
and they are just correct. If you have people who can use them. Right. There is a bit of a learning
curve. There's also a regular curve. There's, there's a 360 degrees of learning curve on those
motherfuckers. Oh, cause there is a circle. Yeah. What else is round your nostril? Do you want some
cocaine? Oh my God. Oh my God. I walked right into it. Oh my God. This man won't stop offering me
cocaine. So we get on the flight the next morning. We head to the airport the next morning. Uh, we
get through the Lisbon airport, which the Lisbon airport is confusing by the way. If anybody ever
flies through the Lisbon airport, give yourself an extra few minutes to, uh, navigate the Lisbon
airport. Uh, but we got there. All the air traffic controllers run cocaine.
You know what, whatever they were doing and they're very clicky, but they show up,
but they show up. They show up. So we get there. We get on the flight. We're going to Philadelphia
this time. We're not doing new work anymore. We're going to Philadelphia. So we get on the
flight to Philadelphia. By the way, I really appreciated my seatmate, the stranger sitting
next to me. Uh, it was a seven hour flight. She did not speak to me until there was about half an
hour left in that flight. And then we had just a very pleasant conversation for the last half hour
before we left. What a pro. Look at you go. I appreciated that so much. Was this an American
that you were seated next to? Uh, this was an American. Yes. Was it your wife? It was not my
wife. She was seated on a different row. Oh, you guys, you guys don't fly together? Uh, we,
we ended up not flying together on that leg. I forget why. I think it was just too full or
something. My, my wife likes to do like some of, you know, like there's a, there's a tier of cheap
seat where you don't choose your, your, your, your seat. And that's right. And you, and you can lose
that gamble. And it sounds like maybe that's, that's what happened there. That may have happened here
because SJ did set up these flights. So I'm not entirely sure, but yeah, something happened on
this one and we weren't sitting together. Did I tell you guys about my return flight from Vegas
last time that I was, are there any dirty, filthy Roma's on there? Not that I could tell, but I did.
White t-shirts because those were the Roma's. Are Roma's from Italy? Where were Roma's supposed,
supposedly from? What's the culture of Roma? I don't even know the, it's, it's what we used
to call gypsies. Okay. Got it. Romanians. That's it. Okay. Yeah. Uh, thank you. Everybody chiming in.
I go, uh, cause Roma to me, it was like a lot of like Italian places have like Roma as a, as a,
right. Right. They're a small tomato. Yeah. Yeah. They are a small tomato. Well, I I messed up and
didn't get my prebook Southwest early registry thing. So I was pretty late on getting on,
you were at the end of the line on the plane. So I sat in the middle of two people,
the lady to my right was at the window. She was fine. The guy in the aisle next to me.
Was having issues. Oh no. Cause we were coming out of Vegas. So the air conditioning was up
and coming into Pittsburgh, he was shaking and rocking like he was freezing to death.
I don't know why he didn't ask for a blanket or something. I don't know. He was having issues
and he brought an entire sandwich on the flight with him.
Rookie. Rookie. Oh, rookie for sure. For sure. Not an experienced traveler. Uh, smelly enough
that I was like, I, I, I know what you're eating. Yeah. Yeah. He should have, he should have just
dumped all the innards of the sandwich and hide inside the bread. Like, like Skywalker.
That would have been the move is like to turn that into a tauntaun for your arm, buddy. Oh, you know,
but, uh, no, he, uh, he didn't, but he was, he was shaken, shaken like a leaf. It was strange.
It was strange. Did you feel like he was going to lose it or do you think it was just done out of,
uh, coldness once or twice? I was kind of, I got a little like, what is happening, bud?
Oh, you're keeping an eye on him once or twice. I was keeping an eye on him once or twice, but he
didn't, he didn't go completely off the rails. Uh, but I didn't, I didn't sleep that flight at all.
I was just listening to podcasts. Did you think to offer him a coat like a gentleman? Did you think
to, uh, had I been wearing any extra garments? I might, I may have, but I was, you know, here,
take my pants. I was just in Vegas, you know, pajama mode. Basically I'm wearing my sweats and,
uh, a t-shirt. I was just ready to go. So, uh, yeah, it was easy peasy. I don't even think I had a
jacket on. Um, yeah, I was just rolling and it's different for men of size. Did you think if he was
maybe rocking, did you think to maybe cradle him, maybe just like support him, lift him up a little
bit? I didn't, I didn't. Ranch Lunk says possibly autism. No, I don't think this was the case. Uh,
he was truly just cold. Oh man. Speaking of autism on my flight home, I watched The Accountant 2.
I watched The Accountant 2 on my flight home. Ben Affleck playing an autistic person made me very
uncomfortable. I'm so happy. I was watching it going like, this can't be okay. And, uh,
that great actor, is it John Barenthal? Is that his name? I think so. Yeah. The Punisher. Yeah,
he's so good. Yes. And he's his brother. He's his brother. And I was like, thank God he is in this
movie. And this movie was in the middle of seven rewrites and they pressed go. I mean, some of it's
like a, like a romp, like buddy comedy, like, like, like, like, uh, like, uh, uh, uh, was it Will Smith
and, uh, bad boys. Oh, bad boys. Yeah. Some of it has, yeah, a lot of it's like got like bad boy humor
moments. Some of it's like, some of it's like Taylor Shar- like right out of a Taylor Sheridan
show, uh, uh, where they're like, they go into like a honky tonk bar and it's like, they get
like an old fashioned bar fight. The whole scene in the honky tonk bar is the weirdest scene in cinema.
It doesn't need to be in it at all. It doesn't make a damn bit of sense. And then they don't show the
fight sequence, which I'm like, they go for like a gag where like, oh shoot. And then just shows
guys like coming out of a window and they get in the car and ride off like a Taylor Sheridan show,
like a Taylor Sheridan. And I was like, and I literally was like, I was like, what, why am I
watching an action movie where you skip the fight sequences? This movie is filled with hyper violence
the entire time and we skip over the bar fight scene. This was like, what is happening? And Ben
Affleck, I guess he like studied a particular kid and has a good relationship with him. And he already
did this in the accountant one, which I didn't watch because I heard he was playing an autistic
person in the first one. But I love Jon Baranthal. So I was like, wait, you didn't see accountant one?
How did you keep up? How did you keep up in accountant two plot wise, man?
And it is just the strangest. Like it is both like, it is scored like a nineties thriller.
There are parts of it that are like John Wick like, like where it's like this network of
people that just keep reporting to other people and like an underbelly and both sides have too
much access to like crazy amounts of information. One woman's trying to like, just be like a good
voice in it. Like it's all over the place. It is really... It really is. There is so much going on
at all times in this movie. It's ridiculous. It is a chaotic C plus of a movie.
I not only watched the accountant two, I also watched the Jason Statham vehicle, the Beekeeper.
Oh, I saw a Beekeeper when it came out. I love Jason Statham.
Both of these. I was like, these are both very much Matt Donnelly movies.
But Beekeeper doesn't waver.
No, Beekeeper is a good old... It's Jason Statham just doing Jason Statham stuff.
By the numbers right through.
Just what you want.
Hyperviolence. No, they don't take a break for me to feel good. They don't try to make
me laugh. It is just... You shouldn't have messed with them. He was trying to retire.
Too bad. He's killing all y'all.
I'm looking forward to Nobody 2, which apparently is the exact same movie.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I love Nobody 1. So yeah, I'll take Nobody 2.
It was great.
No, no. I mean, here's the thing. I like the idea of portraying autistic people in mainstream movies.
Of course.
We have this thing where we don't like when actors now try to portray different things.
Unless you are blind, you shouldn't play blind, or whatever. All that stuff.
I don't agree with any of that.
Yeah.
Ben Affleck is not a transformative actor. He never has been.
Ben Affleck always plays versions of Ben Affleck that we like him doing.
Charming guy trying to do good things.
Yeah.
He's not Gary Oldman. He's not like... I don't know.
What? He's not?
That's what I mean. There are actors we would give credit to really go and play.
No, you know what? The Gary Oldman. Have you seen the one where he placed a little person on his knees?
No, no, no, no. I didn't want my point to boomerang so quickly.
I'm just wrong. I'm just wrong.
Gary Oldman does a whole movie on his knees.
All right. Forget everything Ben just said. We're going to edit that part out. No big deal.
Cut out shoes.
We're editing that whole part out.
Take a bite.
Take two.
We don't give Ben Affleck the credit of being a transformative actor.
I don't even know who. I can't think of anyone right now.
Like other actors.
Like other actors, but we sometimes allow other actors to be transformative different characters.
Is it just because we used to do it?
No, I know what that means. I couldn't get it out of my head the entire film.
Yeah. The whole time, every time he does it, you just go, oh my God,
that's Ben Affleck trying to be autistic. That's all. You're just watching him act
and going like, oh, how do you feel great about this?
Yeah. Oh, the Gary Oldman movie on his knees is called Tiptoes.
Tiptoes?
According to winners. He's brothers with McConaughey.
And McConaughey is a full-sized man, whereas Gary Oldman plays a smaller man.
And it's outrageous. And McConaughey doesn't like him.
Like he has beef with his brother. It's very strange.
What kind of beef? Short rib?
Oh my God, Paul's playing a clip and it just shows a split second of Gary Oldman being tiny.
Doing the thing.
Oh, that's not great.
It's the preview.
Oh my gosh.
So that Paul stops showing this video. I'm going to bookend my Portugal story.
His mom and dad are regular, see? And the mom and dad of the other people, it's just outrageous.
Anyway, yeah, no, that's horrible.
It's just crazy. But Gary Oldman's, I mean, have you seen True Romance?
That's a wild swing from Gary Oldman too.
But I like a lot of his stuff. I think he does.
I do too.
He takes wild swings.
Okay, here's an example. What, he played a crazy vampire, right?
In, what was it, Nosferatu or whatever? Or what was the?
Dracula.
Bram Stoker's Dracula.
Bram Stoker's Dracula, right? I would want to see Ben Affleck in the same amount of makeup
doing like a crazy vampire.
You're absolutely right. He couldn't pull off full makeup Affleck.
Yeah, like he's meant to be just like likable, relatable guy in whatever role he's playing.
Yeah, he's that Boston guy over there.
That's why Batman didn't work for him because he's got 80% of it.
That's why.
Well, I mean, Snyder didn't do him any favors, but he's got 80% of it.
But the Snyder take on Batman was so morose and unhappy.
And when you introduce him in basically a 9/11 scenario, it's like, where do we go from here?
9/12.
Well, I mean, it was 9/12. It was Superman causing 9/12, basically.
Oh, I went and saw the new Superman movie the other day.
Yeah.
I was so bored.
Was it? It was boring to you?
I was just so fucking bored the entire time.
I saw it.
I just don't give a shit.
Animal adaptions went up like 500% after that movie came out.
Oh, is that true?
Yeah.
Because it's all about the super dog.
Apparently, Krypto's the star.
Yes.
Yeah, which that credit to James Gunn knowing what he's doing, right?
I agree. They took two really big swings because you have to try to reinvent the wheel a little bit.
And yet you still have to deliver a blockbuster.
I thought it was interesting that they started the movie where it would be the start of the third act
in any other superhero movie. They start the movie in the middle.
And there's no origin story or whatever.
Again, I think we pointed out another episode, but none of us had seen it yet.
At one point, he ends up back at his home that he was raised in Kansas and it pans around.
Lois looks around and sees, oh, this is the room that he grew up in.
He's been so secretive about his life.
And yet here is his home and it pans to a shelf that has a bunch of trophies on it.
And I'm just like, what was Superman doing in high school?
He just was going ham.
Just fucking wrecking people in wrestling?
What, football, basketball, like speech and debate, speech and debate.
What was he doing?
It's like that moment in The Incredibles where Dash is doing the race.
Oh yeah, track and field.
And they're like, slow down, slow down.
And his parents are like, oh, and he's like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was like, what are those trophies for? What the fuck were you doing, Clark?
Debate club, ranch slugs, that's debate club.
And maybe you're right. It could have been forensics. Who knows?
It could have been all trophies for Spirit of the Latin Club.
You only get little medallions for that.
No.
The woman in front of me on the flight was watching, she was also watching a fine film.
She was watching Speed 2 Cruise Control.
I appreciate this person watching Speed 2 Cruise Control on this plane.
The same danger as Speed 1, but now in knots.
Now on the boat. Who was that Keanu replacement? What did he end up doing?
Oh, I forget his name. He had a little run. I forget his name.
He did. He did.
Jason Patrick.
Jason Patrick?
Yes, Jason Patrick, yes.
Yeah, yeah. Anyway, Jacob, please finish your Portugal story.
Yeah, so the woman on the flight back, watching this woman watch Speed 2 Cruise Control,
they serve a meal on the flight back. And I saw the meal and it was some kind of chicken,
something or something like that. And they had a couple of other options.
I wasn't especially hungry. So when the flight attendant comes by with the meals,
I just said, "Hey, I don't want the meal. Do you have like a little snacky something though,
like a bag of chips or some pretzels or something like that?" And she goes, "I do,
but it'll take me a few minutes." I say, "Oh, no, I'm not in a hurry. No problem at all."
I make my own pretzels.
I make my own nacho sauce.
Whatever you get through doing whatever you're doing, no problem. I'll be right here.
And she got a smile and was like, "Great." So she walks away, she finishes up. And then like 10
minutes later, she comes back and has two bags of salt and pepper potato chips and two little bags
of pretzels and hands me those four items. And I go, "Oh, this is great. Thank you so much.
This will last me for the rest of the time. Great. Thank you." And I have my drink and I'm
happy as a clam. I'm sitting there. I'm watching a little movie.
Wayne says, "That'll be $73, please."
Yeah, right. All gratis. All gratis.
Nice.
So I'm sitting there. I'm enjoying that. And then I hear behind me in the road directly behind me,
woman says, "Hey, I never got my chicken." Because I guess they had run out of chicken
for the meals at some point.
Ma'am, we're still slapping it, ma'am. We're still slapping it.
The chicken is being slapped.
We're slapping it as fast as we can. It's harder to slap at this altitude, you understand.
And so they had brought over all the plates and everything, all the meals. And then for like two
or three people right in that area, they had run out of the chicken. And so they had gone to get
more chicken from the galley or whatever and they come back and they serve those people chicken.
And I guess this one woman had missed the chicken on the second round.
Okay.
And so she ate her plate of food and then she was mad that she had not had any chicken.
So here comes the guy cleaning up. He's not even the guy serving food. He's just the cleanup guy.
So he's coming along. He's cleaning up. He's collecting the garbage. And she says to him
very loudly, and I'm sitting at the window. She is sitting in the window directly behind me.
And so all I can do, I can't see her. I can just hear her. And she says, look,
I never got my chicken in my meal. And at this point, I thought she was kidding because I was
like, this is such a ridiculous thing. I think this woman is fooling around.
You start laughing and clapping. Good bit, ma'am.
A little bit, a little bit.
Good bit.
And I was like genuinely smiling and like, oh, this woman's going to do a bit about where she
yells about not getting chicken now. Nope, wasn't doing a bit.
And by the way, chicken is code for cocaine. I would like cocaine, please.
I can tell you one thing about Portugal is they don't use code words for cocaine.
Under no circumstance will they use code words for cocaine.
Oh, you thought you were getting cocaine? No, sir. I said chicken. I explicitly said chicken.
I clearly said chicken.
I said chicken. I didn't say cocaine.
So she says to this young man flight attendant who is collecting the garbage,
she goes, I never got my chicken. And in exchange for that, you can make it right to me
by bringing me a bag of potato chips.
Oh, she wants the same salt content.
That's right. And so he says, miss, I'm just, I'm just picking up the trash right now,
but the flight attendant will be right back by in a few minutes and you can get,
you can get the potato chips from her. That is not good enough.
Of course not.
She starts raising her voice.
Indignation.
Over the ocean.
People get crazy on airplanes.
She is raising her voice about how she wants some potato chips.
And he says, actually miss, and again, not the flight attendant,
the guy picking up trash, he's holding a trash bag, picking up people's garbage here.
And he says, actually miss, I'm not sure if we have potato chips on this flight.
They actually forgot to load the potato chips.
Oh my God.
On this flight.
And now, but right ahead of her, there's a man eating chips.
And so she says, oh, no, no, no, this guy right here.
I assume she's pointing at the back of my head.
Yeah.
This guy right here got a bag of potato chips.
Who is this royal prince that you pamper in front of me while negating my chicken?
Everyone knows chips equals chicken.
Now, at this point, I had eaten my bag of potato chips.
Just one bag.
Well, I had eaten the potato chips.
They brought out the two little mini bags.
You ate both the bag.
They were gone.
So I'd already eaten both bags of potato chips.
So when you heard him say that, were you like, gulp?
Did you know before she even pointed you out?
I was trying as hard as I could to sink into my seat.
Because I was like, this nice flight attendant did me a solid,
brought me some nice salty snacks to enjoy on here so I wouldn't be eating the airplane chicken.
Clearly contraband snacks.
Maybe.
Well, I found out later they had a few bags left over, but they had, in fact, not been resupplied.
So they didn't have enough bags of chips for the entire plane.
Goodness sake.
But they had like a few bags of chips around.
Ma'am, I will baby bird those chips into your mouth.
So he looks at my tray table there.
And he sees a bag of pretzels on there.
And he goes, oh, miss, he doesn't have chips.
He just has pretzels.
Oh, no.
Oh, shoot.
This guy's digging it even further.
He's only trying to help.
He was trying to help so hard.
And I just wanted to be like, shut the fuck up.
Move along.
Stop talking.
Just stop it.
You are literally a garbage person.
Get out of here.
Go.
Get out of here, trash man.
Do your thing.
But this woman, you're not helping.
You're trying to help.
And I appreciate that you're trying to help, but you're not.
Please, please continue on with your day.
This guy also has headphones.
Do you want his headphones?
He also has-- what else?
He's got a hat.
You want to wear his hat?
So he says, well, miss, there's a button there right in front of you.
If you hit that button, that's the flight attendant call button.
And she can come get you whatever you need.
No, no, no.
She goes, that's not good enough.
That is not good enough for her.
She goes, no, no, no.
I just need a bag of chips.
And I would like them right now.
Oh, boy.
So finally, this poor guy flags down one of the flight attendants.
So strange to be demanding like this alternate-- like,
I need you specifically to change the way you do things.
That's it.
And so finally, the flight attendant who had helped me out comes back over.
And this woman is now-- she's not quite yelling.
But she's yelling.
She is what we in Couth society would refer to as yelling.
This guy got a bag-- you brought this guy a bag of chips.
Do you know this guy?
She's now questioning the flight attendant.
Do you know him?
Is he someone that I should know?
Because he got chips.
No problem.
This bitch.
And she keeps on and keeps on.
And finally, flight attendant comes back over and goes, hey,
I found a bag of potato chips.
Uh, lucky that, you know, comes back and tries to, like, defuse the whole situation.
Right.
And goes, like, hey, good news, everybody.
I found a bag of potato chips.
This bag is just for you, ma'am.
Enjoy your bag of potato chips.
Enjoy the rest of your flight.
I would have loved for it to be over at that minute.
She is amped, right?
Like, she will not--
She's on.
Right.
And she's going.
So now the flight attendants drop everything off.
They've picked up the garbage.
I've now broken open one of my bag of pretzels.
I'm making eye contact with the flight attendant while she was there and just mouthing, I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to start all this.
I don't know these people.
I'm just trying to do anything to distance myself from these people
in the eyes of this flight attendant who, again, did a nice thing for me.
Unlike Enterprise, where we were joking,
you should have honestly turned around and be like, "Do you know who I am?"
Do you know how lucky you are to be in my airspace?
And then this woman gave me the perfect bookend for my entire Portugal vacation
without even knowing it.
The flight attendant walked away.
The flight attendants have now walked away.
And now she is just talking to her seatmates.
She's talking to two other people who she did not know before this flight started.
Oh, God.
And she's now loudly talking to them and laughing.
And she goes, "Ow!
They didn't know who they were messing with.
As soon as I saw this guy get chips, I knew that I was going to get chips.
And you don't even know.
You see, I'm from Jersey.
And in Jersey, I get what I want."
No, in Jersey, you cry and call your brother for help.
No.
Of course this woman's from Jersey and is now going to loudly proclaim it.
I wish I was in a flight.
I'd be like, "Please stop speaking for all of us.
Please stop doing that."
Stop speaking for any of us.
It was terrible.
Oh, boy.
It was so bad.
And I just looked at my seatmate at one point when she started talking to me.
And I just said, "Do you remember when air travel used to be pleasant?"
It was just nice.
I believe she deserved a slow clap.
I think the hands from your seat going right up and just slow clapping.
Just above my head so she could just see my hands.
Exactly.
Good job.
She wouldn't even get it.
I was like, "I cannot fight with this woman."
I picture her telling this story to anyone after she lands,
just watching whoever she's talking to just eyes glaze over with like,
"What are you talking about?"
You were in some psychotic state where you turn chips into currency.
And you could not get off your own emotional high point.
You were over the Atlantic Ocean and you had a breakdown over potato chips.
And something in your brain just said, "Win," instead of assessing a situation for what it was.
You just had to find a way to feel like you were winning.
And she had just had a tray of food.
There was a salad on there.
There were side dishes.
She had had the whole meal except for the chicken.
But it was not a small amount of food.
It was a full-on meal that they served on this.
It was bizarre until she said she was from Jersey and then I understood all of it.
I married a California girl, so what can I say?
Apparently, she also spends part of the year in Miami.
And believe me, she knows how to get shit done in Miami too.
So there was cocaine involved.
I knew this was a cocaine story one way or the other.
She doing that cocaine?
No, no, that's not how you do cocaine, Jacob.
Cocaine, cocaine!
Right in the vein, that's the rhyme.
Cocaine, cocaine, right in my vein.
Jim Dandy.
Go, Jim Dandy.
What the fuck are you here for?
Who asked you to come?
What are you doing?
Nobody knows!
Lovely, Jacob.
Well, that's it.
It was great.
It was a great week.
Glad to be back.
Glad to be back on the old scoops here.
This is great.
It was nice.
It was good to be back.
Thanks, everybody, for joining us.
We ran out of time.
We didn't have it.
We don't have any Jack vs. Nerd time.
We just talked.
We'll be back here.
For anyone joining us live, we'll be recording again on Friday
for the Monday episode, as always.
And so you can join us there.
I was going to ask you guys if we can go an hour early on Friday.
Yes.
Yeah.
Great.
We'll send that invite out to the patrons.
Yes.
Yeah.
There'll be an hour earlier on Friday.
Because I'm heading off to Arizona.
So if you're getting this, you can come tonight.
Thursday, Friday, Saturday in Mesa, Arizona.
7 o'clock shows at Mystique, the Magic Experience.
It's no dinner.
It's just me, an hour long show at 7 o'clock.
Come out and check it out.
And the reason I'm asking to go early is because I am bringing my sons with me to Arizona.
Oh, nice.
Yeah. And so we'll get out and we'll do other stuff during the day and have fun with my kiddos.
Oh, that'll be so great.
Yeah. So I'm excited about that.
I want to thank everyone who joined us here today.
Absolutely.
Canadian Scoop Crystal for hopping on there. Appreciate it.
I want to thank Jacob's Racist Cab Driver.
Again, not 100% sure who he's racist towards.
Sound like everybody to me.
Maybe everyone.
You made quite a case for someone who's unsure.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
But of course, this podcast is going to be possible with the generous people
who've been supporting us on Patreon.
So we've gotten a bunch of new signups.
I think we appreciate that.
As we head into both Scoop Fest and trying to find a new churn at the same time,
a lot of pills are becoming due.
And so people supporting us there, we will be finishing a revamp of our Patreon
with some adjustments heading into this month, heading into August.
And we'll announce all that when it's all settled.
Probably the next episode.
Yep.
And I'm going to thank some of the people who support us on Patreon right now.
And all these people love to shoot people on Pink Street.
That's us.
Sir Tramps, Six Foot Scoop, Scully Wall Scoop, Slightly Slutty Scoop,
Skirpy Kaya Motherfucker, Smells Funny, Smithy Scoop,
Solar Powered Scoop, Solo Scoop, Soundman Scoop,
Spring Loaded Scoop, Stab and Dash Scoop,
Stacey Coleman, Stacey Westerlin,
Steets Magrits, Stephanie Young,
Stephanie Clively, Stephanie Landon,
Steve Swenson, Steven Biggs,
Steve Eames, Steven Jerome,
Steven Marinelli, and Steven Swendeman.
These people are convinced that they are on a seven mile long comet.
Turn the page.
Tess Miller, Tess Sterling,
Thanksgiving for Werewolves,
That Thing in the Attic,
That Thing in the Attic again,
The Bad Humor Man,
The Bad Humor Man once more,
The Sensey Scoop,
The Civic Crew Scoop,
The Damsels of Dorkington,
The Devil's Lettuce Scoop,
The Devil's Lettuce Scoop once more,
The Didgeridoo's twice,
The Famous Ball,
The Going Over Our Friends podcast,
The Ice Cream Headache,
The Ice Cream Headache once again,
The Lapis Lagomorf,
The Nano Scoop,
The SCOOPOP,
The Salty Squid,
The Scoop Lockean,
and The Spirit of the Latin Club.
The following people all know that a bag of chips is worth it,
worth the fight,
worth the steadfastness,
worth taking all the way to the Supreme Court.
That's Steven Verne,
Stuart Wilson,
Strange Uncle's Podcast,
Strap a Chicken on Scoop,
Where's my Strap a Chicken on?
Sugar Rusts Osio,
Supergeek13579,
Sweetest Scoop,
T Patrick Smith,
Ticket Eevee Podcast,
Sustainable Transportation for All,
Tamara Hamilton,
Technical Scoopport,
Teddy Mueller,
and Temporary.Reality Pierce.
These people are convinced they do not need a license to rent a car.
The Upside Down Underscoop,
The Upside Down Underscoop once more,
The Dirty Scoop,
The Man,
The Myth,
The Scoop,
The Man,
The Myth,
The Scoop again,
Thomas,
Thomas Beach,
Thunder Cougar Falcon Scoop,
Tim Wartke,
Timothy Reed,
Timothy Sutton,
TK4T1 Scoop,
Please,
Tom Krieger,
Tom Mankerdy,
Tom Merritt,
and Tom Stott.
And the following people all pick Matt Donnelly up at the airport
when he forgets his driver's license,
Tommy Harrell,
Do you know who I am?
Tony Cowley,
Tony Scooprano,
Travis,
Travis Jurguri,
Travis Murray,
Tristan Guevara,
Tristan Vanos,
Tristi Perry,
Petty,
Troy Anthony Townser,
Tuba Scoop,
Tyler Bartlett,
Tyler Scoop McDuck,
Udo Gerhards,
Ul Ricky,
Uncle Don's Woodshop,
The Verge,
Warren Bro,
Water Eye Scoop,
Wendy Cooper,
Wendy Bumgarner,
Wendy Loomis,
Wes Coughlin,
What Was Like When Scoop,
Who Dat Scoop,
Will Beardy Dan,
Will Kellner,
Will Pritchett,
William McDonald,
and Wind Walker Scoop 23.
Thank you so much.
If you want to be thanked on air
or get a myriad of other
prizes galore at different tiers
that fit your budget
on a both monthly or yearly basis,
we could use your support
over at preachingfun.com.
Or if your name doesn't sound anything
like any of the names that I just said,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz
that along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as $2 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
Matt's right about all that stuff
that he just said.
It's possible that we're going to be
moving into a new studio
the same month as doing Scoop Fest.
You fool.
We can definitely use that support over there.
Fool.
That might just be how it ends up.
Yeah, but this is a great time to support us
if you enjoy what you're hearing.
And also, now that we're doing
more of these live Zoom things,
this is a great time to become a patron
so you can get the invites
and come and join us live.
It's wonderful to see all these lovely people
that have supported us for some,
for a long, long time.
And we really do appreciate
each and every one of you.
And it's a really fun community
in the first place.
But to become part of it live,
that's really special.
We're really enjoying this.
At least I, myself,
am really enjoying this new vibe.
Paul speaks for himself and himself only.
Only me.
I'm the only one that's really enjoying
all of you lovely people in the chat.
I find seeing laughing faces
when I make jokes to be a burden.
Yes, yes.
Well, lucky you.
But thank you, each and every one of you
who are patrons.
We really appreciate it.
Couldn't do the show without you.
It's true. Being a patron
gets you invited onto this live recording.
And I wouldn't have known
to make that cocaine or a runner,
except I kept seeing people laugh
when I did it.
So there you go.
There you go.
That's how it works.
But yeah, Scoopfest tickets
are still on sale.
Go to scoopfest.com and check that out.
And we have a hotel discount as well.
So call the Orleans and demand
to be part of the discount block of rooms
with a discount code of...
Paul.
Superman.
Catwoman.
Invisible Jet.
25.
Catwoman again.
Right?
I think that's right.
That sounds right.
And if this code doesn't work out,
just tell them Scoopfest.
Just call the Orleans.
Tell them Scoopfest.
It'll work out.
But please do make an effort
to come out to Scoopfest.
You're going to have a great time.
If you're on the fence at all about it,
get off that fence.
Talk to some Scoops.
There are lots of groups.
Oh yeah, Flash.
I missed Flash.
Thanks, Big Sexy.
There's...
Yeah, what's Jeff saying?
If you don't have a ticket,
you need to reconsider your life choices.
Jeff is right.
Listen to Jeff.
He knows what he's talking about.
Reconsider your life choices
if you're not already coming to Scoopfest.
It is a wonderful, wonderful time.
We have a great time.
Our community has a great time.
And if you come once,
you're going to want to come again.
But that kind of holds true for everything.
But yeah, please, please come on out to Scoopfest.
SCFI 25C.
There we go.
Mikey Newman confirmed.
So we'll be having movies with Mikey.
We'll be hosting our trivia battles.
He's excited that we're doing four battles this year.
He's so good.
Just made Travel Registries,
one of our other special guests.
I'm very excited about it.
We have pretty exciting...
So many special guests,
so many special gifts,
so many special things going on.
It's always greater than the sum of its parts.
And it becomes this really special thing.
We are eternally grateful
and always surprised by how cool it ends up.
Someone reached out to figure out
technically how to make
Paul's Hollywood Squares graphic work.
And so we're excited about that.
I still want to do like really basic cardboard...
I think that's fine.
Yes.
But we'll see how it goes.
We'll figure it out.
But it's going to be exciting.
So yeah, come on out to Scoopfest.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See ya.