(upbeat music)
- Oh, hello there.
I didn't see you there, but I am so glad you are here.
It's time to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Who are the Ice Cream Truck Drivers?
Well, these are the folks that deliver
that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
Right now, I'd like to thank David Walker,
Dead Lazlo, Dirty Old Scoop,
Galactic President Scooper Star McScoops-A-Lot,
Ice Blue Scoop, Jacob Dinklage, Jeff Harris,
Jobbeth Bowers, and John Mattingly.
If you wanna be an Ice Cream Truck Driver,
and I sure hope you do,
PreachingFun.com is where you can go, PreachingFun.com.
Head over there, sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver,
and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
And now, a show.
- Hey, Johnny.
Do you wanna go to an ice cream social?
- Yeah, I'd love to.
- Great, let's go.
- Oh man, it's so exciting.
We have the stars of Showgirls, the unauthorized musical here.
- Yes.
- With us, talking about all kinds of showgirls.
It's pretty exciting.
I made it at the end right here.
- It's time for Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social,
sitting over there in Las Vegas.
That's Matt Mattingly, sitting in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
That's Paul Mattingly, and in Las Vegas, it's me,
Jacob, the audio guy, PreachingFun.
I forgot Pittsburgh for a half second there.
- It's easy to do.
- Somewhere in Pennsylvania.
- Philadelphia?
No, that's not right.
- No, we're still covered in snow.
It's so cold here, it's disgusting.
It's in the single digits,
and it's gonna be that way for a long time.
- It's disgusting.
- We're gonna get hit with a lot of snow later this week.
It's gonna be awful, but yeah.
- I walked outside with no shoes on today,
and just took the dogs outside, went and fed the fish,
and thought, boy, this sure is a nice January day.
- Man, it's getting crazy everywhere.
I'm fighting with my kid to take a sweatshirt
with him every day.
He's like, "I don't need one."
I was like, "You might."
It might suddenly become January for real.
You don't know.
- If you're out after it gets dark, you'll need one.
I leave the house every day.
If I have a backpack with me or something,
I have a sweatshirt inside the backpack,
because I know once it gets dark, I'll need it.
- Jacob and Paul, what was your opinion
of "Showgirls the Movie" when it came out, and what is it now?
- I love it unapologetically.
We have a friend, SJ and I have a friend
who was in the "Showgirls" movie.
She was one of the dancers in the "Showgirls" movie.
So we've had multiple movie watching parties with her
over the years with different friends,
and she would talk about some of her experience
putting "Showgirls the Movie" together
and all that kind of stuff.
And boy, I was the right age for "Saved by the Bell."
So Elizabeth Berkeley coming into doing an NC 17 movie
when I was in junior high,
maybe a freshman in high school, was a big fucking deal.
(laughing)
Let me explain that to you very clearly.
It was big.
- It really was like took Tiffany Amber Thiessen's
Maxim photo shoot and put it on blast.
- Yeah, it did.
- If you think that's enough, it is not.
- Hold my beer, Maxim photo shoot.
- It took me a little while to get into that flick.
I didn't watch it during its original theatrical run.
I believe I owned it on DVD at some point.
- Okay. - Maybe, I'm not sure.
But I have seen it a couple of times.
It's hilarious to me.
And I am Facebook friends with Patrick Bristow,
who is the caddy choreographer from the show.
- Great.
- He is actually good friends with my pal, Sarah McChesney,
who has worked with Henson in the past.
She's a puppeteer.
And Patrick has gone on.
He is the host of "Puppet Up"
for most of the time that that show has done,
which is the improvised Muppets thing.
- Yeah, the Henson puppet show.
- I think I know where this is going, Paul.
And no, we're not making an all puppet version
of "Showgirls."
We're not doing it.
We're not gonna do it.
- Not yet, not yet.
And also, Matt, it's not an all puppet version.
It's an all puppet version, except for one human character.
That's how it goes.
That's how these movies are produced.
- That's right, that's right.
Who would the one human character in "Showgirls" be, Paul?
- Oh, it had to be Kyle McLaughlin,
coming back to reprise his role, at this age.
(laughing)
He's the only one with the--
- I'm the same guy.
- He's the only one with the gravitas to pull it off.
And with a straight face.
He could do it with a straight face.
- You're right.
- I know, I know, I haven't not thought about this.
(laughing)
So, but yeah, I'm desperate that maybe one day
I'll get involved with "Puppet Up" a little more too,
'cause I've got a lot of satellite pals within that orbit.
- Paul, the question wasn't about you and puppets at all,
as a matter of fact.
It was, what did you think about the movie?
- But what I'm saying is, what I'm saying is,
"Showgirls" is-- - You're clarifying
the question you've always asked yourself.
- Has always been rife for parody and puppetry.
(laughing)
- Well, I believe you do-- - Also, living--
- I believe you do get both in this unauthorized parody.
I'm going to see it tomorrow night, it's a press opening,
so I'm going to see it tomorrow night.
- Oh, nice. - I'm very excited.
- I have tickets to see it, I think on March 1st.
- Okay, very cool.
- Yeah, or a group of us are going to go on March 1st
and go see it.
- Elaine, when this first came on your radar,
what made you decide to hop in and give it a go,
to be in the "Showgirls" parody musical?
- Well, I've always been a huge fan,
and particularly a huge fan of Nomi Malone,
which is the character I'm playing.
I mean, she's just a savage.
When else, as a woman, do you get to, you know,
basically practically stab people,
push 'em down the stairs, play all of the emotions,
but you're just a girl with a dream,
and you just have to do, you know,
she's just dealing with the obstacles in front of her,
taking 'em on one by one, and yeah,
so I've always loved her, and it's a joy to play her.
- A Rosie the Riveter type, if you will.
(laughing)
- A pioneer, yeah. - Sure.
- The feminist icon writer and director, Joe Esterhouse,
(laughing)
named Nomi Malone, 'cause it would be,
basically also mean, "Know me, I am alone,"
and he wanted that to be very significant
about that character.
- I wanna see a list of the top 10 things
that he wanted to be significant in "Showgirls."
- Oh, but you're-- - Oh my God, me too.
- It's quite, yeah, like the license plate,
like he is a lot, he made all the choices
thinking he was making a very significant movie.
- Good, good, that's what I want.
- Well, and he was.
- Yeah, and he was right.
- And touchdown, success.
- Yeah, remind people who Naomi is.
- It's Nomi, actually. - Nomi, excuse me.
- So she is-- - Start there, start there.
- I will see myself out.
- She's the main, you know, main character,
one of the main characters in "Showgirls,"
and we catch up with her kind of hitchhiking to Las Vegas.
She decides she's gonna go to Vegas and dance.
We don't know that much about her past at the beginning,
you know, that kind of is revealed later on,
but she's a dancer, she's ambitious,
and she sees one of the big production shows
in Las Vegas starring Crystal Connors,
my co-star here, Katie,
and she's kind of like, "I could do that."
From there ensues like the path of ascension, you know,
taking out obstacles as they come,
whether that be her fellow "Showgirls,"
or like Kyle McLaughlin,
like who's the entertainment director wooing him,
just kind of, you know,
all the steps that I'm sure real "Showgirls" go through
to make it to the top.
- Well, that's what I was gonna ask you.
I wanted to hear about the parallels
between Nomi and your own showbiz career, of course.
- Right.
- What are the positives and negatives?
- Well, you know, if a man's trying to sexual harass you,
sexually harass you, you gotta pull a knife on him,
obviously, especially, you know, post 2016,
they really, you know, that is encouraged.
- That's option one, go right to that.
- You know, if, yeah, if someone's in your way,
you've gotta push them down the stairs,
either literally or figuratively,
but I do like the literal approach, personally.
- It is, it works, it works.
- Yeah, yeah, it does.
And you just have to, you know,
try and make sure you don't get caught.
Because that's the key to it all, you know.
- We actually did have a guest on the show.
It was a peep show.
And they did have shenanigans.
Do you remember someone put pins in her boots?
Someone was trying to sabotage her
and put thumb tacks in her boots,
trying to take her out of the show.
- Oh, I do vaguely remember this.
That sounds familiar.
There was so much shit that went on with that show.
- Tara, yeah, someone tried to put pins
in Tara Palsha's boots.
- That makes sense.
To be fair, I did apologize.
(laughing)
- Well, you know, this was the path,
the career path chosen by Elvira, Mistress of the Dark.
She came up as a Vegas showgirl.
That was how she cut her teeth.
And then, speaking of cutting their teeth,
Matt, you might wanna close your ears for this.
I've mentioned this before, but it's been a minute.
So you remember the Jenna Jameson, the porn star.
- Who?
- That name's familiar.
- Sorry, I was just trying to--
- She also went through a dancer/showgirl moment
at a very early age, and at a certain point,
she went so far.
In her ambition, she had braces on at the time,
and it would belie her young age.
She had her brother take pliers to her head
and pull the braces off.
- Oh!
- Yes.
- Oh my God.
- In order to pass as older.
(laughing)
Yeah, so she, yeah.
If you've ever read her biography,
that's a hell of a showgirl biography, too.
That's pretty wild.
- I'm gonna do that.
My son has braces right now.
I'll make sure to remove them myself with pliers.
- All right, yeah.
- You don't own pliers.
- Daddy needs smokes.
(laughing)
Jacob, take my son's braces off his face.
- Jacob, come over and bring some pliers.
- There's gotta be some silver in these things.
Melt 'em down.
- Now, Katie, every time I watch this movie,
sorry, I'm just gonna jump right into the next--
- We both are doing the same thing.
We both are transitioning to Katie.
Go ahead, Jacob, the floor is yours.
- Katie, every time I watch Showgirls,
I am struck by the '90s Vegas
and all of the kind of entertainment landscape
that was '90s Vegas.
I moved here in 2007.
And you and I have been old, we're old friends.
We've known each other for a couple of years,
for a year or two.
And yeah, this is my training from SJ.
I just say I've known people for a year or two.
(laughing)
- That's smart.
- Yeah.
Yeah, so we've known each other for a year or two.
How much does that kind of old Vegas
and old showbiz casting in Vegas
and kind of that old showbiz energy in Vegas,
how does that make you feel?
Compare that a little bit to your old days in Vegas,
if you would.
- Oh, well, I mean, I remember,
so when I moved here in 2008,
like the Riviera, which is very prominent
in the backdrop of that movie was still up.
Like some of those old neons that you see in the movie,
we're still here.
And so, yeah, it just, when I watch it now,
parts of it feel still very like today Vegas,
but most of it feels really, really old and not dated,
but like, oh, that was so beautiful.
Why did we get rid of all that?
Um, yeah.
- Yeah, Vegas, Vegas has gone so mainstream now
that you see old portraits of it
when it was still like this cool kind of like escape place
and you're like, oh man, bad ass.
- Right. - Yeah, yeah.
- Kids from Iowa hitchhiking on the side of the road.
- 'Cause-- - Different places.
- Did you always love this movie, Katie?
Do you always have a love affair with this movie?
- No, I didn't really see, it's weird the way I saw it.
- Upside down. - When I grew up,
both of my parents, yeah, right?
My parents were ministers,
so I definitely didn't see "Showgirls"
until I was moving out here.
Like literally the night before I moved out here
to be in Jubilee, I watched two movies.
I'm not even making this up.
I watched "Showgirls" and I watched "Alive"
'cause it was on TV and I was about to get on a plane.
And I don't know what's wrong with me.
- If you had given me a million guesses
for the second movie, I would have not gotten to "Alive."
- Were you simply trying to scare yourself
out of making this life move?
Were you trying to like, don't do it?
- I, yeah, I don't know.
But you know, the weird thing is that "Showgirls"
didn't make me afraid to come out here
and be in a big "Showgirls" show.
It actually like made me even more excited.
- Oh really? - 'Cause it was so,
that movie's so pretty.
The costumes and the makeup, oh my God.
- Will you give people a little inside,
behind the curtain look?
The audition process, we see a little bit
of like the big lineup audition
for the big Vegas "Showgirls" show in "Showgirls."
Will you talk a little bit about those big
kind of lineup auditions where, you know,
100 people, 200 people, 300 people would show up
and they'd just have to basically go through 'em
factory style?
- Yeah, well, the first thing that Jubilee would do,
which I totally appreciated was they held like a stick up.
And before you even stepped on the stage,
if your head did not pass that stick,
it was, "Thank you so much, goodbye."
'Cause you're not tall enough to be in the show then.
- SJ is familiar with the stick.
- Oh no, oh, I'm sorry.
- You're like, "I know, but I still wanna get my tits
"out today and now I can't even do that."
- Oh, she would show up with like tall hair and everything
and they'd just, they'd smoosh it right down with the stick.
I feel like it would be so hurt.
- That's a bummer.
- People know that she was at Jubilee.
- That stick was the director, that's the weird part.
- That stick was named Fluff.
- Right.
- That was Fluff the stick.
- Yeah, and then the next thing they would do is
you had to do PK turns across the stage
because you can tell in one PK turn
if that person has had any dance training at all.
- Oh, fascinating.
- And so then they, yeah.
So then they would make a cut from there
and then you'd start learning combos and stuff.
And the audition-- - So before the combos,
what percentage of people are cut before the combos?
- Oh, 50.
- Wow.
- Yeah, yeah.
'Cause a lot of girls would show up just like,
well, I'm pretty, well, I dance at this strip club.
I could be in this show, kind of Nomi style actually.
- Yeah. - You know?
- That's what I tell myself--
- Well, where do you think they got the idea?
- I leave the house, I tell myself I'm pretty
and then I go about my day with a lot of confidence.
- I'm pretty enough to do this.
- And in this show, you play the villain,
Gina Gershon's part.
Was that something you were looking forward to playing?
Is that something you wanted to play?
- I had played Nomi the last time we did this show,
which was like almost a decade ago.
- Okay.
- And when Troy said he was doing it again,
I said, "Cool, I'll be one of the dancers.
"I don't wanna be Nomi."
'Cause that part's really hard.
You don't leave the stage, it's exhausting.
(laughing)
And then--
- And Leigh just pointed to her head like mental note.
- Sorry. - Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, sorry.
- This is up there with Pym saying,
"Don't write yourself running in scenes."
(laughing)
- Very smart, yep.
And so then when it was getting closer to auditions,
I kind of said to him, "You know, I feel like
"if no one shows up for Crystal that you're interested in,
"I feel like I could play Crystal.
"I've been a showgirl now for 17 years
"and I'm tired and I'm jaded and I get this woman."
- Between the last iteration and this one,
you felt like you've earned the role.
- 100%, yep.
(laughing)
- I want the role that I identify the most with
and that is this person over here.
- Yep. - Go fuck yourself.
And now you and Elaine have been friends for a long time.
You guys have been accused of being twins.
- Yeah.
- You've done a lot of gigs together.
- Yep.
- Was not knowing if you guys didn't realize
at the audition that you'd be working with each other
in the two lead roles, right?
- Well, so Elaine had kind of talked to me
about maybe auditioning for showgirls
before the audition popped up
and then she just wasn't at auditions.
(laughing)
- Fucking boss move, Elaine.
Boss fucking move.
- Yeah. - Best way to get a part.
(laughing)
- Leave 'em wanting more.
- And then like when they were looking for a Nomi,
I was like, "Look, there is one girl I know of in this city
that is beautiful, that is great to work with
and that is absolutely not afraid to be crazy ugly."
(laughing)
- That's the requirement.
- Yeah, absolutely.
(laughing)
- That girl was busy.
- She was too busy making some kind
of giant Hormel chili dip on her.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Elaine, you have this entire other life as this,
do you say bizarre cooking influencer?
How do you phrase your--
- So I say like content creator or like internet chef,
but yeah, I kind of have an alter ego
that's especially on my Instagram,
like a Midwestern housewife who is well-meaning
and just trying to make semi-homemade like Sandra Lee
in the largest quantities possible most of the time.
(laughing)
- You have this gigantic grill
that you always just pile tons of stuff on
to create these amazingly ornate, delicious looking,
but crazy huge meals.
- Well, thank you for the delicious looking.
That's such a, quite a compliment.
Yeah, this summer, like I really,
I just had this idea.
I really wanted to do Blackstone stuff.
So we got one of those big Blackstones,
I think ours is like three feet.
- Yeah.
- Anything that you could cook on a Blackstone
or could not cook on a Blackstone, I tried it, so.
- What's your favorite, what's your least favorite?
- Well, one of my favorites was,
I saw this recipe for twice baked apple and cherry pie.
And so I went to Costco
and bought three large versions of those.
And I flipped them face down on the Blackstone
one after another.
(laughing)
Jizzled, drizzled them with some sweetened condensed milk,
added some other ingredients.
Just, you know, if you need like a big pie to feed a group
of like 60 to 100, like I definitely recommend
doing it this way.
- I still remember, like I became friends with Elaine
through just like mutual friends in town.
And so I became friends on a regular Instagram account.
And then someone was like, well,
obviously she's busy being an influencer.
And I was like, wait, what?
And I was just only friends with your personal.
- I hate when that happens.
- Your personal account.
And I was like, whatever.
And then I went over to your big page
and you're making like a punch for like,
if you're having a backyard, you know, get together,
make a punch.
And then I was like, and I was, I was, I was like duped.
You're like, show like a little thing of fruit punch
and all of a sudden there's like a kiddie pool
and the kiddie pool is being filled, just filled with,
with booze and liquids and all kinds of chopped fruit
and all kinds of stuff.
And I was like, what's happening?
And then I looked at your page, I was like, it's all this.
It's all this crazy stuff.
- It's all that, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you know, like lots of themed party foods.
- I love it.
- Sometimes it's in a fish tank.
Sometimes it's in a kiddie pool.
You gotta make the people happy.
Give them what they want.
- You do, you do.
You did one, like a pumpkin pie one near the holidays
with on that big grill, like a pumpkin thing.
And I was like, I like your videos
'cause you go like, yes.
And then all of a sudden something happens, you go, no.
And then something else happens, you go, yes.
And then you're like, no.
And then by the end you're like, I would eat all of that.
I would eat all of that.
She's right, she won.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I've got to check this out.
I have a Blackstone.
So I've got to check this out
and see what I need to be doing on my Blackstone.
- Yeah, so you're busy with your crazy
influencing content creating.
You say to your friend, you want to be in Showgirls.
You don't go to the audition.
What happens when you get the call from Katie?
Was it, oops, I forgot.
Or was it like, were you on the fence
about committing the time?
Like what happened there?
- No, you know what?
I was on the fence about getting my boobs out.
- Ah.
- Ah, sure.
- Yeah.
I mean, I wasn't on the, I guess like I'm,
I haven't been in a show like Jubilee.
I haven't ever been.
I don't even duper less or anything like that.
So, you know, it was a not sure slash deal breaker for me
with that.
And so I had to talk to her about it.
But then, yeah, when they didn't have a know me,
well, I was like, okay, this is my dream role.
And I figured maybe there was a little more wiggle room
for negotiation with that, you know.
- Holly Barry negotiated like $500,000 a tit
in that one movie she did.
- Monster, I think.
- Oh, Monster's Ball.
- Monster's Ball, that's it.
- Yeah.
Wow.
- Well, my rate is similar.
- There's also a five in it.
- No, it wasn't Monster's Ball.
Monster's Ball was artsy.
There's a movie where she basically like,
like someone goes like, hello.
And she just puts the thing,
like it was like a big action movie.
- Oh yeah, that's right.
- Puts the sun thing down.
She's just topples on the chair for like a split second.
And apparently it was like a million dollars
just to do that scene otherwise.
Yeah, yeah.
And then she did Monster's Ball just 'cause,
I think just 'cause she wanted to hook up
with Billy Bob Thornton.
I think there was nothing else to it.
- Oh, I get it.
I mean, he's dreamy.
- Now, Katie, you're also very shy about nudity,
is that right?
(all laughing)
I was gonna say, Elaine,
you probably talked to the one worst person to talk to
if you're nervous about nudity on stage.
- That's true.
- Swordfish, by the way, swordfish.
- Swordfish, that's it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh yeah, swordfish.
- I bet it was much more negotiable.
I bet Katie was probably the hardest person to negotiate
with.
- Well, yeah, she was pro.
(all laughing)
- Well, Katie takes the term wiggle room personally.
She's like, no, no, no, if there is room to wiggle,
we shall wiggle.
- The funny thing is when,
oh, sorry, go ahead, Elaine.
- No, you.
- When they figured out how to do the topless,
but not topless, I was the only one like,
so I can't get my tits out now 'cause no one else is?
All right.
- So you hit your own deal breaker, Katie, you were the--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Well, I was gonna say, in the parking lot,
post coming in and reading with everyone,
I was like, she had me very close to convinced.
I was like, well, or maybe, like.
- Jacob, by March 1st, who knows, buddy?
Who knows, pal?
- That's right, that's right.
We'll see.
- You've been doing previews, how's it been going?
- Good, really good.
We've had great audiences.
You know, some areas get like way bigger laughs
than you expected, and then other areas you're like,
okay, like this needs to be tweaked a little
'cause it's not getting a reaction.
So they've been helpful,
and they've been supportive and good.
- Yeah, I think parodies are hard that way.
Parodies are, on the broad strokes, of course,
it's like, it's very much a layup
to obviously celebrate showgirls musically
and everything is super fun.
But yeah, parodies get really tricky
because it's hard to figure out what fits in the box,
like theatrically, but you're poking
at the fourth wall the whole time.
You're dealing with an audience
that has the knowledge base of the material.
Paul and I did "50 Shades of the Parody" together,
so that's why we're talking about that,
is that it was always strange to figure out
what your relationship with the audience is,
with the material.
- Well, and also, it's a similar vibe
with "50 Shades of the Parody,"
because we always joked,
it's not really "50 Shades of the Parody,"
it's just "50 Shades," and look how ridiculous this is.
And I think there's probably a not dissimilar effect
with some of showgirls. - All the craziness
came from the source material, yeah, yeah.
- Right, not too dissimilar effect
probably coming from showgirls,
because there are moments that it's just beyond,
it is beyond parody, some of that film, yeah.
- Right, I mean, like, direct from the script,
you know, what's Al's line?
Word for word, it's like--
- It must be strange not having anybody come on you.
(laughing)
- Yes.
- This is what I'm talking about.
- Yeah. - Yes.
- Exactly.
- And Paul, you relate to that line a lot, yeah.
(laughing)
- I was, I was.
- Well, you're talking about source material.
- Yeah, I mean. (laughing)
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Playing Gina Gershaw's part, Katie,
is it as fun as you thought it would be?
More fun?
Is it crazy?
Is it hard?
What was it like taking on this role
10 years after not playing it?
- There are parts of it that feel very, very natural.
I will say, like, some of the things that I have to say
to know me, Elaine, are difficult for me
because Elaine is so, so goddamn funny.
(laughing)
It is difficult at times to,
well, just not to laugh out loud on stage.
Like, my very first scene with her,
I say something and then she screams in my face
and she runs over to a wall and slams herself into the wall.
(laughing)
And it's just like, that's probably the hardest part
of being Crystal.
Everything else is natural.
- Was it a total head trip?
'Cause you basically went from Maria
to Baroness Von Schrapp, you know?
So what's that shift like?
What's mentally, do you find yourself,
are you ever at times in opposition
to the character you're playing in a way?
What's the game there?
- No, never, because as I've gotten older
in the tidy space that is the classic showgirl world,
I see all these young green girls coming in
thinking they know everything.
And so I have slowly just grown into Crystal.
- I think that's just what happens, right?
Like, you just grow up in the entertainment industry
and you go like, yeah, that's just what people are now.
I don't know what you want.
- Yeah, yep, yep.
- You've made us into this.
- No, I was actually-- - That's exactly how I feel.
This city and show business in this city
made me into this.
- I was just visiting with my mother-in-law
and she, of course, was in "No No No Net" with Ruby Keeler
when Ruby Keeler made her big triumphant return or whatever.
And someone brought up,
I'm trying to remember the name of the other,
it was another movie star.
And Ruby Keeler putting on her makeup quietly goes like,
yes, but can she still do a thousand taps, blah, blah, blah,
and just talk shit about this other movie star?
And I was like, (laughing)
based on that she's still an amazing tap shape
at her age in her 60s.
Basically, still out tap any other movie star.
And I was like, man, this is the one who left show business
and still kept her receipts.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- I left this whole thing.
I came back, also, fuck you.
(laughing)
- And Elaine, yeah, my wife is working on the show as well
and speaks so highly of your comedic background.
Do you have a formal comedic background
or are you just a funny person?
- I started in theater and musical theater
when I was a kid, I was like nine.
I went to perform arts high school.
And then I went to AMDA in New York for two years
and I started working when I was 20 in 2007.
And actually like 2008, 'cause I think I started taking
at the People's Improv Theater in New York.
And both Nate Starkey and Ashley Ward were teachers of mine.
- Love those two, love those two.
- Yeah, I know, me too, me too.
And then when I moved to LA, I was kind of
at the groundlings, like on and off,
'cause sometimes I would take breaks between levels,
but between 2012 and 2016.
- That's a lot, that's not a small background,
that's a big background.
And actually, what groundlings training specifically,
where Katie's describing, your groundlings training
must be coming in very handy right now
with these big choices.
- I mean, I love, exactly, I love like groundlings style
and like just characters and, you know, exactly.
- For our listeners, like groundlings is always about
like taking your choice, making it distinct,
and then take it to a 10.
Like that's basically what they're known for
is take your smallest choice
and then make it eat everything else in the character.
Which is why so many of them are iconic
from our old mad TV days to the ones
that had the train that stuck out on "Saturday Night Live"
and stuff, it's like those are the,
that kind of era of comedy where all sketch comedy
was so character distinct
was definitely because of groundlings.
- Yeah. - Yeah, yeah.
So, oh, so you're a heavy hitter.
You're, I didn't realize you stuck with the,
all the training in the post-pit, so that's exciting.
- Yeah, it was great.
Like I think that's my favorite thing in life
is just, you know, like laughter of reflection, right?
Because like it's the best way
to connect with other people, I think.
- Yeah, yeah, I think so.
- Sometimes you do it on stage
and sometimes you do it on the internet through food.
(all laughing)
But through, you are pushed, you know,
through pushing the envelope, through tension spots
and, you know, and messing with people,
like you do figure out.
- Through filling a kiddie pool with punch.
- Yeah, like, no, I think when you surprise people,
their real feelings burst, right?
That's what standups do and everything else.
It's like when you surprise people,
their real feelings burst before they can rationalize.
And so suddenly that's where you get like a real temperature,
a real take of what's happening in the room.
And when you're in a comedic environment,
when we all get to laugh at that time, it's a relief.
We're like, oh, good, we're all, we're all flawed.
We're all laughing at this thing,
which means we're all secretly maybe
hiding our terribleness all the time.
(all laughing)
- Some of us doing a better job than others.
- Speak for yourself.
(all laughing)
Hiding it.
- Well, people who want to be decent are trying to hide it.
(all laughing)
- The time for that game has passed, my friend.
- Well, I'm so excited to see the show tomorrow night.
How long is it running?
It's running at the Majestic Theater.
We should tell people it's at the Majestic Theater.
- Yes. - Downtown Los Vegas.
- Downtown Arts District.
Beautiful, beautiful Downtown Arts District.
So much new stuff in that Downtown Arts District.
Do yourself a favor, go see the show, get your tickets,
get there like two hours early, walk around,
find yourself something to eat,
do a little shopping in the area,
hang out after.
There are a ton of bars right there.
Again, in walking distance from the Majestic Theater.
Yeah, it's really great.
The whole area downtown there in the Arts District
has just been blossoming.
- It's a vibe.
- And frankly, the Majestic is right there
at the forefront of that blossoming.
So, good job to them as always.
- I love that theater.
We know it's our favorite theater.
- Oh, yes.
- We beg Troy to perform there all the time.
And so--
(all laughing)
- He won't do it.
- I love that crazy environment.
And how long is it running?
- Through March 8th.
- Through March 8th, all right.
- Yeah, we've got every Thursday through Sunday
from now until March 8th,
and of course, special performance tomorrow night, so.
- So cool, so cool.
- Fantastic.
- All right.
- Anything.
- We haven't early.
(all laughing)
- Yeah, Jacob wants everyone to come with shopping bags
for some reason,
but we'll figure that out as we go.
- It's fine, it's fine.
- Your favorite scene to do, Elaine,
and then the same question to Katie.
- Well, I really love when Katie and I see each other
kind of for the first time outside of the dance off.
I just think like, that's so much fun.
And God, there's, I love the whole thing.
Honestly, beginning to end,
I love watching her song, "Constant Pain."
I'm on stage for that,
and I kind of get to just like watch.
- Oh, that would have been a better question.
Much easier to answer.
Okay, Elaine, what's your favorite Katie scene,
and Katie, what's your favorite Elaine scene?
Much better.
- There you go.
- Elaine, you're a better podcaster than I am.
Go ahead.
- Well, definitely, like I said,
Crystal's big solo ballad, "Constant Pain,"
just so much fun.
I think there's so many layers
to what has been added in that song,
and there's just things that crack me up.
I mean, starting with the lyrics
and what Katie's put on top of it,
being a dancer, being a real showgirl.
I just think that's a blast,
and the audience is having so much fun at that moment.
- Yeah.
Katie?
- For me, it's definitely when Elaine comes out
to do a song called "Lapdancin."
(laughing)
The first time that she was just rehearsing it,
I had to excuse myself
because I was crying, laughing so hard
that I was disruptive.
'Cause I'm not gonna give it away,
but the pole is, it plays a big part.
Of course, she's gotta lick the pole,
but it plays a big part in that number,
and she just goes so full out,
and it's so goddamn funny.
(laughing)
- I just wanna point out, yeah,
much like Paul and I, when we did "Fat Chase," the parody,
what was particularly great about it
was there's original music.
You're not using typical parody songs,
which is, a lot of parodies use typical mainstream songs
just to kind of make fun of certain elements or whatever,
but this is all originally scored, right?
- Yes.
- That's pretty cool.
So yeah, a lot of great songs in it.
I can't wait to check it out.
Well, thank you guys for coming by
and checking out "Ice Cream Social,"
and we'll put all the links and all that
into our bio and stuff,
and people have plenty of opportunities
to go see the show "Downtown Vegas."
Hope you guys have an amazing run.
- Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
Thanks for having us.
- Break all the legs, y'all.
- Come see us. - Thank you, Matt.
- Oh, we will.
- Thank you, everybody.
I'll tell you who else is gonna go see
"Showgirls, the Musical Parody
at the Downtown Majestic Theater,"
and that is the following sponsor.
- Today's show, Matt and Madeline's "Ice Cream Social,"
is brought to you by Yo-Yo Ma's Yo-Yo Mart.
That's right, from 2021.
This is from one of the Wills.
Yo-Yo Ma's Yo-Yo Mart.
("Ice Cream Social")
- Hello, it is I, Yo-Yo Ma.
Master of the cello.
What I'd like you to do
is shut off your brain for a moment
and hear the sound of a cello
as it's played by one of Yo-Yo Ma's specialty yo-yos.
This is a Duncan Wonder Ball.
(yodeling)
I bang it into the instrument.
That's all I can do with it.
Now, Yo-Yo Ma will walk the dog.
(yodeling)
And now, I will do "Baby in the Cradle."
Yo-Yo Ma's Yo-Yos from Yo-Yo Ma's Yo-Yo Mart
are coated with a special resin
that give them a resonance.
But when you spin that yo-yo,
when you go around the world,
you really go around the world musically
with Yo-Yo Ma's Yo-Yo Mart yo-yos.
- Enter Hey Scoop's Checkout.
(laughing)
I don't know where I expected that to go, but yeah.
- I'm just a better person having listened to it,
so it doesn't matter.
I'm just a more mature.
- Where else is it gonna go?
- This is it.
- O.G. Scoop in the chat mat is pointing out,
"Didn't your wife do something with the Showgirls show?"
- My wife is the choreographer,
but I didn't wanna flex my family's involvement
with the show.
I just--
- No, no, we're just people to go see the thing.
- Yeah, yeah.
I think Sarah and Troy have talked about
working on different projects for a while now,
and then, as you know, Disco closed.
Sarah had free time, and nature abhors a vacuum.
- Sure.
Nature and Sarah abhor a vacuum.
- And so Sarah filled that time immediately
with Showgirls and working on Showgirls.
- Didn't she agree to do it
before Disco Show closed, though?
(laughing)
- Yes.
- I think she agreed to do Showgirls
before she had the time to do it.
(laughing)
- That's how you get things done, I suppose.
- I guess so, I guess so.
- Yeah, so the timing worked out.
Timing worked out, but yeah, yeah.
So we can't wait to...
There we go.
So, yeah, I'm so excited.
I mean, I love that show.
I saw a parody of it in New York back in the day
that wasn't a musical, that was just hysterical, too,
and I just...
- Nice.
- Well, I will tell you that no one actually loves that show
more than my friend.
Maybe I won't name him for the story,
but he was dating a stripper,
and they wanted to watch it together,
and he took ecstasy when he was rolling, when he watched it.
(laughing)
And then he was watching it,
and he thought it was so beautiful and significant,
and then he was looking at his girlfriend
not react that way.
And so he was leaning over to his side
and secretly texting and calling his friends
to express how amazing and important Showgirls was.
- Well, I've watched, actually,
'cause that was Paul Verhoeven who directed that.
- That's right, yeah, yeah.
- That's the man behind Robocop.
- Yes, yeah.
- Like, and if you look at it,
like I've watched some really interesting
commentaries online,
where they kind of deconstruct what's going on.
It's nuts, the stuff that he was,
the messages he was putting in there
that didn't necessarily translate for a lot of reasons.
- No, I mean, that is what's fascinating about it.
If you want to look into it at all,
is like, I forget what kind of filmmaking it was,
but it used to be when you watched student filmmaking,
you watch whatever films from another country
where if they showed a wine bottle,
it was supposed to mean something.
Every little image is actually supposed
to be the significant meaning,
and it never translates to the watcher
unless you know it ahead of time.
- Unless you have also studied that filmmaking method.
- This film is filled with it.
It is filled with trying to make this
such a significant story,
and it just is known for it's like crazy backstage antics,
and then of course, bizarre sex scenes.
- But let me posit this to you guys.
Let me just say like if the three of us
were tasked with making "Showgirls,"
the year is 1990, whatever it was,
and somebody comes to the three of us and says,
"Okay, you guys are gonna make this 'Showgirls' pick.
"We got the girl from 'Saved by the Bell.'
"She's gonna be in it.
"We got all these other people they're gonna be in it.
"It's Vegas, 'Showgirls,' blah, blah, blah."
We'd go, "Great, we're gonna start looking into this world."
And as soon as you start looking into that world,
there is so much interesting stuff.
There's genuinely all of this incredibly interesting stuff
in exotic dancing, in the "Showgirl" world,
and in Las Vegas entertainment.
- Oh, like this--
- If you want to try to communicate
all of that interesting material to the audience,
it's just not a thing that's really communicable.
- No, I think-- - Unlike most things
in the movie "Showgirls," which are very communicable.
- I think, yeah, I think that if this comes out years later,
it's more fascinating as a prestige television show.
- Yeah, I mean, it's a history document.
- Yeah, yeah, I think you really see the world
through the life of the actual occupation of a "Showgirl."
Obviously, the movie came out last, "Showgirl."
People are, Taylor Swift just named her album "Showgirl."
There's still a fascination with this,
and I think largely right now, because it's going away.
Larger right now because of that kind of idea
of putting together some kind of really big production show
with pageantry and that being something
that attracts modern audiences is going away.
Now we need celebrities and IP and all this other stuff
to make people want to see something, I think, you know.
I think the largest driver of tourism right now
is the fucking "Wizard of Oz," right?
Like for Las Vegas, right?
So it's like, I think we have this fascination of this era
that is closing out, right?
Even Dita Von Teese opened up her show over at Bally's,
and the big discovery was that all of those, is it Mac?
What's the name of the famous costumer?
- Bob Mackie.
- Yeah, Mackie, Mackie, you know.
- Bob Mackie, yeah.
- All this is just--
- Dita's show was in the Jubilee showroom at Bally's.
- Right.
- And they were using a lot of the old Jubilee costumes.
I'm just filling people in on what you're saying.
- No, yeah, I'm sorry, I'm trying to let you also.
I didn't mean to be like, yeah, I knew that, brr.
- Yeah, but no, they were in the Jubilee showroom
where Jubilee had been since the '60s, I want to say,
'60s or '70s, and closed, like I have,
I've got pictures on my phone somewhere
of them taking the Jubilee sign down outside of Bally's.
- Right.
- Just 'cause it was right across the street.
And so we'd just watch this happen every night.
And Jubilee was a show that, I mean, I saw,
I don't even know how many dozens of times I saw Jubilee.
And so like Dita's show going in there
with all of the costumes,
and Katie mentioned a little bit, like with the height stick.
And I think I'd even talked about this,
seeing Dita's show when they were doing it.
It was so neat with Jubilee because it was,
it was this beautiful exhibition of,
you know, here are all these people,
and we have gotten a group of people
that we can get to look as identical as we can
and still have a hundred people on stage,
but we're getting them to look as identical as we can
with the height and the build and everything else.
And then we're just gonna display these costumes on them.
- Yeah.
- And so to see that, and so to see Dita then take that
and say, we're gonna get people who look as different
as everyone just truly looks.
We're not gonna do any of that nonsense of trying,
and not nonsense, it's not fair, different time.
But like, we're not gonna do any of that stuff
where we're just displaying the costume.
We're gonna display the people as well.
And so Dita having people that were of kind of every shape
and size up there wearing these costumes that for decades
and from my whole experience had been like,
no, you have to look like this to wear these costumes.
It was a neat thing to watch history kind of get turned
on its head a little bit with Dita's stuff.
But then yeah, I think you're onto something though.
I don't know how interesting that was to the lay person.
- Right.
I mean, it was, I think that it through its efforts
became iconic stamp on like what to go see in Vegas.
- Yeah.
- When you were there, like, and I think part of it
was the toplessness and then that kind of stuff.
- Sure.
- But I think that era where you tried to meet
in the middle, right?
It was like, sure, you're gonna stop us
but we're actually gonna show you production anyway.
We're going to value and you're not,
it's not going to be lurid.
It's not going to be sexual.
- Well, I mean, that scene in "Rocky IV"
when Apollo Creed is coming out and the huge production thing
with the bull that collapses and all that stuff,
that's just a scene out of Jubilee.
- It is.
- They do that shot that's in the Jubilee theater
where they do that shot.
And they just did a scene from Jubilee
and put Apollo Creed in front of it
and put a boxing ring in front of it.
But I mean, that's what they did every night.
- Yeah.
- It was crazy.
- No, you're talking about like, Dita,
they basically had those costumes just locked up.
There was no one in charge of preserving them.
And so basically that production company was like, good Lord.
And tried to like preserve as much of it as they could
and do whatever.
And we don't, we still right now don't have like a museum
or a preservation space for these iconic costumes of-
- This was the same kind of difficulties and travesty
that happened when they closed down the experience.
There were so many pieces of memorabilia,
the Jimi Hendrix experience.
So there were so many pieces of memorabilia
and actual legit costumes and you know,
not to mention all the replica stuff
that just a lot of it went in the fucking trash.
- Oh, I mean, I was working at the Tropicana
after Follies Brejere closed,
which was the kind of the sister show to Jubilee.
It was the other big showgirl show in town.
And I mean, I found a room one day,
maybe a year after Follies had closed,
that just had basically all the costumes
that had been worn on the final night.
They had just taken all those costumes
as soon as people got off stage
and throwing them into boxes and closed them up.
They hadn't washed them, they hadn't laundered them,
they hadn't dried cleaned them,
they hadn't even dried them out.
And so like they were all sweaty, they had mildewed,
like they had just rotted.
It was horrible.
- Well, you know, we'll save the day.
There's a silver bullet, we own it.
We own the silver bullet, guys.
- What's the silver bullet?
- Chapeau, Chapeau was our production show.
- Chapeau could do it.
I mean, we've got the first number written.
- Chapeau would do it.
- We've got the first number written.
- Seduction Escalated.
- We're practically there.
- Yeah, Seduction Escalated, we're right there.
- It's halfway there.
- We are.
- I'll tell you who else is halfway up
that escalator to success.
And they're gonna slap on those butt cheeks
to show their appreciation.
And that's the following sponsor.
- Today's show, Matt and Madly's Ice Cream Social
is brought to you by RFK Junior's Throat Worm Based Losages.
That's from Scoop of Monte Cristo in 2025.
This is RFK Junior's Throat Worm Based Losages.
- Uh, it's, it's, (coughing)
it's, it's golden flu season.
It's golden flu season.
And, oh, milk.
(groaning)
- Ladies and gentlemen, it has been determined
that RFK Junior is in fact Jabba the Hutt
being choked to death by Princess Leia
from Return of the Jedi.
His death scene on the, on the sailing barge
is a literal translation of verbiage from the future
from our Department of Health and Human Services Commandant.
- Enter HeyScoops at checkout.
(groaning)
I didn't know an ad was gonna get us sued by JFK
and Disney all at the same time.
(laughing)
So I got some firewood delivered to my house.
The other day.
- Firewood delivery, huh?
- Firewood delivery.
So what I usually do, 'cause we have a fireplace
in the house, we use that to keep the house warm
during the, during the winter time
so we don't have to run the heat so much.
- Oh yeah, that's that bitter,
that bitter vague is cold, it'll get you.
- That's right, that's right.
You know, it'll get down into the 50s sometime.
- Paul, we are in show business.
We put on productions.
Fire is an element that we have
as like part of our hosting abilities
while we all come over in our short sleeve shirts
for our winter barbecues.
- In the backyard.
- The barbecue, exactly.
Hey, I, believe me, I fucking miss it this year.
It's already been just shit.
We drove yesterday to go visit with my in-laws
to go have dinner at this '80s diner.
It was kinda cool.
It was all '80s vibe, you know,
like they had Ghostbusters and shit on the wall.
- Oh, like an '80s diner.
- Like an '80s thing.
So really good food. - But like in which decade?
- Like '94, '95. - The one right before the '90s.
- I mean, it really, but it is, right?
Like the '80s retro stuff is all
the '90s idealization of the '80s.
It's not what the '80s was.
The '80s was really '70s couches in a basement
with a big ass TV and a Nintendo hooked up to it.
That's what the '80s was.
It wasn't all fucking day glow triangle.
- What's your story, Paul?
- Listen.
(laughing)
I'm telling you--
- Paul telling us what the '80s wasn't.
- We're getting ready to go.
- You know what else the '80s wasn't?
- And the phone alert system goes,
"Hey, snow squall warning."
- Ah, snow squall?
- Yeah.
So Anne's like, "Let's pump the brakes
"on the snow squall warning.
"Let's not leave until the snow squall warning is done."
So it finishes about 10 minutes after we were going to leave.
So she texts our relatives and,
"Hey, we're heading up there now."
We get in the car, we get on the highway.
We're on the highway about three minutes
and snow squalls are coming.
It just--
- So many snow squalls.
- It just did not stop.
And I was like, this is, I mean, it was literally like,
I don't know, 70 feet visibility, maybe, maybe 60.
- Okay.
- It was pretty intense.
- Maybe 65?
- Eh, I'm gonna give it 30.
How about that?
30 feet visibility.
- Great.
- It was bad.
It was really bad.
And then the sun would kind of try and peek out
and make it even more of like a white washing.
I can't see fucking shit.
Anyway, we finally get to the restaurant
and about a minute before we get to the restaurant,
it stops.
Like literally on the road to the restaurant,
the squalls stop.
And I get out and I look at my phone and I go--
- All in all, we're just trying to eat in the squall.
- We were.
I look at my fucking phone and I was like,
oh look, Ann, they issued a squall warning again
about 40 minutes ago during our drive.
She said, can you text them fuck you?
- Can you reply to that text?
- I would like nothing, like to do nothing more.
- I got this at my kid's school
where they always issue, if any bus is late,
the entire school gets a late bus alert.
And I go like, at this point,
we should just get alerts for when the buses are on time.
- Right, hey, everything's going to plan.
Right, every other day, you know that shit's happening.
So yeah.
- I like that maybe there was a guy at the weather service
who was hard of hearing.
And every time anyone said anything, he's like,
what, squall warning?
Oh, I'll send it out.
Wait, what'd you say?
- Hit the squall button.
- Squall button, bang.
- The fact that they cut off the squall warning
and then issued it again like five minutes later.
As soon as we got off the road, they started it up again.
Like, fuck you.
- So yeah, I'm not a fan of this winter bullshit.
- I travel a lot and so sometimes planes are delayed.
The only airline I know that will delay a plane
and then go nevermind, actually we're leaving early,
is Southwest.
Everyone else, if your plane delayed,
then it's just delayed.
But with Southwest, if your plane's delayed,
you're like, don't go anywhere.
Because they might just turn around and be like,
nevermind, it's all here, we're going.
- They do, they do, they do.
Again, spoiled on the fucking Southwest, man.
I love my Southwest.
- So most years I go, I take the truck
and I go pick up firewood.
- Yes.
- And there are these services in town.
- That's what I thought, Jacob.
I thought you were a man, you know?
I thought you went out and got you fired.
- That's the thing, so every year I've done this,
every year I've done this,
this year I couldn't find anywhere that would let me do it.
- Wouldn't let you pick up firewood?
- They wouldn't let me pick up firewood.
Everywhere is doing deliveries.
And I asked one guy, I was like, what's going on with this?
And he goes, oh, some people are, they'll come pick it up
and then they'll drive it somewhere and resell it.
Like on their own.
- Oh.
- This is the economy we're living in, guys.
- And my response to that was, so what?
- You're still selling them a truckload of firewood.
- I agree.
- Like, so why can't I buy a truckload of firewood?
- Oh my God, that's funny.
- I would call your wood people and be like,
look, Ticketmaster couldn't figure this out.
You can't either.
- Pokemon can't.
Pokemon can't figure it out.
That's, there's a whole economy
based around reselling Pokemon shit.
- You can't help it.
- Half of the, half of our current economy
is reselling Pokemon cards.
- So I have this area in my shop, in my garage,
that is the firewood pile.
And it's a big area there,
and we pile all the firewood up there every year,
and it's there, it's indoors a little bit,
like we don't have to go outside
to go get it during the winter time, it's nice.
And so he pulls up in his truck,
and he takes one look at where the firewood is gonna go,
and he goes, "Oh, that's not gonna fit."
(laughing)
And I go, and I say, very confidently,
"Don't worry, I do this every year."
And I point at my truck,
which is the same size as the truck
that he just pulled up in, so I'm feeling good.
I was like, I go load that truck up every year
with firewood, I stack it all right here,
we'll stack it up, and we'll put it in front of each other,
and it doesn't look like it'll fit,
but trust me, it'll fit.
And he goes, "Oh, okay, great."
And we start unloading the firewood,
and we start stacking it up.
(laughing)
He was correct.
I was gonna say, the fact that he was like, "All right,"
was basically like, you know.
- Let's go then.
- You used to be equivalent of someone
who works at a restaurant every day,
and the customer going like, "I eat here all the time."
And you're like, "No, I work here all the time."
And you don't, you just don't.
- He is a professional wood stacker,
as you are a biannual wood stacker, yes, yes.
- An amateur at best.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- And so we got kind of the main space
of firewood storage area filled up.
- Yeah.
- And I looked at his truck, I turned to look,
'cause he was kind of like bringing wood to me
while I was stacking it.
- Yeah, and more to come.
- And so I wasn't really paying attention to the truck.
And so I turned and looked at the truck,
and keep in mind, the area that I usually fill up
with firewood is now about halfway filled up.
(laughing)
At this point, I have filled up about half
of the normal load that I bring in to this.
- Oh, so you were wrong by like a great deal.
You were wrong by a significant percentage.
- A great deal, a great deal.
- But you said they're the same size truck.
- Turns out, when you just have four guys
throwing pieces of firewood into your truck willy nilly,
and just stacking them, a lot less firewood fits in it
than when one guy very carefully goes through
and stacks all the firewood into the truck,
getting as much firewood into the truck as possible.
- Oh, okay.
So this is a stack packaging issue.
- Do you think you have more than a year's worth
of firewood here then?
- Oh, yes.
Not only do I have more than a year's worth
of firewood currently at my house,
I have more firewood that I've already paid for
at this guy's establishment that now that he knows me,
I can just go pull up in the truck and he will load it.
He was like, we stacked as much as we could.
I was like, I'm gonna call it.
There was still maybe a third.
- You don't have an account on Truth Social, right?
- No, no.
- Okay, you should get one because what happens
is they're gonna eventually need to start paying
some people to host book burning barnies.
And so you should make sure
that you're on the forefront of that.
- Jesus Christ. - Get on the cutting edge.
- You can get on the, any book that mentions
the word gay or trans or whatever,
or a black person or country has slavery at one point.
That's all gonna get burned.
- That's all gonna get burned.
And you know what they're gonna need for that?
Firewood.
- Exactly.
I mean, it's strange for me to be telling you
to be profiting in these strange times,
but I'm just looking out for you, man.
You know, we gotta pivot.
Sometimes we just have to pivot.
- You gotta pivot.
- We gotta Jeremy pivot.
- Jeremy pivot.
- So, okay, okay.
Wait, so where are you?
Where are you loading up when you're realizing
this failure of loading your truck properly is happening?
Where are you?
Where is this?
- This is at the house.
- Is that your house?
- So he brings the truck,
'cause they won't let me come pick it up.
So he brings a truckload to the house,
but he has packed the truck in such a way
that he has filled every space in the truck.
- Every nook and cranny is firewooded.
- When the guys fill my truck up,
when I go pick it up,
I basically pull up, hand 'em like $60,
and they just, like four dudes,
just start throwing pieces of firewood
into the bed of the truck.
I'm always a little worried that my truck
is going to get damaged when they're loading it.
- Get out of here.
Really?
- That's how they're loading it.
(laughing)
That's the way in which they're loading this.
This guy had like carefully packed all this firewood
into the bed of his truck.
And I mean, it had to have been three times
as much as I usually get into mine.
- Same price.
- Easily.
A little more expensive,
but definitely worth the extra cost.
- Wow.
But you're at your house.
- I'm at my house.
So we're stacking it up in my house.
- Okay.
- And we got, there was maybe a quarter or so
of his truck bed left, and I called it.
I was like, I can't.
Like I'm going to have to start moving shit around
to find places for firewood now.
And I knew that he was close by
because we had already talked about it.
I was like, you're going to do more deliveries
with this truck tomorrow, right?
He said, yeah.
So I said, if I leave firewood in your truck,
that doesn't screw you up on your later deliveries
that you're doing tomorrow.
He said, nope, I'm already partway loaded then.
That's all that means.
He said, great.
Said, can I just come pick up about this much firewood
later on from your place,
which is right down the road from my house?
- Yeah.
- And he goes, yes, you can.
And he looks at it.
He goes, that's about two and a half wheelbarrow loads
of a firewood that I owe you.
- You should argue with it right there.
You'd be like, nah, I think it's, nah, nah.
- No, this sounds like he was very gracious in victory.
- Hold on, I've got a wheelbarrow in the back.
We'll load it up and test this out.
- This guy was very gracious in victory.
- He was.
- Yeah.
- He certainly was.
He was very gracious.
- I just like, he had a second opportunity
to misjudge his call again.
- I mean, he did miss the runner, but still.
I mean, if you two are the only ones that are getting it,
he's just like, eh.
- I mean, at that point, I'm like, whatever you say, man.
I'm not disagreeing with a single word you have to say.
If you tell me that I should be using
a different type of wood, great.
Load all this up, take it away.
Bring me whatever you think.
I just agree with you.
- Holy smoke. - Amazing, amazing.
- Oh, I went back in the house.
And later on, SJ gets home.
And I was like, you see that giant pile of firewood?
She goes, yeah.
Said, we have more coming.
(laughing)
That chunk, 'cause like, I basically made
my two big piles of firewood that I always make,
and then I made two more big piles of firewood
in front of that.
And I was like, as soon as we burn this ancillary pile,
we're going to get enough to make another ancillary pile.
- The only thing you should have done
is gotten out chat GPT and be like,
chat GPT, how much wood will fit in here?
And then like, put it in his face.
Like, no, I did my research.
I did my research.
This wood should fit.
- It'll be fine.
No, we're stacking it wrong.
We're the problem.
You and I are equally the problem here, sir.
Equally.
- So you load it from his truck to your truck at your house?
- No, no, his truck into the house.
My truck was not involved.
- Got it, I got it.
Okay, that's where I kept getting confused.
- Okay.
- Yeah, we were loading it into like
the wood storage area in my house.
- And he was like, it's not going to fit
in that storage area.
- Yeah, yeah.
And he was like, absolutely not.
And he was just-
- And you took the rest of the wood
and built a second storage area.
You built a second, just put that wood together.
- Yep, that's right.
That's right.
- This is the, you know what this means?
You have too much wood.
We should host some kind of mini burning man.
We should build some kind of figure
that we can torch an effigy.
To celebrate something.
- I can't think of any kind of public figures
that you'd want to burn an effigy right now.
(laughing)
I don't think we have, we need to wait
for a more aggressive political climate
so we can do it.
- Just a know-it-all Norwegian is what we'd build.
We'd build a know-it-all Norwegian.
(laughing)
- God damn it.
Oh, fuck.
- Oh, people are asking why I didn't want
to stack it outside.
I just didn't want to.
It was going to be more of a pain.
This is easier.
- It can rain in Vegas.
Also, like I've got kind of an outdoor fire pit
and there's already a wood pile outside
that kind of runs that fire pit.
And that one's also full.
- Jacob is neat.
He doesn't want sloppy wood about his yard.
He needs things tidy.
- Yeah.
Plus this guy is like a mile down the road from me.
This was just easier.
- Yeah.
- This was just much easier.
- My new little jock versus nerd.
- As a guy who gets firewood a bag at a time
from the grocery store.
- Yep.
(laughing)
It is easier.
- It is easier.
(bell ringing)
- Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for jock versus nerd
(dramatic music)
Explosion of wood
- We got a scooperty from the OG scoop today.
I think he said this was an AI scooperty.
So I don't know what that means,
but we'll find out together.
The categories are Matt, Paul, Jacob, and ice cream.
Paul, you're up.
- I'll try me.
- Oh, lemur screamer.
They are local trees.
Thank you for asking lemur screamer creamer.
They are indeed local trees.
It's a wood like a tree service.
This is the other half of the tree service.
So that I cut down trees in town
and around here and everything,
and then chop them up and let them sit and season
for a couple of years and then sell the firewood.
- So Andy had AI just generate all of the questions
and answers for this quiz.
- Okay.
- Oh, all right.
- This is scary.
- We'll see how this goes.
All right, I'll take me for 200.
- Let's see.
The state where Paul was born,
it's official name is a Commonwealth.
- That would be Kentucky.
- The KY itself.
- My old Kentucky home.
- Let's see, I'll try.
Well, I'll try Jacob for 200.
- I'm asking you, when you put this in AI,
did you put any facts in with it,
or did you simply want AI to use
whatever knowledge you already had of this podcast?
I'm curious about like the actual input
for this quiz. - Oh yeah, that's interesting.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I gave it just some like one word things,
like Springsteen, Louisiana, Bourbon, et cetera.
- Okay.
- Yeah, and then they kind of just went crazy
and some of the questions are really odd.
(laughing)
- I'll bet, I'll bet they are.
- All right, we'll find out together.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- The only US state that is divided into parishes
instead of counties,
a legacy of its French and Spanish colonial days,
it's Jacob's home state that of course is Mississippi.
It's Louisiana, come on.
- If you read the $800 question, it's like,
Matt last sent a dick pic in this decade.
(laughing)
- I feel like we'd all get that right.
Matt, you're up.
(laughing)
- I guess we're on a roll here.
I'm gonna go with, no, you know what?
I'm gonna do Paul 400.
I'm gonna try to change the game.
- Mix it up.
Paul's favorite Star Trek series,
the one with captains, Janeway and formerly Cisco
overlapping in the same era.
- What?
(laughing)
- Nope, I'm on board.
I like this a lot.
- Oh man, I wish I knew this just 'cause it'd be funny
to take this question, but I don't.
- I don't think AI knows this.
(laughing)
- Are you passing?
What's happening?
- I'm passing, oh yeah, yeah.
- Paul.
- I mean, I guess it's next gen.
- All right.
Star Trek Deep Space Nine or Voyager.
Paul loves both.
He quotes DS9 more.
- No, that's not, that's plainly not true.
(laughing)
- Paul, you just saw it on the screen, it's very true.
- This is why we've gotta burn down
these goddamn AI power plants.
Every AI facility must be burned to the ground
because this is the kind of bullshit.
Oh my God, I know, right?
Oh, fuck, fuck.
I'll keep digging into my own grave, 600.
- For 600, the Simpsons episode where Homer goes to space,
Paul can quote the entire rake scene on command.
Oh God, I hope this is just an episode number.
- I know, it's gotta be Deep Space Homer.
- Oh, okay.
- But.
- That's Deep Space Homer.
- Okay.
See, now you're friends with AI again.
- Look at you go.
- No, I'm not.
(laughing)
- You love AI.
- Do you love it, huh?
- I'm not convinced.
Does the rake thing, the sideshow Bob's rakes happen
in Deep Space Homer?
- I don't know.
I'm going Paul for 800.
(laughing)
Paul's go-to improv comedy rule/theorem
that states there are no mistakes, only blank.
- Opportunities, we'll see what they say here.
Opportunities.
- Opportunities, there's happy accidents.
I mean, I'll say opportunities.
That is what he says.
- Gifts.
(laughing)
- I am so on board with this.
Matt, you're up.
- Ice cream, 200 please.
- The top selling ice cream flavor
in the United States year after year.
- Well, according to AI, it's gonna be like strained peas.
- Strained peas Neapolitan.
- Strained peas.
- I'll go with vanilla.
- That's fucking garbage.
- No, I'm sorry, it's strained peas.
(laughing)
- Holy shit.
- It is vanilla.
- Paul.
- I'll try Matt for 800, let's go crazy.
- All right, daily double.
- Yeah, here's where I win.
- How well do you know me, Paul?
I'll be so upset if you get this wrong.
(laughing)
- In what decade did Matt last send a dick?
In 2013, Matt absolutely lost his mind
watching Penn and Teller debut
their jaw-dropping new version
of this classic stage illusion,
one they had spent over a decade perfecting,
involving a live stick of dynamite
and a bullet catch gone terrifyingly real.
- What?
- This is just slop, this is just nothing.
- I mean, this is, I'm gonna say bullet catch.
- Let's try it.
It's the bullet catch, well done, Paul.
- The bullet catch is in the question,
and it's obviously wrong, there's no dynamite.
- There's no dynamite.
- Gone terrifyingly real?
- What the fuck?
- The bullet catch was definitely not debuted in 2013.
- Oh my God.
- That's great.
- Good lord.
- It's me, I'll try, Jacob for 800.
Jacob's favorite style of knife for everyday carry,
originally designed by Bob Loveless in the 1960s.
(laughing)
What?
Who is Bob Loveless?
- You know, your favorite style of knife.
- He had to be a Leatherman, right?
- Did he indeed make knives?
- Is this a Leatherman?
- No, it could be like a Leatherman,
it could be like a Switchblade.
- I bet it's a Leatherman because it's--
- It could be a--
- Well, who the fuck knows?
- Oh, no, no, 60s, I'm gonna say butterfly knife.
- Oh, there you go.
- I'm gonna go butterfly knife.
A drop point or a hunter knife.
(laughing)
- You don't even know your own favorite knife?
Come on, Jacob.
- Apparently not, apparently not.
(laughing)
- Matt! - That's a shit.
- Ice cream, 400.
- This ancient civilization around 2000 BC
is credited with the earliest known ice desserts
made from fruit and snow.
- The Ice Maniacs.
- The Ice, show me the Ice Maniacs.
(laughing)
- I'll pass.
- Paul.
- Pass.
- It's me.
Is it, this is the Chinese, Chinese did a lot of things.
I'll pass though.
Fuck.
(laughing)
- It was the Chinese.
- It's just the Chinese, I just,
I didn't believe in myself, everyone.
Believe in yourself, that's the message from today's show.
Paul.
- I'll take Matt for 600.
- Daily Double.
- Both the Daily Doubles.
(laughing)
- They were on the bottom two questions for Matt.
Bruce Springsteen's debut 1973 album
that gave us "Blinded by the Light" and "Spirit in the Night".
- Oh, Jesus.
Was this--
- Unfortunately, Paul, unlike the last question,
the answer's not in the question.
- No, it's not, okay.
I was gonna go with Bruce Springsteen, but--
- No, no.
Paul, if I was to say hello to you, that's a form of--
- Greeting.
- Uh-huh.
- Greetings from--
- Yes.
- Yep.
- New Jersey City, where he famously started his career.
- Oh.
- This could be the tripping spot.
- Asbury Park?
- Oh!
Is that the album it's called?
- Greetings from Asbury Park?
- Greetings from, I'm sorry, Paul,
it's Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
I'm sorry you got that incorrect.
- Paul's.
- I'm sorry, Paul.
- Oh, boy.
- It's me, I'll try ice cream for 800.
- Oh, you really dinged him on New Jersey?
- He didn't get New Jersey, the AI said it was wrong.
- Was it, is it just Greetings from Asbury Park
or is it Asbury Park, New Jersey?
- It is Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey.
- Oh, okay.
- But everyone calls it, everyone calls it
the Greetings from Asbury Park or Greetings for short.
While we're here, famously, is because Springsteen,
his whole band left after the riots
and went and started making money
with Southside Johnny in North Carolina.
So Springsteen started making money
doing to the New York Village and doing the Dylan route.
They wanted to be the next Dylan,
but he got his band back together for it
and they were still pressuring him
to be like a New York Village musician.
So he insisted the title of the first album
be called Greetings from Asbury Park, New Jersey
as a fuck you to the record company.
- Okay.
- Oh, I like that.
- Yeah.
- I also like that Southside Johnny got a little-
- Anytime we can bring in Southside Johnny, you know,
we are the number, we are by far
the number one Southside Johnny podcast.
- Easily, easily the number one Southside Johnny.
- And we can probably easily get him for next to confess.
So those things are also true.
(laughing)
- I don't know.
- I mean, honestly, the fact that we haven't called him up
for a churn out at a tyrannies.
- That's the move.
- He might've just been downstairs
for one of the turnouts.
- You'd packed the whole place.
- Oh, absolutely.
- He might've been there anyway.
(laughing)
The record holding number of scoops balanced
on a single cone Guinness of 2023 within five.
(laughing)
37.
- Good guess.
- 125.
- It's my left nut.
What are these?
Just like little pancakes of fucking ice cream.
- Little pancake ice cream.
- Bullshit.
- Matt.
- Let's do Jacob.
- Don't worry, Matt, there aren't any Daily Doubles left.
- Jacob 600.
- The NFL team, Jacob bleeds black and gold for.
Their home dome is now called the Caesar Superdome.
- That would be the Falcons, the Atlanta Falcons.
- Of course, the Falcons.
- The Saints.
I'm sorry, Matt, that's the New Orleans Saints.
The New Orleans Saints is actually the correct answer.
- You are taking me on that.
- Paul.
(laughing)
Paul, you're up.
- You are ruthless today, Jacob, ruthless.
- I'm sorry, Matt, it's the AI.
It's not me, it's the AI.
- I'll do Matt for 400.
- Matt's home state, whose nickname is the Garden State,
despite what you might think from the turnpike.
- New Jersey.
- Wow.
- I'm sorry, it's brand New Jersey.
- Sparkling New Jersey, still has that New Jersey smell.
It's me, I'll try ice cream, 600.
The ice cream chain founded in Burlington, Vermont in 1978,
whose flavors include cherry Garcia and fish food.
It's fish with a pH, fish.
I believe that would be Ben and/or Jerry's.
Ben and Jerry's.
- Ben and Jerry's.
- I'm sorry, there's no end or there.
(laughing)
- No or, it's just an end.
Matt, you got Matt or Jacob?
- I guess I'll go with Jacob for it,
or just so I can break even.
- The brand of bourbon Jacob keeps on his bar cart
that's distilled in Kentucky,
but named after a Louisiana parish.
- What?
- Do you know the answer to this, Jacob?
- I don't own a bar cart.
- Is there an answer to this?
(laughing)
I don't even have a bar cart.
- I can't even think of a parish name to name.
- I mean, there's like Orleans, Treme, Rapids.
- I'll pass.
- Paul.
- This has to be a Kentucky.
- Or it'd be a bourbon with a Louisiana name?
- Yeah, pass.
- A Louisiana parish name?
Yeah, I have no idea, pass.
Oh, Jefferson's Ocean, or Jefferson's.
- Yeah, but you wouldn't have gotten Jefferson's.
I probably could have come up with Jefferson's,
but I wouldn't have come up with Jefferson's Ocean.
- Yeah, Jefferson's has other, not Ocean,
but they've got other Jefferson's, yeah, yeah.
I do have some Jefferson's in the bar.
- Cart? - Well, there you go.
- I don't have a bar cart, I just have a bar.
- We gotta build you a bar cart before next time.
- I do need a bar cart.
Paul closing out the category and the game, Matt, for 200.
This duo has performed together at the Rio All-Suite Hotel
and Casino in Las Vegas since 2001.
- Penn and Teller.
- Ziegfried and Roy.
- Ziegfried and Roy, Penn and Teller.
I really like that Ben and Jerry's,
the answer for Ben and Jerry's earlier
had the ampersand in it, but the Penn and Teller answer
has the word and spelled out.
- Good old AI coming through.
- Yeah, that's right.
That is the game, Paul wins with 600
because he loves AI the most.
Matt's in second with negative 400,
and I'm in third with negative 1600.
That's from OG Scoop, thank you, OG Scoop.
- OG, yes, thank you.
- That AI Scoop, and he worked out just fine.
- OG, I'll say this is a fine experiment.
I don't know if it's worth replicating.
- We don't do it all the time.
- No, let's not do it anymore.
Let's leave AI alone.
Let's stop fucking with AI.
Hey, Matt, how is Penn doing, by the way?
He hurt his ankle, yeah?
- He did, he broke his ankle.
He had to cancel all the shows this weekend,
and then of course he canceled the podcast,
so I only know from a couple of text exchanges
that he's doing okay, he's on the mend.
- I remember distinctly, it really hit me again yesterday
when I read this news and they had to cancel shows.
I remember distinctly on, I believe it was March 12th
of 2020, right before the shit hit the fan,
and I was talking with one of the bartenders at Absinthe,
and we were talking, 'cause there were rumors of things
having to go on pause for a moment.
We didn't know what was up, and I said,
"Well, I'll tell you this.
"I just found out that Penn and Teller
"have put their shows on hiatus,
"and there has to be some real shit for that to happen,
"so I think things are coming down."
And sure enough, the next day and a half later, kaboom.
- Yeah.
- They were a little bit ahead of the curve.
- But it all turned out to be fine.
Paul, as usual, was incorrect about that.
- Everything's just been up, up, up, up, up since then.
- That's right.
- Turned down, it was a hoax, and we're not still doing--
- Me and my negative Nancy thinking.
Well, I mean, I am a little concerned
that I could explode at any minute,
having had many vaccines and updates, but whatever.
- But the government's following your every move now
that it has, you know, Microsoft--
- That's true, I do have lots of tracers in here.
I'm basically a walking air tag, so.
(laughing)
- I've said that about you for years.
- Oh, we're getting a shout out here.
Hey, Paul, Nick's son is playing basketball
at Madison County tonight.
Go Eagles, beat the Indians, let's go.
- Go for it, yeah, beat the Indians.
Of course they're still the Indians.
We're not gonna change that.
(laughing)
Of course my fucking alma mater, Madison Central Indians,
are still the Indians.
Good lord.
I will say, it did give me that one wonderful moment
when, and John has told the story before, I think too,
but you know, I was able to, during a homecoming parade,
the Latin club, I chained up my brother
to a giant papier-mache rock.
And, 'cause we were the Latin club and we did the myth of,
who is it that brought fire to the--
- Yeah, yeah. - Prometheus?
Prometheus. - That's it.
- So, and he was cursed to have a vulture pick his liver out,
or an eagle eat his liver every night.
So, we dressed John up as the opposing team,
chained to a rock. (laughing)
And us, with a hatchet, like an Indian hatchet,
chopping his liver while he was chained to a rock.
- Oh my god. - It was,
I got to drive my brother getting his liver chopped
(laughing)
by another football player.
Down the main street of Madison County, Richmond, Kentucky,
that was a fuckin' highlight.
- Yeah, John says he's not show business.
That's a starring role.
That goes on the resume.
That better be on his resume somewhere.
- It should be, yeah.
Opposing team Prometheus.
(laughing)
- I have another list here,
another modest list here, Jacob, are we?
- We're figuring out what's going on with the list thing.
But yeah, we're gonna keep on thankin' people.
- All right, well, I wanna thank-
- We're getting to the bottom of everything.
- I wanna thank Ben Jaffer for creating this podcast.
- Thanks, Ben.
Get well soon.
- I wanna thank Elaine Hayhurst and Katie Hurd
for stopping by to talk about the Sharples parody musical.
- Fantastic to have them there.
I do, I love it when we do stay nice and contemporary
with Vegas Entertainment News.
- Yeah, absolutely.
And I wanna thank the following people
who have all been paraded by Paul Mattingly
through the town to create the Prometheus myth
they have had their livers packed out with axes and birds.
Danny Allwine, Dark Shift, Dave Serial,
Dave Hanson, Dave Peterson, Dave Slusher,
David A. Small, David Grassi, David K,
David M. Rikov, Risho?
I don't know how you pronounce that, R-I-C-H-O-U-X.
David Smith, David Sorensen, Deb Tytle, Dennis Hand,
Derek Dozier, Dippin' Dots Jack, Dimitri Stepanchov.
Yeah, I got that one right, too.
- Yeah.
- Doc Scoop, Don Donnie, Dr. Tobias Scoopay,
and Ed Rosen, thank you so much.
- These people, just like Jacob,
have tried everything on a Blackstone,
including sucking his dick for magic tricks.
Emily Relf, Emma Antonka, Truck the Pony,
Emma Gregsten, Eunice Raccoon.
Finn Steffenson, Freeze Dried Scoop, Dave Enright,
Gage Saucido, Galen Diggs, Gavin Bristo,
Gaspacho Scoop, Gene Zink, Genetic Scoop,
Gerardo Garcia, Greg Reckton, HS Float Water,
AKA Whiff a Scoop Ball, Hoosier Scoop,
ENA Chapman, J Rock, Jake Schneider, and James Fox.
And I wanna thank the following scoops
who all put thumbtacks in Tara Palsh's boots.
That's James Hubbell, James McPhee,
Janine Lanker, Jason Horcastes, Jason Speckland,
Jason Street, Jason Vasquez, Jeff Ackerman, Jeff Bizarre,
Jennifer Reyes Carrero, Jenny Ebar, Jeremy Hudson,
Jesse Miller, Jesse Rain, Jim Inmanu,
Jimmy Sloanina, Joe Magistralio, John Carter,
John Jacob Schubert Heimer Schmitt, Johnny Parker,
and Jordan Smith.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do appreciate you.
- We do. - Mestrangelo.
We should've switched lists, Jacob.
I had that one down.
- We should have.
Mestrangelo, that's it.
I hear these names and know them,
but then you see them and you just have no idea.
- You're on the spot, you're on the spot.
All eyes are on you with these thank you lists.
- This is the Wednesday episode, yeah?
So this goes out Thursday, is that right?
Or Wednesday? - Correct.
- That's right.
- All right, so I wanna give a heads up to scoops.
We're aiming for a Friday night Zoom hang.
9.30 EST, my time.
So it'll be 7.30 on the West Coast,
but then we'll go for a couple hours
of playing some games and hanging out and chatting.
I'll get the-- - You said that'll be
Friday, Paul? - That'll be Friday night.
- Friday, January 23rd.
- That is correct.
Friday, January 23rd, this coming week.
And I will send out the invites through Patreon shortly
after our second recording here
and try and get that all squared away.
Leon is coming aboard, thank you, Leon,
to help lead us through some games.
It's gonna be a real fun night.
Yeah, we're all gonna have a good time.
These hangouts have been exceptionally fun,
so I'm looking forward to it.
And please hop on board and join us on Friday night.
And I don't have to, I'm on vacation right now,
so I don't have to work.
I don't have to worry about getting up early.
So I'll be well rested and feeling bright-eyed and bushy-tailed.
Who knows, I might go for a while playing games, who knows?
And hopefully Matt and Jacob can drop by
at some point in the evening, even just to say hi.
- Yeah! - When is it?
- It's gonna be Friday night, 730, your time starting.
- I will be performing a show in Cincinnati, I believe.
- There you go.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, that's why we're doing a double today,
is 'cause Matt can't do it on Friday.
- Yeah, so January 23rd, I'm in Lexington.
January 24th, Cincinnati.
January 25th, Bloomington, Indiana.
Then off to Chicago, and January 27th,
I'll play in the comedy club there.
28th, Green Bay, Wisconsin.
29th, Madison, Wisconsin.
And January 30th, Milwaukee.
And January 31st, Wabash, Indiana.
- I'll also give a shout out to the 31st,
that's Saturday the 31st.
Myself and my friend Sarah are gonna be teaching
my free improv workshop that night.
- Oh nice!
- And I've already put the stuff up
on Scoop Group and whatnot.
Appreciate everybody retweeting and sending out the word
to people you might know if you're in the area,
or you might even find yourself traveling to the area.
It's out there near Pittsburgh in,
oh, what's the place called?
I can't remember the name of the crazy little town.
But yeah, look it up online, it's right there.
It's on Scoop Group and whatnot, but it's free class.
Two hours of fun with me and Sarah teaching some improv.
Come check us out, hang out, come see me.
It'll be great times.
- Remember, there are no bad things that happen in improv,
only gifts.
(laughing)
- Thanks for listening everybody.
Stay safe out there and we'll see you soon.
- We'll see you soon.
(upbeat music)
- I am hoping the weather holds
for these next couple of weeks.
It's gonna be kinda crazy out here.
(upbeat music)
- Come on, yeah.
- See ya!
- Trenum, that's the town.
- Trenum.