Well hello there it is my favorite part of the show this is the time where we get to
thank you the ice cream truck drivers who are the ice cream truck drivers well I will
tell you the ice cream truck drivers are the folks who deliver this fucking ice cream straight
to your fucking ear holes sorry I just got distracted by Matt's son at Darvin furniture
the holidays are where our employees really shine why because at Darvin the employees
own the company hi it's will harris for darvin furniture as employee owners we know that what's
good for the customer is good for the company and what's good for the company is good for us
and that's why darvin's employee owners go the extra mile do whatever they can to make sure
that when you walk out the door whether you buy something or not you'll have a smile on your face
darvin employee owned and proud of it signing on to the zoom chat if you want to be an ice cream
truck driver just like these five folks head over to preaching fun.com preaching fun.com is where
you want to go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save may be your
own oh we don't have a new list yet it's a new month and uh we'll get to all that later here's
a show hey johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah i'd love to great let's go
we have a murderous role of old school suits in today's news right yeah we do
it's time for matt maddly's ice cream socials sitting in pittsburgh that's paul maddly sitting
in california i think that's matt nottley i'm jacob in las vegas we're preaching fun uh yes
indeed my son has entered the chat uh we're recording my hotel room so they might as well
hear but basically i have to behave might as well put him in here so you guys have to behave it's
basically nobody no the gloves are off i've given your son a copy of powers it's over i've he's
fully corrupted at this point that's true we can actually check in with them about that okay yeah
circles on circles circles on circles uh oh i guess if you meet yourself it'll mess up everything
yeah yeah yeah you have to come over here if you want to talk
you can hide i think you can highlight your screen but you have to come over here to talk
into my microphone let's see so uh did paul corrupt you are you now are you bringing that uh are you
gonna bring that dirty magazine to school and show all the kids and uh are you gonna uh
there's no wrong answer here i actually i actually haven't read the comic yet
it's that tantalizing that looks at the pictures i know that's right that's right that's not what i
mean i haven't i haven't read it i haven't looked at the pictures in fact in the car when i was
scrolling i went from back to front so when paul picked it up i was like oh wait did he think i was
looking at that no honestly i didn't even look at that i i honestly i didn't even i really i was i
was like oh crap yeah sometimes there's boobs and powers but it's not it's nothing whatever
man paul stands by his decision i do stand by my decision it's a fantastic comic book it's by one
of the ultimate comic book creators brian michael bendis and uh yeah i stand by brian michael bendis
can't do convince young boys to actually read the thing and not just look at the pictures that's not
true i think he's inspired a generation he's again he's the guy behind miles morales he's uh he's had
more than his share of successes um so yeah yeah yeah so yeah well uh you know we're in arizona
we're in mesa just phoenix phoenix adjacent mesa arizona and so i took my uh basically we looked at
the cost of the my wife is is about to help relaunch disco and so yes me being away figured
whether whether we would uh um you know hire a bunch of baby child care stuff i have a bunch
of babysitters or i just take them with me and so uh you know i did what any dad would do i was be
like boys this is the difference between the las vegas strip club and a phoenix strip club and i
took them out to show them the different ways um but uh more hands on so yeah we road tripped it
and uh we came out here to uh it is the uh um paul is holding up his phone that says the comic
book that we mentioned earlier well people were asking in the chat i'm just yeah you're just
just showing people powers all right this is what this is the bonus content you get when you tune
into the stream this is yeah this is the regular not bonus content that everybody else gets when
they don't do it what do you mean but this is incentivizing more subscriptions it's cheap
if they hear us talking about your phone you can see my phone it's three now it's three okay three
bucks we have god god inflation never stops three bucks you can see my phone yeah um uh yeah yeah so
uh we road tripped it out here uh you know all the times we would bitch about the vegas heat
and then our listeners from arizona would go like whatever dude check it out check out our
our our neighborhood i used to be like it can't be that different it is oh no they're right it's
so yeah they're right it is that much more it's hotter here i understand people moving to las
vegas there is stuff in las vegas there are things to do there's work there's jobs there's fun there's
all these things arizona doesn't have any of those things they're just hotter
it's less fun and hotter yeah we gotta uh as my youngest said it's a free sauna free sauna yeah
one of the most miserable times that i've ever experienced was when we did a star trek promotion
at a diamondbacks game it was 108 degrees we were all wearing our full costumes
we're walking around this was like a fan thing happening at the baseball game it was a promotional
event for the experience and it was like where your star trek stuff to uh to the baseball game
yes and one of our cling-ons threw out the first pitch and didn't attach his gauntlet properly and
threw his gauntlet as well part of his costume fell off i was like ah amateur hour how embarrassing
get it together kermash that's like god kermit that's where the expression is toss his gauntlet
with this fastball came from right that's right that's right that's right yeah it's similar to
throw out the baby with the bath water it's the same the same family of sayings uh but it was
crazy like after that day of walking around we were just drenched so much not muting themselves
oh we got them they're back they're back uh we were just we were funky it was it was gross so yeah
and and like uh you know in vegas there's a whole you know oh you could cook an egg on the sidewalk
or da da da but out in phoenix it's like oh yeah i i can look out the window and see shit melting
like like the traffic lights are drooping have you seen stuff like that matt oh yeah uh no they
figured it out they know how hot it is here so nothing's drooping nothing's drooping they know
how to build their their just man it was drooping 20 years ago we went uh we went uh in fact uh we
finished up the show last night i basically want to finish in time to make sure the kids go swimming
at night this is got oh yeah we got a hotel pool and so uh did you explain that to the audience
as you were rushing through all the tricks just pick up the card already all right we gotta go
we gotta we're going swimming tiktok we're going swimming guys come on panther no panth
uh so uh we uh yeah yeah so we were swimming and even at night uh 10 o'clock at night the
pool was still wicked warm from the day oh yeah uh out here a nice sometimes it's nice sometimes
a nice gooey warm pool for you it just feels it just feels like it feels like pee it does that's
why i like it but then you let me get that pee pool but then don't get that that that fun thing
of when you pee in the pool i don't know i just i just want to add to it i just want to feel like
i'm contributing you're worried about not feeling the contrast of your own pee that's right that's
right i swim for contrast i like my pool to be 98.6 so that when i pee i just have to feel the
difference in buoyancy would you would that be the only way i can tell would that feel really really
hot it would right yes it'd be yeah 98.6 is nice nice and it's what's real warm it's not a hot tub
it's not hot tub hot yeah my hot tub is at 104 yeah we keep the hot tub at 104 98.6 those it's
it's pretty hot oh we actually dare ourselves to go into the hot tubs of the pool would feel
cool oh smart so even though it was hot out we went into the hot tub and then then went in the
pool and then the pool felt refreshing they had the hot tub on they did they did wow that is
that is surprising i agree in august in arizona it seems like a waste well it's 110 let's fire
up yeah hey some people still have bad backs you know all right you do you you do you
i do i do sit in my hot tub because of my uh because of my bad back so i i do get it a little
bit yeah exactly exactly i did see a fella trying to beat the heat on the las vegas strip the other
day during during my walk i don't remember i told you guys about this guy i don't think i did though
uh he was wearing uh no shoes like i started at the bottom with him and worked my way up just just
observing this person he was wearing no shoes and uh mismatched ankle socks and uh he was wearing
a pair of super mario brothers boxer briefs uh it in lieu of pants uh i haven't told you guys about
this guy right no but i'm just all so far all paul heard was super mario brothers and he was like
yay i'm wearing this shirt paul is currently matching this person that's right i got my crocs
on well you're already beating him then because he did not have shoes okay he was wearing he's
wearing socks he was not wearing pants he was wearing a pair of super mario brothers uh boxer
briefs he was wearing a tank top with uh one arm he had one of his arms through the head hole of
the tank top so he's wearing a tank top but it was like an off the shoulder number it was kind
of kind of nice don't think he was having a day he was just he was punching bricks left and right
hoping a mushroom would pop out of the top of it you have no idea how right you are matt donnelly
because on his left hand he was wearing one blue boxing glove stop it i'm 100 socks no shoes no
pants super mario brothers underwear tank top with his hand through the arm or through the through the
head hole and then a boxing glove scali wall says so a 10 p.m walmart sharper yeah yeah basically
that's this was this was at about six p.m walking down the las vegas strip six and i'll tell you
what six p.m and you know how when you are walking near a person who is um let's say has different
sensibilities than than the average average people i mean they're high maybe they're high maybe they're
homeless maybe they're a little off kilter maybe all of these things like you you see these people
walking and and you kind of you kind of clock them and because they they have kind of a manner
about them that that suggests even without the clothing uh it suggests that they are a little uh
a little off maybe maybe they're not entirely based in reality yeah beating beating their own drum
there you go that one of the most disconcerting things about this man is he was walking along
seemingly just fine if it weren't for his appearance the manner that he was walking he
was walking as though he had somewhere to be he wasn't in a terrible hurry but he was walking with
some purpose just heading down the street i think i know what happened possible i think i know what was a
refugee from a mr beast contest oh that's possible matt now matt what's your theory that is possible i
was gonna say i think what he happened was he found that invincible star where you go and he just went
all over the place and then the star ran out and that's what he looked like when the star finished
and there's like oh he didn't realize how much damage he was doing to himself with the invincibility
exactly even though he was invincible so he was invincible but his his clothes weren't his clothes
were his clothes took a beating yeah he was fine but his clothes really took a beating
no i think there's a new mr beast coming out tomorrow so i'll see it oh there is a new mr beast
episode coming out all right hot drop we can find out if paul's take is correct look into his sweet
dead eyes and obey that guy's a monster our pal neil fisher just wrote a book on that monster
just put out a book i can't wait oh nice i can only imagine he sent it to me uh i should i should
send him an email properly but why don't use the podcast to thank him my kids uh it is it is
fascinating yeah mr book oh by the way uh we talked about this this book on the on the show
several weeks ago if you haven't started reading cults like us by our friend jane borden it is
so fucking good i'm on the audiobook jane reads it it is so good it is so interesting it's so good
i was watching the news superman and going like oh my gosh like this is the thing that she talks
about in her book where they like i did the same thing from the puritans they they demonized
intelligence right yes and people who are who are smarter freer thinkers and so glad we're over that
shit well no she's like you know you think yourself as like you know whatever your policies are if you
think yourself more than open-minded politics you don't think you're you're bought into this but yet
when she breaks down the like that we just love a rebel a rule breaker right and so and we just
like oh that part hits home really hard yeah and so you're like oh every character i like in every
movie and tv is the same thing that i'm hating about the current political climate right and
everything that we do in movies tv about taking brainiacs and saying they're terrible people that
should be ostracized and made fun of and taken care of you know and it's like and then free
thinkers are like not being respected we've lost a complete a complete respect for expertise
it adds a layer in that it makes you uh not care about kind of the the current problems yeah because
a strong man you know a hero is coming yeah yeah we've been we've been conditioned to uh just not
even believe just conditioned to understand that that a hero is going to come along and they're
going to use some kind of physical violence and they're going to take care of us so i do i do that
uh yeah so so so jane's book's been with me every time i watch tv or movies or bring a book or
whatever it is it has legitimately changed the way that i look that's the last thing i'm going to do
watch tv movies then maybe read a book right right but yeah and uh and also it's helping me be a
better uh better parent and as one of my children listens on but like the idea that we teach
moralistic storytelling just better her point that we teach moralistic storytelling and therefore
good things happen to good people and bad things happen to bad people so things go wrong you turn
in and start hating yourself and blaming yourself versus other cultures that uh teach you know
fortune right like fortune switch both ways things go good things go bad you know you're not in
control of that and so sometimes life isn't fair but it is consistent right and that it's just going
to swing both ways no matter who you are no matter where you are it's just going to go you're going
to you're going to live a roller coaster and like that's so much better when uh my kids experience
something bad and i then want to beat themselves up like it's it's really important so yeah her
book's incredible cults like us yeah pick it up it's great it's very good and it's and it's a very
good read and she does her own uh reading for books on tape so you get to hear her her lovely
her lovely her lovely dulcet tones and i tell you what i tell you one of the uh most fun parts about
listening to her read the book is all of the little asides because she she loves to put the little uh
little comments in on what she's commenting about yeah so she there's there's a little like uh almost
kind of the office moments where she turns the camera and goes like eh see but it's all her talking
it's kind of great and so listening to her do the asides on the audiobook is pretty fantastic yeah
yeah yeah but yeah and like i said we we she's funny we did improv back in the day she was a
powerhouse improviser at the old ucb so yeah awesome stuff i know she's great so we um we drove down
here to uh to so this is mystique dining but not a traditional location this is a this is a collab
with a fever up productions okay uh and they do kind of pop up stuff and so when i got the address
of where we were going i pulled into like this you know like vegas has phoenix and vegas stuff
they have very similar uh architecture so in terms of this kind of like sprawling uh kind of almost
like a warehouse feeling thing where like it's just a bunch of little pods of buildings where
oh yeah you have sweets one through 50 and then the other one's sweets 50 through 80 you know
whatever right that kind of thing and so pulling i go like there can't there can't be a magic show
in here like it's not it wasn't like a storefront there was no kind of whatever this is where the
props for the magic show gets stored and then uh we finally my my uh my son pointed out they found
the logo on the door like no it's there and i was like what oh and then we pull up and uh it's i
would find out later they're like oh yeah well it used to be a church and i was like that still
doesn't explain it like that still doesn't make it it's a weird spot for a church too exactly it's
just it doesn't it doesn't mean uh but but you know these are pop-ups right so they're not looking
for these like you know they're gonna take over a giant theater space so they're not gonna take
anything big out and so uh makes it kind of cool and so when you do walk in it is like a crazy it's
own magic trick it is an instant transformation you walk in and it is this ornate beautiful kind
of like uh dragon themed bar and lounge with this with this parlor in the back and this how yeah
really nice uh that's fine performing uh magic parlor so yeah so that part was super cool the
only problems we couldn't get in uh when we got there and uh oh you weren't uh you weren't cool
enough and it was so hot the guy uh frank this great guy frank was the easy uh opener he's the
close-up magician and uh you know uh helper outer person whatever helper outer person well well he
he's normally just the close-up magician helps work the bar yeah and uh it turned out our house
manager uh his car broke down and so uh he couldn't couldn't get to the the space his car melted
so frank's trying to get things open and i i thought frank worked there and all of a sudden
couldn't get the couldn't get the place open and i was kind of like that's weird uh but he would
never been in this role before but again it was so hot i went to talk to him he goes no no no he
weighs me off and he goes back into his car turns on his air conditioning and he points to his phone
he's like i'm not standing at the eat we're gonna talk air-conditioned car to air-conditioned car
right next to each other that's that is some arizona shit right there i thought you were going
to say that frank invited you to sit in his air-conditioned car with him and you can chat
not even i know he's not letting some hot man come in and take his air you crazy he's on this
giant thermal force enter that yeah he's not he's no idiot he knows he's like i'm happy to
talk to you as long as you sit in your car your carbon footprint is far too large for the occupancy
of my vehicle get the fuck out stay the fuck out so he uh uh so he's having trouble with the door
code but i actually was like oh i i i did the san diego location i'm well aware of the weird
keypad uh logistics of going inside now you know uh you knew the lock yeah so i was like oh let me
give it a shot so i get it open and we go inside and and and it really took me a minute um to figure
out that frank was not uh uh a true staff person but just a magician is he is he is like he's getting
he's putting my kids to work right away he's handing them remotes he's like now see if this
works and see if this works and i think he's being cute and like taking care of my kids while i set
up my show and after this after it was all over he's like no no i i needed their help i didn't
know how to open this place and so i was handing out stuff to be like go figure this out
i wasn't babysitting your kids i needed their help
you know who else needs matt's children to get things done that's the following sponsor today's
show matt manley's ice cream social are brought to you by the fine purveyors makers outfitters
and sources uh a horse is a horse of course of course waiting for hotel wi-fi to work on my phone
also dracula's orange juice today's show is brought to you by dracula's orange juice from laj in 2022
drink dracula's orange juice
hello it's me michael crofford from phantom of the opera and i'd like to talk to you about
oh ah oh oh hello it is me dracula i have killed michael crofford to tell you enter hey scoops a
checkout that's all i need to hear good riddance michael crofford he was low on vitamin c
and easy to kill drink your orange juice that's right dracula can more easily kill you
now here's the thing i really i mean it for me you know i'm selling this stuff because i do i want
you to get your vitamin c but more importantly i want your blood to be sweet and full of valencia
goodness uh pulp or no pulp pulp pulp oh hey scoops a checkout
hey guys i just need a good clean drop of paul yelling pulp like a vampire yeah yeah yeah now
you've got that classic drop of the vampire yelling pulp everybody will know what that
is whenever you need it that's going to be that's going to get that thing you're going to wear a
where a hole in that button uh companion piece to cults like us i would recommend and is and
has been reading this and telling me all about it it is the hot shit right now murderland you
guys know about this one i've heard of this yeah so murder land is the hot business right now
so this is a book this is all about how uh in the uh 60s and 70s the uh oil corporations put
additives in the gas that they knew were poisoning us uh and lead and all that kind of thing mostly
lead and the smelting uh places that were processing lead uh were poisoning everyone
around the smelting area and uh how basically you can trace like people like ted bundy uh and other
serial killers to a certain radius of where these places were seriously seriously and also and just
in general how a generation got poisoned by these uh gasoline additives that they knew were poisoning
people because i've i've heard because i never understood unleaded gas growing up as a kid right
i just heard about the gasoline yeah right uh i oh it was i forget what podcast i was listening to
but i never heard the correlation perhaps not causation perhaps causation who knows of violence
to let uh basically that like because basically we hear stories of our generation of men older
than us right who would tales of just getting into fist fights right like it became like a trope in
every movie we see you go to a bar somebody just pokes your chest and boom you get into a fist fight
and i just remember growing up being like that happened so little as a bartender like so little
and then i didn't know that uh people uh some people think that the lead in gas was actually
why we were so violent yes right and and it was like your president super star mcscoops a lot in
the chat is is pointing out paint as well yeah it was every all the paint stuff and it was paint
everywhere was all lead paint it was so dumb because the reason they put it in the gas there
was a decrease in violence with the with the unleading of gas oh yeah well and there was also
an increase in iq just in general like it just dumbed the whole generation down and here's the
worst thing uh our generation actually got secondhand damage because folks like us who
were born in the 70s uh our mothers had been exposed to this stuff and it turns out that
babies in the womb absorb uh calcium they look for calcium from the mother right and in the taking
of the calcium to not me i looked for booze to build those baby bones well besides booze in here
lady you look for the booze and the calcium those are the two main things so you're looking for
alcohol and you're looking for calcium but when thank you i feel seen when that fetus is calcium
the glory are yours now and forever amen amen but that baby is building its body up
from lead infused calcium deposits and it's basically fucking up the the the fetus and it's
like you know i i don't have to wonder too hard about my hip you know basically turning into mush
after a couple years you know and i i don't know if you guys i i haven't your mom was a huge paint
drinker right well no i but i i i think i've mentioned to you guys before i had back when
i was a kid i had straight up force gump leg braces for a long time when i was a little kid
yes yeah oh yeah i was very pigeon-toed in my leg just recently my my brother found some old home
videos of me walking around as a baby i am the gimpiest motherfucker ever seen i mean i had really
deformed ass legs and hips and shit i'm like fuck man no wonder my stuff is broken down no wonder i
was in such terrible pain also no wonder that they gave you those braces and kind of fixed you like
the hip thing didn't happen till later in life and we didn't know you as a gippy person so we have to
also give some credit where credit is due that they addressed it there was some there was some
addressing but also but clearly one leg was longer than the other and that's part of what the hip
thing was all about and a bunch of stuff but but yeah and that just makes me sad knowing that it's
quite likely that some of that was due to environmental uh lack of environmental protections
oh that little baby the demonizing of breastfeeding and moving up into formula then right that kind of
thing too yeah go back and then all sudden formula is evil yes other stuff and you know whatever i
mean people don't remember when i was when i was a baby my mom my mom was actually encouraged they
said yo breastfeed breastfeed your baby and everything so she would she breastfed me uh but
she would smoke leaded cigarettes while breastfeeding me because that's that's simply what her doctor
recommended that she do she would add lead to unfiltered barbara cigarettes and she would just
smoke those if anyone's stink guy for breastfeeding she'd go punch him right in the face she didn't
care she just no no no like of course like our our our system of whether we do or don't care of
healthy products and how that affects our physical health i get it is strange to me the idea like i
think of getting in fights feisty cuffs yeah right as an emotional thing not a not a physical thing
do you know what i mean like i think it's weird oh i do yeah i see what you mean that's that's the
distinction i find strange is that like i'm pumping gas and something i go like what'd you say
what'd you say man like this is what i find strange is that like like we were getting into
fisticuffs more that's why we got an electric car so i i wouldn't have to get in as many fights
i just my body just can't take it anymore i'm getting older matt i just can't fight twice a
week every week i need recovery time i do you need me to fight once every two weeks i'm there
but this is the frequency at least for another 10 years i've got i've got to fight a week in me
yeah i find it i find it strange um well i will say on the positive side of nature is healing
perhaps somewhat uh and and i last week went to a flower festival this is the freedom farms flower
festival this is the hippiest bullshit i've ever heard of in my life well i don't know how hippie
i guess it's kind of hippie no no no jacob you get in one autobahn society and you have to go
to these events is that what it is they're keeping score right oh you didn't go to that flower
festival i thought you were a member of the autobahn society i was a little trepidatious
because it was freedom farms and anytime anything comes with the moniker of freedom or liberty or
anything like that my alarm bells just go off because as we all know whenever a bill is passed
in this country that's something like the child protection and free cotton candy act it explicitly
somewhere in the bill states all children under 13 should be executed and cotton candy should be
banned right it's like it's always the opposite of what they're saying in these after this recording
i'm taking my kids to cracker barrel for breakfast good good i just found out they're they just put
legislation to rename it america barrel america barrel yeah okay i just thought they were going
to rename it to a white people barrel just barrel just better it's always just been a barrel why do
we have to qualify for who eats there i mean honky barrel kind of rolls off the tongue right we can
work with hunky barrel definitely it's a self-selecting sample already oh it's so i i mean i do love that
food um hunky barrel was my uh college band we were hunky barrel it's open for hootie yeah yeah
yeah after we won the battle of the bands we got to open for hootie you know honky barrel is what
bozo the clown used to call those little cups that you'd throw the ping-pong ball into and if you get
up to 13 you win the prize the big prize yeah uh so you went you went to okay uh it's a flower
festival uh freedom farms flower festival yes whoa the f the classic fff yep uh the quad f
fantastic four uh whose idea was this you are ants i'll give you i'll give you three guesses
and the first two do not count so it was paul's idea it was ants but paul was a target on instagram
and honey look at this what's your shoes on quick it's a flower festival holy shit in the middle in
the dead middle of summer one of the hottest days let's fucking go calm down for five for
for flower for festival for four flower festival anyway it was cute it was kind of cool um
you drive up it was adorable it was adorable it was pretty adorable so we went on the first day
so we got good pickings because this is the thing they have rows and rows of flowers
just growing out there and you can just go and pick flowers as many as you want
20 bucks get all the flowers you want all the flowers you can eat within reason all the flowers
you can eat there were sunflowers so i suppose you could eat some of that they say this is one of the
last all you can pick uh uh flower festivals most of them are retro you know going retro and they're
becoming uh flower halls they're they're representing the flower halls that was a really
clumsily constructed joke about las vegas uh getting rid of all the buffets and replacing
them with food halls um oh oh i was spelling it h-a-u-l that's what i was thinking too flower
hall i'm gonna uh i'm gonna go to cracker bell i'll see you guys all right matt's gone uh so
you get on a little tractor and it's got they've got it it's fancy like the tractors pull in these
fancy people wagons it would be a really cool little hayride kind of thing so we do to do to
do up to the up to the place and up top they've got like i said rows and rows of flowers that you
can just go through and pick and then they had some live music playing they had farm animals you
could go and check out they had some food places they had really good barbecue pardon me barbecue
and um like crafts we bought the barbecue place who's i'm trying to figure out who's got the
friendship where they figured out how to how to like you know this you know what this flower
festival needs some barbecue it was called effing good barbecue oh good the f also they stuck with
the f they stuck with the f-f effing good barbecue and their mascot is a like looks looks basically
like a wild boar as the grim reaper so by way of my understanding this and a reaper boar this pig
reaper god is slaughtering his brethren to provide us with with hog meat for eating which i'm cool
with i think there's something there's something interesting in there with like oh wow this shit
must be real good this guy knows his pig he is a pig you know even the pigs eat it like you go to
a cannibal restaurant you want a guy who actually eats there yeah you know i mean you don't want to
just go you know you enjoy those flowers can i interest you in some human ribs exactly well i
don't know are you are you eating them i am oh then yeah if they're good enough for you i want
their damn falling off the bone oh what i mean is like again we are we are we're making fun of the
almost conflictive nature of this barbecue place being at this flower festival i just want to know
how that friendship was made like right i don't know i think i think it's a combination of
proximity that is darren from effing barbecue kind of uh meet cynthia from the flower festival
and go like right oh i'll bring my brisket it that's exact names are frederick and francine
clearly it's a proximity thing i think it's mostly proximity thing because you had that you had like
this really great kettle corn that i got oh okay i do like a good kettle corn holy fuck the best
kettle corn i've ever had and then to top it all off how much kettle corn do you want when you're
eating kettle corn do you want like the big the big package of it because i want like a handful of
it and i'm really happy with about a handful of kettle corn no no no no no but the two bucks you're
just worried about what kettle waste is that what your concern is i bought the medium there it is
that ranch slunk has got it there the pig grilling out for richard scary uh the uh that's an awesome
image uh the i want i bought the eight dollar medium bag and after i was after i was home eating
this freshly popped stuff i was like i should have bought the giant bag because this is it wasn't
enough this is the best and and i was saving half for ann so i was just like i'm tearing through
this stuff uh so oh i'm i'm see malia saying she she asked her husband to go to the flower festival
last weekend this is what she didn't ask her in pennsylvania interesting surprise surprise oh
interesting can you believe it can you believe it anyway uh it's probably it's probably fairly well
picked over at this point as they say uh but no the big topper the big topper her husband said no
by the way i love you matt has more willpower than i what can i say um malia's husband and i
would get along just fine to tell her about the barbecue what happened well there's that and
the big topper amish donuts on site real deal amish donuts to the point where there were little amish
kids running around rumspringer style chasing building little barn chasing the tractor just
giggling talking in whatever language they speak what do they speak oh yeah yeah uh pennsylvania
dutch right yeah i was gonna say it's a dutch a lot of dutch i'm just just like they were just
running around giggling in dutch well i don't think it's dutch i think the people who speak
dutch can't understand them i sure as fuck good yeah and you don't even speak dutch i don't even
speak dutch uh yeah so i don't know which is really german yeah exactly turn the page says
it's german yeah uh so it was it was fantastic uh just seeing all this it's a version of older
german yeah it's like ancient german the the language of the druids uh so i am i am more
excited for the sequel to spinal tap than i want to be what are we talking about here cinnamon sugar
what are we doing what are we doing on these donuts name name your desire frost and cream
done everything under the sun man they had so variety of donuts yes i was shocked shocked at
the variety were they made to order or were they were they they were well they were making them
fresh on site and then you could just uh pick up but i mean you're you're standing three feet from
the the donut boiling vat they're doing it yeah they're just making it man they're just cranking
out the cranking out the fucking donuts and it was so good it was so good i'm just picking myself
like laid out after a belly full of brisket and like 11 donuts and be like i'm so glad we came to
the flower festival this flower festival was so worth it this is what country fairs are like man
that's what that's what ham days is like you go and you get the pancake breakfast in the morning
then you get the ham in the afternoon then you get the barbecue at night it's just it's just
all food how many people are here it was just like is this is this is i'm gonna say there were
probably well there was paul there was an malia wasn't there so that's still just two i'm just
boys speaking gibberish i'm gonna guess there were three to five hundred people bopping around
so you're part right some big grass lot big big lot everyone you park in a parking lot big parking
lot and then they had some overflow parking and then everybody just walks up to the tractor and
then zips back they had two tractors man all these people like roller coasters and shit they're
trying too hard flower festival yeah i mean there's a field there's some flowers there's some barbecue
and some donuts what else do you want it's it was really easy oh there's a oh somebody's magic
shells tell me about uh long john's uh oh in lancaster pennsylvania uh it's worth the five
hour one-way drive okay all right i mean further up in the chat there they were talking about the
pennsylvania dutch uh and i never i never knew this turn the page was saying in the chat and
oh g scoop was was chiming in as well that it's uh misheard so the the dutch is apparently a
bastardization of like deutsch oh so it's i don't know you're speaking dutch or something
it's all german yeah yeah i don't know uh while we're putting out things in the chat i'll just
point out uh uh scoop beard none says it always amazes me that matt and jacob look like their
bodies match their voice and then there's paul it always shocks me wonderful people i don't know
what that means i don't know my body doesn't match my voice wait do you want to describe
i guess cool that i'm curious describe who you expect i sound like a thinner man yeah do you
sound like a nerdy i sound like a thinner guy i have to put on my full-blood mila to uh
to get people to understand my girth are you i was confused by that post as well but not because of
any of that because they called me jake i sometimes still call you out once in a while and i don't
know why i don't know what creates the jake comes out every now and then yeah but before to type it
you gotta mean it to type it scoop beer none are you able to unmute yourself or
now are you at work or something no no i'm uh here oh wow you sound so different than
what i expected but what what what did you think paul would look like by his voice
well and uh i i it took a while before i saw him in pictures stuff i heard him a bunch of times
before i started looking up how you guys looked and i thought he was
more fit i guess more fit he sounds like a more fit what i mean you sign like a really fit guy
trapped in the not so fit guy's body that's essentially what i am that's what i am yeah no
no no honestly look look look seriously i've been working at the targa i got some serious
definition happening suddenly guns all you got i got them guns man i got these traps these traps
ain't no joke these traps go for the the pen diet and uh keep it for uh like four or five
months oh they don't lose the traps i know i wouldn't i wouldn't lose the traps no yeah no
it's always i'll just say this scoop beer none just turned on his camera and he does look how
he sounds uh yeah i'm not surprised by how he looks at all i can see myself so but where are you
almost eight o'clock in sweden gottenberg uh at the barbecue going oh man that looks amazing
ah it just looks like perfect weather for it too living better than i am i can tell you that
don't ever make it better if you pushed out your amish donut kit and roll that up next to that
i see the barbecue i don't see the flower festival well beer none no not much i appreciate that you
think i sounded healthier i think i i don't know i think that's true i think i'm just a fairly
healthy guy with a little too much weight on me you don't eat vegetables let's just i don't eat
vegetables i hate them and i am an emotional eater i'm an emotional eater have been since i was a kid
that's kind of the thing you know i don't eat because i'm hungry i eat because i want you know
i eat because it makes me feel uh less nervous and upset i don't do drugs i don't drink so i guess
that's kind of the thing uh i don't know all i know is scoop beer none's wife or girlfriend
or someone came out and they turned it off like that i don't want you to uh show off our house
we gotta keep it safe we gotta keep it safe all of our listeners that can easily stock sweden
for its different locations yeah but beer none's right and i should if i our show is infamous our
show is infamous for people casing houses to rob in sweden we have a lot of geo what's it called
geosloots or whatever it's called if anyone comes here if they can chase them what are you making
what are you making on your grill uh well uh some sausages and a club steak that's not unwrapped
yet but uh some carrots uh some uh what is called uh well grilled carrot don't sleep on it paul
don't sleep on a carrot sound carrot is solid beautiful well you guys have a nice little feast
going on out there i'm trying to do the last uh day of vacation oh nice got it got it well i hope
it's a good one back to work huh oh so sorry what do you do out in sweden uh i am an electrical
engineer uh consultant working for an oil refinery working for wow refinery an oil refinery all right
all right wow that's that's important yeah people like gas and diesel and stuff and uh we just uh did
a well an expansion for a bio uh fuel so we're taking uh bio uh i feel like uh like like what is
that like facts uh from uh uh uh what do you call uh plants and uh animals oh really oh great great
and make uh jet fuel diesel uh regular gas and uh well does ethanol fit in that is it oh propane
no no no they they had an uh ethanol plant but it wasn't uh didn't make money so they just
ethanol is mainly a u.s thing right does anyone else really do ethanol do any other countries
really do a lot of ethanol we have our we have our uh first primaries in iowa just to make sure
that we keep ethanol as a subsidized thing in america so yeah yeah for some reason we love
ethanol here that's what they fail to do in sweden they they fail to leverage it politically to make
it that's what it was yeah it's well everything's political but still yeah i understand that iowa is
also going to start being the first primary for sweden that'll be a nice change i'm not sure they're
welcome the swedes famously hate iowa no no we come visit how long how long have you been there
at the company oh well i started my company five and a half years ago okay uh so has a lot changed
in that industry over the last five years well there was a lot of more money made in uh the
in uh carbon uh well fossil fuel uh businesses oh yeah starting from around
yeah corona and going through uh the ukraine thing oh that makes sense sure
so it's uh well pretty much the same through corona uh when i started i got in there in
2019 okay and uh then uh they started the big uh bio refining thing and uh well putting got a bit
too uh grabby and changed the whole world and then the the crude oil market and the the fuel market
bumped a lot so it was like a good uh a good margin was around four or five dollars per barrel
and then it swooped up to 30 got it so they made the refinery made uh around uh so i know i know
there's a language i know there's a language barrier but uh so but i think it's fair to say
you're a fan of pudin and what he's done politically it's helped you out that's what i'm here well
in the same way that you hate uh your home states and everything around you and uh
children your wife and uh parents and you don't have any difficulties coping with your mother
that's how they say yes in sweden so in that way yes
thank you thank you for coming on scooper and i appreciate it thanks bernard thank you guys i will
try to live up to my the sound of my voice i will i will endeavor to uh to to lose to lose some
foundation who you sound like well you know there was a time there was a time way back in the aughts
that i wasn't i got really focused on my health and i dropped to right at like 205 and that was
the skinny as i've been in a long time that was good took a lot of effort i could do it again
i suppose uh probably should maybe i will now there you go it's a firm maybe all right let's
take it from here i won't be thinned by scoop fest though you're gonna see big old ball and
scoop fast whenever i talk to other podcasters i always say the mistake that i've made over like
the whatever we've been doing this for like 12 years or whatever definitely school 13 years 14
years whatever is like uh basically you tend to only hear from the people who complain about little
things you don't know when sure no one ever just takes time to write like enjoy today's pod signing
off in fact one of the cool benefits of doing these new zoom episodes is seeing people laugh
and enjoy it in the chat and that kind of stuff but it's very helpful right uh to it and i always
say what happens is you end up podcasting to those voices you end up talking like you're trying to
avoid the nitpicking little things that come your way that kind of just bother you throughout the
day right right um and then when i go out and do magic shows i get to run into listeners right and
i always find that refreshing because then i picture those are the people i'm talking to when
we're doing our podcast right aha i never been picturing a fit swedish dude over a grill with
sausages and carrots that's not something i'm thinking about right you think he's outside our
demographic that is clearly our demo man that is very different things that's all i've been
picturing the whole time i it would be it would be good if we did right i feel like i find it so
reassuring that we have listeners like beer none uh he can't be the only one so that's great i think
anytime we have listeners in other countries you know you know wendy's up here she's out in australia
the whole time like we it's so awesome yeah yeah but yet uh a guy i listen to us at his grill in
sweden it's pretty cool to think about as a podcaster it's what i love about our international
listeners is that we get to have them tell us how bad it looks from the outside and get to empathize
with what we're going through as a country which is nice uh and and and they still listen to us and
they realize that we are stuck here with this bullshit game that's being played yes thank you
uh thank you bassie we support you uh yeah no it's uh it's reassuring to have uh outside uh of the
state's uh listeners as well i'll tell you who only pictures fit swedish men grilling oh and
that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by the prequel to the famous paul sky to
being a dead horse series jacob sky to murdering horses hey i'm jacob you want to kill a horse
here's what you do just go ahead and build yourself a cliff you build a cliff build a big old tall
cliff maybe about 30 feet high and then what you do you go and whip that horse whip it whip it whip
him and ride him right to the edge that that cliff then jump off the horse right as he's going over
the cliff you tell him jake you tell him jake get him jake yeah that's right that's right i'm jacob
take him take that horse off the cliff whoa there you go dog food oh well 100 percent 100 oh 100
percent oh for sure oh for sure jake when was the last time you and sj went uh picking flowers
together oh all the time we go in our backyard here with our fake grass i gotta say you know
ann has made a list of things for us to do around pa and she does come up with these things like the
the flower festival and that kind of thing and i can be a little bit of a curmudgeon from time to
time but i'm trying to break myself for that a little bit more and just okay go for these things
and do it and i almost always enjoy myself and i really i did enjoy myself at the flower festival
no lie so your wife takes you to flower festivals uh my wife proposes that i do things uh at the
house uh my wife adds on honey do lists so uh we yeah we had a guy coming out the other day
yesterday as we're recording uh had a guy coming yesterday to uh to look at part of the backyard
to put some new fake grass in some additional fake grass in to to our yard and right before
he gets here sj announces that she has a new idea for part of the backyard and it affects part of
the grass but it affects part of the fake grass because uh where she's talking about it's kind
of takes up the same space and i want to know if uh if your spouses have uh ever asked you for
something like this my wife looked at our backyard and said do you know what we need in our backyard
and i think we can put it right in this area right over here she motioned towards uh towards an area
uh she said i think that we need a stage a stage my wife is proposing that i build us a stage
in my backyard wow and i'm kind of along for it so can i make an added suggestion go ahead you might
as well i'm already building a fucking stage in my backyard can i recommend that the stage double
as a gazebo you can recommend that sure and the guy goes to one flower festival
and he's suggesting you add a gazebo to your backyard he learned the word gazebo make the
gazebo the stage you know have a have a pergola roof on the gazebo uh-huh so that it's some some
shade uh-huh you can maybe string lights up there at night yeah yeah we could do that i could just
see a band playing inside the gazebo let me ask you this have you ever been asked to perform inside
a gazebo as a stage uh yeah so have i it sucks it sucks at the stage because those are terrible
stages yeah it's theater in the realm but it's not really we're not going to be watching everyone
to watch you through a fence it's like every every shows a neighbor across across the way i'm not
saying the gazebo has to be a traditionally built gazebo you could just make the roof connected by
like five main tiles oh a non-traditional gazebo yeah more like a stage jacob more like a traditional
a non-traditional gazebo more think more stagey this is not you will this is not your mother's
gazebo this is not your mother's gazebo no no that gazebo would be a terrible stage
paul's non-traditional gazebo however i might write that you do have a very uh elite barbecue
every so often in your backyard so a stage makes sense for your backyard uh no a stage is not the
dumbest idea that has ever been proposed for my backyard i think we're going to do it where are
you going to do it well i that's part of i think that last night i was i was taking a stroll last
night sj was in california on a gig so i was at home last night by myself and so i took a little
stroll and i think i i think i've given an a plus note to where uh sj was talking about having it
oh because she was talking about having kind of in the back of the backyard yeah and i i think
we're kind of going to kind of move it over to the side a little bit and uh you know the rock river
yeah i think it's going to cover part of the rock river i think it's going to be over the top of
that rock river so when water flows through it it'll flow out from underneath the bottom of this
stage that's pretty cool give it more of a gazebo vibe yeah i'll give it more of a gazebo vibe sure
a non-traditional a non-traditional gazebo a river doesn't run through a traditional gazebo already
either of you have either of you ever really wanted something for your backyard
like what i'm laughing because literally my wife and i were in the middle of having like a very
serious not a serious discussion like uh like we were just having a deep conversation and she just
looked at the backyard and immediately changed the subject to something she wanted to change in the
backyard and i was like we're really just switching gears all my wife does is one of us we've actually
already we actually have you've got a lot of work on that backyard i was gonna say jake you haven't
been over in a while but if you would you wouldn't you actually would be surprised in our backyard
right now it's we've had so much done back there oh nice uh so matt can i ask you about works two
full-time jobs she decides to get them some things changed in the backyard can i ask you matt about
your uh your backyard is this too sensitive a topic from the uh fourth of july i know there was a fake
grass incident what's what's what's the status uh i i so this is a sensitive topic i know
keeler's weighing in yeah so uh we had everybody over the fourth of july you know all the things
that we were buying for our kit uh for for our backyard we bought a new fire pit because the
the the chiminea that jacob delightfully lent us so many years ago uh has been destroyed by the sun
and weather and and and became a non-functioning chiminea yeah can i get that back yeah you get it
back from the lending whatever neighbor the lending term is over whatever neighbor took it we put it
out for bulk trash day you get it back from them good good i'll go get it and uh so i bought we
bought like a new little like you know quick put together a fire pit type of thing we can put in the
and then the kids wanted s'mores on fourth of july so i quickly built the fire pit i put it
together right this is after i put together all the new furniture in the backyard in 40 hours before
the cookout as well we had we put brand new furniture outside everything was my bike when
i bought this one kit it was all alan key the entire thing was alan key and i like my hands
hurt for days but yeah all the furniture he uh they built so much furniture on those on those
the days before fourth of july when i came over to matt's the entire the entire living room was
covered in these uh seating uh pillows that were expanding he left them out expanding but also matt
had all brand new wood flooring throughout the house yes so i came in and the first thing i said
is oh this looks really nice and he's like fuck you i'm like what are you talking about
i really like your floors making fun of my pillows all over the front cover
he's like eat shit maddingly i'm trying to make a nice backyard go fuck yourself i don't care about
your messy thing i'm talking about your nice new floors
so uh i built the gym and they uh uh built the fire pit um and you're saying build it you're
talking about like one of those fire dish things yeah it's on a little stand and yeah giant black
bowl with a screen with a screen on top of it and so we we built it so the kids made s'mores in the
front yard and then and then the party's over so we're trying to wrap it up and so uh keeler got
a water gun we started spraying out the fire they started smoking like crazy and then i'm trying to
put everything away and then i have all these neighbors that come by and the user uh with their
dogs and use our front yard as a toilet uh-huh and so uh i was walking around cleaning stuff up
and someone to be clear the dogs are using your yard as a toilet not the neighbors i don't want
to be that clear i don't know okay okay i don't know so i uh the woman is oh good i'm glad you're
out here i saw that smoke and i was like oh people are making a big deal about this smoking fire
thing so i move it into the backyard but i don't want to put it too close to the house i don't want
the smoke going up the side of the stucco so i put on the side yard our side yard is fake grass
right and even though we put the fire out the bottom of the fire pit was still a very hot
instrument and even though it has little pegs holding it off the ground it wasn't high enough
off the ground that it didn't melt a square foot patch of fake grass uh to to oh no to hard plastic
ruin and uh my wife was not happy with me about my decision to move the fake fire pit so all again
all i was trying to do is keep everyone happy and what happens bites me in the ass yeah that's right
that's why a lot more interesting that's it basically like can these guys play on a barefoot
or is that a hazard basically i just need to figure that out and so i oh yeah set the children out to
play like play and if you don't come back to bleeding i don't have to fix that little patch
but if you come back cleaning and grind i do i think you can fix this i think this is i think
you you take a uh an exacto knife or a you know box cutter cut a kind of big square out of this
go get you some new uh fake grass just get some cheap fake grass from like home depot or something
like that you nail it down in there bob's your uncle so this is a good good talk jacob and this
is what i looked up and i said that and i said oh maybe we can fix it and sarah said you can't you
can't fix fake grass like that i said well i just looked up on the internet and the internet says
you can but the internet says all kinds of things yeah i bet you can do it i bet jacob's right
and that was my first incident the internet says that step siblings are fucking each other left and
right i mean there's no evidence to the contrary i just believe evidence for none against yeah uh so
uh will we hope there's also really i can see matt's son on camera right now i i'm uncomfortable
with how quickly he got that joke very quickly yeah this is not i don't like that at all i feel
old now the internet is not a mystery to 11 years old to 11 year old i feel old now i don't like it
so um so the question is the the burnt thing which you can only see when you go up close you
can't really like when you look across there will it looks fine from a distance will the exacto patch
stick out more to my wife's gaze that's the issue you gotta you gotta do some serious color matching
here that's the hard part because it can't possibly because it's been weathered it's been the sun for
years yeah exactly so there's no way we're gonna find an actual matching patch you might have done
the right thing maybe just buy some spray paint is the when they did you put the fake grass down
this is a silly question did you put the fake grass down or did you hire somebody to put the
fake grass uh go ahead i'll give you three guesses on the first two don't count jacob okay so matt
hired people to put the fake grass down if they did the ground prep under the fake grass yeah it
might be easy to pull that grass up and just put new grass down and and redo the whole thing that's
what i was that is actually what i was thinking it might be it might be pretty easy to do the whole
thing if they did the ground the ground prep yeah they did they did they did the big sand man yeah
all that stuff yeah so yeah i i basically thinking like down the road it's probably like a new patch
of grass is probably like a five to seven hundred dollar expense yeah for that space maybe not even
that much you might be able to just buy some buy some rolls of it at home the whole thing well
matt has kids now his kids are gonna do this sure they can open up a weird hole in the wall factory
magic place they can they can they can roll out the grass yeah i just called the company it was
funny because when we got that installed right before the pandemic right and it's like foolish
was we're right in the middle of foolish right and i bought a basketball net a recliner and those fake
grass and then all of a sudden we're like oh wait we don't have jobs anymore and i was like wait i
can't afford to hit this stuff yeah we tried to cancel all of it and for the grass company they're
like well we already cut the thing we just haven't installed it so the only thing you save on is labor
no like you're still gonna get charged for the creating of the entire thing right yeah so you
just had to go you know the sand was piled up uh yeah not not put down with bags of sand and i just
was like yeah we just have to eat it we have to be even more we're just doing it now but we have to
finish it out yeah we have already done this now it's it's past tense might as well keep going
yeah yeah yeah yeah we did that with the uh with our windows we bought new windows for the whole
house ten scoops says just put a garbage can over it oh a terrible idea or just put a fire pit over
it make that the fire pits well i will make this suggestion matt yeah i was asking you guys if you
ever wanted anything in your backyard because i want something in my backyard very much i've always
wanted and i keep oh before paul says that i'll tell you out of the twitch chat that uh fifth
fifth leah maybe i suggest you just put a gazebo over it and there you go so you have your nice
little burn spot gazebo not a traditional gazebo no no no no no i think we're past traditional
gazebo at this point an 18 inch hexagon with lattice work in a roof it would be like look
we put a stage in too it would look like an 1800s phone booth
you could put in a phone booth you could just set a phone booth right there at your side yard
canadian scoop crystal suggested a wishing well that's not a bad idea oh yeah yeah uh which
reminds me of that hilarious mr show sketch about the wishing well which is if you haven't
seen it scams and flams uh no i have always wanted i keep giving and the guff i want a chinese
bridge in our backyard the kind that has a really big arc you know okay yeah that's what i want
and she's always giving me guff sorry colin colin sadler either either went to ai or there do sell
children's gazebos but it just put a follow-up of a mini children's gazebo that's very funny looking
oh it's a sandbox a gazebo sandbox yeah funny that is what you would call not your traditional
gazebo and jake the sandbox was my wrestling name i would say uh matt if you didn't have
cats that might be a good idea but that's gonna just become a big old poopoo hole we used to have
sand in our backyard and we had to get rid of it because it did become a cat poopoo hole yep
that's the hopefully it was just cats cats like to poop in sand it turns out
oh where would you put your bridge in your backyard well so again like it opens up the pandora's box
of needing a water feature kind of thing which we don't have and that would be a lot not impossible
how would this affect ann's ranking in the autobahn society they would probably take it up it would
take it up a little notch because uh a bigger water feature is something that she could add
honestly though she's knocking it out of the park the only thing that they had against her was it
wasn't quite big enough she needed 800 more square feet of habitat which she could do if we just
trick out the front yard with bushes and shit you should trick out the front yard with troubled
water and that way you can make a chinese bridge over troubled water like a chinese bridge over
troubled water oh that's so much better than i was afraid i was afraid that he was gonna do it in a
chinese accent i just did bridge over troubled water that's all i did i said dim sum yeah i did
do the chinese accent i'm thrilled we've progressed as a as a podcast as a people right i mean we're
growing um you just put the bridge over a flower field that's exactly right that's
flowers over there no instead of water make donuts next to them instead of water you put
flowers and make the flowers look like a flowing flower uh water thing kind of yeah so that's
thank you keeler that is exactly what we were uh considering and we still might at some point
uh we'll see but yeah that's the that's my dream is to have a chinese bridge and ann's just like
we don't need a fucking chinese bridge but i'm like i want one is she okay with other nationalities
a bridge oddly oddly she got really angry when i suggested a spanish bridge the other time
like she got mad i have always suspected that ann is racist towards the people of spain is going on
uh no no not at all uh who knows um you know she's got some cool water features she's got
some really nice little fountains and stuff we might do a bigger one uh we'll see we'll see
all right well good luck with your spanish tiled chinese bridge over over veroma's waters of her
troubled flowers like a bridge over troubled flowers you know let's do a little jock versus
nerd and he's right your wife is a bridges ladies and gentlemen it is time it's simply a bridge too
far for her oh hey flowers i have a revelation that came straight from ann that you and the
scoops may be interested in a revelation to paul she listens to the podcast religiously
she listens to every episode she just informed me that sometimes she has to fast forward my
commercials if they're gross she says i'm doing gross jokes sometimes she has to fast forward
it because it makes her gross out so checks out well you're good yourself you couldn't pay my
wife to listen to the show so still no i know i i mean i i'm so i i thanked her again i was i i i
don't mind i get it as i say you know who you married and you know the jokes the kind of jokes
in the sense of humor she's like i know but sometimes you get really gross on those those
commercials and i just have to fast forward a little bit and i'm like okay my every now and
then my wife will listen to the show it is it is rare i mean it's she's in the same boat as matt's
wife and uh and i mean when she does it is so surprising to me every time it just shocks me
like she showed up to scoop fest last year in a in a costume i was like what how did you do this
oh my gosh yeah and he's right think of the sponsors what about the sponsors paul
think about them do they happy with their gross portrayal of course they are they paid for the
gross stuff they pay for that foul stuff all right that's what they come we got a scooper to come
down today from silver fist scoop the categories are oprah chopra opa ikea crimea gonorrhea
jupiter saturn uranus or witch prince all right uh it's me first i'll try which prince for 400
fascinating topics this man was born in 1958 is it prince andrew prince william or prince
uh huh okay so i think prince williams out prince williams one of like the princes now right yes
yeah yeah so he's right he's right out prince andrew i think 58 is too young to be prince
andrew so i'm gonna just say prince i think the purple one it is press good job did my math out
loud and everything matt well he died right at 50 right it was something it was right around there
yeah you die in 09 i'll do which prince please which prince for 800 made an honorary fellow of
the society of light and lighting in 2016 prince andrew prince william or prince i'll go with
prince william okay it's prince andrew really they're still giving that guy awards in 2016 huh
i don't know what the society of light and lighting is so uh who knows it's give him awards or give
him children one or the other he you know he you gotta you gotta pick your poison there i think he
accepted from epsom island paul i will go with uh ikea crimea gonorrhea for 400 you can find uh
cornea here is it ikea crimea or gonorrhea i'll go with crimea i mean that's it seems like a proper
noun it is oh it's the cornea river crimea river that's me i'll try um uh let's try jupiter saturn
or uranus for 400 you would this is the fifth planet from the sun jupiter saturn or uranus
jupiter yes i had to count on my fingers jupiter matt uh i'll take uh ikea crimea gonorrhea please
daily double let's do it all of it jacob big money big money one negative 800 points this was
featured in a song by little wayne and drake in 2010 is it ikea crimea or gonorrhea oh gosh i
really hope it's crimea honestly i really hope that little wayne and drake did a song about crimea
i don't even i let's see um my guess was gonorrhea um all right i'll go crimea
all right it's gonorrhea gonorrhea cha cha cha gonorrhea cha cha cha
paul you're up a prince died at 57 thank you tin scoop for that information i thought it was just
50 that was mj the data 50 uh so he died in 17 right or 19 or whatever 16 16 i think okay or 15
anyway uh i'll do ikea crimea gonorrhea all right again you can find clipping here k i k l i p p a n
is that ikea crimea or gonorrhea i'm gonna go with ikea yeah let's try ikea it's a sofa
ah clipping our vice president's favorite item at ikea i'll go i'll close that ikea for 2000
sold the russia-based mega family shopping center chain to gazprome bank in 2023 is it ikea crimea
or gonorrhea all right i'm just gonna do the math here did gonorrhea sell the russian-based mega
family shopping center chain in 2023 you don't know gonorrhea's life i don't all right i'm gonna
say that it's not gonorrhea i don't know enough about the political socioeconomic structure of
crimea to be really sure about this answer does the country of crimea own things like like a
shopping center chain yeah that they can then just turn around and sell i don't know or is this a
subsidiary of a subsidiary of ikea yeah i'm gonna say crimea all right
shit it's ikea scuba flip the coin got it wrong man you i just because i was the only one who got
anything wrong and i was really get my butt kicked um let's see here i have 1600 uh let's see i'll go
with you have negative 1600 i'll go with jupiter saturn uranus for 2000 all right in mythology this
god was both the son and the husband kinky of gaia is it jupiter saturn or uranus oh i don't think it
was uranus you don't think so wait now that i now that i pronounce it the right way it might be that
jupiter is a jupiter is the god i know reference a lot in shakespeare and stuff okay saturn jupiter
is the roman counterpart of zeus yeah jupiter of course famously where girls go to get more stupider
right and saturn sets the pattern yeah uh my gut was to go and uranus is inflamed i'm gonna go with
jupiter okay okay let's see it is often it's uranus ah it was it was always uranus matt
paul you put uranus on the line uh i'll try jupiter saturn uranus for 800 boy we're all
steering away from the oprah category this planet has the second largest moon titan in the solar
system is that jupiter saturn or uranus uh this plan i think that's a saturn moon titan you think
it's saturn it is saturn hey look all right to me i'll close out uranus for 1200
in mythology this god was the parent of pluto is that jupiter saturn or uranus
uh let's see pluto is hades right i thought hades and zeus were brothers
well if that i thought hey then jupiter but i also but isn't because Poseidon is saturn and zeus and
jupiter Poseidon were also brothers and jupiter is zeus right and jupiter is zeus
so i think i guess it's uranus i'll say uranus that's jupiter oh man adam fuck it
i thought paul's running away with us and not in the usual way not because we loaded up our nerd
questions and he's crushing it but uh jacob and i have buried ourselves in this one yeah yeah uh
matt you're up fucking uh oprah excuse me i'm cursing for my kids that's how you know how much
i'm enjoying this right now um let's do witch prince for 2000 which all right has a ba in
geography at the university of saint andrews is that prince andrew prince william or prince
this is the first one where i've sincerely felt like it could be any of the three
yes exactly it could be it could be i mean uh
saint andrews of course in ireland i'll go with uh prince william good guess all right
it's prince william i'll try some oprah copra oprah all right this person was born in january
1954 is it oprah winfrey deep pop chopra or oprah or uh oprah or an oprah uh oprah born in 54 probably
uh i don't know for sure though i'll pass uh let's see that passes to uh me oh shit uh i have no idea
but i have to guess anyway i will say that that was uh deep pop deepbox oprah it's oprah when it
was oprah now i'm just getting more buried it's me i'll uh which prince 1200 daily double good
that's what i need to get me in less negative points what i was quoted as saying the internet
is completely over in 2010 was that prince andrew prince william or prince oh again this two of these
is very possible yeah i'd be really surprised if it was prince william uh boy i kind of think it
was prince i'm going prince yeah it was prince yeah uh matt you got uh oprah for 812 or 2000
the only way i can get into positive points is 2000 yes that is true okay all right don't blow it
this person launched virgin comics in 2006 with richer with richard branson is it oprah winfrey
deep pop chopra or an oprah why these all feel like the wrong answer yeah right i don't see a
comp a comics company i don't see oprah doing that but i certainly don't see deep away deep pack
chopra comics yeah might make sense because it's like a deep thing uh i'll go i'll go with deep
pack chopra okay it is yeah yeah yeah all right man listen to his son and didn't screw it up
oh you got 800 or 1200 either way paul's gonna win good uh i'll try the 1200 then why not this
person was sued for copyright infringement for a book they wrote in 1993 is that oprah deepak or
an oprah uh who's an oprah i we have you know everything that i do yeah uh i'll pass i don't
know uh it's me i'll say um deep pot yeah sue him get him lost get him and i'm closing out the
category and the game if i get this correct i will be tied for second place with matt donnelly
this is a deeply kneeled laterally compressed discoid fish
deeply keeled laterally compressed discoid fish stay down oprah stay down oprah one freak
deep back chopra or an oprah i love that that's just a straight up answer that's just great
i'm gonna i'm gonna be like d your mom oh boy i believe that'd be an oprah it is an oprah and
that is the game paul wins with 2400 matt and i are tied at 400 a piece and that's from silver
fist scoop thank you silver fist scoop if you want to send us a scooperty or a price of scryte jock
versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd head over to hey scoops.com that's where you can go
hey scoops.com right there on the home page make us one of those jock versus nerds send us some
scoop mail buy your tickets to scoop fest do all the things right over there at hey scoops.com i
believe for scoop fest we are now officially sold out of the jacobs whiskey barbecue okay however
now with gazebo now with more gazebo however i don't think we're going to have as many of our
guests uh coming to the barbecue this year as we've had in years i just don't think we have
as many guests uh that are going to be in town for it so if you are wanting to come to the whiskey
barbecue as part of scoop fest hit me up uh hit any of us up honestly uh but yeah we'll figure out
a way for you to come uh because i think that we can make it work so uh from from here on out uh
it's just a catch-is-catch can on the whiskey barbecue there may be definitely squeeze some
more people in limited exclusive tickets still available through jacobs directly that's it just
just hit us up and we'll uh we'll figure it out we'll get you on the list tickets are still
available either three day or two day passes depending on your budget uh for the regular
scoop fest go to scoopfest.com we are at that point where we can basically we think we will
be able to accommodate everyone uh with the scoop fest bags yeah because of sizes and stuff at this
point we can't guarantee your size um for the item that's right that we're that we're selling
we'll have stuff but uh you know at this point if you buy a ticket we will we will do our best to
accommodate sizes i can tell you right now you're gonna be so happy with the mystery item you won't
care i'm gonna tell you right now oh it's so great it's so good people i'm gonna tell you right now
the first photos that are coming out of scoop fest you're gonna laugh all right uh really fun
surprises on the way for that surprises galore in fact galore yeah get it over scoopfest.com
buy your tickets now you can also get call up the orleans and get on that that room discount block
it's a sweet discount man it is it's always they always give us a fantastic discount s c f i two
three c two five two five c uh there you go um check that out s c f i two five c just get them
on the phone big scoop fest god damn it okay that's it uh thanks so much it's the beginning of the
month so we don't have thank yous for it but this podcast is possible because people support us
over on our patreon and we really appreciate it so if you have it uh within your hearts and your
budget for both a monthly or yearly support um we we really appreciate it each and every time
so head on over to preachingfun.com
or if you have ever burned a hole in your fake grass that your wife was super happy about
head on over to fartsinabag.biz
that's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com and take a look to our patreon page
where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air head on over
there preachingfun.com fartsinabag.biz if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars
hit us up over there right now we can always use your support and uh right now we really could uh
matt son has just taken his credit card and is signing up good we got a really big uh patreon
bump right here uh this last donation came in all in roblox bucks oh fantastic we'll take it um so
the people have been love uh it's been so lovely to join us on our zoom if you have a minute to
go over to the bucket show.com if you get a free amazon if you're an amazon member there's a free
subscription button there absolutely and if you can give us the amazon subscription that that gives
us a few dollars uh that are not out of amazon's pocket not yours um so it's a huge help to us so
if you take a second just go over to the bucket show.com and check that out um and uh for everyone
else you know uh if you want to help us out without money but you want to help out our show
participate in our obelisk scheme choose one person and one person only you think they might
might like our podcast and turn them on to an episode today no that's a really really helpful
don't try to get five people do it and get those five people to do it that's a pyramid scheme it's
enough that's a pyramid false promises please just choose one person and one person only
there is a very small pyramid on top of the obelisk we don't mention that we don't even
talk about it weird it's really even brought up now all right uh thanks everybody stay safe out
there we love you and we'll see you soon we'll see you soon oh i recently guested on a podcast
called creators cafe out of los angeles it's a podcast where the uh host jessica pain talks
to different creative people and uh and show business all over the place really fun and uh
had a nice long uh conversation with jessica over there go check it out creators cafe anywhere you
have your fine podcasts it's on youtube too go check it out we're preaching fun we are preaching fun