Let's be honest, healthcare can be expensive. So check out Redeem Health Share. It's a faith-based
way to manage medical costs with flexible programs to fit your budget and your values.
You're not dealing with insurance, just a community of believers helping each other through
life's ups and downs. This is more than healthcare. It's hope. It's healing. It's faith in action.
Call 1-844-REDEEM-0. That's 1-844-REDEEM-0. Join the movement. Share joyfully. Live redeemed.
The stakes are high this season, and the competition? Fierce. Nematodes and disease?
These guys don't play fair. With your yield on the line, you can either get lucky or you can
stack the deck. With Victrato Soybean Seed Treatment, featuring Timerium technology,
it's your ace in the hole to flush out royal pains like nematodes, SDS, and red crown blots.
Victrato Soybean Seed Treatment. Read 'em and reap. Always read and follow label instructions.
Oh hello there. I am so glad you are here because I would like to thank the ice cream truck drivers.
Who are the ice cream truck drivers? Well, those are the folks to deliver that fucking ice cream
straight to your fucking ear holes. Right now, I'd like to thank Darth Scooper, David Walker,
Ted Laszlo, Dirty Old Scoop. I'm here on the job site with Dale, who's a framing contractor.
Hey, good morning. Dale traded up to Geico Commercial Auto Insurance for all his business
vehicles. We're here where he needs us most. Yep, they sure are. We make it easy for him
to save on all his insurance needs, all in one place, with coverage that fits his business and
bottom line. Oh, I shouldn't have looked down. It's all right. We're so far up here. Look at me.
Take a deep breath. Oh, I'm good. So good. Get a commercial auto insurance quote today at Geico.com
and see how much you could save. It feels good to Geico. Dr. Scoop Little, an Elk and Magic Scoop.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, just like these fine folks,
head over to preachingfun.com. That's where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver.
And who knows? The life you save. The fade out button didn't work.
That was the stop button? To be fair, I suppose the fade out button might work. I haven't tested it,
but the stop button works effectively. Okay, good. Yeah. All right. The stop button works
just fine. I literally was like, wait, do you have to start over? Like, what's happening?
No, no, no. See, Matt, I'm covering it with all of this. See, nobody even noticed it
because I covered the lack of a music fade with this clever banter.
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to. Great. Let's go.
I'm so excited, guys. We're broadcasting from Core Sensors in Morristown, New Jersey.
I'm in a conference room.
Yo, very nice cabin. Yeah. It's time for Matt and Natalie's ice cream social.
Sitting in Jersey, it's Matt Godley. Sitting in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Vegas, it's me, making the audio guide. We're preaching fun.
That's where you're wrong. I don't know if I can break a computer.
I couldn't see. What's in there? Pressure sensors and pressure transducers.
That's what's on display. That's what's sold. That's what's made and sold here.
Do you have an end with the pressure sensor and transducer mafia?
I do. What's going on?
It's true. Who's your hookup?
I've been connected to the pressure transducer industry for quite some time.
Is it true? Yes.
Who's your pressure transducer pimp? Who's your pressure transducer guy, Matt?
One of my original roommates in my party house of Fort LaForge, my buddy Sam.
So the ones that are on display last week when I was like,
I need new pressure transducers. Where were you then?
I don't want you to take it up my supply.
The ones that I'm seeing in that cabinet, are those on display as check out the hotness
or are they our vaunted history? What is this? What am I seeing?
I don't even know. I wasn't given a free samples.
I was because here's the thing. So my buddy, Sammy, it's his company.
I am staying at his house. His office is closer to my magic show that I have to literally,
as soon as we wrap, I'm leaving and going to do two magic shows.
And he said, and the internet's stronger here.
So let's just sit up in my conference room. What a nice guy.
Yes. He's a very nice guy. And so, yeah, I did not get the two penny tour though.
So I'm very curious myself as to what is on display on these shelves as well.
And I assume when you leave, you will be given several pressure transducers.
Oh yeah. I got to bring the kids home something.
Does he end every sales call? Does he end every sales call with no pressure?
No, no, no, no. Good, good.
Cause that would be the end of his business. He did tell me something.
So he gets, you know, it was a business. I mean, it's cold called all the time. It's fan called.
Sure. He found out if I should betray this or not.
Here we go. Getting the fucking pressure sensor to y'all.
Pressure. Pressure sensor talk, talk and pressure sensor, sensor pressure.
Pressure sensor. It's our new segment on the show.
If you're spam called by someone in India, there's a term you can use an insult in India
that basically makes people break script and either curse you out or hang up on the spot.
Wow. No. Yes.
There's a magic super curse that we could be using this whole time.
Yes. And it basically translates to, uh, uh, basically sister fucker. Like you're, you're,
you're, you, you, you, you fuck your sister. Um, it's a good one.
So we're, we're implying that they have more fun than they're comfortable having is what you're
saying. It's pronounced, you know, Ben shot. That's how you pronounce. That's, that's the term.
So right now exactly. We just got, we apologize to our Indian listeners right
now who are screaming into their phones. And, uh, he indeed proved it to me.
He took a spam call while we're having breakfast and it was someone trying to, to buy his home.
And they said how much? And he goes, uh, about 140, 150 Ben shots.
And the person hung up the phone immediately.
Hilarious. 150 Ben shots.
This is one of those terrible things because on one hand I feel it's, it's a little punching
down because the person running the phone isn't the asshole who's doing all of them.
But they are the one actively doing it. So it's, yeah, I don't know. I do like it though. I like
having a magic word solution. Nobody gets hurt. I've been, I've been getting a lot of phone calls
lately from, uh, numbers that I don't have saved. So I've been answering unknown numbers when they're,
when they're popping up and, uh, yeah, so I've been getting hit with a couple of good spams lately.
And, uh, I'm glad to have a code. I really couldn't believe it.
Yeah. When I saw it in action, I was like, oh my gosh, you have seen in the chat with a T it's
with the D shot. Uh, yeah, yeah. Uh, which, which part of it is, is it a direct translation?
The shod be like fucker. I mean, I think like it's like a, to a degree, like the ultimate degree,
right? Okay. Like, I know like, like in Italian, you can say like Blanco or like,
you know, uh, whatever that means white, but if you say like Blunky Sumo, it means like the most
whitest white. Uh, I said that to somebody, I was joking with an Italian where I was talking
about whether I was good at basketball, like my brother. And I said, I was, uh, not only Blanco,
but Blunky Sumo. I was the most white and it made him laugh really hard. Um,
it's weird that basketball is the place where we get to talk about race with the, uh, the least
amount of concern, right? No. Yeah. It's really kind of nice. I was, you know, hanging out on the
ship. I just got off yesterday. Uh, and one of the, uh, one of the, the artists was, uh, he was,
he was from Israel. He lives in, you know, the United States currently, but it was from Israel.
And, uh, we were out with, uh, a black comedian, uh, it's great comedian named Orlando Baxter.
Okay. And I already had some like weird conversations with my
Israeli friend as he would drift into certain politics from time to time.
Oh, he had, he had interesting views that you didn't necessarily find incredibly comfortable
to talk about. Yes. Oh, okay. Okay. Interesting. And somehow the topic came over to the Cosby show
and then the fact that, uh, uh, Malcolm Jamal Warner had died recently.
Oh, that's right. Yeah. He had died, uh, uh, drowning and swimming. Yeah. Yeah.
Trying to save his daughter. Did he, did his daughter live? I don't know. I, I believe so.
Okay. I'll find out. And this person then made a joke about black people and swimming
and I excused myself from the table and went to the bathroom. Oh dear. Oh my.
Because you were laughing so hard, you were.
Oh, God damn it. God damn it. What the fuck is wrong with people?
And then, uh, he brings up that, uh, Orlando brings up that his wife is indeed a chemist,
uh, from Harvard. And then, uh, uh, my mentalist friend then brought up
that, uh, Harvard was supporting, uh, genocide in Sudan and that he should be mad at Harvard.
And then Matt had to excuse himself again because he was laughing hysterically again.
Why, why, who, who taught you that this is the way to have conversation?
All right. This was so similar. My, my mom used to teach when, when my mom, uh, was a college
professor, she would, uh, teach all of these international students. Yeah. And it was not
uncommon around the holidays for, uh, uh, an international student or eight to show up at
the house for, uh, the big, big holiday meal because, you know, she would invite them over
because they didn't have a family or whatever in the area to go spend the holidays with.
And, uh, there was this cat one time I never saw him again, never had never met him before,
uh, but he was just an Israeli student of my mom's. And I remember his, because he, you know,
he was Israeli. He w he had been in the Israeli military before, uh, coming over to the U S to,
to go to college. And, uh, he, his job in the Israeli military had been peel potatoes. He had
worked as a cook. And so he was like, I peel thousands of potatoes a day. Uh, let me peel
the potatoes for dinner. I can peel them instantly. And he could, uh, we gave him a potato peeler at
first and he was like, I don't know how to use a potato peeler. I just need a knife. And so I got
him a, got him like a little paring knife and he peeled enough potatoes for like, there were
probably 20 of us at the house that day. He peeled enough potatoes for everyone in like a
minute and a half. It was incredible to watch. That's awesome. But I was over there. I was,
I was probably, you know, in junior high, maybe, maybe young high school or something like that.
And I was over there and he was telling me about, uh, like Israeli military and, uh, telling me
jokes about Israeli military or jokes that they would tell each other in the Israeli military.
And, uh, yeah, as a young teenager, I was like, I need to not be in this conversation. This guy is
saying things that I am not. Like he's, this is his thing. I'm going to, I'm going to go piss
myself in the bathroom. He has forgotten the first rule. The potatoes have eyes. That's right. You
can't just go around behaving however you want around the spuds. Yes. Uh, Malcolm Jamal's, uh,
Warner's, uh, daughter was saved. She was saved by a surfer. So yeah, she was, she was, uh, okay.
Cowabunga, dude. Yeah. What happened to Theo? No way.
Gnarly. Uh, Matt, were there any jokes you wanted to repeat about, uh, Theo Huxtable drowning?
No, no, no. Oh, interesting. Okay. No, I didn't, I didn't think of any in the bathroom when I
walked away. I didn't think of any. I just saw a preview for something last night with Malcolm
Jamal Warner in it. And I was like, Oh no. Yeah. Yeah. Was it the ocean? I know. That was what it
was. It was Davy Jones locker. I, uh, yeah, no, no, it wasn't, that wasn't even the only awkward
conversations that I'll bet. I'll bet. I'll bet. Even the most awkward conversation. You know,
if I gave a damn enough to want to talk to people, I'm sure I'd have a lot of
awkward conversation. Right. Right. I don't push myself. You're, you're, uh, you're a bold man.
Also, you're stuck on a boat. It happens on boats. Yeah. You can't, you can't, you know, we, we all
have to like, what am I gonna do? Like, you know, get irate and then spend the last three days giving
someone the silent treatment for the ship. And you're going to see them every five minutes.
Exactly. You're playing pinball with people on the ships. Yeah. Yeah. No, no. Oh, speaking of awkward
conversations, I forgot to talk about this one. I went out with, uh, uh, uh, Rondell Sheridan when
we went, we went out and so we went to a little bar after the comedy club and the bar, all the
staff want to take pictures of Rondell. We get back out of the street and, uh, the four of us are
waiting for an Uber and there was a gentleman like 10 feet off of our conversation who just sees us
joking around. Oh, decides to insert himself and he was into his cups. Oh, yes. Oh dear. He was,
he was like, you met the mayor. He was, I met the mayor. He literally, and he literally just
like stumbled towards us. He had like this big maroon UMass sweatshirt on over like shorts.
And then, and, uh, and he had like a perfect like movie for my first mustache, like 22 years old,
my first bushy mustache, like mustache, uh, that looked like it was like put on by like a costume
person and not like, like it wasn't, didn't belong on him. And, and he literally like,
like while wobbling, smiles ear to ear and goes like, can I get in on this?
Damn it. That person is a hero. Damn it. Damn it. What the hell? Can I get in on this?
Y'all having a good time? Let me get in on this good time. Oh my God. You look like a bunch of
good time fellas. Let me get in on this. Good Lord. Can I get in on this? And then like, we just
like, I hear that, but my, my two friends were still talking like, just keep talking, you know?
Yeah. And, uh, uh, and he's like, and he's just like leaning in and going, uh, yeah.
Seamless transition. Like, like as if he's like camouflaging into a party or something,
but like, it's just the four of us. This is great. And the other three are like,
just like including Randall are just like, not like looking at me, like I am not engaging this
man. Right. But he like is not going to, because they don't want to live and he is staying like
two-dimensionally confident. Like he is just still doing like listening, like eyebrows and
listening ears. And like, he's, he literally puts like an arm up, like a teapot, like a teapot.
I am in this conversation. This is a conversation that I'm going to be a part of.
Finally, just go like, all right, I'll, I'm going to jump on this grenade. I'll isolate.
And I just, I just square to him and I go like, you doing all right, pal? You having a good night?
And he's like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. You guys seem like a lot of fun. You guys,
you guys like comedy? I like comedy. You guys like comedy? And I was like,
I can't tell whether he is or isn't making out Randall Sheridan or not. Do you know why is this
happening? As much as I have involved my life with the comedic arts. Yeah. I have never, ever
initiated a conversation or even said the words. I am into comedy. You know what I mean? Like I've
never, I've never said that. I don't think I'm into comedy. No, no. It's, it's, it's in the same,
it's in the same category as people who criticize jokes right after saying that they really like to
laugh. You know, I love to laugh, but you know, this joke just really pushed me in the wrong
direction. You know, it's, it's that, it's that same family. So my buddy, I'm really into comedy.
My buddy, uh, Tom noting that I, I, I, I stepped in it, decides to just push me further in. And he
goes, Oh, if you like comedy podcasts, he knows a bunch of people do comedy podcasts. Oh, I mean,
this is a guy to chip. If there was ever a guy to chip, this is a guy. Get him listening. Uh,
and then I did probably one of the most obnoxious things I've ever done.
He keeps bringing up famous people that he likes that are funny from the improv comedy world.
Good. Do you remember any of his examples? I'm not going to say examples. I'm going to
tell you what I did. Oh, okay. Okay. I got out my phone and showed that that person was someone I
could call and then said, but we're not going to call them. And I would close my contact.
And he brought up someone else to go, Oh, sure. Yep. We can call that person too, but we're not
going to, you and I are not going to call that person right now. That's a good asshole move.
That's a hell of a move. I just kept showing them all these people I knew from the UCB theater from
back in the day. Cause that's what we liked from like the comedy bang bang and other kind of podcast
space. And he literally was like, whoa, whoa. He was like flipping. There's no way this could be
faked. Exactly. Exactly. There's no way somebody can have these names stored in their phone without
their, without the correct numbers. Good point. Good point. I could have just been like, sure,
Alec Baldwin here, you know, whatever. Isn't this amazing? I'm just thinking this says Alec Baldwin.
Wow. We're here now. We're here now for phone. We are fully here now for phone. Right? If I'd done
this 30 years ago, people would have thought I was insane. This means phone. Yeah. Oh, you're talking
about the gesture that I'm holding a brick. My creepy claw hand means phone. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Matt's just holding up his hand to the camera like he's holding a phone. Yeah. We don't do hang loose.
No, we don't do that anymore. No, we don't even do hold like a thing, like a receiver type. We do
claw hand. But we still do the, we still do the crank thing for a car window.
We do somewhat. We do somewhat. Well, I will, I will say that, uh, and of course we still have
the picture of the floppy disk to, uh, to save things. The car that I have right now, the car
that I have right now, which is just about to turn six years old or rather 10 years old is the first
car I've ever had with power windows. Uh huh. So it was only a decade ago. Just so you know, if you,
if you ever get a text from me with celebrity's name on it, it means you're about to get a phone
call and you're supposed to be that celebrity when you answer the phone. Oh, I would do that in a
heartbeat. I would do that in a heartbeat. That's a really good idea. That'd be really fun actually.
I'm afraid three of us need to remember that. Yeah, we should. That could be really good.
I did a bit, I did a bit for Teller a couple of years ago. Oh, this is Daniel Craig, isn't it?
He had a friend that wanted, uh, wanted his kid to talk to Batman. So I did Batman for the kid.
Yeah, I did. That's me, Batman. What do you want? It was very bail. It was very bail.
I understand you can help me find the joker. And I like the kid was looking for the joker
for like a week. I got totally keep an eye out when you're in a parking lot, just scan,
make sure you look everywhere. The kids started out in the joker. So yeah, that I think that's a
good bit. Let's be an ice agent. Let's start. You set them down the wrong track. No, I don't,
I don't know. I don't think they can find the joker. It's not just going to change his wife's
name to Bob De Niro on his phone. That's great. Oh, here's me, Bob De Niro, isn't it?
Good. Get me some bangers and mash your Bob De Niro. I am. You guys are just getting
better and better at your piff impression. Yeah, we're just, we're just chilling piff the whole
time. It's true. It's true. By the way, any, anybody who goes to see Matt at any of the magic
shows, if you come see Matt at a scoop event, feel free to name celebrities and see if that
that has to be obnoxious. I just, I didn't know how to like, he wasn't going to go away. So I
just literally was like, it was like shiny keys. Like how do I bounce shiny keys in front of his
face to keep him from, I basically was like, I have to keep him from either recognizing or pestering
Rondell Sheridan is what I was probably also is probably the nicest thing you could do really.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cause you probably made his day. You're like, Oh, I'm two degrees from that guy.
Uh, uh, lemur cream or lemur screamer creamer wants Clooney Batman. Paul, let's hear on Clooney
Batman now. I don't know what your game is. Freeze. Perfect. I don't know what your game is Robin.
I don't know what you think about man. Didn't know a lot of game. I don't know what you think
your game is. Poison Ivy. Jesus. And Myra wants, uh, post care, uh, post cancer Kilmer Batman.
It's a lot quieter. I don't know what your name is Robin. I don't know what your game is.
Batman. Wait, I'm Batman. I don't know what your game is. Poison Ivy. Wait, no. Two face was the
one in mine. I'll tell you who else definitely did not feel uncomfortable by that impression.
And that is the following sponsor. This show is brought to you by, uh, Dicks Out for Democracy,
Crouchless Shorts for your next anti-Trump rally.
Hello. I am Jerry Daisy Duke Farla Flon and I've started a company. Of the Montana Farla Flons?
The same. Out here, out here in, in God's country, we all like to free ball, but we also
don't care for the rubbing of, uh, denim. So what we've done is we have eliminated the middleman,
literally. We've cut out the spot where your wieners at in all of our jeans. And I don't sell
just jeans. I sell Daisy Dukes cut high and tight to where you can't tell if it's ass or, or what it
is because it's so high. Ass or other options. That's right. Ass or who can say.
And now we've confused the issue even further by eliminating more of the material on the,
on the gene to let your dick and balls fly loose.
That's right. Go to, go to free as your own balls.org and sign up today
to get on the mailing list. We're just pre-ordering them right now.
There is nothing more democratic than crotchless Daisy Dukes.
And the question of what is that ass or what have you.
There's a time where people debated whether the snake or the turkey or the eagle was the
greatest symbol of us and our rights. When our own free swing and scrotum was hanging
right there the whole time. Seriously. It incorporates both snake and eagle
because you have the serpent-like phallus and the comfortable bald nest of the majestic eagle bird.
There's nothing more American than a coiled wiener sitting atop a pile of fuzzy balls.
Enter Hey scoops at checkout. Patriots.
I also would like to endorse this product.
Thank you Val.
Oh Val Kilmer Batman.
Yes. I wore very tight pants. I wish I'd had a hole for my ween ween
because boy I had to hold my pee in a lot.
On most days, many days I couldn't pee. What's, what's your game killer croc?
There have been some new, there have been some good drug ads lately.
An acne medication that I saw the other day it had a warning that it would just cause eye problems.
Instinct eye problems. That's all it said was eye problems.
What is this?
And I thought that was-
Did I take this medicine?
That was probably a Paul medicine. It caused eye problems.
And I thought that was going to be the worst one I saw. I saw one last night.
I paused it and had to rewind to it.
It caused an increased risk of lower limb loss.
Lower limb loss.
But it doesn't say legs. It just says lower limb.
And it doesn't say what the loss might be.
Because the way it's phrased, it definitely looks like it's just going to fall off.
Wow. And what does the drug help?
This was a cholesterol medication.
All right. Lucky you.
Well, I mean, I guess I want that low LDL enough. I'll give up a foot.
I guess. This seems, if we're going to advertise drugs in this country,
the warnings at least have to make sense.
No, there's no, no, they don't.
And I know our European listeners are just confused about drug companies being able to
advertise on TV. We are too.
It's insane times, man. It's insane.
Yeah.
I was just seeing somebody talking about the whole Tylenol debacle, right?
Yeah. What do you mean debacle? We figured out what causes autism.
Sure. Well, this is a cause for celebration.
The thing that they mentioned, and I don't know, it seemed to make some sense to me that they were
like, why wouldn't Tylenol have started a lawsuit by now if their sales had been impacted in any way?
Apparently nobody's listening to this bullshit, but he's still piloting fucking Tylenol, right?
I mean, we're in the land of commerce here. That's all that matters is bottom line.
So apparently it's not hitting them in the pocketbook enough to make them
because there is no more litigious society than the United States.
Right.
So I, you know, I can only fathom, you know.
Not only has Tylenol stock not dropped, it is trading near its 52 week high.
There you go. So there it is.
Okay.
Yeah. There was a brief significant drop in September,
but apparently it bounced right back like the next day.
Okay.
Interesting.
There you go.
That is fascinating. That actually makes me feel good that it was that dumb that people
were like, okay.
And it also kind of makes me feel good that they aren't suing.
They're like, oh, we can't demonstrate damages.
So I guess we'll just leave this one alone.
Yeah, that's so strange.
Oh, I never, Basi in the chat, just the thing that was created in the 50s is
responsible for something that was discovered in 1911.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I need to think about that aspect of it.
That's a fine way to think about that.
There's not a whole lot of medical research going on here at all.
Well, I didn't believe it until now.
I mean, it's not like Basi's statement just caused me to shift my opinion on Tylenol.
Excuse me, Jacob, you're talking out of your neck.
I got to tell you, I'm pretty sure just looking at you,
because I could just look at people and diagnose them.
I'm pretty sure that you were circumcised way too early.
That's what I think now.
Damn it.
Val Kilmer?
It's me, Val Kilmer, back from the dead.
Quado from Total Recall?
What's your game, Freeze?
He'd be an amazing, he is an amazing villain.
What the fuck am I saying?
He is a fucking Batman villain.
He is a Batman villain.
Jesus Christ, we're surrounded by Batman villains.
And not in the good way.
No, there's nothing fun about it.
None of them look like Uma Thurman dressed in plants.
Oh, Uma Thurman.
Sorry, everybody.
I just got Paul started on jacking it.
Just set him off, everybody.
I'm sorry, that's my fault.
Uma Thurman.
Come on.
I'll be back in five and just a nap on camera.
So we're getting the house repainted.
It's crazy out here.
We're trying to juggle, making sure we get home in time to help them
get the stuff they need or whatever.
And, you know, but we're staying out of their way as best we can.
But we got to put the dogs outside sometimes.
But then the dogs and stuff's getting painted.
So stuff got painted last night right where the dogs were outside.
So we had to lay down some cardboard and the dogs wouldn't go on the cardboard.
So we had to carry the dogs all around.
It was a site and had to go get some special new clothes
because she had a special interview come up last night, yesterday.
So we were out doing dogs were such a mess.
You had to go get new clothes.
No, no, no.
Like an 80s movie montage where you wait outside the dressing room.
And like she just kept coming on outfit after outfit.
And you're like, yes, no, maybe that's how we do it.
Every time, every time we go to Kohl's and I go first into Kohl's.
I have her wait in the car and I go into Kohl's first
and grab a couple of scarves and sunglasses.
Go ahead.
I basically transform into the character of Hollywood from Mannequin and Mannequin 2.
And so I take on this new persona.
And when she comes through the door, I just say, oh my,
let's find something for you that will just work.
And then, you know, she starts trying things on.
And then as she comes out as Hollywood, I will then comment and say,
well, I guess the 1950s called back, you know, something to that effect.
And then, you know, she'll come out again.
I mean, oh, goodness, no one told me Miss Greta Garbo was going to be in the building.
Huzzah, you know, things like that, things of this nature, things of this nature.
So then so I wonder what percentage of our audience was not alive
when the movie Mannequin was released.
That makes me scared to think about zero.
It's not zero.
You're right.
That movie's older than Acetaminophen.
Someone in the chat says Acetaminophen was actually used back in 1893.
I don't I mean, whatever.
I think we can fact check everything, including the link between Tylenol and autism.
Missing link.
There.
The missing link.
Yeah.
Nobody thinks that we know what we're talking about.
Yeah, I admit it.
Apparently, nobody thinks that RFK knows what he's talking about either.
Since that doesn't affect Tylenol stock price.
I'm constantly doing this noise while I'm going down on Cheryl Hyde.
Her pussy is just full of this voice.
Oh, you know, it's hard enough.
Most men to find the clitoris.
Her clitoris runs away from my voice.
All right.
Andy Cheek points out that we have done more research than the government on
the link between Tylenol and autism just here.
I believe that's true.
I believe that is true.
Agreed to disagree.
He got us.
What's your game calendar, man?
Drove through Taco Bell the other night after work and the guy on the speaker goes,
yeah, it's like 1 a.m. or so.
And a guy on the speaker goes, hey, how's your night going?
It's doing all right.
How are you doing?
Shitty, man.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for asking.
So I put my order in.
I pulled up to the window and this dude just leans out of the window.
He goes, man, I've been having a night that needs to tell me just all the jerks
that have pulled up to the Taco Bell drive through that night.
He just needed to vent.
That's amazing that you were you were there for him.
I was like, what you got, buddy?
I'm here for you, man.
I was just talking.
We said we just sat and chatted in the drive through for about five minutes, too.
We had a nice little chat.
He's a good guy.
We were just talking Taco Bell at work the other day.
And some of my younger co-workers, I was like, guys, I don't know if you know, but.
Back in the day, if you spent twenty dollars at the Taco Bell,
you had ordered the entire menu.
Yeah, like, yeah.
Now you can get the big you can get the big case of.
Yeah, you could get a box like it was like for like 15 bucks, yeah.
Fifteen bucks for like 16 time.
It was crazy.
Yeah.
And now it's just it's.
Things used to be cheaper brought to you by talent.
Oh, yeah, we're raising the prices of tacos.
Don't say taco around the Mr. President.
He doesn't like that.
Paul Brogan in the chat already mentioned that they were not alive when Mannequin came out.
Well, so there's there's one already.
Brogan, I hope you have at least seen Mannequin and Mannequin, too.
OK.
No, Brogan is shaking their head in the chat.
Well, Brogan, you've got homework because Hollywood is I fucking conic.
Yes, you don't have any homework.
You don't have to watch Mannequin.
Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social does not want to encourage people to watch the film
Mannequin.
I mean, I do.
Peek Andrew McCarthy, you know.
Peek Andrew McCarthy.
That is true.
Peek Andrew McCarthy for sure.
It's it's it's what's her name.
It's it's oh, my God.
Him control.
Him control at the height of her powers.
My God, she's unstoppable.
I mean, if you want a little peek into what formed old Paul, baby Paul's idea of.
Because it was so mysterious up to this point.
He who would have thought that Paul's ideal woman would be a beautiful Kim control
that could then turn into a life size action figure who would have ever imagined.
I'll tell you who else wanted to fuck a mannequin when they were a kid and still kind to do.
And that's the following spot.
That's the whole thing about Mannequin.
He sets up these beautiful, elaborate sets in the windows and becomes famous for his
beautiful sets.
I just wanted to see one where the mannequin is dripping goo from the previous night's
escapades.
Did they use this mannequin and shooting Ghostbusters covered in slime?
Following sponsor, why does this Macy's display say, mind if I use your shower?
Today's show is brought to you by an eyewash station.
Please do not touch the mannequin goo.
Seriously, no washcloths.
Today's show is brought to you by Feral Child's wedding video voiceover service.
That's right.
If you need a wedding video voiceover, you can get it done by Feral Child.
That's from Nola Scoop in 2021.
What was like when proposed to stay together for life?
Well, now can remember with Feral Child's voice.
Remember, mom and dad walk down the aisle.
Remember, dog carry ring.
Remember, little boy pee on altar.
Accidents happen.
Remember, bridesmaid get caught on fire from standing next to candelabra.
Remember, bridesmaid require eight years plastic surgery to regain facial recognition.
Remember, bridesmaid still not right in hand about terrible burning.
Oh, I got to fast forward through this part.
Bridesmaid and bridesmaids say vengeance will be hers.
Oh, man, we got a lot of bridesmaids.
I'm going fast forward a little more.
Okay, here we go.
She's still alive.
Most of head look hamburger, but she not gone.
Enter eight scoops of checkout.
Fourth surgery not successful.
That bridesmaid ruined my wedding video.
I mean, it's an event to remember.
You'll never forget that time the bridesmaid caught on fire.
No, you won't.
You won't.
Oh, man, I watched hacks, season four of hacks on the plane.
Okay.
On the plane here.
I fell off of hacks.
I liked the first two seasons a lot.
And then I fell off somewhere in season three.
And then I picked up a season four, obviously missing some of the information from the end
of season three, I feel like I gathered all that information pretty quickly.
And then I just watched three episodes of them being horrible to each other
and then being horrible people.
And I was like, where are the jokes?
What am I supposed to be watching?
Because the first two seasons of it were like, they were too close to home for us.
Oh, sure.
It was too much Las Vegas showbiz and it was too accurate.
Yes.
And yeah, now it's, oh, well, this is just, okay, I get it now.
All right.
Yeah.
Broken people being mean.
When they, and they changed what the show is.
They change it from, she's like the older person who's trying to revitalize her career.
And now she's just rich and powerful.
Yeah.
And I was like, who am I supposed to be rooting for and where and why?
What am I supposed to want to do to do things?
Right.
And I just was like, oh man, it put me in such a bad mood.
I was really in like a sour mood getting off my plane.
Oh.
And I literally was like, why am I in a bad mood?
I was like, today's nothing.
I'm just traveling.
All I'm doing is traveling and get to get to get to my friend's house
to go grab dinner and watch football.
How am I in a bad mood?
And I was like, I think hacks put me in a bad mood.
Thanks a lot, Elizabeth Smart.
Well, there's your hacks hacks.
Don't watch it.
And I know people who write on it.
I know people who film it and stuff.
But I pulled out, I pulled their names out on my phone and showed them to my friends.
Gene Smart.
Thank you.
Who was it designing women with me?
Shaq Taylor who played Hollywood iconic mannequin character.
Seven degrees the Hollywood.
You know, it all goes back to mannequin.
You know, it goes back to mannequin.
Paul, Paul, Elizabeth Taylor.
Okay.
Elizabeth Taylor married briefly to Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson married briefly to Priscilla Presley.
Priscilla Presley married briefly to a mannequin named Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson was a mannequin.
Hollywood.
And say only four degrees, four degrees, four degrees.
It wasn't as smart with a girl who was kidnapped, right?
I would rather watch that than the rest of the hack season.
You'd rather watch Elizabeth Smart be kidnapped.
Rather just watch it.
Apologies to Elizabeth Smart.
Andy Cheek is pointing out I got it wrong.
It wasn't Priscilla Presley.
It was Lisa Marie that he married.
Okay.
I don't know that he didn't marry Priscilla.
I'm not a Michael Jackson historian.
Exactly.
She went from one King of Pop to the next.
I am watching Task.
You're still doing it.
Okay.
Yes.
It's so depressing.
You're putting Matt in a bad mood.
But I'm just in.
It does make me so sad.
But I'm going to bed then.
You're ready though.
You're ready for that.
I'm going to bed sad.
I did that for my whole childhood.
No.
But the thing about it is so Mark Ruffalo,
he grows his hair out.
He's got kind of bushy hair.
And then he gets a head injury at one point.
And he also gets beat up.
So his back is all jacked up.
So at one point he walks in.
It's like a dead serious scene.
It's like a pivotal scene in the series.
And he is walking and talking like Columbo.
Like he is just being Columbo.
It's full on now at this point.
He just looks like Columbo.
And he's literally doing the like, yeah, just one more thing.
And like he's bringing up things that he knows that he figured out.
And he's trying to make a guy basically cave.
He's Peter Falk in it.
And I'm so distracted.
I'm like, this is like four o'clock in the morning on my cruise ship.
But I'm like, this is just Columbo.
I'm just watching this thing from Columbo.
This guy could have found Elizabeth Smart.
Six episode wind up of watching the most depressed hunk of American life.
And I am just totally distracted by this Columbo impersonation.
I'm watching this thing.
It looks right out of Columbo.
Mark Ruffa Columbo.
Yeah.
Well, my other excitement and all the fracas that went on last night
and getting everything squared away, getting the dogs where they need to be.
Because we're wrestling around.
I'm wearing my this new hoodie that Mizzoula got for me, which I love.
It's this really cool Star Wars hoodie that he got for me.
And I put some doggy treats in the pocket.
To because I was, you know, wrestling, wrangling dogs.
I'm doing laundry today and I put it in my second load.
And I go to clear out my second load and I had left the doggy treats.
And I'm like, fuck me.
Cleanest doggy treats in Pittsburgh.
I'm so mad.
And it's just, luckily it was the gunk of it.
The treats were all just in the pocket and the sweater.
It didn't break out.
You didn't get the rest of the laundry exactly.
But I had to clean, clean, clean the sweater out.
And it's still not coming clean exactly.
It's in the dryer now.
But I took the rest of that load that looked fairly okay.
You know, it didn't have like stuff in it, but it had been washed.
I've always said that about your loads.
Your loads usually look fairly okay.
They look fairly okay.
But well, they look best when dripping out of mannequins.
Sure, sure.
But I-
Use the eye wash station.
Please save yourselves.
But I threw everything in the dryer and then I go to take the stuff out of the dryer.
And I'm taking it out and I, you know, because I used the like the little,
the scent booster stuff, the anyway, the downy scent, whatever it is.
Yeah.
Anyway, I give a little sniff and it's got just this sort of very faint,
but they're sort of beefiness to it.
And it was like, fuck, I have to wash all these clothes again.
Why did you have to wash?
But they already had the scent of beef.
Why did you wash them again, Paul?
I'm trying to rid myself of the scent of beef.
I'm trying to un-beef my laundry.
You have beef experience.
I do, brother, do I.
So this is-
I'm looking for that right now.
This is my afternoon is-
Oh, I know what beef is.
I have had beef experience.
I know beef.
It's true.
And brother.
Know it, I wear it.
Exactly.
So yeah, that's my excitement for the day is cleaning my new favorite shirt and finding
I sabotaged my new favorite shirt with a bunch of fucking dog treats.
With beef scent.
So hopefully-
Some say sabotage, some say improve.
Hopefully it's fixed.
We'll see.
It dried finally.
We'll see what's going on.
Good Lord.
I want, I want all of Paul's wardrobe to just smell like beef.
Well, give it a couple days.
It might.
We'll see.
I need to put some more perfume on it, maybe.
Yeah, that's probably what it's missing.
All right, you want to do a little scoop mail?
That's all I want to do.
I ache for it.
Message for you, son.
We got one here from Poutine Scoops.
Hello fuckers.
Here's an Italian air show story from my childhood.
Back in 1995, there was a referendum in Quebec to separate from Canada.
As dumb as 13 year old me and my friend thought, we're gonna need our own money as a country.
We proceeded to heat up a Canadian penny with a lighter
to engrave it with a fleur de lis or something.
The lighter didn't soften the penny enough, so we went outside
and grabbed the red gas can for the lawnmower, oh, gas can, gotta be gas.
Grabbed the red gas can for the lawnmower and tried to soften the penny some more.
Spoiler, you can't melt a penny with gas as a 13 year old.
What?
Jet fuel doesn't melt steel pennies.
No, I guess not.
We put too much gas on and at some point, my genius self tries to put the fire out
by stomping it down with the first thing I got on my hand, which was the red gas can.
What?
So you had a fire that you were trying to melt a penny in the fire, pouring gasoline on it,
and then you had the gas can in your hand, and so you tried to use the gas can to then tamp out.
Tamp out the flame, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh no.
Oh yeah.
We now have a significant red gas can fire on our hands.
My friend runs to grab the water hose with the full red gas can on fire.
Won't stop burning because it's a gas can.
Quick, get more gas.
We gotta put up the gas fire.
Throw some rice on that.
Oh, that would have fixed it.
Now, do you guys remember the red gas cans exploding in 80s movies?
Because I did.
It's gonna just explode and destroy the house.
I'd better kick it farther away from the house.
Oh no.
So the bottom of the red gas can had already melted on the grass,
so only the top of the can got kicked away and the not yet burned gas went everywhere.
So as a 13-year-old on fire guy, I proceeded to...
I don't know what that's supposed to say.
This is an oddly written letter.
I think this person might still be on fire when--
This is a traumatic event, clearly, for this individual.
Yeah.
I am watching it burn right now.
I type as I...
I'm doing voice-to-text!
This group is reliving this, yeah.
Went all the way around the house to the back to get my water hose
friend who then extinguished my legs.
Oh my god.
Your legs caught fire?
Yeah.
This reminds me of a wedding video I just saw.
The girl with the flame on the chain and she tosses it all over the place?
Oh, I haven't seen that.
Oh, okay.
Did it really happen?
She burned up people?
Yeah, she tossed a flame ball into the crowd of people at a wedding.
Does they all freak out when it happens?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Did anybody die?
Three months in the hospital, skin grafts, all the things.
My legs still look weird, but they weren't great.
The worst thing about it is my scars won't sweat and it's a good part of my legs,
so the end of the scars sweat like crazy because it's all going out wherever it can.
Oh!
It gets a little itchy, but no big deal.
I'm so sorry, Poutine Scoop.
Oh, that's so awful.
The referendum went 50.2 to 49.8.
So no, I'm still Canadian and we still don't have our own pennies.
That's Poutine Scoop.
You know, I don't think Canada even has pennies now.
So it's all for naught.
Well, I don't think they even have pennies now.
Just like us, I think they also got rid of their pennies.
I see Crystal Twist is saying I'm right.
They don't have pennies anymore.
Oh!
So not only was it for naught, but it wouldn't have even worked before.
Well, technically, the US has never had pennies.
We have one-cent pieces.
The English and the Canadians have pennies.
There's no US.
Poutine Scoop.
That is such a heartbreaker.
As a former young adolescent boy who played with fire, I can only say that there but for
the grace of fate do I not join you in insanity.
I remember one day we were at a friend's house and he put gasoline in one of those little
plastic dinosaurs that are about six inches tall, right?
Do you remember those old hard plastic dinosaurs?
Yeah, yeah.
And they were hollow in the middle.
Exactly.
So he filled it up with gasoline and he set the mouth on fire,
thinking it was going to look like breathing fire.
I'm with this kid.
This is a smart kid.
It didn't really do much.
It just started melting the face.
But then he went and tipped the tail and the gasoline barfed out of the
thing and it filled this basement with fire.
And lucky there was nothing on the floor.
You were inside doing this.
It was, yeah, it was inside a basement.
It's a concrete floor and luckily nobody got hurt and it got out.
But it was scary.
Burned the house down.
It was scary for a minute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's actually pretty scary here at the core sensors building.
Zach broke the light.
So there's a light that broke the light and now we'll never find our way out of here.
I live here now.
Well, at least you've got some sensors and gauges.
That's right.
If I'm wondering how much pressure I'm under to finish this episode,
I can actually figure out that number right now.
But I appreciate Poutine sharing that trauma with us for our interview.
I definitely, we definitely went through like a fire period when we were kids.
Yeah.
Everything we would hear about.
There was this, there was this period of time in the 80s and 90s
where you'd hear about these things and people would tell them as cautionary tales.
Like make sure you don't mix, what was it?
Ivory soap and gasoline on an electric stovetop because that's how you can make napalm.
Yes.
And would be told that it would be like, well, clearly that's what we're going to do.
I'd say it's time to make some napalm.
Yeah.
Yeah, and we would do that.
We had like a hot plate out somewhere.
Like somebody had gotten a hot plate.
And I remember we were in a culvert one time in some neighborhood.
A hot plate in a culvert?
Yeah, it was crazy shit.
We read one time that if you cut off a whole bunch of strike anywhere match heads
and shoved them into a tennis ball, that it would act like a hand grenade.
Right.
Which it shockingly almost worked exactly like that.
It was, you talk about like pouring gas on the floor of the basement.
The hand grenade tennis ball was my pouring gas on the floor of the basement.
Where'd you throw it?
We were outside and I don't think I threw it.
I think one of the other guys threw it and just up against the brick wall.
Oh shit.
And like it just went.
It exploded and little nubs of fire.
Just thousands of little nubs of fire just went in every direction.
Wow.
And it definitely started a couple of fires.
It was terrifying.
Oh god.
Yeah.
We used to ride our bikes up to the recycling center.
Steal newspaper out of the recycling center newspaper.
And then we took matches from a bucket of matches at 7-Eleven.
And then we would go light newspaper on fire.
Yeah.
It's its own fault for being so flammable.
That'll teach it.
That'll learn it.
We got one here from Anonymous Scoop X.
This recently happened and understandably I can't possibly tell anyone in my life.
But this is where you three boys and your confession booth of frozen dairy delights comes in.
Yay.
Here we are.
Now we're actually serving our purpose.
This gentleman falls within the first blow job topic.
Oh.
Falls in?
Sounds like there's some qualifiers here.
It sounds like there might be.
I've been dating my almost 40-year-old partner
as a 34-year-old woman I can't bring myself to say boyfriend for the last few years.
We were flirtatious friends for many years which escalated
to friends with benefits and finally to long-distance partners.
We'd meet up every month or so in person, go on dates,
play games and perhaps most crucially fuck for hours.
It's been a journey of exploration for both of us.
We both have what is probably an unreasonably high sex drive
and we both enjoyed exploring new kinks and experiences.
I take particular pride in bringing any dream or fantasy to life for the champ.
As a former cosplayer, I've also had a lot of fun sewing costumes,
making outfits and embroidering and embodying new characters.
Amazing.
As much as I've wanted to play out some of these things,
it's the first time I've met someone who was as adventurous as I was who I was comfortable with.
Jacob, this is clearly AI or some weird old penthouse forum thing
where someone's just pretending to be awesome.
I never thought it would happen to me.
Can't be true, this can't be true.
This is real life, David.
Matt, all of those penthouse forum letters had to come from real people,
so I mean clearly those things really happened.
All right.
All of this is important context for what came next.
It was always a running joke in our friendship group that my fellow
was two scoops of plain old vanilla.
As an alternative lass covered in tattoos and arresting bitch face
to rival the best in the business,
we managed to go completely under the radar for a long time.
But behind closed doors, he was very different.
We dabbled in toys, different positions, role plays.
We would laugh about how if they knew, they'd be shocked.
Cut to a few weeks ago, years down the line, two days in a row,
I'd woken the chap up with a good morning blow job.
He recovers quickly, so both mornings, he'd manage to come twice in a row before work.
Holy smoke.
What can I say, I'm dedicated to the craft.
That's an incredible refractory period.
That is.
Anyway, after day two--
This man should be studied by RFK Jr.
I don't know how you do that.
Anyway, after day two, we were talking away, and it got into the topic of porn.
He let me in on the fact that he watches role play porn.
The boy watches it for the plot.
I was in absolute hysterics.
I couldn't believe it.
I didn't know these people still existed.
He's really rooting for that pizza delivery boy.
He asked what porn I watched, and I had to explain that
I didn't think he would know what all the letters stood for in my search term.
I'd simply said, if there are less than four people in the room,
I'm probably not interested.
He was also surprised when I said that I can't stand the introduction,
so I just pass forward to the good bits.
So L-E-M-O-N, those are the types of things you put in there?
That's right, that's right.
Lemon party.
P-A-R-T-Y, because I like it.
That's when the situation escalated, and it hit me like a bust to the face.
Well, I'm quite vanilla.
You know that, or I was before we met.
Before you, I'd only had one blowjob.
He mumbled, somewhat embarrassed.
Then in an even quieter voice, he said, well, sort of half of one.
He explained, one girlfriend once had tried it and decided it wasn't really for her.
Had been married since, and she was absolutely not forgiving it a go.
Boys, I'm ashamed to say I laughed my fucking ass off for a long time.
Throughout the day, periodically, I laughed repeatedly, and not a chuckle.
I laughed at the volume of a demented, drug-addled clown.
I couldn't believe that he was telling me this many years down the line,
what must be literally hundreds of blowjobs later.
He'd had four blowjobs in the space of 24 hours,
compared to the half a job he'd had in the previous 38 years of life.
It's important to say I wasn't laughing at him.
I was just laughing at the ridiculousness of the situation.
Yeah.
Although apparently clarifying that did not make up for how hard I was laughing at the time.
So that's my story of how my partner's dreams came true
when he realized he'd met a human vacuum cleaner
who'd happily putter around in a homemade poison ivy outfit.
Oh, poison ivy outfit, full circle.
If it meant hit be happy, although not quite a first blowjob story,
you'd have to have a very specific category for the first blowjob story for that one.
Thanks for giving me an outlet for this tale.
The podcast brings me absolute joy.
That's Anonymous Scoop X.
Thank you, Anonymous Scoop.
And like most people that like our podcast,
Anonymous Scoop insists on remaining anonymous.
People don't want to like our podcast openly.
I get it.
Hey, the fade button works.
Nice.
That's a nice change.
It's time for Jack vs. Nerd.
It's on.
You ain't doing no Jack vs. Nerd action.
Oh, am I?
Fuck, yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
No.
We got a scooper today from Swedish Scoop.
The categories are San and Santa, Shakin' My Spear, Old MCD, Deformed Farm.
Do you think that girl went on to blow someone else?
Do you feel like she's also had to retell that story to a partner?
The one who wasn't for me?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think later she got used to it?
Tried another?
I doubt it.
I didn't used to like this nearly as much as I do now.
But these days, I don't even talk without a cock in my dick.
That's right.
Old McDonald's Deformed Farm.
Oh, that's what that Old McDonald's Deformed Farm and songs I weep for.
Okay.
Paul, you're up.
Well, I got to try Old McDonald's Deformed Farm.
For 400, this animal had an ab-ab here and an ab-ab there.
Here an ab, there an ab, everywhere an ab-ab.
That's A-A-B is how ab is spelled.
Oh, jeez.
I mean, like a deformed sheep, I guess.
I guess.
Oh, a dyslexic sheep.
Oh, they all have a condition.
Okay.
All right, we get it now.
All right.
Matt, you're up.
Songs I Weep For.
Eponine, I never remember how to say her name.
Eponine sings this song of unrequited love and loneliness in Les Miserables.
What's it called?
I love him that every day I'm learning.
Master of the House.
That's it.
I can't remember, Pass.
Passes to me.
Shit, all I could think of is, oh wait, is it Castle on a Cloud?
That's the little girl song.
Yeah, I don't remember who is who.
I don't remember what French name belongs with what character in Les Mis.
ScooperNovaGirl typed it into the chat if you just want to read it and get it right.
Oh, okay.
I can't see the chat.
You guys can see the chat during the--
Oh, I didn't know that we have this advantage on you, Jacob.
Oh yeah, no, I can't see the chat during the scooperties
because I'm sharing my screen so you guys can see the scooperty.
Pretty great.
Oh, is it?
On my own.
Wait, you can't see the chat?
He grabbed.
No.
That's so funny.
He grabbed it.
All right.
I mean, I know the show.
You knew the song, yeah.
Yeah, I just had to find it in my head.
Me, it's-- I don't know what San and Santa is, so let's try that.
400.
Jesus's mom in Espanol.
So how do you say fictional in Spanish?
[LAUGHTER]
How do you say historical fiction?
What, so it's Mary in Spanish?
I think it's different than that.
OK, I pass then.
Paul.
I think it's Magdalena.
Oh, I see.
Santa Maria.
Well, shit on me.
Shit on my penis.
Mary Magdalena.
Paul.
Fucking shit my dick.
I'll do songs I weep for for 2000, because I got to get on the board.
Fire Maple Song is a single off the first album by this '90s rock band,
better known for Wonderful and Santa Monica.
Oh, that's Everclear.
Everclear is correct.
I saw them at concert.
On the board.
They were terrible.
No.
Yeah, they were awful.
Matt, you're up.
I left before they were done.
I'll do Shaken My Spear for 400.
I've never gone out of my way to see Everclear.
This tragedy focuses on a pair of star-crossed lovers from Fair Verona.
Did you know the girl was only 13?
Yoinks.
It's about Jerry Lee Lewis.
This is Romeo and Juliet.
Romeo and Juliet.
Is that the whole answer?
I don't know.
I forgot what the category is.
I believe that's the answer.
Oh yeah, Romeo and Juliet.
I didn't know if it was going to be like a Romeo and Juliet,
get fucked, or something like that.
Let's see.
I'll try, I don't know, Shaken My Spear for 800.
Daily Double.
Tomorrow and Tomorrow and Tomorrow is a famous soliloquy from this Scottish play.
That would be the Scottish play Macbeth.
MacGregor the Bridge Builder.
No.
Macbeth is correct.
Paul.
I'll try Old MacDonald for 2000.
Wow.
This animal had a crack-crack here and a crack-crack there.
Here a crack, there a crack, everywhere a crack-crack.
Oh my gosh.
It's probably an arthritic duck, but I don't want to guess for 2000 points.
I'll pass.
Matt.
Pass.
Or what's that condition that Mr. Glass had?
A drug-dealing duck.
Oh, drug-dealing duck.
Good lord.
See, there's a lot of ways that could have gone.
Crack-crack here and a crack-crack there.
Yeah, I would have gone like a plumber duck or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Matt could have been a plumber.
Shaken My Spear at 1200.
This titled Prince of Denmark asks, "Am I a coward?" in Shakespeare's longest play.
Hamlet?
Indeed.
Hamlet is correct.
Where's the thing?
There it is.
Me, I'll try, I'll close out Shaken My Spear.
I actually know these.
Shakespeare's wife shares a name with this modern actress of The Dark Night Rises,
Selina Kyle and Le Miserable Fantine Fane.
It's your girl, Matt.
Oh yeah.
Catwoman.
Batgirl or Catwoman?
I don't remember, but it's one of them.
It was actually Catwoman, but she went Batgirl.
Who was Batgirl in that movie?
I can't think of her name.
Princess Diaries.
Oh, now you got me on it.
I don't fucking hardly remember her name either.
I don't like her at all.
Pass, baby, pass.
Matt's just sitting there just slowly jacking it.
He's just keeping it in half-staff.
He's ready to go.
I can't remember her name.
All right, half-staff, Donnelly, what you got?
Anne Hathaway about her.
Oh, yes, there it is.
Anne Hathaway.
Where there is a will, Anne Hathaway.
Yeah, she does.
I'll try songs that I weep for for $1,200.
It's not time to make a change.
Just relax.
Take it easy.
Sings Cat Stephen, Youssef Islam in This Tearjerker.
Oh, this is a good one.
This one got me for real, in real life, because I listened to that.
I went through the Cat Stevens binge when I moved to the Virgin Islands,
and I was living off of my own.
And then I listened to it after I had a child.
And I indeed felt both sides of the song, and it fucking destroyed me.
I have to pass because I can't remember the title of the song.
It goes to Matt.
What is it?
Father and Son.
That got you?
Believe it or not.
Yeah, yeah.
Interesting.
I hope you don't ever have kids.
It'll really get you.
Um, it's really, you know, the lyrics respond back and forth between Father and the Son.
And that's it's super, super deep.
And I think it's a really good song that they sued.
Who's that psychedelic band ended up just absolutely just copying the song by accident
and had and had to pay up in the lawsuit.
I don't know.
I'll look it up in a sec.
Someone to check and look it up.
But was it in the in the 60s?
They did it?
No, it was in the late 90s of the 2000s.
There's a Flaming Lips.
That's what it was.
Flaming Lips.
Oh, Flaming Lips basically ripped one off.
Too similar to Father and Son.
In the settlement, the bands agreed to a royalty split
with Stevens receiving 75 percent of the publishing royalties from Fight Test.
Yeah.
Okay.
Man, Cat Stevens had some good lawyers on that lawsuit.
He sure did.
Holy shit.
Let's see.
What is it?
Matt, your turn.
I will do.
Score check.
By the way, Matt is crushing both Paul and I.
He has 4,800.
Paul and I both have 1,200 each.
I can step into it with Daily Doubles here.
I'll do songs that I weep for for 800.
Daily Doubles!
There it comes.
Oh, no.
From your mouth to my ears.
This legendary Academy Award winning song asks,
"If happy little bluebirds fly, why, oh why, can't I?"
It also ranked number one on AFI's 100 years, 100 song list.
Baby Got Back.
Somewhere Over the Rainbow.
Oh, I just brought back a flashback of Judy Garland
singing that 100 feet high in the sphere.
Was it crazy?
I'll try.
Yeah, it was. It was really crazy.
San and Santa for 800.
This is what you get when you eat breakfast on the beach in California.
High property taxes, am I right?
I don't know.
What's the thing?
Salmon Sand?
I have no idea.
I'll pass.
Paul?
A breakfast sandwich?
Oh, San Diego.
I get it now.
Paul?
Old Deform McDonald for 1200.
This animal had a rub-it, rub-it here and a rub-it, rub-it there.
Here a rub-it, there a rub-it, everywhere a rub-it, rub-it.
It's got to be a habitual masturbating frog.
A vitally masturbating frog.
Close enough, perverted frog.
Matt?
A horny toad.
I'll do San Santa.
I'll horny toad.
1200.
Horny toads.
Musicals adore this New Mexico city with characters in both newsies and rent,
dreaming of running away to there.
Santa Fe?
But how do the songs go, Matt?
I don't know the Newsy Santa Fe song.
Santa Fe.
But I'll do the whole score of rent for you right now.
The newsies are trying to get to Santa Fe?
The one, Christian Bale's character, he sings the whole song about Santa Fe.
What?
It's like, it's the big torch song.
It's like Santa Fe, I'll be there, I don't remember anymore.
I mean, I've been to the city, it's fine.
That's a perfectly plausible city.
How can that compare to New York?
I don't get it.
Well, that's why there's only two songs about it, not the dozens about New York.
I suppose you're right.
Let's see, it's me.
I have 1200, Paul has 1600, Matt has 10,800.
There are two questions left and no more deadly doubles.
Anybody's game.
I'll try Santa and Santa for 2000.
This character threatened Chris the octopus in a heartwarming children's tale.
It isn't Chris's fault, he lost his hat.
Yeah.
So that's the homeless guy, the bum.
No, no, no, he didn't threaten him.
Okay.
What's the category, Jacob?
Oh, I don't remember.
Santa and Santa.
Oh, he's the bum dressed as Santa?
It's just Santa Claus.
Santa Claus is the villain in Christmas.
Santa Claus is basically the bad guy in Christmas.
Isn't Santa Claus the bum though, too?
No, he is the surrogate for Rudolph.
Oh, I haven't read Christmas plus recently enough.
It's all right.
Well, we're working on the sequel.
It'll be a big thing.
Yeah, I'll bone up on the original.
So I'm not confused by any of the plot lines.
We're going to do some reprints.
Yeah, it'll be awesome.
It's going to close it out the category and the game.
Old Mac Deform, Old Mac Deform Farm.
Yeah, you know.
Yes, Old Mac Deform Farm.
This animal had a hith hith here and a hith hith there.
Good Lord.
Here a hith, there a hith, everywhere a hith hith.
It also starred in Disney's Robin Hood.
Mike Tyson the snake.
If Mike Tyson was a snake, this is what I would sound like.
It's a it's a lispy snake.
A lispy Mike Tyson snake.
Nailed it.
And that is the game.
Matt Donnelly ekes out the win with ten thousand eight hundred points.
I'm in second with thirty two hundred.
Matt said Paul's in third with twenty four hundred.
That's from Swedish Scoop.
Thank you, Swedish Scoop.
If you want to send us a scooper or a price of Skraite,
Jock versus Nerd or Anomalous, Jock versus Nerd,
or just send us some email.
Head over to HayScoops.com.
You know what else you can do at HayScoops.com?
You can buy Scoop Fest merch.
That's right.
There is twenty twenty five Scoop Fest merch there.
You got Fezzes, you got hats, not hats.
The Fezzes are the hats.
You got Fezzes, you got robes and a pair of T-shirts that you can choose between.
They're all really cool.
Do the thing.
Oh, and if you buy a T-shirt, a robe and a Fez all together,
there's a discount that kicks in at checkout.
There you go.
Yeah.
So if you buy the whole package, there's a discount that kicks in later on.
Get the package, Scoops.
Yeah.
And post those pics on the tag HayScoops.
We want to see you in your robes and Fez.
Yeah, we do.
Also, yeah, this Thursday, by the time you're hearing this,
but people on Zoom, but this Thursday, you can see Paul and I at Tierney's Tavern.
Just come out to Tierney's Tavern.
It's 20 bucks.
So soon.
We're going to do some improv, we're going to do some stand-ups, some magic.
You know, it's going to be a casual fun day.
It's going to be super, super fun.
Super, super fun.
We've already got a bunch of Scoops going.
It's going to feel like a homecoming for Matt.
It's going to feel like a mini Scoop churn out for us.
Yeah.
It's going to be great.
It's going to be very fun.
Can't wait to do it.
So come check it out.
You can go to HayScoops.com/ComedyNight and grab your tickets there.
Yes.
You guys, yeah, you continue to make us look like rock stars
when we have these events and lots of you show up.
It's pretty awesome.
Cannot confirm or deny Chris Christie's attendance.
Cannot confirm or deny.
Well, keep it hush hush.
As long as he doesn't have to get on a bridge.
Can he fit in tyrannies?
I want to thank the following people who support us on our page.
All of these people played both Batgirl and Catwoman
in my musical version of Batman.
Fucking range.
Scoopy Scoopy Jess Jess,
Scoopy Bartfast,
Scoopy Ramone,
Scoopy Dooby Doo,
Scoopy and the Beast,
Scoop Trek the Experience,
Scoop So Hazard,
Scoopometrics,
Scoop Nick,
Scoop Neon Black,
Scoop Lakisa,
Scoop Neck Patty Whack,
Scoop Kata,
Scoop JD,
Scoopitor Ascending,
Scoopy Lauren,
Scooper Nova Girl,
Scooper Metroid,
and Scoopa Luga.
By the way, quick shout out.
I watched the movie Ballerina on another flight.
Plot not dissimilar to Gymkhana.
Plot not dissimilar.
She has the her dance moves are her special weapon kind of thing.
Like, no, it's just goes like in Gymkhana.
It just goes to a village and just people just want to kill him.
And that's the plot is that a bunch of people send them out where they go in the villages.
And then the village happens to have a pommel horse in the center of it.
Yes.
Right, right.
Because if not for that pommel horse, he's dead.
Yes.
Ballerina found to be very similar to that movie.
There's a ballet bar in the middle of a village.
If it weren't for that ballet bar, it should be dead.
One of the whole walls of the village is a mirrored wall with a ballet bar.
They have a ballet bar and a mirroring wall.
Good lord.
Paul.
Oh, the following people.
I had one.
What was it?
I had thought of a joke.
I forgot it.
I did.
Do you want someone else to go?
Jacob, go.
Oh, shit.
No, I don't have a joke.
What do you think I have a joke ready for?
Yeah.
I don't have a joke already.
I'll finish up then.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll come up with something.
The following people.
I gotta go.
Looking for love in all the wrong places.
Scoop DeJour.
Scoop a real good.
Scoop Emily.
Scoop Dave Ville.
Scoop Chang the Beijing Mugle.
Scoop Bucky.
Scoop Brady.
Scabby the Rat Scoop.
Sex Guy Jimmy D. Scoop.
Sarah Boyle.
Sandra Petrovich.
Sam Reed.
Saltlick Scoop.
Second Mingle.
Ryar Appledorn.
Ryan Hayward.
Rose.
Rod Heck.
Roger Edge.
And Rodimus Scoop.
The following people.
All approve and disapproved of Annie's different outfit choices in a montage in an 80s movie.
Scoop Mids.
Scoop Paul's Drag Race.
Scoopa Troopa.
Scoopaholic.
Scoop T.
Scoop Skywalker.
Scoop of Saltwater.
Scoop Nurse.
Scoop Mipha.
Scoop Lord Tristan.
Scoop Lindsay.
And Scoop Jesus.
The following people are interns cleaning mannequins.
Robots Ahoy.
Robert Paulson.
Richard Hill.
Richard Graffiti.
Richard Fastknot.
Richard Dunn.
Richard Dunn again.
Reverend Nick Ningman of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster.
Remember the Alamode.
Refrigerator Perry Scoop and Randy Glenn.
And the following Scoops all wrote in and specifically asked me to say their names
very slowly this month.
This is Randy.
There's Ralph Barrett.
There's Raggedy Girl.
Radioactive Scoop.
Matt, just get comfy.
Quiet Quiet Scoop.
Pryro, Proto Scoop, Proper Scoop.
He's gone.
He's out.
Matt's out.
Philip Guyden.
Phil Tomlinson.
Phil Renley.
Petty Officer Scoop.
Peter Sansone.
Peter McDougall.
Peter Hines.
Peter Burford.
Peter Bougie.
Peter Romano.
Pebeck Scoop.
P.E. Scoop.
Polygon.
Paula.
Paul's brother.
Paul Hoser Scoop.
Luxton.
Onefell Scoop.
Okie Scoop.
Nicky Benoit.
Nicole Levin.
Nicole Busenbach.
And Nicholas Petty.
Thank you all so much.
If you want to be thanked on air or get discounts to our events or get ad-free episodes of our show,
there's all kinds of different rewards and tiers for you over at patreon.com/hayscoops.
Oh, so confusing.
Oh no.
Type in preachingfun.com.
Or if you've had a rough day and need to explain it to somebody in a Taco Bell drive-thru,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz.
Along with preaching fun, that will take you to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
That's right, this show's got bills.
Hopefully, you think it's worth more than $0.
And hopefully, you'd like to go over to preachingfun.com/fartsinabag.biz.
Sign up today to be a Patreon.
Hey, that Patreon, the whole goddamn thing is about to get turned upside down on its head.
Not Patreon in general, just ours.
We're going to change it all up.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
So keep your eyes out.
We're changing a few things.
Huge changes.
Dogs and cats laying together.
Very casual pruning of our Patreon that's happening.
No, no, it's huge changes.
I like that technical support looks like he's giving technical support in his window there.
Oh, good.
It's legit.
The name's legit.
Nominative determinism.
Oh, he's got the company shirt on and everything.
All right, I want to thank Core Systems for giving me a home here.
Pocket some of those pressure sensors.
Pressure sensors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can see that.
I want to thank Pendula for creating this podcast.
And I want you all to stay safe out there.
Know that we love you.
And we hope to see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
I've got a fucking fly in my face.
Let all these spiders live down here.
They're not doing their fucking job.
Maybe the squirrel ate the spiders.
But why would he eat the spider to swallow the fly?
I don't know why.
Okay.
Maybe he'll fucking die.
Perhaps.
See ya!
There aren't many guarantees in life, but there are in life insurance.
If you're 50 to 85 years old, call Colonial Pen now.
1-800-757-4488.
With Colonial Pen's guaranteed acceptance, there are no physicals, no health questions,
just permanent, whole life insurance designed to help cover final expenses and medical costs.
And as long as you pay your premiums, your policy can never be canceled.
That's right.
All those worries you have?
How your family will manage the bills when you're gone?
Will they be okay financially?
Colonial Pen is the answer.
Plans are available to fit almost any budget,
because cost should never be the reason you can't protect your family.
So again, if you're 50 to 85, call 1-800-757-4488 now
for your free beneficiary planner from Colonial Pen.
There's absolutely no obligation.
That's 1-800-757-4488.
1-800-757-4488.
Two-year limited benefit period.
Ages vary by state.
Once insured, your rate will never go up.
You choose an option that's best for you.
Premium is based on the option you choose.
Benefit amount based on age and gender.
As long as you pay your premiums, coverage can never be canceled.