Hey Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great! Let's go!
Oh man, it is Scoop Fest here in Las Vegas!
Let me hear your scoops!
Of course we have a great night here with us.
It's time for Matt Madley's Ice Cream Social!
Sitting to my left is Paul Mattingly!
Across from me, that's Mr. Matt Donnelly!
From the knobs and tiles is Jacob the Audio Guy!
Oh, I love that guy!
We're preaching fun!
How we doing, Scoop Fest?
We've had a long Scoop Fest.
Yeah, it's been a good one.
It's been a real good one.
You guys having a good Scoop Fest so far?
Oh, thank God! I'm glad it's not just me.
Yeah, it's been a blast. It's been such a cool deal.
Of course, we just always got to cap it off as our last kind of live event
before we do the big jock versus nerd ball.
That's right!
So, gotta bring back our boys. Our brothers.
Our brothers from another podcast.
The O.O. Boys!
The O.O. Boys, if you will.
The O.O. Old school boys.
Gentlemen, thanks for being here.
Oh man, I mean it's the best.
It does not get better than hanging out at the Orleans at Scoop Fest.
Is it just us that like, I mean just Las Vegas is the Orleans to me?
Everyone else is trying too hard, the Orleans?
Oh, like in terms of like if you really try to boil down Las Vegas.
I feel like every other building in this town is trying to be something they're not
except for the one that we're sitting in right now.
It's the most honest building in Las Vegas.
Yeah, right down to the three alligators playing jazz.
The iconography of authenticity, anthropomorphized alligators.
And also like just the sheer size.
When you walk in the Orleans, they're like 20 foot alligators.
Yeah.
Like who turned in the drawings?
Like that's how much space it should take up when you walk into this place.
Yeah.
Can I?
Alright, so a long running joke that Brian and I have had whenever we've been at the Orleans
is that nobody knows when the Bailey Wick is open.
Yes.
Always true.
And they've posted hours.
I've never seen, like as far as I knew,
like it opened when somebody like phased into existence inside of it.
Like there is no rhyme or reason.
You have properly summoned Bailey Wick.
Want a beer?
But like they actually posted hours and they're even more fucked up.
It's like it's only open from like 3 p.m. to 10.
In Las Vegas at 10.
Yes.
No, your premium bar.
Fuck you, get out.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, the place for live music and food and booze?
Nope.
After 10 o'clock, you are not allowed in here.
Done.
Yeah.
Just psychotic, just sociopathic behavior by the Bailey Wick.
Somebody do a Netflix series on the Bailey Wick.
Let's go.
Find out what skeletons are in that attic.
Bailey Wick doc series.
TM.
That is ours.
So Brian, you have kept up your bit of asshole blackjack?
Oh, Jesus.
Now I know why he's homeless.
All right.
Yeah.
Now I am homeless.
Okay.
First of all, I was gambling with somebody who didn't like the idea of asshole blackjack
because he's somebody who feels like, hey, man, gambling is supposed to be fun.
And you're like actively, does anybody not know?
I don't know why I'm phrasing it this way.
We don't know it.
What's asshole blackjack?
How do you explain asshole blackjack?
Refresh.
So blackjack, game where cards come out.
People at tables get very mad if you are not playing correctly.
Quote, unquote, by the book.
By the book.
Because they believe that the cards that you got by playing incorrectly or didn't get by
playing incorrectly is affecting them.
And no matter who's sitting at the table, they want the table to play as a team as a
whole.
Yes.
Against the dealer, not against each other.
Just how it's supposed to go, right?
Right.
So what Brian does is the opposite.
Yes.
Well, every so often I'll play something a little bit off book or do something silly just
because it's delightful when doing something wrong yields amazing results.
And then I hear to my left, that was my ace or whatever.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And it's like, okay, well, then now we're no longer playing blackjack.
We're playing asshole blackjack, which usually lasts about five minutes, and then the game
is over and all my money is gone.
But every so often an epic run ends up happening.
And Justin and I laugh and shout and make a lot of noise, chase everyone off.
And then as we leave the table, they say, excuse me, you dropped your Percocet.
Yes.
A true thing that happened, one of the first times we played asshole blackjack is we just
infuriated a family from Alabama that were just like spitting fucking mad.
And we could not stop laughing.
And then at the end, my Percocets fell out of my pocket.
Now, just collapsing this fucking caricature of a human into startling relief.
Oh, this just got real.
Now, as I was trying to explain, the beauty of asshole blackjack is a piece of performance
art.
And I like to think of myself as a patron of the arts by spending all my money on asshole
blackjack.
Jesse, our friend, had the mistaken impression that the point was to piss people off.
No, that is a side effect.
Ah, yes.
That is righteous and good.
But it is not the point.
That's right.
The point is to bend reality just a little bit and maybe just maybe you'll get lucky
and doing the wrong thing will yield something magical.
So Jesse and I were playing blackjack and eventually got down to just the two of us.
Jesse did not believe in asshole blackjack.
He didn't believe it would work and he didn't much care for the idea of it.
And then I got dealt a five and the dealer had a three face up.
And then I got dealt another five and then a face down card, right?
So we all know what you're supposed to do in this situation, right?
Split.
Well, okay.
So I take my chip and I push it forward and they say double.
I said, "Uh-uh."
The rules say you're supposed to double there.
That's right.
Yeah.
So I split my fingers and I said, "No, split."
And they're like, "Are you sure?"
Do I look like a man who is sure?
Pit boss kind of glances over.
Yeah, yeah.
First card, an ace.
And then push that second chip forward.
To double down.
To double down on a soft 16.
All right.
Next one, five.
Three goes down.
It's an eight.
Yeah.
Chip goes forward.
Let's go.
Keep it going.
Finally, there's -- oh, wait.
I'm sorry.
I left out the most important part.
When I split them fives, the first card that was dealt was a five, at which point that got split.
So there are three fives.
I forgot that part of the story.
And it was upon the third five that another five was dealt.
Chip goes forward.
Four fives.
Four fives on the table.
Oh, man.
Another card.
It's like some bullshit in the teens.
And then finally, last one.
I think it was another -- I think it was another eight.
And I doubled down on it again, at which point 13 -- it ended up -- they threw down a bunch of cards.
And then they said the word's 21.
And I was like, "Well, dang it.
That would have been a neat story."
But then there was like a weird vibe.
And then she smiled and was like, "Eh?"
I'm like, "I don't get it.
You took all the money."
And they were like, "No, it's 21.
It's 22.
We busted.
You won."
And then they gave me a $500 chip.
Hey!
Believe in magic, people.
Yeah.
Assholes win.
Exactly.
Show your hole on the tables at the Orleans, the home of asshole blackjack.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just spread 'em.
Justin.
Yeah.
You're running the Politics, Politics, Politics podcast.
Yes.
Quiet, quiet, couple weeks.
Nothing to see.
Just real tumbleweeds, you know, bunch of action.
Does that mean, like, as a podcast, you consider it, like, a great time to be a political podcaster?
Like, how does it feel when things are so divulgent?
It feels great that I don't have to think about what I'm going to talk about.
Because you have to do, at a certain point, beyond all of the, you know, the subject matter,
is obviously as emotionally charged as you can make it.
But I have to kind of make the donuts every day.
Right.
It's a lot easier when it's like, "Okay, well, here's what we're talking about.
Now we're going to have somebody on, and we're going to talk about the very obvious thing
that everybody wants to hear about."
But, yeah, no, it's fucking insane.
It's crazy.
Do you ever wake up and be like, "I just want to do a football podcast."
I often fantasize about doing another podcast.
And then I realize that that's what's gotten me into this mess.
Doing too many fucking podcasts.
But usually, yeah, it's usually like that.
It's like, "Oh, my God, I would love to just have shitty hot takes on sports."
But then I'm like, "Eh, but then I would have to actually, like, think about them,
and I wouldn't want them to be embarrassing."
Right.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But also, yeah, I don't know.
Most sports podcasts are like that.
That's the sound of you ask too real a question.
Yeah.
You pumped them right in the id.
Sorry.
Sorry, apologize.
Give me a sports hot take right now.
No, no, no, no.
I will be up at 6.30 in the morning.
Hopefully, I'll go to McMillan's across the way.
Yeah, what is this thing?
What is happening?
Well, the Steelers are playing the Minnesota Vikings in Ireland.
Right.
In Ireland.
Yeah.
So I'll be over there.
Several of you just asked why.
Who knows?
No one knows.
If you want to improve relationships with Ireland, you send Aaron Rodgers.
Yes.
That's right.
You send...
Our best and brightest, Carson Wentz and Aaron Rodgers.
We send our cave-dwelling ayahuasca-drinking weirdo conspiracy theorist to Ireland.
Look, if the red zone offense stays in the 80%, then I will also take ivermectin.
Seems like a needless wager on your part, but okay.
Yeah.
That's fine.
I don't know how it happens, but we're scoring a lot inside the 20.
Mattingly.
Yes.
You woke up early.
You took scoops on an outing.
Some scoops on an outing.
I did.
We had a little nerd out.
Went out to Alternate Reality Comics out here in Las Vegas.
Yes.
Big shout out to Alternate Reality.
It's my boy Ralph.
Ralph has been holding it down for damn near 30 years out here.
It's the best little comic shop in Vegas.
I just love it.
Love it.
Yeah.
Some scoops were kind enough to join me in the morning.
Vegas early.
But we went out there and had a great time.
Terri.
I really, it was awesome because I've just gotten really back into comics in the last
year and a half or so.
So, I was able to give heartfelt, earnest recommendations on what is on the shelves right now, so that
was kind of fun.
And people bought books I recommended, which was great.
That was really cool.
And then we went-
A lot of tits.
A lot of boobies.
A lot of circles and squirrels.
More circles and circles.
They're just circles and squirrels.
You don't know what I'm saying.
You mean like in the comic shop or in the comics?
In the comics.
So, this is the thing.
Paul handed my son a comic with tits in it.
Nice.
But your son is 28 years old, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a bargain bin.
He said tits only to Paul.
Give me that book with them tits.
An old 50 Cent issue of Powers, and it's one of my favorite series ever.
And I was like, "Here you go."
And Michael Avon Owing's artwork is very stylistic.
Sure.
And it's really just circles and circles when you're looking at the boob, but whatever.
Paul's staying at my house this time around though.
He actually says that in real life to his wife as well.
It's just circles and circles, baby.
Yeah.
They're just circles and circles up there, baby.
Thank you.
My boobs don't look like that.
Circles and circles is my favorite.
Oh, oh boys album.
Yeah.
Boobs is a flat circle.
No, that was awesome.
And then right next door to the comic shop is a new card shop, which is under new management.
I had never been.
Card?
Card.
Collectible cards, Pokemon, Magic, all that kind of shit.
It was incredible, well, really well kept, nice, run well.
I spent way too much money in these types of shops too?
No, sir.
No, no.
So this is all just like magic cards?
All Magic the Gathering and Pokemon.
And maybe a little dash of Lorcan.
Don't know what that is.
It's the Disney trading card thing.
Good.
Yeah.
So yeah.
And they really were holding it down.
They run tournaments there.
So clearly they had their stuff on.
It was just clean.
Shop was clean.
Prices were right.
Oh nice.
Which is a huge thing.
I don't know.
Do you guys keep up?
I mean some dirty Magic the Gathering shops, right?
Oh god.
Filth Fests.
No.
Seriously.
Do we have any Magic fans out here?
Any Magic players?
You know what?
That was a no.
I gave up Magic the Gathering in 1993.
Okay.
And I gave away my Black Lotus.
Damn.
Before you did that, Mr. Brine Brushwood.
Oh shit.
That's valuable.
What does that mean?
That is an extremely valuable card.
Okay.
Before you did that, Mr. Brine Brushwood.
Oh.
Would you say that the average conglomerate of Magic the Gathering players have the highest
standards of hygiene about them?
There are signs on many Magic the Gathering convention doors that say, "Wash your ass
before you come in here."
Like seriously, there are rules in tournaments that are like, "Stinkies go home."
It's a problem.
I'm almost certain that for a while there was a Twitter account that was nothing but
ass cracks at Magic the Gathering.
Oh yeah.
There was a Twitter account.
There was a dude who would always take pictures with his hands in prayer emoji form by just
heinous ass cracks at Magic the Gathering.
If you can look it up.
Yeah.
That's right.
I forgot.
He did his little meme of praying.
Yeah.
His ass cracks.
And many were strewn with stuff.
Just bad.
It was a fucking ...
Look it up.
Strewn with stuff?
I'm telling you.
I will not look it up.
By the way, and here's how fucked that community is.
They yelled at the guy.
They banned the guy from coming to Magic Tournament when it's like he is a Pulitzer Prize winning
journalist who has just broken loose a horrifying scandal.
You should be thanking him.
He should be the commissioner.
You leave our dirty butts be.
Exactly.
But no.
Big ass told him to fucking pass out his hand.
So all that to say, when you find a really clean Magic the Gathering shop, you're like,
"Holy shit.
I might be able to breathe in here."
Yeah.
So it was really well kept and really nice.
And then, of course, just down the way from there ...
Much easier to tap two mana than to wipe twice.
Good Lord.
It's a fucking fact, man.
Their asses are their graveyards.
It's just ...
What is with ...
What is that expression?
Bones are your money.
Yeah.
This is the thing with pro wrestling too.
Especially for big shows, you'll have these things on the reddits that are like, "Guys,
shower."
For the love of God.
Yeah.
Why are you going to show up and just stink out everybody?
Now, like WrestleMania here in Vegas, the cheapest seat that you can get is $800.
And imagine that you're standing next to somebody who's a fucking biohazard and just stinks to
high heaven the entire time.
That's going to be bad.
Paul was just telling me about this the other day, about the WrestleMania thing here, just
being so fucking expensive.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Luckily, I have just purchased a black Lotus card.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'm going to sell that one.
What deal did you get?
There you go.
No, I got it for $400,000.
Yeah.
I'm just going to use that.
Is it really worth $400,000?
According to this, it is.
Yeah.
Look, when you need three mana ...
It depends on the addition.
It depends on the condition.
Yeah.
In the early days, they didn't have the play balancing quite right.
So in tournaments where you're playing for keepsies, then all of a sudden it became profitable
and made sense.
The value went up, and then the legend grew long and all that stuff.
But I quit because I was finally making friends in college, and that was ruining my friendship,
so away it went.
Yeah.
That was exactly a conversation that was had at the Magic Place, because he was talking
about he plays commander, and he's got a couple of different decks, and he has to decide
on the day, "Do I want to keep my friends, or do I want to play a fun game of Magic?"
Yeah.
Well, because if you're playing mathematically, then some pretty unfun, brutal strategies
start to make sense.
Exactly, yeah.
There are mechanics that you can lose forever friends from, yeah.
Just by taking all this shit, taking all the cards.
You could play a high-risk thing, and so it's not fun for the other player.
There was a land killer deck that I played where it's just like, you need land for energy,
so imagine if you never got to take a single step forward in the contest, and then meanwhile,
the moment you put down one land, like, "Fuck you, fire, dead," you're not doing anything.
Go on, go on, go on.
Yeah.
So why are the black lotus card?
So this is so early, nobody had even heard of the game.
There were what they called black-bordered alphas, and so we would just, we would congregate.
I heard they make the rockin' world go round.
They did, yeah.
Yeah, like we would wait for them to show up with the Tuesday mail, and then we would
just like, you know, like vultures, just crrrr, and stuff, everything.
Okay.
So it's like an unboxing on a package.
Yeah, yeah.
You just found one in a pack.
Yeah.
And that's that black rim.
Oh, there it goes.
Did you ever play it?
Oh, sure.
It was just a card to me, and then I gave them all away.
I think my brother gave me 70 bucks for all my cards, and he later, I think, sold it for
500.
Yeah.
Did you even have them sleeved back then?
No, goodness, no.
No, rock on.
Them sleeves, though?
Them sleeves?
Oh, them sleeves, though.
They weren't no sleeves, though.
Yeah.
They used to, in the very early on, they wanted to, they claimed ...
Them sleeves, though.
They claimed that you had to ante every single game, so you would shuffle your deck, and
then blind, you'd have to set out a card, and then you played, and then the other person
got it.
That didn't last.
Well, that was the whole thing with Pokemon, too.
It was all six prizes.
They would go.
Yeah.
Now, what time period is this?
Fall 1993.
Two fist fulls of cookie dough.
Yep.
I remember those days.
No, because I'm trying to say, what's weird now is that, as someone who, they're teens
and twenties in the '90s, any niche culture was actually kind of shit on.
You just kind of ... You always had to alf the alf.
No matter what was going on, as soon as it became popular, it was like, "Go left."
This is before the great flattening of the geek empires, thanks to the internet.
This is at a time that I was excited about Magic the Gathering, because it was a more
approachable bridge to Dungeons and Dragons at the time.
I'm like, "Well, they're just playing a game."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because what I'm trying to say is, you chose friends over this game, right?
This time.
This is before the dark times, before Mikey.
Yes.
But now I feel like you don't, right?
I feel like the internet makes these communities a thing, that people aren't even friends.
There's just no king media.
There's no king thing.
There's no mainstream anymore.
Everything is just its own niche.
It's like, all right, is there a one weird thing that people are all obsessed about?
Yeah.
You want to know the problem with the internet?
Nobody's lonely.
When you're lonely, you have to do a little thing called compromise and meet other people
at the square dance, you dipshits.
Instead, everyone's all making hierarchies.
This fall on Fox News, Brian Brushwood shares the real truths.
Why aren't the kids at square dances?
I had to tell you, Brushwood, as someone who's just been dipping my toe, by dipping my toe,
I mean paying two 20-year-olds to edit clips for me.
Oh, is that what you're paying them for?
It's part of it.
We have different hobbies.
Yeah.
Believe me, take the reels.
It's so much simpler.
Trust me, you'll be happier with the reels.
Okay, so which means I've experimented with putting things on Instagram, Facebook.
Everyone loves them, super supportive.
YouTube is a hellscape.
Luckily, it's not one of our jobs to fucking stare at the raw feet of God's butthole the
whole day long.
Actually, it was really funny, even one of the clips, I looked, I was like, "What?
40 comments?
What the fuck's going on here?"
And simply, it was a thing of doing a trick I bought from you.
Oh, that's right.
I think my wife saw this.
She was like, "Hey, I think you take tricks pretty good, but yeah, I'll let it stand."
I'm doing your trick, and I simply say, "What's your favorite book?"
She goes, "I don't have one," and I go, "Correct," and that's the whole hoping-to-go-viral moment.
And then a debate breaks out about whether or not books are stupid.
In the comments.
Yeah.
Nothing to do with me at all.
Yep.
Just people going at it like, "Why don't you fucking read?"
And defenders go like, "No, reading's dumb," and it just goes on and on and on.
So yeah, I had this conversation in the car back from the fucking...
That reading's bad?
This is why...
He's from Kentucky.
This is why we need to support comic book stores and libraries and all this kind of
shit.
We need to read.
Fucking read.
I love the fact that comics went from being the scourge of literacy-
Wait, wait.
Yes, to, "Guys, at least there's words in them."
No.
This is...
Honestly, this is the-
If we put words next to the titties, they might read.
They might notice that.
That was my hope.
I'm trying to get Matt's kids literate.
What's this hidden word around this areola?
Constitutional democracy.
What the hell?
No, but even at just a base level, I've always, in my head, thought, "What better way to
get people of any type to learn how to read, but by having visual representation of what's
happening accompanied with dialogue and explanation?"
Eventually, they'd move on to chapter books.
Right.
What the fuck?
Some people do.
Paul hadn't moved on yet.
Props to Chuck Winding.
Who won in the comments, from your opinion?
Books or no books?
Books crushed it.
Books did.
Good for books.
You know what?
I would say I'd be okay with those random arguments if YouTube would bake into the system
the ability for you to be the judge.
Man, this is your room.
There's no fight.
You get to call the winner.
That's it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll write them.
Dear YouTube.
You should post that.
It was John Waters.
Right?
I believe it was John Waters.
John Waters' quote.
He was like, "Please, if you go to someone's house and you see that they don't have any
books, don't fuck them."
Right?
I think I'm attributing that properly.
Yes.
I think it was Houdini.
Oh, you're right.
It was Houdini.
Shit.
That was not an option.
You walked in.
You're like, "Here's a gift of a book."
No reason.
I had some.
Do you have a shelf?
Put this on.
Matt bought three girls the entire Encyclopedia Britannica before he left the Virgin Islands.
I'm back with G.
Yeah.
That hit the spot.
One, I was thinking it would be really funny if you just said, "Worked in a big way."
I was like, "He's right."
Then we all rushed to comic book stores and created a wave of everybody to do it.
I get lost in these conversations because we're getting older, right?
Yes.
Speak for yourself.
Slow decay.
Slow.
As someone who started a magic career late, I went on tour as a guy and now I'm touring
as an old guy.
I definitely noticed that where people talk to me to start and then they're like, "Okay,
we're done talking to the old man.
Now let's go back to talk to each other," and I'm like, "Oh, okay."
On the slow road to total burdendom, you can see the light in people's eyes slowly start
fading as you drone on and on about the Gulf War or some shit.
I used to be guile.
Now I'm dulcet.
The slow road to total burdendom.
Yeah.
You're just like, "So Norman Schwarzkopf was popular."
"Nope, nobody here saw Good Will Hunting."
I don't know.
Fucking their brains just rotted with a million TikTok trends.
That's it.
The internet is everything, right?
Right.
No, what I mean to say is we talked about this off air, but on the episode we did something
kind of serious.
Yes.
We said it's hard because there's so many forces that profit from the destruction of
hope.
Yes.
Basically, by making it feel like a hellscape all the time, it makes money and it also tells
me to go for self.
I don't have to worry about the future.
I don't have to worry about future generations because they're never going to change.
They're going to fuck it all up.
They is whoever.
I'm talking about any issue, they.
They're going to fuck it all up and then so therefore I don't have to worry about shit
anymore.
I don't have to think about things anymore.
You know what I feel like the solution is?
In-person events like what's happening right now at ScootFest.
Agree.
I agree.
Also, we talked about it years ago.
We talked about you have to identify the they.
You can't just be able to say they.
I think it's important.
It's super important.
Thank you very much.
People are just bringing me booze.
It's great.
Name them, Jacob.
Who's bringing you booze?
By the way, I'll sign up for that as well.
Dos Equis, please.
Or whiskey.
Cheers.
Cheers, mate.
That Whiskey Break is brought to you by our sponsor.
Yes, that Whiskey Break is brought to you by our following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Mally's Ice Cream Social, still haven't moved the commercial tab to the
front page of my phone.
Why do that?
That's too much.
Time swipes to the right before I get to the square in the middle.
It's fine, it's fine.
Who's getting older?
Not us.
Jesus, that font.
So bright.
Matt, just hold your phone up so the background can read it.
I think you can read that from space.
What the fuck?
I'll just have the bartender tell us who's sponsoring this today.
Oh my God, did you hear the wave of horror?
Matt just showed his phone to the room and there were legitimate "whoa"s.
No bullshit, hold that up and if you can read it, stand up.
There you go.
How far back can people read that?
I think it is rivaled only by the Hollywood sign.
I actually can't see the Hollywood sign right now but I can see that.
I legit was surprised by the reaction from the audience.
This has been a startling mirror onto self.
No only because I know that I'm actually holding out of this font size.
I've gone up one and if I go up two I'm going to feel really old so I'm trying to hold it
down.
I say bull the fucking ripples.
Let it go baby.
All you're doing is fooling yourself.
I'm going to tell you right now, my font size on my phone is the standard size.
I can't read it but I will not change it.
I switched to video games.
Jacob has not read a text message in three years.
That's right.
He blindly responds, "Ha!" to everything.
I give a lot of thumbs up.
100%!
Very nice.
Oh great, pass my whiskey back over then.
That's keeping tabs over here, Jacob.
Anyways, today's show is brought to you by Beef in a Box, now with Extra Box.
That's from Belgian Tripple Scoop in 2023.
So people tell you no beef, bullshit.
You want beef and you want beef in a box and you want extra box so come on and get this
beef in a box with the extra box.
Boom.
Unh.
Box.
Beef.
Beef in a box.
Boom.
Boom that beef in a box.
Yeah you hear it mooing?
That's your beef.
Sorry.
I'm distracted by this commercial.
Someone threw up a package of Aldi hot dogs and Brian is squeezing it like a stress toy.
I will warn you of this, Brian.
Should the contents of that in any way touch your skin, you will be unable to remove that
scent for at least two nights.
You will not be allowed in.
That's great because I have a Magic the Gathering tournament scheduled for tomorrow.
And I'm not joking when I say, yeah you're right, that's kind of the vibe.
It gives off the scent of a gathering of Aldi hot dogs sweating, sweating too close together
and letting their ass cracks out.
That is unfair to disgusting people.
No it's not.
Do you think that that shit happens because people can't smell or have they become immune
to smelling themselves?
When you are saving up money to buy $500 pieces of cardboard, other things slip through the
cracks.
Like lava.
Like loose toilet paper.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think really it is a combination of that kind but I think it is just living really
stretching stuff out and not even thinking about that.
That's a cry for help right?
Yeah.
Being that smelly.
I don't know.
I think it's a sign of depression.
Yeah.
But also there's a bunch of like creators that I see on TikTok and what not, they're
like don't wash your hair.
I know right?
I'm like ew.
They're like don't wash your hair.
I'm like what?
I legit had an LA friend tell me to stop washing my hair.
See this is what I'm saying man.
And they probably don't, I don't know.
I don't want to get into a hygiene debate but I will.
No but nobody is saying don't wash your ass.
Yes.
I'm spoiling for a hygiene debate.
I'm just waiting for the right YouTube short magic trick to bring it out.
I will finish the trick and be like whoa pull that one out of my ass.
And they'll be like you shouldn't store stuff in your ass.
Yes you should.
You should use pockets.
We are evolved to store things in our ass.
Asses are dumb.
That's why we beat the monkeys.
It's nature's pocket.
Nature's pocket.
Excuse me.
Today's show is brought to you by nature's pocket.
Oh god.
Interhase script's a check out.
I just got done writing my 200 word comment about South American tariff rates on bandana
banana.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
But oh yeah Interhase script's a check out.
Yes.
Nailed that one.
Extra long commercial.
If folks brought stuff we're going to do like a physical school mail thing during the concert.
Yes.
We won't do a physical school mail thing now just because narrating gifts is burdensome
to the listener.
Not the greatest of.
But we do have a microphone for people who want to do any kind of in person.
Narration of the gift that they brought.
Scoop mail.
No.
In person scoop mail.
We won't narrate it but if you want to narrate it.
Or argue about whether or not reading is dumb.
Yeah.
You can also do that.
Those are the two things that are mostly what we want.
But I guess for you could also do anything else.
So if anybody has a in person scoop mail you'd like to do come on up get lined up at the
microphone up here and we will get to that in just a moment.
That doesn't include an item.
Is it just me or is the energy weird.
The energy's weird today.
The energy is weird.
No the energy's weird.
I don't think it's bad but it is weird.
No I think we're at day three.
Yeah that's it.
Also I know I am pacing myself for tonight right.
Yeah.
That's what's going on.
These guys are just taking it to zero and then at eight o'clock it's ass cracks out.
Yeah.
I can answer your question about what happened to the mood in the room.
Okay.
Oh.
You got all the international scoops arrested so that's what happened and all the good scoops
left.
That's true.
That is true.
Okay.
Let's bring it up.
I apologize.
Okay.
Good.
That joke is from Penn Sunday School so good.
This is good.
It's like a comic book series.
You have to listen to them all together.
That's right.
Yeah.
It's good.
Very nice.
Yeah.
Well a lot of these people have had two nights at McMullin's.
It's a lot.
Oh yeah.
No we're running on empty here.
Fucking redlining.
Holy shit.
Yeah.
Oh.
We have someone coming up here.
Oh hey.
Even if I'm an international scoop.
Shame on you.
No.
It was so real.
I don't know why it was so real.
I've never had any kind of a police job or I don't know why anybody would believe you
had an earpiece.
Yeah.
I don't know why it thundered forth so big.
I do have one question because I asked Scoop if they know the answer for it and I don't
remember it ever coming up.
Who is Annie?
So the person we are getting our emails from, from Patreon.
Oh Annie.
I never ever heard anything about the person behind that.
Is she okay?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask her?
Annie are you okay?
She honestly, and this is the timely because she was recently hit by a smooth criminal.
Damn.
She was actually struck by a smooth criminal.
She was hit by an amstruck by.
By the way.
Hilarious.
Great question because 1200 episodes in.
Yes.
Annie.
Was it early?
Was it a listener?
Yes.
We don't know.
She definitely was a listener.
Yeah.
We think she still listens.
And we first busted out the Patreon.
We were overwhelmed.
Yeah.
As happens.
And we offered a lot of stuff and so we basically said none of us have office skills.
Does any scoop out there have office skills?
And Annie stepped up.
And we created an email address for her.
And also we just thought it was a good idea to have a barrier.
Not from like a don't bother Jacob, Paul and I with stuff.
But we actually just thought our listeners will talk more honestly and frankly with someone
whose job it was to talk to scoops.
Like if there's an issue.
Yeah.
Like some scoops might not want to come to us with an issue, might be easier to go to
Annie with an issue.
Yeah.
And so we have to interact with Annie all the time.
She emails us before episodes.
Yeah.
That kind of stuff.
And so she does all of our kind of like Patreon relationship housekeeping.
And has done it now for fucking.
As long as we've had Patreon.
Nine years.
Yeah.
It's been crazy.
She's great.
No Annie's amazing.
I have met her, I believe the other two have not.
Nope.
I have not met Annie.
I follow her on the socials.
I see she and her kids do Disney World occasionally and yeah.
Nice.
Good.
People were doubting Paul but he came over the top of that Disney World thing.
The guy wants to know Annie's condition.
You can't fabricate that detail.
She's in the Magic Kingdom.
I occasionally email Annie.
By the way, I love this question.
Do we have like weird small ice cream social minutiae questions?
Yeah, this is great.
There it is.
More mystery.
No, line up.
Line up.
Come on.
But I met her and her husband.
They came and saw me open for the Magic Dragon in Connecticut at Foxwoods.
Annie is lovely.
She's a super sweet, awesome person.
How has she not been to a scoop fest?
Oh, we don't let her.
Oh, she doesn't like us.
No.
Give us your scoop name.
What's your scoop name?
Scooper Nova Girl.
There she is.
Yeah.
Do you guys have a lot of call and responses and greetings?
Do we have a toast?
A toast?
Oh.
Well, the answer is we don't.
I don't think so.
I don't think we have an official toast.
Well, I mean, we have my toast, which is Kapla and Good Journey, which combines my love of
Star Trek and Master Universe.
You guys can pick up on one of our favorites.
What is it?
Which is jizz.
Yeah.
You ever notice it?
Jizz.
All right, if you do that, that's rude, crass, ugly.
Oh.
If you add the word mate, they assume you're British.
Jizz, mate.
Oh, I got you.
Okay.
He's not like that.
And actually, we started doing that on a podcast where the head of the network was on it.
It was a...
It was just a cheap way to just say jizz on a polite society livestream.
But at some point, we just keep... 'cause it was a New Year's Eve thing, so booze was
fun.
Happened a lot.
And so we were cheersing a lot.
And so we're just like, "Jizz, mate, jizz."
And at one point, he just looks at me, and he's just like...
That was it.
How long did it take him to realize?
We got seven, eight jizzes before he even...
You got so much jizzes in.
Oh, we were firing ropes, dude.
Like, it was...
Let me...
I mean, it was Peter North all the way down.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We don't have an official thing, but I think we could all do a salt pork, I need help.
Scoop or Dove Girl, do you have a suggestion?
Not off the top of your head?
No.
I'm not that good.
Fair, fair, fair.
All right.
Yeah.
Right, what you got?
Scoop's name.
Doc Scoop.
There he is.
What up?
We fall in love with characters over time and people that come and go.
Haven't heard from Brit Mukai in a while, and any updates on how he's doing, what's going
on with him?
Well, again, he's another one that I follow on the old socials.
Takes his kids to Disney World every now and then.
Yeah.
Kids going to Disney World.
Kids now.
No, his VO career has continued to be successful.
Recently he's had some health and dietary struggles.
Not trying to put you on blast, Brett.
But he's sharing all that.
He's doing it publicly.
Yeah.
He's sharing all that.
But he's doing really well.
If you follow Brit Mukai, he's not hard to find on socials.
He's doing lots of convention work and signing autographs because he is the voice of many
anime characters.
Oh, fantastic.
That people know and love right now.
Yeah, he's working.
He's doing well.
Yeah.
Brett is working.
No, Brett.
That's why he's not hanging out with us.
He's in LA making that dollar.
That's right.
You think we can get him to do a phoner?
He?
Check in with us?
He bought property in California.
Whoa.
Yeah, right?
Like, yeah.
Well, damn.
But you bring up a good point.
Tell me about this home.
It has been a long time, and we should probably reach out to Brett for a touch base, maybe
a Zoom.
Thank you, Doc Scoop.
You should probably call him right now.
No.
I feel like I've got at least another year in me before I need to talk to Brett Mukai.
Are you going to try it?
Just give him a call.
All right.
He's going to try it.
I mean, it's Scoop Fest after all.
You're right.
He's going to try it.
When all miracles take place, they say that if you rub your two fingers together, that
Brett Mukai will send us the voicemail.
It is a pretty miraculous time.
Well, I mean, it's, what is it?
It's a Saturday afternoon.
It's as good as time as any.
I guess so.
He might be at a con.
That's quite possible.
At a con?
God.
Signing them things.
It's my only Star Trek joke.
Brett's doing great, man.
Brett's doing great.
What have you got?
Scoop name?
Technical Scoop board.
Checking in again.
Oh, hold on.
Wait, wait.
Sorry.
Sorry, technical Scoop board.
We've got Brett Mukai.
Brett Mukai, do you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
What's up, brother?
You are live at Scoop Fest in front of hundreds of Scoops right now.
How's it going, Scoops?
Oh, my God.
Brett, literally, someone came up and just said, how is Brett?
Why haven't we heard from a while?
Where is he?
So how are you, Brett?
What's going on?
Dude, I'm fucking rad, man.
And in fact, I was going to hit, it's so crazy.
I was going to hit you guys up.
I'm actually going to be in Vegas next weekend.
Oh, fuck yeah!
I'm one weekend too late.
Can you come on the Friday episode?
Yeah, I mean, we're on Zoom, you can come on any episode, but yeah, come on by.
I'll be in Canada, but don't let that stop you from doing it.
What are you up to?
Tell the Scoops something they can dive their teeth into.
What's up, Scoops?
I'm at a convention in Florida, in Tampa Bay, and yeah, I'm just eating dinner with like
Pokemon voice actors and people like that.
And yeah, I'm just chilling, having a good time, and ate a great burger just now.
Oh, there you go.
Well, Brett, thank you so much for answering my call.
If you didn't, I was going to be so furious.
So I appreciate you doing it.
That's the only reason I answered it, Matt.
I was like, "If I don't answer this, I'm going to miss out on something awesome."
All right, give it up for Brett, everybody.
Take it easy.
We love you, Brett.
We'll talk soon.
Bye, pal.
Technical Scoop board.
You got a question?
I do.
It's been quite a while since I've heard the haiku from the Patreon requests.
Is that still a thing?
We are changing the Patreon right now.
Yeah.
So this has been really tricky because Patreon changeups happened right around the time Scoop
Fest preparations really kicked into high gear.
So we're hoping to have things remedied and squared by the middle of October.
You're the second person who's asked this.
So I propose, and this is just Paul, and I might just do it by myself if I have to.
I propose we try and make good on what suggestions we still have in the kitty and maybe a few
that come in now and do maybe a special hour long bonus episode of just the haikus and
the what do you call it, and the triple threats and all that.
You guys would like that, maybe?
Yeah.
And then they are going to go away, except for special occasions.
Except for when we want them to come back.
Yeah.
And then we'll do them.
And by we, I mean we, all of us.
But it's not going to be an essential part of the Patreon moving forward.
Right.
Thank you.
Can you speak a little deeper to that question?
Oh, please.
Get deep.
No, no, because like in truth, comedy has changed a lot since we started doing this
podcast.
Yeah.
12 years.
And sensibilities have changed a lot.
And an awareness of being like three white dudes doing a podcast has been a thing on
our minds.
And on some level, like in the room, like when we do the Bucket Show, we do other things
like that.
Like when we're in a room with people who like us, who trust us, and just like any other
group of people where you're in a room where people trust each other, you can toe the line.
You can push the envelope.
You can basically get laughed for saying something a little, a little insensitive.
You have some latitude.
Knowing that the person thinks you're a good guy.
Right.
And as comedy changed and as we got older, like the idea of leaving constant physical
evidence of us doing haikus and saying your mom, a difference between your mom and blank
and that kind of stuff just started getting a little like, uh-oh, maybe this might be
a bad idea in the long term.
And so we got a little gun shy about doing that.
You didn't want to turn on the printing press of liability receipts.
Yeah, exactly.
And it's a shame because like, I know that like, we've always joked from the beginning
like we are dumb jokes for smart people.
Like it's like always like kind of like what I like to think of us.
And so like, I know we get the benefit of the doubt from the people that do it.
And there is something like, there's guilty pleasure about being childish in humor, sometimes
stuff like that.
But we do enjoy doing it.
Like we still do it at the bucket shows and things like that.
But it just became something that got a little dicey for me for doing on air.
I think it's also something that is going to be better received as it's rarer.
Like if you do a thing every once in a while, you know, that's a very involved bit.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's hard, it takes away some of the magic when you see it so often that
it becomes mechanical.
Of course.
I mean, our first Patreon was a fucking nightmare and it was so funny.
And that's what we loved.
Like we made a very funny Patreon.
Right.
You go, you guys had fucking the most convoluted reward system.
It was one time.
We would eat weird things on camera was one reward.
Oh, I forgot about that one.
Oh my, no hands, we would no hands eat things.
No hands eating.
Right.
We did that.
Yeah.
We did that at a fucking pepper mill.
We did it at a pepper mill with Ryre.
We recorded people just eating shit.
Eating things without using our hands.
I forgot about that.
We, we used to try to do individual made up credits for each person we thanked at the
end of episodes.
Yep.
Every single person.
And then it mostly was just...
And then it just got to be too many people.
Yeah.
So we'd literally be like, technical school board.
Technical school board.
He graduated from this university.
Allegedly.
He did all this.
And then allegedly he did this.
Yeah.
We would do like five minutes.
And at first it was a blast.
And then it became like really unfunny.
And then we just finished the episode like, I don't want to end episodes doing our most
unfunny shit.
Right.
We just run this fucking momentum into the cliff face of like mandatory fun.
So like, and you know, it's like Paul and I are improv guys.
And so like so much about like being improv, like we can always make it up on the spot.
We can always generate gold.
We can do this.
And then putting it to the test, you know, for three hours a week for 12 years, it's
just, you know, maybe, maybe gold is the high standard.
You know?
And so I think we tried to kind of, we also, yeah, we would kind of pump breaks on weird
shit like that.
Yeah.
But as I said, it's just not going to be part of the patron going forward in a large capacity,
but we will do a make good episode from some of the old stuff.
If you got one specifically, you really want to hear, send it to Jacob.
And we're, and we're going to do them.
Like we're, we're still going to, we're still going to do all of our stuff, you know, as,
as time goes by.
Uh, but yeah, maybe just not quite as often.
Yeah.
Is that fair?
Very fair.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Come on up.
Welcome to the Belgian Triple Scoop.
I love it.
Actually, I'm very grateful technical scoop port, cause you kind of started the question
that I have, which is, you know, um, I bought tickets for Scoop Fest before I, I'm now in
a serious relationship or about to be a year, but she doesn't share the same kind of sense
of humor that I think we, everybody in this room really loves.
Come on guys.
Yeah.
Dumb jokes for smart people.
Woo.
And you're, you're asking us if you should leave her?
No, no, no, no, no.
This is so awkward and unexpected, but yes, you should.
Stacey, that's not what I'm saying.
Stacey, you should leave.
I'm feeling bad that you said that because now four people just said, you know what?
I'm over it too.
And they just left.
Dropping like flies here.
But it's, it's how do you marry that idea of this is something that you love, right?
Like it's, you know, you, you talked about, you know, obviously your very thoughtful response
to how you do the different jokes and oh, this is great comedy gold.
It's comedy gold everybody, but explaining the Captain Morgan podcast and why that's
funny.
Sure.
It's sometimes difficult.
I don't think I can explain why, if the Captain Morgan podcast is funny.
Super cerebral.
But it's exactly, it's my watermark.
But that's the idea.
It's, it's, how do you...
Captain Morgan, did you wander into script?
I just wanted to let you know that the podcast is funny because my name is Captain Morgan.
What do you want me to do?
What are you doing?
Captain Morgan, you seem like, you seem like you're on the precipice.
You're, you're refusing...
On the precipice.
Well, okay.
Hold on.
Get out of my precipice.
What?
No, no.
I'm prespiring on the precipice.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm just here for you, Brian.
Well, I know you seem very upset though, Captain Morgan.
Why do you have hot dogs?
Well, it's, I invented hot dogs, by the way.
I didn't know this about you.
I didn't.
Funny, funny, you should ask.
You have a hot dog that I invented.
Okay.
I invented one.
Yes?
Not the rest.
Well, tell me about it.
I put it together in a spindle that I carried in a bindle.
Oh, are you homeless as well?
Nope.
Oh, no, you're not.
No, I have a boat.
I take my boat around to the high seas, and if I ever see a hot dog I don't like, I kick
him off.
I say, get the fuck out of here, hot dog.
Okay.
Well, why?
It's a real problem.
Now, wait a minute.
These days.
Hot dogs everywhere.
Where?
Running, hither and yon, can't trust them.
Can't look a hot dog in the eye anymore and say, hey, we're going to make a square deal.
Now these hot dogs be doing, hot dogs be trifling.
Did a hot dog disappoint you?
Fuck yeah.
Oh, tell me about it.
One hot dog crashed the stock market and high interest loans, and next thing you know Obama
was president.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen, Captain Morgan.
Belgium.
But that's exactly what I mean.
I'm doubled over laughing, and you guys, I mean all five of you have-
75% of the audience wasn't.
But that's the point.
You guys all have partners.
You have children.
You have people in your life who may not share that.
How do you find the kind of balance in you guys making your living off of jokes that
I find amazing, but I have a hard time sharing?
How do you find that balance?
Oh, none of our spouses think we're funny.
My wife does.
None of our spouses think we're funny.
No, my wife thinks I'm funny.
No, no.
She calls me all the time and tells me.
No?
Wow.
She thinks I'm funny.
She just thinks I push it too gross sometimes.
Should there be a statute of limitations on lore?
Like at some point they expire and you have to let them go?
What?
Say it again?
Should there be a statute of limitations on lore, like at some point, because it's impenetrable
at some point?
It's like-
Dude, you haven't heard from Mothra's secret agent in a while for a reason.
So yes.
Because the last time I started to hear from them, Matt and I just yelled, "No!"
It doesn't happen.
Yeah.
So I mean that's-
I mean, you look at The Simpsons, right?
They didn't think they were going to go 30 years and so all of a sudden they're being
held accountable for decisions they made 20 years ago.
Like that's fucking bananas.
Yeah.
Because it implies, because you're looking back, it's like the powerhouse of that you
knew what you were the whole time and not that you were desperately trying to get anyone
to pay attention to you doing anything that came into your brain and just hoping it flew
in the moment.
Yeah.
I mean-
But no, I mean, I think anytime you try to make any kind of living being creative at
all, something that really comes from your heart and your mind, it's fucking ballsy.
And anytime you get any kind of audience of support, it means it's really something special.
Well, comedy is also very, very specific.
There's not a lot of objective elements to comedy that you can say like, "Well, clearly
this is funny," because it's all dependent on where people come from, their expectations.
I think I've quoted this one before, but this is my go-to right now.
Zach Anner, the comedian, multiple sclerosis guy, he's amazing.
He's fantastic.
I love social media, Zach Anner.
This is his whole thing.
Comedy isn't meant to be timeless.
Great comedy is in service of its time.
It helps start the conversations that will eventually deem it irrelevant, outdated or
offensive.
You laugh, you think, you grow, and you move on.
That said, farts are always hilarious.
But it's so true.
I went back and listened like last week, two weeks ago, I listened to a Bill Cosby comedy
album.
Boy, I didn't know there'd be edgy humor on this show.
It was the edgiest, not even edgiest, but it was hilarious.
It was a huge seller of its time, and I went back and listened to it, and forget about
all the Bill Cosby stuff, or try to, or just go to sleep and forget about it.
It's fine.
He'll make you forget.
All of that aside, it's just not poignant.
It's simply not relevant to this day and time anymore, and it's so hard ...
Jacob's like, "When you guys are done bitching about the other stuff about Bill Cosby, I'd
like to take the content of a special for that."
Can we get to the real issue here?
I'm going to really focus in on the minutia of Bill Cosby.
The drain-bamaged bit.
But it really is.
You go back and listen to it now, and it's just a ... It's a relic of the past now, is
all it is.
You're listening to that, and you're listening to it for the nostalgia.
It's pure nostalgia at this point.
It's not comedy anymore.
It's a history.
It's a time capsule.
I don't think you guys are time capsules.
Eggs.
Eggs are in the cake.
No.
The kids won't pull up their pants.
So to be kind of, just to wrap everything up, it's figuring out that way to share that
part of your personality in your comedy, but not push the envelope too far, but understand
that it's of time.
I don't know.
Drawing the line.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to make this more serious.
No.
You always want to say, "Hey, whatever I do is not for everyone," but as soon as you find
out it's not for everyone, it's devastating.
Really hurts your feelings.
You do.
You always say, "My comedy hero has never cared about mass popularity.
My comedy hero just made the funniest thing possible," and then it's realizing you hope
you're wrong.
You hope it's like, "No, I'll be as funny as my heroes that didn't get the recognition
that they deserved," and then you're like, "Oh, no, but I'm not getting the recognition
that I deserve."
No.
When I go do a show on a cruise ship where the audience is just the energy just fucking
zip, I absolutely go to sleep hating myself going, "I guess I'm not for everyone," and
then I have to walk around the ship with them the next day, and then go up and hide on deck
19 and look out and hope I don't get harpooned, but it's not for everybody, but the bottom
line is that looking at us over time or any kind of stuff, the body of work, all that
feels cool.
To create something that people want to come to feels cool.
In the moment, the smartest thing that we decided we were was that we are a service,
and that service is a weekly service, and we are there to help people in that moment.
We hope that that podcast helps people in that day or that drive or that walking of
their dog.
Yeah.
Everything else after that, sure, but that's the primary deal.
That's why we keep doing it.
I'll tell you what.
When scoops come up to me, and this has happened multiple times this weekend, it happens all
the time.
When scoops come up to me and say, "Hey, I listened to the whole back catalog.
My blood runs cold every single time."
Like, "Good God, what did we say a decade ago?"
Yes.
Agreed.
Oh, I'm terrified all the time.
I start laughing.
Next.
Exactly.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Scoop name.
Give it to us.
Gelato problems.
Love it.
So my question's about commitment.
What the fuck?
I don't know if it's...
You know commitment?
Go ahead.
Explain it to him.
Commitment to a bit.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, commitment.
To the point of...
To the point of endangerment.
You know, it just felt like this was like a love line segment from like 2001.
So I don't know if my husband's Max the Ginger Scoop, and I don't know if he was always going
to be a commitment guy, and you just named the thing that he does, or if he's just following
you to be a commitment guy, but he is that guy, and he will kill something until it is
dead and buried, and I'm like, "Please stop," and he won't.
And so my question, this is a crowd that will show up at the party tonight in commitment
outfits.
Yes.
You guys love commitment, but is there any commitment that in your lives, maybe bad jokes,
like there are some bad jokes that I'm like, "Kill it, and it won't die," and bad jokes,
commitments, bits at home, or bits in your lives that you're like, "I'm gonna keep doing
it no matter how upset it makes everyone at work or at home."
Anything like that?
Paul?
Your moment has come, sir.
The audience said it first.
The people that I love the most get nicknames, and those nicknames stay forever.
So...
Matt and I don't have nicknames.
That's true.
So far I see no complications.
Everything's good, girl.
It seems legit.
Well, but you're the audio guy.
Don't.
Move on.
It's fine.
It's worse if you try to make it now.
It's worse.
Yeah.
Just go ahead.
Finish your thought.
I will.
But I will.
I keep at it.
I started calling Ann...
It's so great if you just shoehorned "Madinator" in, like he had always done it.
I started calling Ann "Snakey."
The old "Madinator."
When we were dating early on, and she was like, "What the fuck are you talking about?"
And she didn't like it, but I kept it up, and I have called her "Snakey" for damn
near 20 years now, and now it's cool that she knows that I'm Snakey, and it's all good.
The hunk, my beloved brother, that came up, we were what, 12, 10, less, yeah.
Younger is the word you're looking for.
He's also from Kentucky.
Yeah.
Not with the math.
Stop fucking with the math on us.
We were lesser people.
But that's what it is.
It started with that, it started with those kind of things, and there will be moments
when I am in a real goofball mood, and some days Ann is like, "Enough, enough."
She will sometimes just say, "You got to stop here and make me cry."
I'll be like, "Okay."
I don't mean to, because I think it's ... But then sometimes it's really hard, because that's
when I know, "Oh God, this is really funny."
She hates this.
This is amazing.
That's when you know that the shields are down.
It's a combination thing, so I have to be very careful.
I understand that I wield a certain power, and I need to respect it, but for the most
part I will pull back.
There are few things funnier than the true flash of rage in the eyes of somebody that
you love very deeply.
Oh my God, oh my God.
I will say that this is one, I'm going to give out a posthumous shout out.
Many of you guys listen to Geek Shock.
Shout out to the Geek Shock boys, and big ups to 80s Jeff who is no longer with us anymore.
We lost 80s Jeff last year, it broke my heart.
That's a real commitment.
80s Jeff was the butt of a lot of my shit.
If you listen to those old, even just those old episodes, one of the worst was he came
over.
He came over to the, we would gather up after Trek almost every, I don't know, every three
nights or so, and we'd all be playing video games, and watching anime, and just acting
a fool.
And this is after you all watched Star Trek together?
All that kind of stuff.
Just doing very nerdy things in somebody's house, and there's like eight or ten of us.
Very nerdy.
Eight or ten people playing looky cookie, oh my God.
80s Jeff had a habit whenever- That is a case of pink eye waiting to happen.
Whenever he walked into a room, whenever he walked into a room, it didn't matter what
was going on, if something was playing on the TV, he'd be like, "What the hell is this?"
That was his go-to thing, he'd just, "What the hell is this?"
Just didn't matter.
He could have been something he kind of knew, could have been something he hadn't, just,
"What the hell is this?"
And we all made it, he always says, "What the hell is this?"
And so finally, there was this, I can't remember exactly what the anime was, but it was this
moment of these samurai looking guys, and gals, and very traditional kimono garb, and
all these things, and these sakurai flower petals are falling all down the ground, and
he's like, "What the hell is this?"
And I go, "It's your wedding."
And he goes, "What?"
And I go, "This is footage from your wedding."
And he says, "What the hell are you talking about?"
And some of my friends start laughing, and I go, "Yeah, man, this is your wedding, this
is your upcoming nuptials."
And he says, "What do you mean?"
And then people really start laughing.
And I go, "Yeah, this is Jeff's wedding.
We got this on tape already."
He's like, "What are you talking about?
That's not funny.
What are you talking about?
I'm not married."
And then everybody's like-
Because Jeff was not married.
And then everybody starts to really lose their shit, because he gets that angry.
He gets angry.
He's like, "What do you mean, my wedding?"
And everybody's like, "No, it's your wedding, dude.
This is your wedding."
But it's not funny.
And everybody is just fucking losing their minds.
There's nothing better than when somebody starts shouting, "It's not funny.
Yeah, what's funny about it?"
And this goes for an hour of bullshit back and forth until he's just like, "Fuck you
guys.
Fuck you guys.
I'm not getting married.
This is not my wedding.
Fuck you."
And then to this day, to this day, you go up to one of the geek shop crew, you want to
get them going, you say, "Hey, Jeff's wedding."
And we all just fucking fall out, just Jeff's wedding.
We all fucking lose our shit.
But there came a time when we could not say it anymore.
That's great.
Around him.
Magic the Gathering.
I lost casual friends to a bit.
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah.
So in my comedy group, Possible Side Effects, we loved doing bits.
I loved doing bits.
Part of why I wanted to do a podcast with Paul in the first place was that I was like,
"I want to keep doing bits all the time."
And I loved...
And I hated when I did improv videos, when they'd police bits, like, "Oh, you guys are
doing a bunch of bits."
I'm like, "Shut up.
This is my love language, and let me do bits."
And I was walking, we were visiting friends in Boston, and I was walking on the sidewalk.
It was definitely a not...
It was not a jovial mood.
Just calmly walking.
And I go, "Oh, man.
This is getting hard."
And the guy's like, "What?"
I was like, "I'm Dr. Sam Beckett."
And I leapt into Matt's body, and I am trying left and right to figure out what wrong to
write, to leap out of this fucking body.
And my comedy group was like, "Yes!"
And they just would grill me about being Sam Beckett, and I would have to start answering
questions like, "Oh, shit."
And I started answering questions of Sam Beckett, who leapt into Matt Donnelly's body to write
wrongs in his life.
And so whenever my comedy friends were bored at a party, and I'd said anything, one of
them would just go like, "Whatever, you're not even Matt."
And I'd be like, "All right, let's not."
And I would commit to being Sam Beckett immediately.
And I'd answer questions of Sam Beckett, who leapt into Matt's body, for years.
For years.
If it came up, I would never not be Dr. Sam Beckett if they brought it up.
And it ruined people I was hitting on.
It ruined just casual friendships.
Wait, you'd be hitting on somebody and one of your friends would go over to you and ask
Sam Beckett a question.
And you'd be like, "We're going fucking Sam Beckett, I'm cock-blocking Matt."
And I would just be like, "Oh, I'm sorry, I don't want to get the wrong foot with you,
but I am.
I should confess that I'm Sam Beckett, and not actually Matt Donnelly."
And I mean, we did the bit for a decade.
I don't know when we stopped doing it, but I would never not do it.
What a checkmate move when somebody's just trying to lay some game and then just be like,
"Oh, wow.
I guess my only options are, do I explain quantum leap to them?"
I remember my buddy, Steve Buck on Neutrino, he would do a thing called Bitbot, give me
a quarter and I'll do a bit.
And this drove improvisers crazy.
And then I would just get out an invisible quarter every time.
I was like, "You guys are watching the best bit in the world.
He'll do a bit on anything."
Congratulations.
And I would sell Bitbot.
And I just fucking loved it.
I would say as I got older, I guess I'm not as super major bit crazy, but when I get in
the groove, I love it.
And my wife and I met doing improv, so we do fucking really filthy, disgusting bits
all the time, and really say next level offensive things to each other.
And it's so fun, 'cause it's almost like a game of chicken with each other sometimes,
and it is a love language, and I do love it.
Yeah.
I think my wife might not like me personally, because I will just run fucking bits that
aren't funny.
I could repeat them to you.
They're not even clever or interesting, but they make her mad, and that makes me happy.
Does your wife think you are a funny person?
I suspect that she does, but she would be very fucking loathe to give me any hint that
she will suppress laughter.
She will turn her face away.
Oh, she's going to give it to you.
You won't give me that point.
Oh, no.
That's SJ.
SJ will not laugh at me at home.
Really?
Don't give me that point.
SJ's like, "Go fuck yourself."
No, 'cause she knows that if she laughs, then she's going to hear that fucking joke for
the rest of her life.
She knows the ones that are sticky, and she's like, "I can't tell you that's clever.
I can't tell you that's interesting, or else it will just be repeated right before we go
to sleep for the rest of her fucking natural days."
And she is right.
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah, she's absolutely correct.
She is dead right.
100%.
I mean, Brian, I know Bonnie likes you 'cause you're thin, but does she like you ...
Oh, Matt, good news.
Bonnie just texted me, and she said, "I don't know why, but I like Matt a little more right
now."
Yeah.
Trim it up a little bit.
All right.
No, I actually have good news from the future, 'cause your kids are how old?
10 and 12.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's like there are families that do music, and they'll just naturally, the kids grow
up, and they just learn to harmonize instantly.
It is a fucking blast when you have teenagers who have grown up where just naturally bits
are ongoing, and you understand the importance of setting up a runner and all that stuff.
To be honest, I was really hoping that Josie didn't want to go to college and instead would
sneak out to be the surprise guest at ScoopFest, but it's like she is objectively the coolest
of all her friends, and I am certain it's because of all the ongoing bits and her natural
understanding.
Yes.
So I highly recommend ...
Oh, you tell Josie any time she wants to come to ScoopFest, call me, and she can just come
to ScoopFest.
Tell dad to stay home.
Yeah.
Doing bits with my kids is awesome.
Thank you very much.
If you hear Max ... This is the one that I want people to boo him.
If you hear Max say that he kicks children for a living because he's a martial arts instructor,
it's a stupid joke, and I've heard it for eight years, "Boo him, boo him."
Max, you keep kicking those kids for a living.
No, we have a lot of bit people in our audience, and I love it.
I love seeing the bit game over our audience.
I love Max.
Max actually hopped in one of my shows in New York, and I literally was like, "Hey, I need
a punchline for this magic trick.
Just do this at this point of the show," and it was so awkward and it was so random, and
he just did it, and then he crushed, and it was awesome.
Thank you, Max, for hopping in my show.
We got two more here.
We've got to wrap it up.
We've got the bobo, the flound.
Talk about commitment.
Yeah.
I don't know what you're talking about.
All right.
Oh, wait.
Do you guys not see this person dressed up in front of the microphone?
What is objective reality?
No.
Back to that one.
Is it just a microphone?
Just a microphone.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I don't know why no one would take a microphone.
There's a microphone right there.
I actually have Gilbert Godfrey doing the voice for me in the background right now.
I'm actually just doing it silently.
All right.
My question on to you is, where do you draw the line in the sand for a comedian to clown?
Because you'll have like prop comic, you'll have physical comics, but they're not necessarily
a clown.
So where do you draw that line in the sand?
Oh, interesting.
Because I definitely have a line in my mind, but I don't know where it is.
So as I, and maybe I have a weird perspective on this, but if you have a physical skill,
I put clowning above comedian.
Oh, I do too.
It's ancient.
You know, clowning is just ancient.
You are.
The questioner is ancient.
Oh, I mean, the truth is off the bat, I don't have an answer.
Like I don't, this is not something I've contemplated before.
I definitely do, as you bring it up, I go, oh, I do see a difference in it.
It is a blend of intellectualism and physical comedy, but yeah, I don't know where that
line is.
And there is, it's weird because I definitely have a real line in my head between people
in my life that are comedians and people who are clowns, and I don't know exactly what
that line is.
It might be self-identifying.
I'm really not sure.
I will say, I don't know artistically, but just in the difference between clowns and
comedians that I have met in my life, they are very different people in general.
Like a comedian, once you've been around people who've done comedy, there's an archetype,
you know, kind of brooding, like there's little like buttons and love languages that you can
understand.
Clowns are far more like carnies and renaissance fair people where there's like, there's a
fucking tough as nails element to clowns.
There is a like, you can't phase them.
Yeah, but also it's like, you know, maybe there's a dark secret.
I don't know.
Like there's an element, usually comedians' dark secret is that they didn't get along
with their mom.
Right.
You know, actually.
I'm shooting off a hip here, but I think like comedians, you tend to like their perspectives
on things.
You kind of like want to know a comedian's perspective before you kind of laugh at their
jokes and clowns seem to like want to make what's ever happening an event that's happening
like right now.
Well, even presentationally, like presentationally, clowns kind of remove your ability as an audience
to look in to the performer, right?
Like the performance is its own thing.
It is very loud.
It is big.
It is in your face, but it's not like somebody telling a story about, you know, breaking
up with somebody and people in the audience are like, wow, that makes me think of that
experience that I went through.
It's very performance focused, which almost makes it harder because now you don't have
a little bit of the emotional buy in that can make art kind of like special and magical
if it hits.
But if it's, you know, a cloud act, then you are looking at physical reaction.
You're looking at, you know, athleticism, timing, like all the the basic building blocks.
This got fucking boring, deep into comedy, but it's important for our it's important
for our legacy.
That's true.
I wanted to hit an eject button for me.
Thank you.
This is actually very insightful.
Can I tell you a joke?
Yes.
Go ahead.
All right.
Why do Catholic priests touch little boys?
Why?
Because they can't get none.
Ah, OK, boys.
All right.
There it is.
Mystery solved.
I'm now regretting following that.
I don't know why.
You guys in a conversation.
Oh, sorry.
Shula scoop.
There he is.
This fucking liar.
This popped into my brain after something you said in the conversation I was having
back there.
When I was in college, one of my friends in theater, I was in theater at the time, whenever
he would go to his room to masturbate, he would tell everybody he was going to get ice
cream.
So, like I said, short, but that was all I had to say.
Oh, my gosh.
That's great.
That's a good bit.
I loved it.
10 out of 10.
No question.
That was great.
That's fantastic.
That's it.
On that note, I think it's time for me to go get some ice cream.
Yeah.
I'm going to go get some ice cream.
Hey, Justin, you want to go get some ice cream together?
I'd love it.
Let's go.
All right.
Two scoops.
Two.
Both of them.
Okay.
All right.
Give it up for Brian Breschwood.
Hey, guys.
Give it up for Justin Robert Young.
Give it up for all y'all for coming out to ScoopFest.
Yeah.
We appreciate it so much.
Thank you all for being here.
Thanks so much, and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the Cone.
As always, check out Great Night.
Check out PX3.
Check out all the things that these fellas do.
We're back.