Oh hello there I didn't see you but I'm so happy you are here because I'd like
to thank the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers. Right now I'd like to thank Frankie, Sticky Scoop, Fifi, Elton Magic
Scoop, Dr. Scoop Little, Dirty Old Scoop, Dead Laszlo, David Walker, Darth Scooper,
Darren Cunningham, Christie Salinas, Christine Elsesser, Chasing the Dragon
Scoop, Blue Line Scoop and Bearded Scoop 3. If you want to be an ice cream truck
driver just like these fine folks head over to preachingfun.com. Preachingfun.com
is where you're going to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the
life you save may be your own and now a show. Hey Johnny do you want to go to an
ice cream social? Yeah I'd love to. Great let's go.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social sitting in Pittsburgh
Pennsylvania that's Paul Mattingly. Sitting at sea it's Matt Donnelly sitting in
Las Vegas the bad-ass me jacking the audio guy. We're preaching fun.
I'm doing wonderful I'm out on the the seas outside of Canada. I said last week
that I was gonna go to st. John Newfoundland and I was so excited. Turns
out Canada's wicked wicked crazy with st. John's so it turns out it was st. John's
New Brunswick and not St. John's Newfoundland. They're lousy with St. John's. Now I already have an
affection for St. John and the Virgin Islands plus St. John's Newfoundland that I
wasn't about to get off the boat for this St. New St. John. I was like I don't have room in my
heart for a third St. John's. You have plenty of St. John's in your life you
don't need more. Do any of these locations go by St. John's? Because that's a
real thing you know. What going from St. John's to St. John's? Yeah well it's a
there you remember Airwolf right? Of course I remember Airwolf. So Stringfellow
Hawk yeah he was always looking for his brother
St. John and that is a shortened way of saying St. John. So there were kids that
were named St. John I just wondered if they ever if that ever applies to like
cities. I'll open my porthole and ask. Okay. Anyone go by St. John? I'm just kidding my
porthole over looks out into a wall. A wall in the boat? Yeah. My porthole looks out
into the vast six feet away is a wall. That's what I. Oh you're just docked
right now. No no no no. Oh no it's an internal porthole. It's an internal porthole. Oh my god. It is a glory porthole. I mean he might be docking
right now as well. Oh yikes docking in a glory porthole. That's cameras from the
waste up so we have no idea. We never will know. Are you ever gonna be on boats
with Pipe to Plain again soon? I don't know. I'm on there they're joining the
boat the ship that I'm on right now next week. Okay so ships in the night.
We would have crossed paths on the day. Yeah. Like them getting on the way. Me
getting off except that I am and now I have to get off early. Right. Here's the
thing so I'm on the ship for four days and that's because originally they wanted
me here for the week but the week started at Scoopfest and I said I can't
do it I gotta go to Scoopfest. Right. Then I got this offer for Virgin Voyages to
join Virgin and that was a two-week gig so I want to say yes to that and basically
saying told by agent I will I will let go of this gig if it means you know if I
have to just just to still do Virgin. Right. Yeah. And that would give me days
off after Scoopfest. Would that be nice? So I was like there's no way they're
gonna agree just to have me on this ship for four days but they're just going to
just truncate the front and back end of the week and they did. Now you have
discovered the true infinite money glitch that is cruise ship lines apparently.
What also meant that means that I knew that I was getting on a performing like
those I was doing shows. Right. And so was it when you got on? Yeah. I didn't do
two shows that night. Wow. And then two shows the next night. Holy shit dude. How did that
go? Luckily you were nice and rested. So yeah. So at Scoopfest I had the already
had this hard task of it that I've never go away for three weeks and I'm away for
three weeks and then on top of the three weeks I'm gone for on cruise ships I
have two shows in Sparta New Jersey on October 16th and the Improv Jam reunion
on October 18th. October 17th is the Sparta shows and so I had to pack for
magic shows for all of those things plus materials you know I could go you know I
go through materials things like that and and and so I was already pretty
nerve-wracked plus I did magic at Scoopfest which means I had to bring stuff
to Scoopfest so I had to bring it I had to perform and bring it home or whatever
so the only chance I had to really pack with sanity was in the dinner break
between daytime Scoopfest and nighttime Scoopfest. On Saturday. Yeah. Right. Which
was a two-hour break and it was like a true two-hour break because we finished
up right before the break started in the daytime session until we actually had
about two hours between the daytime session and the jog versus nerd ball. And
during Ice Cream Social I was getting notifications on my phone from Air
Canada. Right. And I was like that's weird I mean I'm flying tomorrow but I can
check in sure whatever. And they were and they were inappropriate messages right
they were like dick pics and a lot of stuff. They were showing me that. They're
basically saying no there was they were showing me mine and they're saying if
you don't respond to these text messages we're putting these on the internet. So
you didn't respond. And now they're out. Holy Mike Johnson!
I don't know. Paul. Air Canada. Okay. I'd gotten an email like a week before
whatever and I saw that they were shifting the time of my flight to like a
half hour earlier and I said okay great. What I didn't realize was that they also
shifted it to a day earlier. A day earlier than a half hour earlier. God damn! 24 hours and a half hour earlier. Yeah and this is Air Canada not not not my cruise
booker right. Yeah right. The ticket was booked and then the airline moved it's the thing well they
moved. Oh it's Air Canada so the times are metric. That explains it. That
explains that explains the disconnect. It goes by how long it takes ice to melt.
That's how they that's you know ancient ancient Phoenicians had sundials. Most
things in Canada are based on how long it takes ice to melt. That's right. So I
just spend the dinner break rescheduling my travel frantically just on the
emergency line lines because suddenly I was not on the flight that I'm supposed
to be on. Right. And and I should have been on there like the whole that's the
whole thing and so I could. You know how to take the reservation but you don't
know how to hold the reservation. And I so I basically had to come back to the
jack-versus-nerd ball without knowing what I was doing the next day and then
at the end of the costume parade I got an email saying that I had to be on a
flight at a 6 a.m. flight so I had to be at the airport at 445 in the morning.
That is some bullshit. Bullshit. And then because it was a last-minute flight it
wasn't direct so I had to take three flights to get to Canada. Holy fuck man.
So I was three flights total of 15 hours by the time I got to my hotel. They let you
sit on the wing. And then I had to sleep and get up right away and just get to the
ship. And it was like go to the ship there's a guy on a bike who just goes
Matt Donnelly he goes yeah he goes forgive me it's my day off and he's just
dressed in like head-to-toe and beautiful biker riding bike outdoor gear.
Right. And I was like. Forgive it. Stranger? Yeah. But they're waiting for you get in
there. And I was like oh I said I can't have gotten here any faster than me
meeting my driver on time and my driver getting me out of time. I don't know what
I could have done. Yeah. Step on it. What do you mean they're waiting for me what yeah.
There's an extra C note in it for you if you get me there in time for my show.
I get around to the port and the port because we have no record of you being here.
I was literally just told two minutes ago and a hundred feet ago that you were
waiting for me inside. Yeah. Apparently not that guy. So finally a guy from business
comes out and basically reprimands someone at the dock for looking up my
thing improperly. And then that person being very defensive and I was listening
to a very snippy conversation. Guys guys guys could you please have this
uncomfortable conversation after I get on to the boat. I would like to get on
to the boat. You guys could have this conversation for as long as you want
after I'm gone. And so this is like normal little gangway that goes right up
to the fourth deck. Yeah. And then there's a zigzaggy gangway really long
gangway that goes up to the seventh deck. And the person from Princess
gestures me to the zigzaggy gangway that goes up three stories and I have two
giant banks and my my backpack and bags and I was like are you sure I can't go up
the little one yeah. Yeah. But there's like no that's where most of the guests
are getting off to go into it's a Saint Joe to Halifax. And so I go to move like
all my stuff and there's a guy you know working for the cruise like an eager
young young guy English out of first language goes can I help you with that. I
was like boy can you. You sure can. And he takes me up but I'm in a crew cabin not in a
guest cabin. Yeah. And so we get on the ship and I was like showing him my room
number and he's trying to get me to this the seventh deck where the crew for the
regular cabins. Right. I'm trying to explain to him no no I'm in a crew
cabin. Yeah. So he's stopping as he stops like a janitor and they and they speak
Spanish to each other and the janitor's like no follow me. And I go through this
ornate path where all said I'm like outside of the ship on this weird deck
area where I'm like I don't know if this is supposed to be here then boom I'm
into a crew area and then into finally into my cabin. And the good news is my
cabin is 50 feet from the theater. Oh that's nice. Oh that's that's big. That's
big. Yeah. Yeah. So I get all my stuff from the theater I'm back in the thing
and then I realize I should go get like a cup of coffee or something to eat or
something and I am walking aimlessly in the crew area. Please someone give me
coffee. Try to find your way out. Yeah. No one no one showed me how to get out to the
regular ship. Yeah. And so I see two guys and I'm like I'm just trying to get to
like the I don't know regular part of the ship or like where the passengers go or
whatever and they go who are you are you supposed to be back here what are you
doing and I was like oh no. You've done it now. There is a there is a hard line
like I said when we were doing second city tours we had a very fortunate
situation where we had passes that were literally crew and passenger status.
Right. We had both so we could we could go anywhere but yeah if you haven't been
designated they get snippy. Yeah. But they they they figured it all out. Did you do
a little quick bit of table side. Honestly or did they harpoon you. I straight up
just I straight up just walked away. I walked up to another floor. I'm good. And
then I went up there. You just left them arguing about who you might be. I was
like I don't want to I don't want to do this. And now that's awesome. That's
awesome. You know what I can find it on my own. You guys have a good day. Never
mind. Yeah. So yeah it was it was it was it was a it was a big adventure to get
here and then just do two shows right away and they went really well. Good. I
was like I was like this could get this could have gone a lot better if I had if
I was able to sleep. Yeah. Those shows were all right. Imagine if I had slept. So
listener Chris Lowry is on the the he listens to the show and he and his wife
book book travel for people. Yeah. Go with Lisa.com that's where they help set
up people want to see me on the ship and stuff. And so Lisa his wife is on on the
ship and I met her before. She's come to my Elton shows. They offered to take me
out to dinner at the beautiful Crown Grill. Nice. On my on the second night I
was on board and then they were telling me about how they ran into people who
saw my show on St. John. I was like oh I don't think they're gonna tell me a
story where they complimented me. She was like yeah one guy was like yeah it
wasn't really for me a mind reader guy or whatever and I was like why are you
telling me the story? Yeah. What the hell? Oh that's gonna make this next story super awkward then
because I just saw several people that hated your show. I understand. I'm not
for everyone. As I said as I said at Scoopfest you know you know you're not
for everyone but as soon as you hear it it's devastating. They were also very
critical about my outfit that I was wearing at the time. It really hurt. But
they talked about how they basically said like oh we're going to the and
basically the Crown Grill but they said the other name for another ship's
steakhouse. Yeah. Cagney's I think it was called. Okay. And so then that so I go oh
so they were coming here to this thing tonight that's what they told you they
invited you to dinner to join them here and I go yeah so they're here yeah and I
go like oh okay and we look around or whatever we don't see them. Just now
getting back to my room from getting coffee for this episode I end up taking
an elevator and two guys are like oh you're the mind bender guy and I go yeah
yeah we saw your show the other night. I go yeah and then nothing.
Yeah okay and then we saw the whole thing we saw all of it and then the
awkward silence the guy goes I think we saw you the night at Cagney's you're
having dinner with Lisa and I go oh my god it's them. It's the guys they were
talking to. It's the eyes not for me. It's not for me guy. Amazing. I'm face to
face with two guys who definitely did not enjoy my show. Fucking shit. That's
great. And it was like a tea like a bet like a murder she wrote mystery novel
where like I had the key I had the key that they they named the steakhouse the
wrong steakhouse and it's the only thing they could have said to clue you in. This
is confirmed but they did not enjoy my show. Yeah. We saw your show the other
night. It was a show. There were chairs and everything. Hey Eureka is making a
great point in the chat here. She's saying Matt is upset that Noah
compliments his show but when he runs into audience members he doesn't
compliment them either and that's a really good point. Yeah. I have to go
back and tell those guys nice hats. Nice hats assholes. We have to do that. Oh you
guys were great at Cagney's the other night. I saw you order that steak. Amazing
work. Yeah well Eureka I'm not upset that no one compliments my show. I'm thrown
off when people insist on telling me a story that someone did not enjoy my show.
That is weird man. That's weird. I have no problem hearing nothing. That's
different. That's different. Is that what is that where your brain goes after you've
booked people on thousands of travel experiences is that you just get to like
oh yeah well you know a lot of people just hate you and they don't really. Yes.
I mean people definitely get into that state of mind of like none of this
matters to me so why would it matter to you. Right. Yes. Right. That's the
energy of like we're just shooting the breeze I just know this I know that. Yeah.
These guys hated your show but it like in their mind she's sitting there
thinking like oh Matt has done this show so many times. Well surely people have
disliked the show before. It can't bother him it's just water off a duck's
back like who cares. We're being harsh too. It wasn't that he hated it just wasn't for
him. Oh no no he actually sent me a message as well. I have that to read in school mail. He did. He hated it.
The way the story actually goes is that the subtext of the stories is told to me
is basically didn't didn't believe I was an actual mind reader. Oh really. Well in that case I've got good news for them. They were they were right. So this is
Simon Cowell's cousin. I should make no claims during my show that I am like I
set the premise of the trip but I do I do know I basically like all of my stuff
as if I'm doing any mind reading bits it's all comedic. Right. Like I get the
results correct but I all I'm trying to do is make sure it's funny along the
way and that's the it is the weird it's the weird thing I imagine but you it's
a you can't deny it if someone goes like I don't think you really do that you're
like that's right that's correct and so if you're upset with me for even towing
the line for claiming to have superpowers I could if that upsets you I
get it like I can't do anything about it. It's it's it's it's the deal. Right. All
right I did it Jacob. Nailed it. I said Orica's name correctly on air. Oh nice. Oh
I am impressed. I know I noted that I have never heard I'd never heard the
pronunciation correct and I was like oh it's Orica. Yeah yeah took me 12 years and
and herself in my abracadabra to get it right but that's what happened. Finally
got it. Oh man Jacob you're gonna ask me for a sponsor and I can't access my
phone so I'm gonna go over to a webpage and open it up there. Oh nice. Well while
you're doing that we'll just we'll just talk a little bit about scoop fest here
we just had our big scoop fest. It was amazing. It was fantastic. We are all
almost recovered and by all I mean like fucking everybody I imagine. I mean I
don't buddy. Yeah everybody got beat. I didn't get COVID this time. Well there's
that. That I know of. Yeah but also like legit like I felt like everyone not just
us I felt like the attendees were like Jesus by the end of it. Yeah well
actually I was having a conversation with Ryre the night of the loadout
because we even commented during the during the show during the scoop fest
podcast that the energy kind of like went weird in the room for a while and
we and we were kind of chatting about that and the energy of the of the whole
thing and it really seems like everyone came to scoop fest as you know in a way
that you would expect which is a relief you know they're coming to scoop fest as
this as a big energy relief thing and especially by the end of it everyone was
kind of like sitting in that lull. Yeah I don't know it was it was a it was an
interesting it was an interesting thing. Yeah I think I think so I think I think
this I really you know we talked about this on a few episodes back but like I
that is it is a crazy time yeah and I think and I think during Penn Sunday
School live like Penn really hung a lantern on it in terms of talking to his
children yeah you guys don't know but this actually is incredibly unusual
right and like what's happening is impossible yeah and so you know none of
this that is happening can happen it's none it's all impossible but it's
happening anyway yeah yeah yeah and the show's also 12 years old or whatever 11
years old and so are indeed our we've all gotten older we're older and so is
everyone else maybe the evening festivities started 7 and not 8 wrap up
around 7 I don't know I don't know about all that we're all gonna go to the
sizzler and have dinner around 4 no I mean like something to spearheads the
the the nighttime programming and stuff I was like panicking trying to add stuff
and then by the time it all went down I was like oh I put a lot of stuff up here
oh yeah we need we need I did have I did maybe over program some some of some
nights there was activities no lulls though that's for sure no I mean to go
in order a bucket show crushed so fun yeah big thanks to Brenna, Mark, Robert, Mark
that was fantastic that's again and like I had so many scoops coming up and saying
it was the first time they'd seen a bucket show and I was like well hope you
like that one because it's never gonna get any better that was actively telling
people to not come back to future bucket shows because that one was that was to
be the best one I don't know if I went quite that far but I just said that is
the best it's close yeah as close if you came to see both those shows shit I
don't know man I know it's tell you that's great we're doing we're doing one
of Tunis Tavern like real soon it's like October 23rd let's oh we're gonna crush
that one we already sold some tickets for it let's not know we're gonna crush
that one because that one was already planned that one was a was a carve out
and Paul statement never see another one unless you've already planned to see no
it was just it'll be better it was just really it's just one of those things too
again and even like I was doing that interview for the documentary and I
recounted our first meeting Matt and how you had friends in the audience that
night after we'd done our show and they asked you how long we've been working
together yes it's just well it's just one of those things it just kind of
remind me again it's like we had two brand new people who we hadn't played
with and forever don't play with regularly and it was like you know forget
it I had never I had never coached Brenna's impromptu team yeah or one with
Brenna yeah I just knew we just we vibrate Brenna obviously his podcast
co-hosts and friends and stuff and she always said like oh we should all just
shook around some time everybody it's a cold runner and everybody hey wave to
all scoops she's got to go pick up our giz from the grandparents so she's she's
running across the state to go grab the doggy yeah yes yeah rainbow bright shirt
represent me be safe sweetheart holler if you need anything I love you
too did you guys have a favorite part of scoop fest no I mean so many as well as
I was trying to zip through an order because the next day was the barbecue
right and Jacob you cooked barbecue pulled pork and yeah my god dude you
fucking crushed that too oh it was so good I really wish I could have got more
of that pork but I I didn't get enough but it was good yeah the food Alex
Bartman made fresh pizzas for everybody oh yeah - the pizza was great yep the
food was the food was all was all solid SJ made SJ's famous mac and cheese that
shit was great - yeah so we all we all pitched in a little bit this year
instead of doing any we didn't or last year we cooked the main stuff and then
ordered the sides and this year we said now fuck it we're not ordering anything
yeah we're doing it all it was really good and it was it was nuts it was nuts
for you guys to pull off all the stuff you pulled off yeah it was windy it was
the only thing we didn't account for was wind I remember driving a day and it
rained for like two minutes I was like rain we have not we have no backup plan
for rain dead if it rains I had a germ of a plan but it wasn't a good plan it
was not a good plan at all yeah yeah yeah I mean scuba nova girl in the chat
is saying everyone cram into Jacob's house that was gonna be plan B yeah yeah
yeah I feel like we were definitely just gonna get to plan B well as funny as it
was it was still pretty hot and the Sun was pretty blazy and you know you had
that shade wall everybody just rammed up against the shade wall yeah and then I
got really red to the point where scoops were like are you okay I had to let them
know that that's just what the Mattingly jeans do I just get real red looking I'm
fine I didn't I didn't burn like you can see I don't have a sunburn at all but I
just I got really red I look like I'm gonna explode when I'm mowing the lawn
out here like if I come inside just be at and hands it's like oh my god you're a
lobster I'm like it's just what I do my body just it gets that's you know that's
how I'm getting the heat out it comes to the front but yeah I do I radiate
exactly a pine of plane played the barbecue they were fantastic that was
the that was the biggest swing I did I pulled for this one was that my friends
from Ireland were all off they weren't they weren't obligated to be on ships so
I said if you're available let's get you in here and so they I flew them in from
Ireland to be here is their first time in Vegas and they just were absolutely
blown away by the exhausted and I had to write them a note being like you know
it's very common that people love Las Vegas and also think three days is
plenty right oh yeah and that was the case for them they were definitely like
just wiped at the end sure but they yeah they crushed it at Jacob's house and
they're they're just that I love those guys so much and they're so charming and
they're such they're great at what they do and it's they've such different
personalities and they all find a way to really shine and it's really funny and I
like them and so yeah they I was I was very emotional watching them play in
Jacob's backyard yeah it was great it was a very scary deal for me we were
supposed to have you you're talking about the wind we were supposed to have
another entertainer at the at the barbecue but the wind kept Michael Doe
from being able to juggle at the barbecue right so much no it's Parkinson's yes
and he asked it he said yes to doing school first before he knew he had it
right because obligation and then he has to juggle you know 500 throws every day
to make sure he can keep movement in his body and be able to do what he does for
a living while he fights this vicious disease and then it's fucking windy as
hell yeah it's windy we might not go and I said oh you can't you don't want to go
he goes well I can do it the show will be funny but there will be no juggling in
it and then he said no successful juggling throwing but not not catching
okay let's let's let's just call it so I was aggravated too because it was like
it was perfect all afternoon and then like 20 minutes before Godot was was
set to go up that's when the wind kicked up yeah like it was it was and then like
half an hour later it was it was back to being like there was a light breeze but
it was fine after that still but yeah it was crazy it was crazy for a minute yeah
yeah oh and then but he still was phenomenal yeah one then he did the
variety show yeah yeah yeah so then that night we surprised the audience with a
reuniting of two characters in a clown shortly after the very recent breakup of
the podcast to do a podcast battle Jimmy Sonina dressed in full clown regalia he
did was delightfully ironic because in their Cirque show it's Johnny and RJ
have to wear a lot of makeup and Jimmy doesn't and so it's very funny for Jimmy
coming full makeup while they were there goes and we had delightful trivia
battle hosted by Mikey for between between us and they won yep they did
spoiler alert because we're gonna put those in our patreon feed like always
and so that was really fun then while I was doing my shows at the Magic Castle a
month ago someone on my special like touring company feed on my abracadabra
babble which is a whatsapp thread right I share my my all my all my adventures
and someone said why aren't you and Nick doing scoop fest and I literally just
turned to him backstage like good point Nick what are you doing this dates like
when I was like all right come out to scoop Nick and I did our pillar set in
that we did the Magic Castle at scoop fest which is so fun because in our set
I get to do an illusion with Nick that he normally does with his wife and I
love doing this bit it was great the whole thing was great that whole that
whole show was really really good so you make you make an excellent magic
assistant Matt this is this is a running gag right that was really funny that bit
was funny Alex Ramone had a bit in his show where he has someone called
misdirection and then his regular show he used to show girl as misdirection and
we did the Magic Castle I came out as misdirection and the foolers tour I came
out as misdirection and telling me to just improvise and dance and pretend I'm
a showgirl is not a tall not a tall ask for me in any way no I I will I will fake
dance until the Sun comes up and basically it's also me going like I have
no magic responsibilities great I'll be over here being funny yeah yeah you do
all the work I just have to pretend like you know doing so that no problem oh and
I still get credit great even better and so yeah we have to do that bit and man
yeah the show Nick and I have done is really come together now we've done it
two different two different runs each run is always like 15 shows yeah so it's
really become like a really fun show to do I really enjoy doing it and and that
was fun and then Lindsey Benner I don't know dude and Gary and Lenzie and Gary
and Emily when they're playing Gary I don't know how to like tell people what
you're gonna see right now because you're like I guess she's a juggler but
like not really a juggling show like it's just this beautiful piece she does
called the book of love and I know this because she ran into this with it's now
it's now part of the party over at Las Vegas at the cosmopolitan right and same
thing where she said like hey you know I can do this bit in the show and I heard
she told me you know I hope I'm not betraying any confidences but she said
that they were a little like what I don't know or whatever and she basically
was like just let me do it yeah yeah because like whenever she does she did
that she was part of like the magic live one year she had the whole bit of magic
live and got like standing ovations for it it's like it's not I'm yeah it's just
this beautiful really cool beautiful art piece you get some of the audience and
does this whole arc of love with these juggling comedy bits and it's just
beautiful that's funny and it's and she's just a brilliant person it's funny
it's it's poignant and it kind of goes from from one almost variety slot to the
next on its own and it just it it flows and it works yeah and they're both they
were both so committed and fantastic oh yeah just yeah Gary comes out and it's
just and Gary is just a fucking icing on the cake with all of this it's it's so
good yeah and it's just and so yeah that crush so yeah that was and that was that
that was that was night one yeah which was it was a lot yeah and then we fell
over day two one and it goes into day one technically yeah that was the that
was the extra all right that yeah it wasn't even day one that was just the
extra yeah that was the VIP yeah let's do let's do a quick sponsor and then come
back and do day two today's show is brought to you by Bobby Budkiss's kick
butt buttery hello I'm Bobby Budkiss and I got a kick butt buttery you want some
butter for your butt for your buns I got bun butter I got butter for cobs I got
big butter I got bitter butter some of my bitter butter is comes in itty bitty
pallets would you like some of Bobby but kisses itty bitty bitter butter pallets
for the house are too small for me the pallets are too small yeah you want to
try some of Bobby butt kickers bitter but a bigger pallets it to be a palette
okay it's approximately four times the size of our original Bobby but it's
bitter but a bit it's like a bucket now that's a whole nother product oh the
bucket yeah we've got palette we got buckets then we've also got we've got
ladies that's the other that's the other size what's holy whole lady size of
water it's just a lady made of butter that's right it's a it's a man a
margarine mannequin oh oh yeah I'm just here to pick up my lady butter your
margarine mannequin we were delivered to you you don't have to come here for it
my god why you have a gun what are you doing I'm here how do you butter oh my
god this is how it goes down for Bobby but no please we want whatever you want
is yours oh god interface groups at checkout it's really kind of a send the
audio from that recording after that terrible incident yeah we should not have
aired that that was tragic yeah well that's what you get for recording
commercials on ring cameras it's very on tour but sometimes every now and then
you get a home invasion in a whole damn it we're just trying to do some ads here
every now and then you get a home invasion what you're gonna do so on to
day two technically day three and also technically day one yes yeah how this
keeps happening to us how we get tired of these things yeah is the variety show
and this year was the most like frogs in a wheelbarrow year ever you know for
those expression but they're trying to keep frogs in a wheelbarrow they keep
hopping out you know we try to get new people in and and and still honor if
other people want to come back and do it and you know there are people that were
on board up until like days before bailing out there are people who want to
do it but then like took jobs a month ago that left town like and it just was
like I just kept watching the thing and at one point I was texting Jacob like
days beforehand being like I'm really in my head about this right this year's
variety show and I was coming up with like backup plans of maybe doing
violin prob with Maeve Kennedy from the trio how funny like I was like really
like what's happening and then some things just fall in our lap like Stapes
was still in town just around or what JD was like you know Stapes is down I was
like oh right we got Stapes that was great days before Harrison Greenbaum
calls me up as is hey I'm gonna happen to be at the Rio this week are you in
town I was like well that scoop vest and of course Harrison was like yeah down no
problem yeah so good he was goddamn that was so good it's like really happy about
it and someone I've been trying to get through for years to do it because we we
have a lot of friends in the burlesque community and like to go a little
burlesque and we're Vegas we could throw in a little a little a little fun
burlesque although we our cabin is always like hey as weird as you want to
be oh yeah like whatever shits like been too weird for other burlesque shows do
it do it here yeah go oh like I mean jumping ahead hazel performed and hazel
and I spoke a month or so earlier and she was like I I could do just like a
classic burlesque thing and and just come out and be pretty and and have
pretty costumes and fans and everything I was like that's great people will love
it I'm sure if you do it you can also do your weird stuff yeah the weird the
weird stuff will play and she came out on stilts just like a giant tree yeah
she was a hint from Lord of the Rings and she was tree beard a sexy stripping
in the Lord of the Rings beard it was amazing two tiny hobbit dolls that she
made kiss and make out with each other and they stripped - yep and but I finally
we've tried in the past with our friend Nick Byler came by who does this really
incredible act in absent and he's just and he's also in disco studies the the
host they're extremely talented fascinating guy yes he does this really
we did this really weird thing in the show hot trashed or the pandemic where
he tries to make a banana daiquiri while trying to still hit a triangle on the
notes during this one song it's this conflict between trying to make the
daiquiri and at the triangle all while he's wearing just a banana a skirt made
of actual bananas right and it was great to have some equal representation from
the male side of the burlesque world and then I had Jonas Wilburton and I forgot
that I was also burlesque a bit yeah yeah but he was a very funny John John
McEnroe uh-huh where he has the audience hit him with tennis balls and so he does
a seer wheel which you know those of you in the circus world are familiar but
those you may not be it's a big giant steer steel wheel it looks like a giant
hula hoop a steel ring that he is able to manipulate and swirl around and this
was a steel ring with a radius of about what six and a half feet or not radio
yeah what's the thing across the circle whatever that distance is radius right
yeah this was the smallest stage he'd ever perform this yeah we only gave him
eight feet of space he had done it on a on a nine-footer I think maybe mm-hmm he
he had kept next to me like there's a version I can do without the wheel I
said then let's do that and he goes well just send me the dimensions anyway and I
said the dimensions and he goes oh that's pretty small I go then don't do
the wheel just do the other part and he goes okay well I'll bring the wheel just
in case and I go okay and then he sends me we load in and I see it's a carpet
and stage which is again not ideal for zero it's carpeted so if you don't want
to do the wheel do not do the wheel and yes all right I probably won't but I'll
bring it just in case yeah and then not only was it carpeted but it had ent
leaves and leftover banana daiquiri all over it tomato juice yes it had tomato
seeds banana juice and fucking leaves so I would I had been sketching stuff away
with my foot the whole time because I knew that wheel was coming trying to
make sure that was oh yeah but we all were we were all like try to clean the
stage as much as possible I told him afterwards I said that was fucking brave
dude and it was amazing but it was it was also really really funny and really
really awesome one coming up on in November he's doing a show over at the
Vegas Theatre Company so we're gonna have him on as a guest oh great great
great great yeah yeah but yeah Brenna did in more another goblin burlesque
Stephen Roberts came by crush to do a stand-up yeah that's not a not a show
without Stephen yeah and without personal highlight for me was Michael
Gudeau yeah yeah and seeing Mike do it seem like you don't do it it was so good
it was so funny and holy fuck yeah we talked about it at the at the con but
uh you forget we're friends with Michael Gudeau we hang out we chat with Michael
Gudeau we all forget that you get Michael Gudeau on stage and he's a
goddamn killer I mean it's just what he's gonna get on stage and just do it
it's crazy to me too I was lucky enough to go see him with the Lance Burton show
way back in the day right and this is when I was first working with second
city as a full-time second city and a class act that Lance Burton is he called
me out in the show had me stand up and wave to the people cuz nice cuz Lance
Burton knows how to be a fucking entertainer yeah you know we help each
other we talk each other up right that's what it's about and that that had that
moment has stuck with me and just like the fact that Michael Gudeau and Mac
King both specifically came out to watch us do the bucket show I got I put it up
on our Facebook and whatnot Mac tweeted about it because he loves come see us
which is just so amazing to me cuz he's one of my heroes too we have we have
fucking strip performer royalty at this fucking thing yeah like real deal you
can't get any higher on the totem pole how many shows did he say he'd done it
was 19 years 19 years thousands and thousands yeah I mean it's nuts and I
just forget like he just gets the audience right in that pocket and as soon
as soon as they're there you're like oh I forgot it's just cruises yeah from
here like it just he just is so funny and there's so many gags and he just
nails them and it just was like oh god it was great he really you really that
was the second time I was very emotional at scoop fest was was that right there
was really awesome it's a big moment it's a big moment I again I'm just I'm
just honored that that not to say that Harrison's ice stacking prediction via
9/11 theme didn't really I loved that too my brother was involved in that trick
and that made it even more special for me it's only it's only appropriate
because your brother was involved in the in the real day too right involved
involved is a big way to say helped out with building seven but I mean you know
you sure you say what you want to say involved masterminded I know he won't
take credit for the master minding of it but that's only because he's modest
then we had our mouth finger bottle competition oh yes oh my gosh it gets
better every year I so all through scoop fest I make it a point so we you know
our room there at the Orleans our big our big convention room there at the
Orleans it's right off of the main hall in their convention space there's other
conventions going on while we're there there was some religious thing going on
on one side of us there was a family reunion going on on the other side of
us so I made it a point to as much as possible keep those main doors open
but no no no figure but I'll just during the whole goddamn thing it is it is
entertaining for me to watch people walk past those doors it's the reason that I
keep them open I love watching you watching watching people look in and be
like oh I do it every year I love it during my there was a crowd of people at
the doors with just pure confused look it was great at one point I went to you
know use the facilities and I was in a bathroom stall in the men's room and I
heard two guys talking go like yeah they're not really checking any badges
over there that whatever that scoop thing is going over there and then the
other goes yeah but like what the hell's going on over there one guy's like we
could just go in there they're not gonna stop us and the other guys like yeah but
should we do I want to do that dare I dare I let my freak flag fly what I'm
trying to put an obelisk I believe inside of me I don't know how they were
gonna do it that makes me laugh they're not checking badges like you wouldn't
know like you wouldn't stick out like a sore fucking thumb if you weren't a
scoop or if you weren't at least down to clown this year our mystery our mystery
gift was a fez yeah where you could bejeweled so we had a bejeweling
station you could you could you could which was a stroke of genius by the way
that bejeweling station was that worked out well that goes that I mean easier
than that goes up Michael Osroth is basically our director of scoop fest at
this point he really is he did a fantastic job with these these turned out
awesome he kicks everything uphill for us well we tried it well we all pull our
hair out trying to pull off school fest and and acts as a wonderful ambassador he
and Laurie in the party room to help really initiate and introduce other
scoops to each other in the party room really gets the conversations going and
that that vibe carries on the show itself we were running in the new tariff shit
we were running all kinds of stuff yeah and I we really wanted pink robes to
continue the robe theme to figure out the Neapolitan effect we had vanilla now
we have a strawberry and and and then what's coming next chocolate robes I
said get warm and some experience pain I do an idea to mess with it okay but but
I don't remember the game of the idea of Fes but then Fes is like I think it was
me it might have been you I mean we could look through that we could look
through the text but I think it was me I'm not taking I know it wasn't me so
that's I'll give you full credit okay it was me it was it was you or it was you
or Michael yeah me and Michael I think but Mike but again so many times were
like oh because of this is getting expensive because of this we can't do it
or whatever and else fraud just kept after it yeah to make sure that we had
everything we wanted to deliver to the scoops the way we wanted yeah I have
ideas and Michael actually makes them happen
it's yeah exactly ideas yeah those of you guys listening just just picture
casino floor and a bunch of people in pink robes and maroon fezzes with a big
not a cult on the back we're going in and out of the casino right and it is
the best site it is the funniest thing to walk into it's just so funny it's so
good it's just great so yeah and during all this yeah I think I think we'd figure
it out we had a documentary crew running around during all this yes
capturing all this madness yeah yeah it was just really really great and yeah a
supernova girl in Chad saying the group photo never happened yeah I just want to
note an entire documentary happened so just just yeah there's gonna be there's
gonna be like clear we really didn't cover it yeah I mean if you really want
to get technical like hundreds of thousands of group photos happened as
the documentary goes on we also we did we did a group photo with the at the
ball too at the job we did we did we did do that yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we
usually do one earlier in the in the event yeah but yeah we did one at the
ball this year yeah I have great news I just got a text message I'm being
offered it's not even it's not even asking me to to respond to it and to
apply for it I'm being offered a new job right now it's only gonna take 60 to 90
minutes a week some weeks at most 60 minutes a day 250 dollars no they're
willing to pay me up to $3,000 a week get out of here yeah you have to murder
apparently let's see Paul Mattingly oh I even know that guy I'll split it with
you yeah remote work I could work from anywhere let's see oh I get instant I
get several weeks of paid time off instantly with this with this new
position that's nice and no experience necessary so they're gonna give me
three thousand dollars a week and they don't even care that I don't know what
the gig is I it feels too good to be true but it must be yeah this is I mean
it is a hard time to be looking for work right now and yeah this shit happens to
us and we're not even looking for work right you know what I mean like fucking
every day it's fucking nuts I feel so bad yes oh yeah in the chat a wall scoop
says even if they crash scoop fest what would you have done if they were
enjoying themselves and not being disruptive excellent point and the
answer to that is probably nothing well that's why I just commented I said exactly
we just try to obelisk him yeah we give him some poker chips and say please
download our shit that's what I do all day long man
get it out chips and hey check us out yeah yeah it was nuts it was nuts
now figure but whole oh those are things that we had a confessional booth set up
oh I know our separate repeat I am excited to hear those I haven't heard
anything I don't know and one of our old friends was a Piper was behind there
helping out and I said are you having she was there and also you haven't
functions oh I'm having a blast because it is so great to be in the room where
I'm not the weirdest person in the room oh and I said like think of it - yeah by
my beautiful beautifully said and I was like that's exactly what I want people
feel like yeah they come to the best you know it's like that's exactly it's all
about letting your freak flag fly man yeah we don't give a shit it's like you
know yeah yeah we're welcome very welcoming community yeah look at that
we're up to 40 participants that's a new record for the chat guys we're doing it
that's growing what else was it scoop fest we had the mouth finger butthole
tournament we had all of the quizzes with Mikey oh which yeah yes oh yeah he
outdid himself again this year oh uh we should say on the show too several
people asked about it at scoop fest people saw some medical attendance
checking out Mikey at one point that was just a it was a very minor thing no big
deal everybody is perfectly fine it was the casino being a little overly
cautious just having their people check check Mikey out after a little slip and
fall that we checked on him he was okay yeah everybody's good they were they
were everybody was healthy and happy oh then we had oh Celestia thank you
scuba cabra in the chat for reminding me Celestia was there doing caricatures
yes jock versus third ball whole every time I walked over to see what she had
done for for a new group of people over there it was more disgusting and more
wonderful well anything I will say my brother was like oh we should get a we
should get a caricature and so I did play my scoop card and got cut sees in
line to do a dare you I know but it was you know I see my brother maybe twice a
year if I'm lucky in person so it was really nice to actually get a moment to
come to have this and we've got a year we have to get Celestia to do one of the
three of us yes yes we should well I mean shit she'll do that hard to go sit
for that anytime you know what maybe we can have her do that during the zoom
because we're having her on soon we can do that because I'd love to I'd love to
get one and put out put it up in the new chart well we'll talk we'll talk to her
about that when we have her on next and see if she can just watch us during a
zoom if that would be enough for her to get us I'm sure it would would work yeah
so she was incredible like and also I had a personal highlight with the
Pollywood Squares that fucking tell us about Pollywood Square what happened
there so I was a little worried because of the board I was kind of like all this
work into this fucking thing and if this doesn't go well it's gonna be the worst
but then Ryar summed it up. Last year at SkooFest I was like the only note I have was
not enough Paul was not enough Paul that was my whole thing and so like like we did a
lot of stuff a lot of things but Paul you know was not I basically was like
Paul is funny we're trying to get him involved we were trying to get you to
host a little bit of the trivia battles and so the adjustments we made was let's
let's take on everybody in trivia so that it's right it's it's Paul and us
against everybody instead of having two podcasts face each other right and then
my brain was like oh Hollywood Squares but everyone's Paul that's Paul's
characters all of Paul's characters and I we reach out big there's a way to do
with technology but I go no no I want a physical clunky awkward big square yes
where we have to move squares around Paul and I of course turned to Ryar
Appledorn to be like you you know what I'm talking about you know what this
means so Ryar Appledorn made the biggest clunkiest Hollywood Squares board that
could even fit through the door right with hangable X's and O's it was like
nine feet what was it was like nine feet by nine feet it was huge yeah yeah and and that
was the the thing Ryar and and Mike were bringing it out and Ryar said they
couldn't hardly fit it through the door right and it started off well they
couldn't fit it through the door that's why they had to come through the a
different area from backstage on stage it started to crumple and bend and fuck
up and the moment it started to just fall apart Ryar was just like oh this is
gonna be perfect and he was right he was right the stupidity of it all just
added just layers of dumb and it just oh it was so good it was down you were you
were Paul Lind Johnny Australia yeah Truman Capote which is a new one in the
day Mumra Mumra my favorite Paul Stanley vampire Bill Cosby
barrel child barrel child yeah oh man and it was we were just asking trivia
questions and making Paul's characters answer all of them Paul just came
buckled right into the format of knowing how to play Hollywood Squares and I
watched a lot as a kid yeah yeah and it was hysterical it was so fun it's really
good I was like and I was like you were like I would know I was like this is I
as soon as it came in my head I was like hit it's in and it was floating is like
I could we could do this multiple times like I was like if anything short I was
like do another round with more care even one point Jake was like well if
it's good and I was like no this is good I don't know why there was doubting I
don't know why there was doubting this pimping Paul nine times is exactly what
the show needs and at the end Paul was almost guilty about how well I went he
said so it felt a little self-indulgent and I was like you're festival it's true
yeah yeah we're at a festival of you talking about that's all good we're at a
festival about you yeah and we are celebrating a show that has your name in
the title it was it's it's possibly a little self-indulgent in some way the
whole thing is self-indulgent right now on the list right with mouth finger
butthole it is now just a it's just on the list yeah yeah it's like that could
be done at churnouts too yeah yeah well now we've got an idea for it for for
zoom too I've got an idea for it for on camera oh hell yeah yeah yeah mini
version that Paul can just stick his head through that sounds fucking
fantastic it's gonna be great that is good good good it was fucking hot shit
and it made me laugh too so that was great yeah I'll tell you what else Paul
is gonna stick his head through and that's the following sponsor pizza for
your hands that's right no more chewing with that pesky mouth of yours now
there's pizza for hands hello I'm Reginald Felicity Guinevere and I have
invented pizza mittens that's right pizza mittens cooked fresh every day
made to order slathered in the finest of pasta sauces and mozzarella cheese the
mittens are then placed on your hand piping hot and it's like the old Edward
40 hands days remember those days remember being an Edward 40 hands do
you ever have friends do that to you and when 40 hands they would take a cold 40
of alcohol and they would duct tape the 40 to your hand and then you had to
drink the 40 because it was so cold to drink the 40 quickly to stop all the
cold really fast is a similar thing but with pizza as mittens and so the pizza
comes on it's pretty hot so you got to eat the pizza very quickly to get the
heat off your hands but then the heat goes in your mouth and you burn your
mouth but it's still really good it's still really really good yes yes yes
yes and her haste groups to check out pizza mittens
so then what else what else was oh Gabrielle Lester just destroyed she
just crushed Gabrielle yeah so fun and that was Carrie's mom who was up there
with her I believe she's just known as mama scoop now yeah so so for those of
you who don't know I hope I'm not putting anybody on blast here but Carrie
brought her sister and her mother which is great and I think her sister spent
more time than she thought she would hanging out with some of the events her
mom certainly did her mom wasn't sure she was gonna enjoy it at all clearly
she did oh by the end of it her mom was in yeah and I thought even by the end of
it halfway through it mom was in I believe this was on Friday they got the
hard news that their brother had suffered a stroke mmm oh jeez yes and so
that yeah mom was upset sister's upset or Carrie's upset they're all fucking you
know it's rough because it's in fees in Florida right what can you do
luckily scoopfest acted as a distraction and by the end of the event his health
had improved he was doing much better of course still you know not an ideal
situation but things are going better and yeah yeah yeah so I think not only
did it like it helped as a distraction and everything but yeah it was really
cool seeing mom scoop find out what this community is all about and kind of just
get with it it's pretty crazy the shenanigans that is involved in this
community yeah yeah but yeah Gabrielle was was great and then we brought back
the pie the plane people to play for everybody to play for all the people not
just the barbecue and of course that culminated with sweet Caroline we finally
got to combine the the two bits the one the one that we knew yelling fucking
whore in between the bits and then again a great time to be looking out of the
front door of the convention hall and watching the people walking by oh I bet
I bet did they lose their fucking minds I bet those oh pure confusion it's
wonderful and then adding in I don't believe you you're making it up and so
we finally got both bits combined into sweet Caroline yeah and while we were
shouting it Phil just turned the Fionn and said what is happening right now
right who knows they know they were confused but they loved it right I mean
they they just yeah well here's the funniest thing okay so one of the things
that happened behind the scenes was you know they say we'll take requests and we
hadn't take a break to do Hollywood Squares and so in the break people
come up to me give me different songs you know one of things that what's it
called Princess of the City or whatever that's not the famous Irish song is by
the Pogues oh it's a what's it called a New York City fairy tale or something
like that yeah fairy tale of New York that's what it's called very very New
York it's a traditionally Chris it's a Christmas song but it's it's crazy it's
about the deterioration of this long-term relationship these two people
that grow to hate each other and yeah it's real it's a beautiful song but it
isn't originally traditionally a Christmas song they're just cracking up
going like I guess we'll just play it even though it's a Christmas song Merry
Christmas yeah and then another song someone came up to Fionn and again just
like you know time and culture and everything else he's the he plays the
flute in the band and someone came to feel it was like oh would you play like
the orange flute of blah blah blah or whatever I don't know the name of the
song no that was it and film just dead face was like ah maybe I don't know if
we know that one and in this face is that it is a song about the English like
conquering the Irish like the orange flute is about like the orange like yeah
it's like you were not playing that it's like when I first when I first start
when I was first sitting there at the barbecue watching I was like I wonder if
they'll do like the the Outlander theme and I was like that's Scotland you
dumb I didn't say anything but I was like the Outlander theme that would be
and I went that's fucking Scotland you don't even doubt shut your fucking yeah
people who are from Scotland do not want to be told they're from Ireland and vice
versa and vice versa it's very key thing I don't know why anyone would do it yeah
very crazy Ozzy no I'm not gonna I'm not gonna touch that so there we go and they
never played long distance no they didn't play long distance we didn't ask
we didn't ask them to learn long distance that's okay I'm sure they know
it I'm sure I'm sure they've just picked it up by just hearing it on the radio on
the international radio stations all the time so that being like I can't believe
somebody's ass that's great basically get any other situation we would just be
entirely offended but it was like let's just let it go I'm sure it was just an
earnest request and not a lot of behind it not realizing what it meant and yeah
yeah that's amazing that's amazing orange flute that's it the old orange flute
oh yeah yeah this is just this is about this is the story of the Irish version
of Benedict Arnold basically betraying the Irish to the English yes so now so
now it's not a song that they play all the time is it but it but is it a
traditional Irish song and not it it recounts a terrible time for the Irish
but it is the one that I'm finding here is by the Dubliners and it was done in
19 it was released in 1965 so that would be that would seem to say it well it is a
traditional Irish song but just of a very sensitive topic yeah it'd be a
different thing we've gotten out of the knowledge that I have okay I have is
entirely based on reading these lyrics here and that's it I love that they did
a wild Rover because when I used to sing at the bar at Star Trek the experience
when I was doing I'd do a Klingon opera occasionally we would get some Irishmen
in who and we'd swap songs it was great and they did Wild Rover and I learned
Wild Rover yeah and so I knew Wild Rover and then but I knew a call for Wild
Rover it's an offensive call I don't know they were ready for it I don't know
if they've ever heard it but it's you know that I've played the Wild Rover for
many a year and I don't know this but then he goes and it's no name never
right up your ass no never her no more will I play the Wild Rover no never no
more so but that I learned that from other Irishman so it is a legit call
response move for that song but yeah that was great they played that one too
yeah yeah they were just it was great and I sent them to they got to go to
Mystere while they were here oh fantastic did they get to do a backstage tour - no
they had to get back and play the show at least they got to see it that's cool
I said I sent it to Piff Piff the next day so you'd see Piff show the next day
yeah next day Penn Sunday School live if you it's coming out this week just just
check it out Penn coming back from England fighting a nasty nasty cult yeah
tough it out for scoop fest of him telling a story about Piff Piff is there
so Piff comes out from backstage and surprises the audience very funny Jets
it's Piff the magic dragon and he's got a steel chair I got to do my if
impression spot-on yeah oh yeah yeah I could oh said and there's a really good
it was a really really fine episode of Penn Sunday School especially all things
considered Penn's health but it was it was great yeah then Piff stayed by he
broke down his appearance on foolish with Hondro that was funny that's the
funniest thing is that you know Penn want people I know if Penn was sticking
around Penn can stick around cuz he was sick you want to know if Hondro's gonna
call in the Hondro wasn't available to call in sent a small video but I was
like I was there I'll help or whatever and I just should know better by now the
Piff the magic dragon is always ten steps ahead of everyone got it has
already planned everything yeah and so I tried to you'll hear if we play that it
will play it on those feet or not I'm not sure I don't think it's maybe it's
good audio that video but I try to help early and then there's a point where I
just realized I should just shut up he's got it he's got it yeah yeah and and he
just it just did a very funny presentation of all of breaking down his
this is disastrous appearance it was a disaster it was it was funny to watch
live yeah I mean it really is it's up there with your cutting the tip of your
finger off at that performance that you did I mean it's the same kind of thing
yeah yeah and Piff had a perfect sense of humor about it it was great oh sure
yes and Hondro will probably develop a sense of humor about it one day well I
mean he was good enough to leave a message that was nice yes their trivia
battle with great night our epic battle continues yes you're now to what to know
in our last battles against great that it's pretty impressive if you don't
have the other battles that we've had against great night we are two and oh
against great night I'm telling you ever since Ryre made that badass fucking belt
that's ours baby that championship now we've got something to fight for yep
yep and we and might I say I'm pretty sure I put us over the line with
blueberry hill that's right you say yes you sang us into victory last year was
because the movie was one that I had actually seen before the terrible movie
was one that I had actually seen before this year Paul Golden pipes Mattingly
blueberry hill there it is and the ice cream social live you'll hear it that's
the episode that just went up and so that's there and so we go to the jock
versus nerd ball for baby probably the one of the best years ever it was a
solid jock versus nerd year the foolers were there unbelievable including math
the mind noodler it Michael else Roth dressing up like Jessica Jane Peterson
from head to toe from the foolers tour was really something else
only weirdly accurate outfit we're the accurate great well for a minute I
thought she was here I thought that was her I was JJ got tall what the hell yeah
it was pretty great yeah turn to Michael's thing I got a set of photo to
JJ and he even going I hope she's not offended by anything I've done here and
I said are you kidding me she is what Jessica Jane I found these shoes on the
strip Peterson offended by yeah I mean if you put on Vegas stray shoes get the
fuck out nothing nothing can faze you you're beyond the human capacity for
phasor at that point I can't fathom that process I'm still thinking about that
from last go fast clearly I am she's not you she's not of this earth I don't know
why you're yelling at me about it Paul I just said Jessica Jane got something
else going on he does he does he's just a little wood nymph it's amazing yeah so
funny see and then I said to the whole foolers thread so Christine dressed up
as Alex as Vinnie Grasso with a bald cap on great healthy people of cards left
and right yeah it's really funny yeah really got good at that Amy was just as
me as hillbill which is very good Amy did a card trick for me at one point as
hillbill it was Amy had me pick the card and then she flipped me off and said fuck
you I'm from Jersey
the Alex remote would just Alex it with abs just an ab shirt and a stuffed dog
and just Alex wrote me saying thank you for the ABS thanks for giving me abs and
just know everyone can I get over Michael as well as Jessica Jane Peterson
well and then the top it all off we had Penn and Teller for fuck's sake yes to
introduce the whole thing yes Rock and Carl being Penn and Teller those are
those are I want to ask about those suits they were legit suits they were
nice suits were bespoke yeah those are I think they just went and had suits made
for themselves no joke like to me bespoke yeah Oh Kurt says Amazon
specials well there you go oh man really good Carl and Brock crushed
that look that was awesome and and of course the the winner of the costume
contest the tickle house tickle house damn let's all go to the tickle house
such a cut that's the tickle house repair gardeners Chris angel was yes
also excellent multiple pig assists with someone dressed as a ghost buster just
became an awesome awesome constant of their own who that go really great who
that go that go oh yeah oh man I came in with a who that goat was amazing it was
like a really right now I think yeah professionally applied thing now Colton
nailed that look and and that's the other thing too just the it's so fun at
scoop fit I mean first of all the costume contest always blows my mind
because we see bits we see bits from the entirety of the run old stuff new stuff
it's just why bits that remind us of the bits exactly the the horse they can see
nine times oh yeah the the girl who wanted you to watch the balloon Jesus
Christ Nick my balloon girl was there damn that was so funny that was great
bananas burlesque bananas yeah Mario and ready yeti throwing confetti spaghetti
and and ready and yeti spaghetti confetti it hit it was so good it's just
all good man everything everything was great it is so fun so fun and and and
just seeing also just during the during the week all the t-shirts and stickers
and hats and different merch that we've made it's been a we've been doing this
for a minute now right like we got yeah stuff there's there's there's these
really nice social baseball jerseys and I was like whoa oh those were great yeah
those were so great right oh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh verminous coot had that
right was it verminous coot with the patch which patch the patch on the on
the sleeve of that one of those it was just a really great patch of the three
of us yeah yeah yeah it's fucking great man those those jerseys were all great
yeah yeah oh there was informative lemmy informative had all the all the facts
written on yeah that was great that informative lemmy was really good too
yeah oh man yeah so good it was facts from like some of the facts were like
from the scoop fest is so funny right yeah so many so many anyways yeah so it
was just a beautiful beautiful event crazy great did everyone come out yeah we
can't do this without our community it's just incredible and fingers crossed for
where the documentary goes thank you all for participating in that oh thank you
our safety cones we could not do it without our safety no jeez that's the
whole thing man oh yeah my lobster club barista guy was there oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah so fun so fun we look as true country scoop we learned that Krypton is
the eighth most common gas in the atmosphere and that was one of
informative Lemmy's cards mm-hmm amazing yeah and by learned that I mean
Mikey told us that and we all took it as truth and none of us have done any
further research I believe Mikey 100% Oh me too clearly Mikey yeah yeah I'm fine
with this I'm just narrating but it was great and then had a wonderful time over
at McMullin's McMullin's actually worked out this time this was a good
good yeah I think did you guys like a revamp or whatever like their staff was
on points did you see that does the staff had a scoop hat on they somebody got
what got one of the waiters a scoop hat or they got I don't know how they got it
but they had a scoop hat on yeah while they were serving on on Friday night I
was a country scoop in the chat gave him gave that to other bartender oh yeah he
was oh man and he wore that for for at least the rest of scoop fest he was well
done countries days that was really really kind of you it was incredible and
and and like always the scoops treat everybody really great tip-heavy bought
me food bought me drinks it was great up just so oh and if anybody wondered if
the Irish trio pint of plain went to McMullin's and tried Irish nachos yes
yes and they loved them oh my god yeah I said I said I was afraid to even show
you this whether you think it was like offensive to you or whatever and they go
well there's nothing like that in Ireland but boy this should be this is
really good they're really blown away particularly by the nacho beef the beef
that goes on the Irish nachos right and it sounded like an Irish stew beef the
corned beef with the nacho beef yeah no wasn't corned beef it just the regular
regular ground beef okay they're spiced ground beef yeah oh but the way they
make it at the at the McMullin's they're like this tastes like Irish like stew
beef this doesn't taste like nacho beef and they were like flipping out about it
that's cool devoured two plates of Irish nachos blown away yes victory it was
super that was it was my favorite but I sent them a picture with them in front of
the plate I said my four favorite Irishmen it was the three of them in a
plate of Irish my favorite Irishmen and my three friends from Ireland the
country's time again it's the same beef they use in their shepherd's pie there
yes and this is why it's like it's like it's actually why I like I like that we
do every year and a half for a variety of reasons one is right now to give us
breathing room to not think about the next one oh to like that extra six
months ago our lives change enough that different people come into our lives to
bring to scoop fest yes you know we get to include different people in it and so
that's like really always kind of exciting to do and and and also we lose
track of how many we've done so it makes them all very special because I'm like I
don't know how many like how many businesses I'm like I have no idea I
don't know and how awesome I think it was was it you Matt or Jacob one of you
two what me came up with the thought of selling 2027 scoop fest
I don't think that should be said on air but yeah I hear your buddy and I
appreciate it okay they're not for sale right now so no no no no no I'm not
saying that I'm gonna be an edit yeah yeah but yeah yeah it's all good yeah
that's fine all right well we'll say it out loud now people at scoop fest were
able to buy super early bird tickets for the next event yeah yeah yeah but that
just I was one to say with that was that it just to me speaks so highly of people
trusting us and then being enthused about this event yeah that's not even
announced yet well the people basically okay the people that come year after year
after year and I really wanted to reward them yes we're doing that yeah and so we
wanted we wanted to give people a special discounted early bird even though
we haven't figured out where it's gonna be there's no the time frame of where
it's gonna be we know it's gonna be a year from late April early May inside
the actual specific dates yeah we've got a window yeah and and so basically if
you were willing to roll with the punches we want to reward people who
come year after year and so we give you a special a special ticket so they're
there each everyone else and we'll get everybody else we'll get early bird
tickets out and at some point in the in the future as well once yeah once we
figure more of our ducks out exactly yes yeah yeah we usually announce it about a
year out yeah yeah I'm trying to put anybody on blast but do you understand
it to the listener this could not be the best news do you understand why I was
trying to not do it no okay is not everyone had the opportunities to do it
well people who are listening to the show weren't all at the show right all
right no it's great but and we will we did we did discount for the people there
we'll do a different early bird discount for everyone when we get the the tickets
up to yes yeah we're gonna take care of everybody as much as it could be a bit
of a sticking point for some of our international scoops as I'm seeing Bozzi
right now but that's not our doing per se yeah yeah yeah well I mean we did vote
for him twice some people three times good Lord but yeah yeah it's gonna be
great we're looking forward to the next one do we have any kind of trivia or
something lined up now we have we have talked everybody's ears off at this
point I think it's time we give them a break we've done a full show here we've
done we've done all this talk and everything do we want to do do you want
to do a quick scooperty you want to race through one sure yeah yeah let's race
through one here's a little jock vs nerd break something fresh off for the
listener we got scooperty from silver fist scoop categories
are one hit artist one hit albums one hit songs and one hit music videos Paul
you're up first I'll try one hit music videos for 400 artist the Buggles video
song what is it fish no wait is it fish heads was that the Buggles no that is
that the Buggles shit that's the entire question I know
I'll go with fish heads all right now the radio star I wasn't fish heads it
wasn't I knew I was wrong but I'm still got it wrong what an asshole that's me
I'll try I don't know one hit songs 400 artist Michael Sembello album bossa Nova
hotel song I don't know Matt poop Street Blues it rolls downhill
oh I will pass let's see here Oh maniac from Flashdance that is a good one Matt
one hit songs for 800 artists Stacey Q album better than heaven what's that
song pass Paul
I believe that's I don't want to fall in love all right let's try it now fuck it
was that one oh I don't want to fall in love from Stacey Q no it's not Stacey Q
had some other person Paul you're up geez I gotta try and redeem myself I'll
try one hit music videos for 2,000 all right points back on the board from
musical youth what is their song video musical youth Oh pasta dutchie
redeemed redeemed that is correct Paul has taken the lead yeah what a turn around I'll try one hit
albums for 400 it's a daily double still just for 400 the waitresses song I know
what boys like and what is the album also have to tell you the name of the
album the terrible category oh and it's a daily double I can't even fucking pass
it that album was called tips are for losers wasn't tomorrow wonderful I was
so glad I was just confused what a cute thought I was a waitress
Matt you're up just to get it away off the board cuz no one's gonna know any of these a lot of
miles song black velvet what was that album called Matt our Paul I think it's
black velvet but I'm gonna pass I'll guess black velvet oh no just self-titled
six of us eponymous Paul you're up I'll do music videos for 1200 let's see here
a flock of seagulls what is the song and it must be the full song title I ran I
ran so far away I ran so far away yeah sorry you did two irans Paul one Iran is
enough I can never have enough Iran's oh no no there goes our podcast I'll try
one hit artist for 400 album somebody's watching me song somebody's watching me
artist who the fuck did that song he he worked with Michael Jackson on that track
yeah that sounds familiar yep that's Michael pass doing the thing
yes oh it's like Mac Dylan or some shit make me make clump McClumpy I can't
remember it exactly so I have to pass all right Rockwell Rockwell your or or
McClumpy as I call it yeah all McClumpy Matt let's get let's keep I says I know
none of these I'll go with albums just to get it out of the way great the
Vapors song sorry the Vapors is the artist turning Japanese is the song what
is the album pass Paul oh it's a filthy title but I can't remember it off pass
I was like cunt wallet or something like that something like that yeah new clear
days clear days oh my god Paul music video get that image out of my head the
video is Mickey the song are the the video song is Mickey the artist is Tony
Basil Tony Basil I finally knew one and I didn't get it I did you know she
choreographed once upon a time in a Hollywood for QT she did yeah they're
amazing that she's still fucking kicking ass all these years later still working
yeah that's me it's me I'll try doesn't matter one hit albums 2000 Jermaine
Stewart to the song we don't have to take our clothes off and that's off of
the album brother Matt who knows this somebody it is tall I'll pass I don't
know frantic romantic oh wow someone knows it Matt you're up you got one hit
artists or what hit songs when they hit artists 800 please the an emotion song
is the I'm sorry the an emotion is the album the song is obsession and the
artist is who may not know that's a different man pass Paul my obsession who
do you want me to be to make you sleep with me I have to pass me to oh it's an
emotion there you go that's the name of your Paul like what he does originally
Hulk Hogan's walkout music right it was it's for 1200 please who do you want me
to be brother to make you sleep with me brother no there's a Saturday night
whatever the same age as I was like there's a part where W just used music
recklessly and yes that's right and that was the original Saturday night but
you're right the Saturday nights made event that was there I got it oh yeah
that was the artist is Paul Hardcastle the album is Paul Hardcastle what's the
name of that song I have no idea how to pass camera what he did Paul's hard
castle boy I just add an apostrophe s bye oh that passes to me I don't fucking
don't pass I'm a pass passes to me oh my god that's that sad Vietnam song well
there's a cup there's a couple fun ones because I'm surfing in Vietnam everybody
surfing surfing surfing for Vietnam I'll tell you Charlie don't surf but that's a
lie Charlie will serve come give it a try artist swing out sister album it's
better to travel and the song was Reno when Bruce Springsteen did it later it
was actually a cover of the original swing out sister song ain't the best
we've ever had that's right not even oh no it's breakout I was confused I was
confused for this one is breakout I was confused in that and Reno I don't
remember breakout when you ask for a quick scooper D I guess you got your
wish and that we don't know any of these that's it move them let it move the
line yeah let's see Matt do a quick score check before these last two
questions Paul is currently in the lead with 2,800 Matt is in second place with
zero and because of two daily doubles I'm in third place you know that to to
two scoops at least two scoops reported the same tactic for mouth finger butthole
where they threw mouth every time and that's what got them further along yeah
and the thing they threw mouth every time mouth does the trick yeah and I
bring that up because I passed the whole time I'm coasting in a second place no
problem yes oh my god - guys got both daily doubles I got stuff we need a new
shirt design for mouth finger butthole mouth finger butthole on the front and
on the back I'm throwing mouth that and I want to know it's like I'm serving
cunt but it's I'm throwing I'm throwing mouth I like it yeah Oh Brogan's doing
it yeah Brogan Brogan take the wheel thank you bro Matt you want one hit
artists for 1,200 or 2,000 you're gonna know one of these I'll go I'll go I'll
go 2,000 just cuz it's more fun to pass that one let's see it album living in a
box song living in a box by the artist boxcar Willie living in a box I'm a
living in a cardboard box I'm a living in a box I'm a living in a car box it's
some dude I can't remember his name though show me some dude oh no I'm sorry
it's living in a box his name was living in a box get the fuck out of here artist
name is also living in a box that's really funny that is Paul closing out
the category and the game one hit artists for 1,200 their commissar is the
album the song is their commissar the artist what's his name Paul what were
their name
Stalingrad or some shit I think it starts let's see Stalingrad oh no I'm
sorry Paul it's after the fire sure of course after the fire of course after
the fire I had to make a guess just for sportsmanship that's right Paul still
wins 1,600 Matt congratulations you got second place with zero and to me go fuck
yourself I got negative 3,200 silver fist scoop thank you silver fist scoop if you
want to send us a scooper to yours or a price of sprite jock vs nerd or an
obelisk jock vs nerd head over to hey scoops comm you can also send us some
scoop mail from over there hey scoops comm do all the things right over there
right now I was just about to say you can go there and get your tickets for
Scoop fest that's not true anymore oh that's right that's true that's not
true right I'm gonna think Ben jeff green this podcast thanks Ben I want to
thank the following people who all these people they all saw living in a box and
concert you know before they sold out Peter Sands own Petty Officer Scoop Phil
Rendley Phil Tomlinson Phil Gaiden pick it up pick it up pick it up proper scoop
proto scoop pyro quiet quiet scoop radioactive scoop raggedy girl Ralph
Barrett Randy Randy Glenn refrigerator Perry scoop remember the ala mode
Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church of the Flying Spaghetti Monster Richard
Dunn Richard Dunn Richard fast knot rich graffiti Richard Hill Robert Paul's
robots ahoy and Rodimus scoop the following people even though it goes
against all warnings did in fact go in the tickle house scooped mids scoop a
luga scooper Metroid scooper Nova girl scoopie a Lauren scooper ascending scoop
JD scoop Kata scoop knack patty whack scoop lock Kisa scoop neon black scoop
Nick scoop a metrics scoop so hazard scoop Trek the experience scoopie and
the beast scooby-dooby-doo scoopie Ramone scoopie Bartfast scoopie scoopie
Jess Jess Scott a Scott Andrews Scott Ashlock Scott Ashlock again Scott
headington Scott moldering Scott show field Sean Kellner
Seanathan P see Baskin Robbins and SF the following people will all tell you to
take that orange flute and shove it right up your ass that the Roger Edge
Ron heck Rose Ryan Hayward Ryre Appledorn second mingle Saltlick scoop
Sam Reed Sonya Petrovich Sarah Boyle sex guy Jimmy D scoop scabby the rat scoop
scoop Brady scoop scoop Bucky scoop Chang the Beijing bugle scoop Dave Ill
scoop Emily scoop it real good scoop de jure scoop Jesus scoop Lindsay scoop
Lord Tristan scoop Mifa scoop nurse scoop of saltwater scoop Skywalker
scoop tea scoop a holic scoop a trooper and scoop Paul's drag race who once
again crushed it at the jock always and gorgeous Jake got there early this time
yeah it was great they were able to really take it in this time was
wonderful yeah the following people have decided to prove that they have even
more bravery and skill and have taken their CEO seer wheel onto a three foot
stage Sean shoeless Scoop skilly and scoop silver fist scoop sir scoopy mix
scooper tin three as choir six-foot scoop Scully Wally scoop Scully wall
scoop slightly slutty scoop slurpee kayak motherfucker shmitty scoop solar
powered scoop soulless scoop sound man scoop spring-loaded scoop stab and dash
scoop Stacey Coleman streets McGreece Stephanie Young Stephen Clively Stephen
Landon Stephen Biggs Stuart Wilson strange uncles podcast strap a chicken
on scoop and sugar rush socio and the following scoops are all the answers to
all of Chris angel's questions that's super geek one three five seven nine
Swedish scoop take it easy podcast scoop Tamara Hamilton technical scoop port
temporary reality Pierce turn the page that thing in the attic the bad humor
man the sensei scoop the civic crew scoop the damsels of dorkington the
devil's lettuce scoop the didgeridoo sh the famous ball the going over our
friends podcast the ice cream headache the ice cream headache the lapis
ligamor the lost ice cream truck driver oh you're lost I'm sorry get found the
nano scoop the SC double-op the salty squid the scoop lock in the spirit of
Latin Club the upside-down under scoop I just lost my place that's a shame the
man the myth the scoop Thomas Beach Thunder cougar Falcon scoop Timothy
Sutton tk421 scoop please Tom Krieger Tom Mankerdy Tom Stott Tony Cowley Tony
scuprano Travis Jaguri Travis Murray Tristan
Guevara Troy Anthony Tanzer tuba scoop Tyler Bartlett Tyler scoop McDuck Udo
Gearhards Uncle Don's wood shop Warren bro water ice scoop Wendy Cooper Wendy
Bumgardner Wes Coughlin what was like when scoop who dat scoop will beardy Dan
will Kellner William McDonald and wind Walker scoop 23 we love you all
sexually and thank you so much all right I think y'all so much if you want to be
thanked on air if you want invitations for our zoom meetings if you want a
plethora of other rewards get involved support us today with whatever way that
fits your budget at preaching fun.com
and if you're definitely going to come to scoop fest next year because this
story made you jealous head on over to Fartsinabag.biz that along with
preaching fun.com it does take you over to our patreon page where for as little
as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air we are able to
do this show entirely because of our patreon backers so if you think this
show is worth more than zero dollars please head over to preaching fun.com
Fartsinabag.biz and there's new shit coming to those real soon yes so I go
check them out all right thanks folks everybody stay safe out there we love
you and we'll see you soon
thank you again for another amazing success with scoop fest thank you Jacob
and Matt for all your hard work organizing for that event
we're preaching fun love ya and see ya bye