[Music]
I'm not anywhere until August 20th to 24th. I'll be in the Magic Castle.
Nice. And then, uh, then someone went to, like, give me a weekend at a Magic Club.
And I looked at September, October, November, December, and I was like, uh, I can come in January.
Oh, you're booked. I am booked. That's wonderful.
Yes, it is good. It is good. No complaints. No complaints.
Now, uh, you're home for a little bit then for like a week or two. Yes.
And, uh, are the boys still out of school right now? Right. As the last week, they start school August 11th.
Okay, so you're finally putting your boys in school. Yeah, the homeschooling thing turned out to be, you know, it's for some people.
Uh, but yeah, yeah, no, I get you. But it turns out if I'm on a cruise ship, you know, virtual learning from me on a cruise ship is not really the best way to.
Oh, can you imagine any of us just homeschooling in general? Just homeschooling anyone's children.
Look, we went through the pandemic. So every parent has a taste of what they'd be like as a home school teacher. Right. No matter what.
Um, and, uh, part of it was a little, I mean, as it was daunting for all of us, it was exciting at some point.
Like at one point we were like on our own for a couple of weeks while the schools figured out what they were doing.
We were like diving in at home, trying to figure out ways to like do cool stuff like anything our kids were curious about.
Turns out there's a YouTube documentary on something or the other. That's true. Whatever.
So we did for a little while have like, uh, we're going to watch an educational documentary a day. Um, we did work on their stuff.
Um, the strange thing was that in the panic of and maybe other parents relate in the panic of, uh, schools getting their shit together, originally they just put together work packets for the parents to do at home.
Right. I remember that. And then they switched to giving everyone a computer and doing virtual classrooms with the teachers and the classrooms and the virtual classrooms with a kindergartener and a first grader were useless.
Yeah.
And the work packet stuff was awesome. Like I actually liked when they were just handing us different work packets to do at home.
Yeah, you can teach from that. Sure.
It was really, it was really great. And so I basically was like, I remember like a month into like the, the, the, the virtual classrooms and watching my kids just like, like, you know, when like kids are so bored, they're like crying with boredom.
Like they're just like, yeah, being with boredom. Like I was just like, I see that happen automatically every now and then too.
No, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not immune. I was like, I wish we were just working on the packet stuff, but I guess for people who actually had to like work, work and not just cry and hope that entertainment wasn't over as a thing.
Those people were more, more grateful for the virtual classrooms.
That's probably true. Yeah. Yeah.
Are you guys up on the descendants? You guys up on all the zombies movies on all the Disney, on the Disney channel?
I am not. The descendants are doing zombies right now?
There's two franchises in the Disney world. One is called Descendants and one is called Zombies.
Zombies is like the B franchise. Descendants, like last year I went to the kids Halloween parade and I was like, why is everybody wearing dressed as, as like, as like, is everyone dressed like Deadpool?
And turns out, no, no, they're all dressed as this character Red from Descendants.
Yeah.
And here's the thing, my, my, my oldest kid didn't get in either one of them. My youngest got into the zombies thing.
But then Kimmy Gatewood, Apple sister. Yes. Got hired to direct the latest descendants movie.
Oh, wow. And then all of the Disney, right? So then all of a sudden there's these concerts with all the people from zombies and descendants doing live concerts across the nation.
And so Kimmy got everybody backstage passes. So all the Apple, all the Apple children went to the concert and then went backstage and met everyone who's in Descendants and Zombies.
And the side effect of that is that it is way into it. Now all my kids listen to in the car, like everywhere. It's like we're driving Arizona and back and driving them all to, you know, their soccer and drums and also their stuff or kids houses.
I am just listening constantly to Disney music and it is driving insane.
Who is read a descendant of because they're all descendant from like famous heroes and villains of this. Yes. And it's hysterical because in the show they'll be like, and my dad, you know, you know, Maui or whatever.
They go and everybody acts shocked when they find out a kid is related. Like basically the show is just a parallel of like like a Beverly Hills grammar school where like everybody just finds out that their parents work in show business one place or the other.
So like every single character is a child of a major Disney character and they all have a wink to what there is. And so read is the child of the queen of hearts.
Ah, so okay. A bad person.
Most of them are. It's mostly the children of villains. Yeah. But are they good children.
Yes, they go through their own adventures where they figure out whether they're going to be good or evil. So it's runaways. That's cool. Yeah, but Disney owns Marvel now. So that's totally fine.
Yeah, yeah. No, I mean, I'm fine with it. I will not have you disparage the originality of them.
Hey, rehashing all of them. I don't know if Brian has a writing credit on descendants. He may that be great. Who are the runaways children of of all kinds of Marvel villains.
Yeah. Yeah, but they're like mid tier villains that you don't necessarily know that much about.
But I like I like that your point is that it is even more unoriginal feeling that it was already feeling.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Don't worry, Matt. It's already not that good.
They're like we have two options. We can either pretend to zap them and make them go back in time to children or we can say that they're children of the property we already own.
Yes, Cupernova girl in the chat is saying I never watch runaways. I never watch runaways either. I read it. I can't speak to the quality. Oh, no, I can't speak to the quality of the show.
I'm not please up motherfuckers. Take a moment to puff on that pipe.
You intellectual. I've not heard the best things about the film adaptation.
I prefer to see it happen in the eye of my mind. No, honestly. Yeah. No, no. I mean, it's a graphic novel.
I don't have those kinds of abilities, Jacob. I can't just read books. I need picture books. Come on. Yeah, I read it.
But the thing is like it's it's Disney, right? So they have like these crazy, you know, music and, you know, everything's a musical and that kind of stuff.
And it's all really well produced music like some of them are catchy, which the snag is that it's all sung through the throats of very precocious children.
So like it's all like these really super like it could be like rap or R&B or like all these things that like a very popular music. And then it's just like tiny children singing it.
And you're like, it's weird. Yeah, it's kids bop. And it really kind of makes me I'm like, is this a good thing or a bad thing? Do you guys listen to kids bop?
Did you go through a kids bop phase when I was younger now? No, I mean, with the kid with your kids.
No, this is the part of like the things like I like I said, like my kids were born just after Frozen was popular and I was like so glad to not be listening to that on repeat.
And, you know, Moana didn't catch on as feverishly as as that. No. And then my kids got into like real music.
So they always used to switch from basically real music into like just YouTube YouTubers YouTube music where they just sing about video games. And some of that was pretty good. And some of that's just strange to me.
But they go back and forth. Is Hill still in his Gigi Allen phase? Because I know he was way into that.
Wait, who was the drummer that you had to like wear raincoats and stuff to perform with him? Because he was so disgusting.
Keith Moon, because he was always crazy with Ginger Baker. He was dangerous. Oh, no, no, I don't know. I don't know.
No, never. Anyway, anyway, whatever he did. He did all kinds of gross stuff on stage, too. You know, he'll used to in the car used to fall asleep to Iron Man. That was the way to get him to fall asleep was that he would just chill to Iron Man and the Sabbath Iron Man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So, you know, and then we went and saw MJ the musical over the summer. And so Michael Jackson music was dominating our household, which obviously gives me mixed emotions apparent. But the music is catchy. The music is well made.
And so now I'm stuck in Disney produced weird music land. Would you prefer the Disney or Michael Jackson? Well, I would have let me say I would not have liked someone getting a backstage pass for my children to meet Michael Jackson.
So let's just say let's start there. Oh, interesting. Interesting. Okay. Okay. We're different people.
All right. No, my only my only hope for the coming out of this phase that my my my oldest is still in school of rock. And so he is learning different rock songs on drums and he has a concert coming up. I'm hoping that that music will take over the car soon.
That's what I'm hoping. Probably will. There you go. Yeah, probably. What's his favorite music to play?
Do you have a favorite song to play or anything? Yeah. I mean, like he plays like like Red Hot Chili Peppers Weezer.
I'm trying to think what else they go through over there. Yeah, he plays it. He plays a bunch of different stuff. You want to destroy my sweater. No.
Weezer, man. Yeah, I would love it if your son just started singing Weezer randomly all the time around me.
That would be so confusing, but so delightful. When they first dropped, I had a class that I had to go to, but at the record store down in Louisville, they were putting on a show in Louisville.
Three dollars right when the Blue Album first hit. And I was like, oh, I really wanted to go, but I didn't really know much about him. And I had like, like I said, I had some other little responsibility. But boy, if I could go back in time, I would tell me to go see Weezer for three dollars.
Yeah. So one thing we didn't get into last episode.
And but I was debating whether to share it or not. But it was a low point for me. I was when I was hosting Magic Live. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And I basically we finished one of our shows and I said, I'm going to I have to go to the bathroom, but I'm going to go downstairs because I don't want to hear what people think of the show in the bathroom across from the venue.
No. Okay. But you're already overthinking this. And also, like, take a walk. Like, get away. Like, go. Okay. There you go. I was like, I'm going to go to the bathroom. What's the rule? What's the rule? Just get out of the magic blocks.
What? I don't know. Oh, my my rule was always next county. Next county. Yeah. You couldn't say anything about the show or about the venue or the personnel until you got to the next county over. Yeah. If you're on the road, that's a good that's good rule.
Right. There is like some there is like some universally acknowledged, like five blocks, 10 blocks, something like that. Even then, that always scares me because I because I go into a restaurant. I'll go. I'm the guy that goes into the restaurant like 20 miles away and goes like, Holy shit. That venue was terrible. And then I hear from the next table over like, oh, you were at that venue. I do the tickets for that. Exactly. Yeah. Well, I want to hear the reactions to the show and reactions to people hearing me pee as well.
So I'm fighting it. I'm fighting a UTI and I'm just it's just a lot of like, oh, did someone bring a bean filled horse cock into this bathroom? All I hear is plops and drops. Good God. You know, you should drink some cranberry juice. Yeah, man. Clear that shit up. That's disgusting. Look, everyone's leaving the chat.
That did it. That did it. Madness beans. So I I go downstairs and I finish peeing in the toilet. This is after the show is done. After this one. Yeah, so one more to go. So I'm like, oh, I'm on a break. Okay.
And a guy just goes like, oh, you should say now they can get into the magic circle. There you have a closing joke for your show. Okay, I go. I go. No, it's like I'm already so so to catch people up. I was hosting a show that the show was having any mixed reactions. Some people love that some people hated it. And I was not necessarily like a good fit, I thought for the show. And so I just felt awkward hosting it. And so right.
But it was a big magic invention. And it was a big deal to be asked. And so I am just trying to process those feelings. But I'm but I'm five of six shows and and I'm just like, I just want to part of me just wants to be over already. Right? Yeah. And so to catch people up from the last one, you said the the show was more out there than you were really expecting it to be and probably more out there than maybe anybody was really expecting it to be I spent a lot of it to be out there. But it was a, they all had kind of like a chill and cerebral vibe.
cerebral vibe to it. That's what I wasn't expecting. It was tough coming out to try
to be the funny, funny comedian. Nobody wanted a wacky host in between these bits. Right.
And that's all I'm good for guys. Yeah. And again, like I don't even want to blame circumstances.
I thought I also was doing just an okay job myself. Like just me personally, I just thought
I could have been doing a better job than I was doing. Right. And so it was a bit of
an uphill battle though from the start. Yeah. And so I literally like have no patience.
I go like, I go what? And he goes, no, you say you have a joke for the end of the show
where you say now you get in the magic circle. And I go, I don't understand that joke. That's
not a joke. I just looked at him point blank. I was like, I don't understand that joke.
Simply not a joke. And he goes, the last guy was doing a very comedic version of a cups
and balls routine. And so, uh, and he goes to get into the magic circle in England. Uh,
it's the big organization in England. Right. You have to audition with the cups and balls.
You can't get into the magic circle unless you can do cups and balls. Okay. I consider
myself, uh, somewhat in the magic world, blah, blah, blah, whatever. Yes. I've never heard
that before in my life. I fucking baseball right now. This guy's onto it. Here's how
you deliver it, man. Fine. All right. That last routine was awesome. Now you can get
into the magic circle in England because as we all know, get into the magic circle in
England, you have to present the cup and balls trick. Good night. That's a perfect topper.
It's kind of like my clothes and joke. Yeah. That was my last joke. Everyone has my closer.
So then he said, okay, I'll use that joke like that. Yeah. So I felt bad at being addicted
to this socially awkward person. It's a magic convention. I should have more empathy. Everybody
there is socially on that. You're too close to the flame right now. You don't remember
how magicians need to be ostracized, but this is just, he's got a point. This is just the
prelude. This is not the story. Well, I love it. This prelude. I do love when, uh, civilians
catch you in your blank face. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. When I'm like, Matt, we'll go into like
that, that moment where it's like, he just can't talk to you for a minute. Just give
him a minute now. And then when people go up and talk to him, it's just, it makes me
laugh every time because my comedy entertainer self is the shell I've put over this bitter
asshole who was growing up, growing up without comedy was an angry bully jerk. And so it
was only through comedy that I found a way to be palatable in this universe. And so sometimes
I go back to that kid that would just wants your lunch money if you talk to me and I have
to walk away and I have to recalibrate. Oh man. I just need a second. I need a second.
I know who I am right now and you won't like me. I'm aware. It's not that I'm unaware.
I am aware. That's why I'm taking this walk. Yeah. Yeah. But a closing joke behind them
is some guy, he's like aggressively drying his hands with paper towels and he's wearing
like a drippy t-shirt. He does not look like a magic attendee. What's that? Like he's,
he is like a skinny person and he's wearing like a large t-shirt that is like hanging off
him is like very, he's very much draped and not wearing the shirt. And he's, uh, it's,
it's, he's a Vegas local. So he looks a little, his outfit is not bespoke. No. And he says,
he says, uh, you know, as funny as most people don't even know where the suits of the carts
come from. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh my goodness sakes. You're right. That is funny. That's
it. That's it. Boy. That right there. That's a joke. Finish it out like that. That's my
joke. One last funny thing folks. A lot of people don't even know where the suits of
the cards come from. And so I ignore him. Now you can join the magic circle. You ignored
him. Good for you. And I try to walk out and he stays over my shoulder. Oh shit. He's following
you, telling you the story of the, of the suits. And he goes one more time. It's cause
most people don't know where the suits of the cards come from. Now I will tell you in
this moment, my brain is going through multiple things and I, I literally go like, Oh, I literally
go in my mind. Oh no. Is there religious connotations to the suits of the cards? Cause that's the
way this guy is aping me. I was like, this is not, he's not trying to fun fact me. No,
he's trying to set you up for a Bible. He is giving you what circa 1994 PIF, the magic
dragon routines. He's about to bust out Christian card magic. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The three silks
are the father, son, and the Holy ghost. Look at this glass of filthy water. You would never
drink this glass of filthy water, but you bring in the Holy spirit with the cross cleaned
up and notice I'm still not going to drink still not drinking it. Yeah. Yeah. It's still
horribly poisonous. It's just clear now. So again, I'm in a mood and I don't want to be.
Yeah. So I stopped dead in my tracks and turned to him and I go, go ahead, hit me. I go ahead
and he recoils an offense that I've said, go ahead. Cause I basically, I don't want
to say I'm curious as I'm not right. Yeah. It's like, you know exactly how curious you
are. You and Google could provide me the same information right now. And I want to talk
to one of you. Um, you and Google can both provide me the same information that I don't
care about. He goes, Oh, well, I didn't realize, you know, you're going to be so sour about
it. I don't know if we have to get into it or whatever. We're in the fucking bathroom
man. And I go, well then we don't. And so he huffs ahead of me and turns right out of
the bathroom. All right. Yeah. So I go left and for people who've been to scoop vest or
in the Orleans before knows that this bathroom is right outside the Keno station. When you
walk into the Orleans thing, I know what you're talking about now. So it turns out my man
is just a Keno player. So even though he went right, he just circles back and just weaves
back through the chairs towards me and is mouthing off about me out loud as he parades
through the Keno chairs. I was just going to tell this guy about the different suits
of the cards and where they come from. He doesn't want to hear about it though. I don't
know what his problem is. I was going to tell him about the hearts of the diamonds of the
spades of the clubs. And people don't know about the frogs. That was the fifth suit for
a while, but I was going to tell him all about that stuff. He didn't want to hear it though.
I guess I'm going to play Keno. Bingo. Shit. Wrong game. I'm throwing off my game now.
I mean, 90%. Yes, Jacob. Yes. Exactly what's happening. And I don't know why I stopped.
I don't know why I should just kept walking. Oh buddy. Oh, but I stopped and go like, what
is your problem, man? And he goes, my problem. What is your problem? You're the one being
a jerk. I go, Oh, cause you're being nice. Is that what it is? I'm a jerk while you're
being a very nice person. You just want to tell me your fun facts. Tell me your fun facts.
He goes, no man, I don't need to do that. Whatever man. And then he goes, he goes, no,
you can go off. You go off. Do your thing, man. And he goes, uh, I'll see you at the
throne. Ah, it was religious. And so I go, wow. I go, what? And he goes, nothing, man.
I go, no, what did you just say? What was the statement you just made? And he goes,
no, nothing. I go, no, you said something about a throne. What did you just say? And
he said, I'll see you at the throne. It means that we are done with the life that the Lord
gave us. We meet at the throne to figure out how we spent our lives. Nothing better. You
and I specifically meet at the throne. Nothing better than a heartfelt evangelical moment
from a degenerate gambling piece of shit in Las Vegas. That's what I said. I go, I go,
that's you being nice. And he goes, yeah, I go, really? And then I step right into space.
And I go, so when you and your friends part ways, you guys go see at the throne and you
high five and you walk away. Everyone just says see you at the throne when they get in
their car and drive away. Everyone just say, see you at the throne all the time. I go,
are you just being a condescending dickhead? Yeah. And they see you when you die is what
he's saying. That's what he's saying. I'll meet you when you're dead fucker. I'll see
you when you're on your way to hell. I'll see you from heaven. Yep. I'll be in the throne
sitting on daddy Jesus's fat lap. And while Leon thought that the throne was a gay bathroom
thing, Leon, uh, it would have been better. A gay bathroom thing would have been, would
have been a great surprise here. I actually, yes, correct. I would have actually been much
happier if he was like, I'll see you when you take a shit. Like that's right. I'm going
to follow you to the bathroom. Everyone's gotta go sometime and just respect it. Elvis was
the king. I saw you eating that protein bar earlier. Yeah, it's good coming in. It's rough
coming out. Oh, and I was like, there's a little voice, a voice, a same, a same voice
in my head. It was like, why are you still here? What are you writing? What are we doing?
I was like, if you get kicked out of the Orleans for arguing with a crazy from the Orleans
for this, Matt, I am going to be angry with you. One. I was like, it would be the only
thing people were talking about a magic live is that the host of the show got kicked out
for fighting a crack head religious person. And then, and then the scoop fest is at the
Orleans, so I can't get banned from the Orleans. Right. I need you to not get 86 from the Orleans.
And so I did walk away. Finally. No, dead last one. That last one in the chat says scoop
fest live from the Orleans parking lot. When they 86 you can't be in the parking lot either.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's got to be from like the Chevron. Yeah, across the street. In view
of the Orleans scoop fest. Twenty twenty five. We really have to pull our our weight with
a fucking McDermott McMillan's. Yeah. McMillan's. Oh, yeah. We'd have to be like, please, McMillan's,
please. The alcohol free Irish bar. You know who else is as successful as an alcohol free
Irish bar? That's the following sponsor. The show is brought to you by customs scrotal
implants. That's right. From Scoop of Henny or Scoop of Henley. Sorry. Scoop of Henley
in 2022. That's custom scrotal implants. Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, children of
all ages, welcome to custom scrotal implants. The only amusement park dedicated to fake
balls. That's right. Yes. Come on in. Come on in. We've got nothing but food, rides and
shows dedicated to false testicles. Yep. We have the Ball Buster, our number one roller
coaster in the nation, an 800 foot drop with no seats. So you rattle your taint right against
the floor of the car. Ow. You're going to need some of our famous fake balls after that.
We also have Jimmy Yum Yum's big old buckets of balls that serves nothing but Prairie oysters.
That's right. Go to Jimmy Yum Yum's and get yourself a big old pack of Prairie oysters
with our patented ball free sauce. That's right. It's ball free because there's no balls in
it or are there? We don't know. We don't even know what Jimmy Yum Yum's is selling, honestly.
I brought this guy in. He told me he had Prairie oysters. I took him at his word. It's on you
and Jimmy Yum Yum to sort it out. And don't miss the cavalcade of stars performing in
Testes one, two, three on our big commemorative stage in the Hall of Presidents. That's right.
We talk about all the president's testicular problems from FDR's folded boys that he couldn't
ever access because he was constantly sitting down to Abe Lincoln's ring of ding dingers
that swung like the Liberty Bell itself. All the president's testes, coming out swinging.
That's right. That's what it's called, coming out swinging. The show is called coming out
swinging. And then the finale, which everyone loves, Gravity Wins. That's the finale song,
Gravity Wins. It's nothing but saggers. But guess what, everybody? That's what this ball
park is all about. This ball park is dedicated to fake balls. So when gravity does finally
defeat your testicular sac, you can come here and get what we're really famous for, which
is ball replacement surgery. Get your fakes in there.
As someone who got ball replacement surgery, I can't tell you how fun it is, honestly.
I have my fake tiny balls and I put a bell around my scrotum. And now whenever I play
with myself, people think I'm collecting money for the Salvation Army.
And you might be. There's no way to tell.
When I got my ball replacement surgery, I had them replace it with those clicky clacky
things that are on desks in people's offices, you know, where like the one ball flies in
and it hits the other balls and then the one ball flies off the other way. That's what
I got them to replace mine with. It's great. When I walk along, I just go click clack,
click clack.
There's all kinds of wild, wacky ball replacement stuff. You can get those kinds that you put
on your truck. You can get truck nuts put on yourself. Why the fuck not? Who cares anymore?
Just go nuts.
Go nuts. It's our company's slogan.
That's our slogan. Go nuts.
Oh, man. I want to scoop baby just trying to get out of his seat. And he's got a real
gamer chair, man. He's got a real comfortable gamer chair. Oh, yeah. Oh, look, there we
go. There they are. What are you holding? Oh, proper sack. He's dangling his fake balls.
Yes. I couldn't remember. I need to. Can Jacob to the Internet, if you wouldn't mind? Could
you check out? There is a name for when dogs get neutered. They have fake balls you can
implant on your dog so they don't feel so emasculated. All right. I think are they called
like nudicles or something like that or or nexticles or fake stickles? There's some.
Is it nutrient neuter calls? That's it. Neuter calls is when they get neutered, neutered
calls. I think that's that's the new name of this podcast is neuter calls, neuter calls.
They're called these nuts. You're right. Newticles. Yeah. Newt in the U.T.I.C.L.E.S. All right.
Newticles. That was the one I was searching for. But I was like, it can't just be newticles.
But I guess it is newticles. I guess it is. All right. Yeah, that's all. What was the
story you want to get into before we got on air? Oh, well, so for those of you who may
not know, America is in steep decline and it's being helped when it's being helped along
by a bunch of Gestapo bastards called ICE. And unfortunately, you guys know how many
times I have lamented the options that we have here in beautiful Allison Park, P.A.
for eating. That's right. At least 12. Right. So one of the places that Ann and I have frequented
over the years has been a Mexican restaurant, Emiliano's. They have a couple of locations
around this area. And it is one of our favorite spots to go to. We've been like probably 40
times, I would imagine. Yeah, we go there fairly frequently as far as stuff goes. Their
owner was in Florida, I believe was Florida, was away. She was overseeing her son's graduation
and gets an emergency phone call that there's an ICE raid at the restaurant and comes back
to people missing. There are there's video of they just ransacked the restaurant like
there are ceiling tiles all fucked up. They started a small fire in the kitchen. There's
just shit all over the floors. It's it's insane. It looks like it looks like somebody came
in and robbed the place, which essentially they did. And it just feels so deeply wrong
and illegal that I'm just beside myself thinking that these are government authorized agents
acting supposedly in the name of the people of of Pennsylvania. It's just fucking sick.
And it's so frustrating that we basically just have anyone who's in this country that
wasn't you know, anyone, anyone who's in this country that wasn't born here is considered
a criminal at this point, even if they have paperwork and stuff. And even if they're trying
to get things done properly, and they're being there's a there's a naivete, I guess a ignorance
of basically like how much we rely on illegal immigrants in this country. We do. Yeah, yeah,
we have been relying on people who have snuck into this country for many, many facets of
our economy for a very long time, for generations. And, yeah, the majority of them are not criminals
besides that one aspect we just discussed of sneaking in here. And and yeah, the it's
just it's it's just not. But even that like the criminality behind that, like what we
you know, when we've discussed this before, like asylum seekers, which until the person
who runs the government didn't understand the difference between asylum and insane asylum
got into power. Because that's what he honestly thought that was his insane thing. He thought
asylum seekers were people who were from insane asylums. He doesn't understand what the term
asylum means. Anyway, that's a whole nother kettle of fish. But it's just, it's just so
fucking crazy. And illegal or not. You know, quote unquote, illegal or not. This is fish
in a barrel type shit. There is no actual seeking down these, you know, drug runners
or, you know. No, this is this is this is where this is where this is where the Democrats
have fucked it all up to. Of course, we don't want drugs or or or more drugs or or violent
criminals or any of that in our country. Oh, yeah, I don't want violent criminals in our
country. Nobody does. Nobody wants nobody wants that. But but but you want is a way
for the government to step up and figure out who is those people. And you don't do that
by ripping families apart that have been here for for for decades. No, you know, multiple
generation families attack. Yeah, if your first line of attack is the Home Depot parking
lot and Mexican restaurants, you ain't going after shit. You that's just it's just a stupid
as fucking thing. Right. And I my only hope is that we get this turned around somehow
and that there are any legitimate courts left to fix this. Well, you know, who's stepped
up to to to to to help this situation? Who is helping? We we need a hero. We do. Dean
Cain, Dean Cain. Right. Right. Superman has stepped in. The 90s Superman has announced
that he is joining ICE. Yep. As if the show Master of Illusion on the CW couldn't get
any grosser. Well, he's outdone himself for the Superman curse. Like he's clearly the
worst example of the Superman curse. Yeah. What is the Superman curse? Notoriously that
the people who have portrayed Superman have had very rough ways to go of it in their later
life. Yeah. Who was it? The first guy was fine. George Reeves. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no,
no, no, no. Happened to him. He's yeah, you're right. He was fine. That's a fellow with some
good old horse sense right there. No, they're all they all they all have tragic things.
But this is the worst. This is clearly the worst. This is fucked up. Christopher Reeves
just hoofing it through life. But it is like this is like like I don't understand like
here, like the way ice is operating to go like, oh yeah, I gotta get in on that. I gotta
be a part of that is he's following the the playbook from Oh shit. What's his name? The
action star. It's Steven Seagal. It's Steven Seagal. The next level. Yeah. Yeah. He's just
he's following because remember when Steven Seagal was like doing the the cop reality
show, he was like, I'm a sheriff and honorary sheriff from town and he was like roughing
people up on TV and everything. And they were like, shit, this is this is getting too much
bounty hunting and all that kind of shit. And then he moved to Russia. What a fucking
joke. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Jurassic scoop. He started from Superman to Homelander. There
it is. There it is. It's not a far leap. It's not a far leap if you're not careful. Homelander
is at least funny, though. Dean Cain is not fun. I haven't listened to the dollop in a
while, but the dollop they did on Steven Seagal is outrageous and amazing. It is I can't imagine
it is worth it. Just listen to if you have a podcast or a video or whatever that you're
like, I want Jacob Smith to watch this. Yeah. Just start off by telling me about Steven
Seagal. If you just start your whole thing by telling me some ridiculous thing that Steve
Steven Seagal did in like 1996, I am in for your entire show before he hit at all. Like
before he was famous at all. Yeah, he had three different wives in three different countries.
Like before. Yeah, he was already motherfuckers. Got shit going down. Yeah. That guy is just
a disgusting narcissist from the jump. And yes. Yeah. Yeah. And he does that hilarious
to me. That crazy karate bullshit stuff where he like he's he's sitting in a in a chair
and people come up to me is like, but he says he's an Aikido master. Yeah, he's but the
Dean can't think we talked about this before in the pod, which is like if you're an actor,
like the end of these actors keep making themselves prominent in these different movements and
stuff like that. And right. And it's because like all you want your dream is to be told
what to do. That's what your job is an actor. When you dream of being an actor, you're being
handed something and being like become this. And then having a director direct you to do
stuff or whatever. Yeah. And so yes, it seems like Dean Kane having, you know, hosting 13
episodes a year of Masters Illusion, not enough for him. And so he he needs something to do.
He needs to be well, I mean, it does it does speak to the travails of Hollywood right now.
It's hard to find work. So you know, it's especially hard to find work if you're Dean
Kane. Oh, for fucking sure. For fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You've burned when you've burned
every bridge you've ever encountered. Right. A lot of nobody's knocking on Dean Kane's
door a lot. There are is a great many number of actors who swing their politics the other
way because they're blaming Hollywood for their misfortune. They're saying they're they're
saying they're ostracized before they're ostracized. And they double down on politics so they can
claim that they're victims of something instead of just it's really fucking hard to maintain
a career. It's really hard to be an actor for a very long time. It's really hard to
be in more than one hit thing. It's just hard. I consider myself extremely fortunate and
basically an outlier to have made as much money professionally performing as I did for
as long as I did. Like, that's just, you know, ridiculous. And I'm grateful for that time.
Very grateful for that time. And I'm hoping maybe it swings back again one of these days
or something. But but this is such a wonderful outlet. I'm so grateful for this, having this
opportunity to. But yeah, it's it's incredibly hard. And if you can't just straight up say,
well, due to some circumstances that are in my control, and some circumstances out of
my control, I just don't have the same career that's happening. That's just by the way,
you can outrun Dean Kane. That guy is a little long in the tooth. He's older than you think.
Yeah, no. Oh, yeah. He's him. Him joining ICE is helping no one. That's not. Let's also
be clear. Well, ICE is helping no one. Well, that's that's the ultimate thing that really
just broke my heart today is that Emiliano's has set up a GoFundMe page to try and help
the families that have that are being legal defense. Yep. Legal defense and to help rebuild
their trash restaurant. Jesus Christ. Right. It's fucking insane. But they're already over
40, 40 grand in 24 hours. So and that's that's exactly the point is these people are in the
communities. They are functioning. They are loved in their communities. They make their
communities better. Yeah, it's like it's like we have to find a way to honestly assess what's
happening with these families on an individual level and how they impact their community.
And we have to find a way and a governmental level to give credit to give credit where
credit is due. The Statue of Liberty tells us who we want coming to the country. And
nobody fucking is down anymore. I bet you that preamble has been eliminated on the government
website. I bet you can't find it on the website. It very well may have been rubbed out at Ellis
Island for all I fucking know. They may have sandblasted that shit. You know, Statue of
Liberty's on Liberty Island, not Ellis Island. No, but yeah, you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
But isn't that they're all gone, Jacob. All the islands are gone. No, no, no. By the way,
that was the most ready rich I've ever felt doing a podcast. Correct. That's one quick
little thing. Isn't that isn't that saying on Ellis Island too? I have to find out I
have to find out if this comment is true or not. Jurassic Scoop says they rub one out
on Ellis Island and I got to know if that's true. Hold on. I'm checking the records. I
got got to know. Oh, that was like a bad class trip. What are we talking about? Jurassic
Scoop? Where are you? I think you're just saying that I think Jurassic Scoop just masturbated
at Ellis Island. Yeah. I think Jurassic Scoop is on a saying they were at a fair in Wisconsin
having some fried cheese. OK. Yeah, I'm just curious. I'm just curious what would motivate
someone to rub one out at Ellis Island. That's all I'm just curious. Just curious. Hot immigrants.
I mean, just a bad joke. Sexy immigrants. Yeah. I mean, inside my balls is what mass
free for that joke. That's just how it goes. You better rub one out right now. Have the
courage to man up and be the be the bit. Not on Twitch. Don't do it on Twitch. Not on Twitch.
So anyway, just if you happen to be around the Pennsylvania area and you see an Emiliano's
go and frequent them, give them some business, give them some money, give them some love.
And yeah, just yeah, fuck this shit. This is fucking gross. The poem, The New Colossus,
which is the the poem that you're referring to, Paul, that gives me you're you're tired,
you're weak, all that stuff. That is on the it is inside the pedestal of the Statue of
Liberty, right? According to the US National Park Service. OK, so that is on Liberty Island.
That's on Liberty Island, not Ellis Island. Got it. Got it. Got it. Ellis Island is where
the the immigrants would come in and do the processing and whatnot. Right. Where you change
your names. That's right. I have the the copy of my great grandfather. Yeah. My dad's grandfather.
I have the copy of the Ellis Island form that he filled out when he entered the country.
Wow. Yeah. You can apparently request these through Ellis Island. It has a picture of
the ship that he that he came in on and and the information they took down from him when
he entered at Ellis Island. And he landed on Smith for a last name, huh? That's right.
That's right. All right. Creative guy. Yeah. Yeah. I got my creativity from him. Well,
you know what? I bet back in the day, Smith was probably Smith was probably a good name
to go with because that you just like, oh, yeah, I'm a Smith. I can do anything. I can
do it. Everybody knows how to spell it. Yeah. Everybody knows how to spell it. And it just
means, you know, oh, yeah, I'll be a blacksmith. I'll be a candle, Smith. I'll be a rake, Smith.
I'll be a lawn, Smith, whatever. You need me to rub one out, rake, Smith, a rake, Smith,
rake, r a k e rake, Smith, rake, Smith. Goodness sakes. You need me to rub one out. I'm a Jack
Smith jack of all Smith jack of all Smiths. I'll jack a Smith any minute. I'll jack any
Smith that moves. You know who else is a jack of all Smiths? Oh, who? The following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Benny Ho Ho's Las Vegas new hibachi grill and brothel,
Benny Ho Ho's. And that's from Mike Nelson in 2023. What's up, motherfucker? Benny Ho
Ho. I run this place with a strong pimp hand. You hear me? This fucking garden is full of
bitches just waiting to get rowdy. But you got to bring that cash. $80 to get into the
place. Period. And then 150 per lady plus tip. Benny Ho Ho don't play. That's right.
Break yourself. And would you also like some rice wine? I got that too. Enter a scoops
of checkout. There you go. Just sounds lovely. Just a fella trying to share his rice wine.
You guys ever been to that big Benny Hanna in the Hilton? What was the Hilton? Yes. Wild,
isn't it? I have. The best story I know from there is not mine, but it is Hondros. Let's
hear it. Oh, I love please. He was visiting with a bunch of Spanish magicians back in
the day. Copperfield, of course, was hosting everyone. And it was like, oh, that's where
he's taking him. He's taking him out to that. Oh, this is way back in the day. This is back
in the day. It was the Hilton. Yeah, yeah. The Hanna has been there for a minute. So
when it was like that thing was like the flagship Benny Hanna, right? Oh yeah. And it was like,
if you have an opportunity scoops, go to the Benny Hanna at the West Gate Casino. It's
huge, like multi-story Benny Hanna. It's ridiculous. It's worth a side. It's like an ancient Japanese
village. It's insane. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's crazy. Yeah. Go check it out. It's at the
West Gate. It's beautiful. Um, yeah. So, so Copperfield, Lance Burton, you know, everybody
in town. He's playing host to everybody at the Hanna. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And, uh, Hondo
is there and, and it's not, not often been in America, uh, English, not great. Uh, and
they put down a big dollop of wasabi. Oh, Oh, and Hondo thinks it's guacamole. Great.
And he just takes whatever food he has and just dips it right into a big, big old hunk
of wasabi. And then his sinuses are still clear. Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. Oh my God.
Yeah. I watched that happen to my mother-in-law, uh, at a, at a Japanese restaurant one time,
not with wasabi though, but with ginger. Oh yeah. She just picked up the whole, I don't
know. I might've known at the time, but I don't know now. Uh, but yeah, she just picked
up the whole wad of ginger and just popped it into her mouth. And the expression on her
face was just so confused. It wasn't pain. It's just ginger. It was just pure confusion.
What have I done? Yeah. Why did I do this? A lot of ginger. Yeah. I did see a guy at
a Japanese restaurant one time, like flick a little ball of ginger. Uh, you know how,
like the, um, Oh, what do you call the, the, the chef technique? Uh, where they're like
planking everything around, they're tossing everything on the, on the big, uh, hibachi.
Yeah. So like, you know how the hibachi chefs can, uh, can, can throw the, oh yeah. Tappanyaki.
That's it. You're right, Wayne. It's not, uh, that's the grill. Yeah. Uh, but they can
like flick like shrimp and everything into your mouth and all. So ignorant guys. It was
Tappanyaki. You guys are so, such ignorant fool. Thank you, Matt. I'm so glad that we
have Matt Donnelly to keep us on the straight and narrow. That's right. He's C-wise. I'll
see you at the throne, Jacob. Thank you. It's just something that we say to each other.
It's just something we say. It's just kind words. Yeah. Just kind words. Just see you
at the throne. Hope you don't go to hell forever. I'll see you at the throne. But yeah, this,
uh, it was like, uh, uh, uh, uh, Tappanyaki chef at, uh, a place that was kind of rowdy
had like some college kids in there and they were, they were kind of rowdy and everything
and they're yelling. And, uh, this, this one kid kept, keeps on yelling about how he can
eat anything that, uh, the guy makes and, uh, catch anything and eat it and whatever.
And so the guy just balls up a little ball of wasabi, a little smaller than a golf ball
and picks it up with a set of chopsticks and just flicks it like he's flicking water off
the end of the set of chopsticks. Just flicks it straight into the guy's mouth. It was one
of the more magical things I've ever seen magic live was just in town. I always wanted
to learn to be a Tappanyaki chef. I just thought it'd be a really cool thing to just have my
back pocket as like, I want you to learn that out. Just, yeah, just, I can do the whole
bit. Slicy slice slice slice. Yeah. Once in a while I just come over and I have a big
flat grill and I just do the whole deal. I've got the big flat grill. You can come over
to my house and just do it. I got it. So yeah, there has to be a school here in Vegas for
it. I'm, I'm just going to say, if you learned how to Tappanyaki grill before the Jacob's
whiskey barbecue at scoop fast, I really think it's so intense. There's no way I could do
it in months. Maybe, maybe next year. That's like an apprenticeship kind of thing. Right.
Maybe next year. Just, just working on like twirling the, the, the, the tongs. I just
feel like it would be awful says, but no, you've been a waiter on the job training,
right? Yeah. It will be great. Yeah. You guys want to do a little scoop mail? Yes, please.
Let's do a little scoop mail message for you. We got a scoop mail from Wayne. Hey guys,
I'm writing and looking for some advice towards the end of August. I'm going back to college
to do an animation course and I have a few concerns. Concern. Number one, about a week
before starting the course, I'll be turning 40. Now is a good time to comment on how youthful
I look. Wayne, you look very, very youthful. Very, Wayne is here, right? Yeah. Wayne's
here looking youthful as ever. Yeah. Uh, so it looks very youthful. I fully expect to
be the older, if not the oldest student in the class. What are some ways to help me blend
in with the youngins? Do I just, uh, shout skibbity every now and then? Yes. Yes. That's
just what you do, Wayne. That's just, you, you already got it. You already got it figured
out. Concern number two, it's more than likely that some people there will know my comics.
It seems like every social situation I'm in nowadays, when people ask me what I do, there's
always someone who says, oh wow, you draw those comics. I know this may sound a little,
uh, like I'm up myself, but realistically when I meet someone in my home city who knows
about my comics, I'm surprised every time, even though they were on a giant screen in
the middle of Perth. Right. This is not typically a bad thing, but I feel like it could be a
disadvantage in a learning situation. Maybe more will be expected from me because of it.
I certainly don't want the entire, uh, to be the, uh, center of attention. Uh, wait,
who said that? It was Wayne. Wayne said that looking all youthful and shit. Wayne, is it
weird to hear Jacob reading your words while you sit here and listen now? Is it weird?
Is that like a weird thing? No, it's not. He, uh, he asked me if we just wanted to talk
about it or if he should read it and I said, just read it. Okay. Great. Good. Good. Good.
Good to know. I'll read the rest of it as Wayne. Man, he's talked about how to use,
it's fun to take improv classes all the time. Even as a season difference. Wow. It's like
listening to a mirror. It is. It's just like listening to a mirror. So I want to be more
like my favorite Donnelly animator, Rob Donnelly, just kidding. Love you, Matt. I love you and
Paul. I love Paul and Jacob too. Uh, that's Wayne. So Wayne's worried that he's going
to be the oldest new kid at the school. Yeah. Shaw Wayne is going back to fourth grade.
Everybody's nervous to go to their first day of anything. So like, you know, for whatever,
whatever laundry list you have of your individual, uh, things that will make you feel like you,
you will stick out or not belong or feel weird being in there. Everyone is walking in with
their own laundry list of the same exact thoughts. There are very few people who are like fucking
love school. Can't wait to go in there. And when I'm there, I can't wait to make other
people feel awkward for being in school. There's no one's agenda walking into school. So, oh,
that could be Wayne's agenda though. That could just be your agenda. I've got a bad
relationship with school. I am not good at it. I never do any of the work. Uh, I'm hoping
that it's going to be different this time though. Well, it should be a little different
because this is a subject you're very passionate about and it's not exactly, you know, you're
not going there for prerequisites or, you know, having to do a lot of stuff that you
wouldn't want to do, right? Why the, uh, why the choice to go back to school? Uh, I need
to do something. That's what my therapist tells me anyway. You have too much time on
your hands. Yeah. I honestly do. I understand that. Every time I talk about quitting, uh,
doing shows in town, SJ is like, you will have too much time. She just doesn't want
you in the house, Jacob. Absolutely. School is a form of you forcing yourself to dedicate
the time that you want to dedicate to doing this in the first place. You know, Oh, that's
true. Draw in the chat mentions that you always have an excuse to not do group projects. You
can just say that, uh, you have family shit going on and can't do the other people's schedule
stuff. That's true. You can't get out of a lot of stuff. Sick again. No, be, be more
of a dick about it. Make it about pets and not kids. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Can't my dog.
I can't, can't do it. His name's pirate dog. Oh, you know, I've got it. It's totally real.
I've got this very emotionally needy ferret that needs attention. It needs medication
on the hour every hour. My fur baby has the sniffles. Latter day scoop. I think just look
at it as more of the social engagement that you'll be gaining from it. And you know, don't
worry about, I don't know what your, what is your objective? What are you hoping to
get out of it? Well, it's, it's something that I chose because one, it was cheap, something
I could afford to. It's sort of in my wheelhouse, but not something I'm great at as for sure.
I'm looking at it because everything I know is self-taught. And I went to college previously
doing multimedia and which included animation and graphics and all of it. And it was just
not a good time. So even if I learn nothing, it's not much of an investment put into it.
All right. So at the very least I'll learn something. Hopefully. Again, I, me personally,
I would put the emphasis on the social aspect. The fact that you can meet some like-minded
folks who might be in the same industry. And, you know, I think that's the best that you
can hope for. I mean, don't, don't put this on yourself. It's like, Oh, but you might
meet someone who you can truly collaborate with. And, you know, I really, I mean, I was
fortunate enough to have Matt drop into my lap out there in Vegas, and, uh, wish Matt
would drop into my lap. Yeah, don't we all? Don't we all? But that absolutely changed
the trajectory. Preachingfun.com. Matt will drop into your lap for a price. Totally changed
my trajectory and helped me in a myriad of ways to keep me more creative and the opportunities
that have come my way because of my association with him. So, you know, I think that's key.
At least that's been my experience, is that it really, it's all about networking and getting
those, those social webs designed a little bit. Paul's bringing up something actually
pretty significant, which is that you actually might find someone in there that you want
to collaborate with. In other words, like that's, that would be interesting. All the
things that hold you back, you might find someone is like, is better at it, right? Like,
so like if you're not an organized person, you might have someone who's organized but
not funny, right? Or organized but not a good writer, right? And so like you want to figure
out like you basically want to find someone with different superpowers, right? And so
that might happen through this class. I, I think these are all good ideas. I do think
that you shouldn't ignore the idea of a bit that is presented in such classic films like
old school and the Rodney Dangerfield film, back to school. I think you should emulate
these people. I think these- I'll search out the showers. These should be your heroes.
The raging party zone. I think you should endeavor to have your classmates call you
old blue. I think you should just go with the full bit. Start a frat, start a fraternity.
Isn't that old school? Old school. Old school. That was one of the characters in old school.
That's my boy blue. Because in Australia, blue is slang for someone with ginger hair.
Oh really? Ow! Yeah, it is. Backward slam? What the fuck? It is. Like, I didn't understand
it as a kid and one time- I don't understand it as an adult. And went to the butchers.
I'm like five years old and the butcher says, "Oh, g'day blue." And I'm like, "What the
fuck?" And I'm like- Well, I was five. I wasn't thinking what the fuck. I was thinking, "Why?
This guy is being mean to me." The fuck did you just say to me, motherfucker? Yeah. So
as we're leaving, I'm like, "See your sausage face?" And my mom's like, "How dare you?"
I'm like, "I'm just giving it back to this guy." He gave me the business? I'm giving
him the business. It's up there with, "Hey buddy, nice hat." Yeah, it is. See your sausage
face. See your sausage face. I see a joke about two kids hanging out with the wrong
kind of kids and they've been learning how to curse words and stuff like that and they
just think it's exciting and wake up in the morning and mom goes, "What do you guys want
for breakfast?" And the kid goes, "I'll take some fucking eggs." And mom just backhands
him across the room, be like, "You don't speak like that in my household. And what about
you, little Jimmy? What do you want?" And he goes, "Well, I sure as fuck don't want
some fucking eggs." Yeah, so I think that's what you need to aim for. Okay. Backhand
the kids. Yeah, yeah. Is blue a derogatory term for gingers in Australia? No, no. Sausage
faces though, yeah? Derogatory is, for me to say, a term for gingers in Australia is
"ranger." Ranger? Spell that. Ranger, yeah. I'm assuming it's got to do with orangutans
or something. Oh, because they have orange hair. I haven't searched the etymology of
the word. That sounds right. Yet. No, you just hear that when you run, right? Get out
of there. Right, yeah, yeah. He just hears that word and wants a banana. Well, thank
you. Well, thank you, Wayne. Good luck in school. Keep us updated. Thank you for the
advice. Yeah, yeah. Good luck, buddy. Former frat, an awesome party frat, headed by just
the oldest people on campus. I should make it clear that this is a one night a week,
three hours a week course as well. Well, then it's going to be easier to have the frat house.
They'll never expect, that's at least what the group at least expects, zeta zeta zeta
to form. Thanks, Wayne. Thanks, guys. Let's see, we had Captain James T. Scoop in the
back. Wait, you had a you had a story to tell us. Yeah, yeah, go for it. Yeah. Yeah. Where
are you Captain James T. Scoop? Let me find you here. There you are. All right. So you
said you had a story to tell us about the you had two stories to tell us. Which one's
better? Well, actually, well, they're the same story. I just didn't know it. Even better.
She got you, Jacob. She puts two stories in the same one. Yeah, I will say that. Okay.
So thank you for answering my last email that was about my grandfather passing. I started
that advice. That was really cool. So I mean, he'd already been dead for two weeks. So it
wasn't like super helpful. That's our brand. We don't want to be too helpful. Two weeks.
That's pretty good turnaround for a Scoop Mail. That's better for us. That's incredibly fast.
Actually, you're welcome. Yeah, yeah, never. Never. But at the end of that, I mentioned
something about a return missionary dating application. Yes. And Matt, like kind of grossed
out by it, right? Like, oh, that's weird. I think this is like, actually an application
for will you date me when I get back from my mission? Well, Matt was absolutely correct.
I said and thought about it. And I was like, well, that is like fucking creepy. Like, that's
not funny. That's weird. That's what I'm here for. It just got me thinking. Matt Donnelly,
not funny, but weird. That's right. Now you can join the magic circle. It just got me
thinking about these things that you do growing up, probably in any religion, but growing
up Mormon, that don't seem weird, that are weird to outsiders. Yeah. So I've got a story
for you. July 24 is a state holiday in Utah. It's called the day and it's the day that
we all celebrate, you know, bring me on and the early church saints, as we call them arriving
in Utah, right? So something else that we do for the youth in the church, when I say
youth, this is between ages 14 and 18. You do something called track. You do it during
the summer. Paul, stop what you think. It'd be a lot cooler if it was though. So I had
my track experience. I would, we were, I grew up a military brat. We were living in Virginia
in the time y'all are from the East coast. You know how crazy humid it gets in the summer.
It's like disgustingly hot. So the summer before my senior year of high school, I went
to go with my youth group from church. We went up to the Marriott ranch in July, you
know, to celebrate pioneer day. Even though we weren't living in Utah, we all had to dress
up in pioneer clothes. Oh, that's great. I'm already happy with this. Slow or slower. Were
there buckles on your shoes? Tell me there were buckles on your shoes. My regular, I
think I had regular shoes on. I don't remember that. So this was like a three day trip. We
were not allowed to bring anything that the pioneers would not have had. So that's not
just like phones and you know, MP3 players or whatever at the time. I mean, that's like
toothpaste. Yeah, that's a lot. Oh, come on. Disgusting. Yeah. No, yeah, I'm serious. It's
so a bunch of 14 to 18 year old teenagers in pioneer clothes, pushing hand carts on the
Marriott ranch for three days with no deodorant or toothbrushes. These guys are going through
hormonal changes and puberty and everything else and they already feel horrible about
themselves. How can we make them feel even less attractive to each other? We must. Did
you see Latter Day Scoop posted an image in the chat there? Does that match your experience,
James T. Scoop? They're pulling some kind of wagon and mug. Oh, it's people like strapped
up to a wagon and pulling it themselves instead of horses. Yeah. Also, I've got, I've got
bad news. That's pretty much what they were doing, huh? I've got bad news for you, James
Scoop. So Brigham Young arrived in Salt Lake City or the Salt Lake Valley in 1847. Toothpaste
was invented in 1824. They already had toothpaste by then. They were just fucking with you and
didn't want you to brush your teeth. They were lying to you the whole time. Couldn't
you technically bring golden glasses and a couple of tablets and be like, "Hey, I just
read on here that every modern thing is cool. It's all good. We can just bring whatever
the fuck we want." I should have, right? I should have. No, I've got some invisible tablets
here that say tooth brushing is fine. Become a new prophet. Yeah. Kudos to the rich. I
mean, I'm a woman, though, so they wouldn't have listened to me. Yeah. Kudos to the rich
kid that was like, "I'm bringing a horse. We're bringing a goddamn horse. We're taking
care of the horse the whole time." So is there a start point and destination? What exactly
is the- Yes. Yeah. So there's the place that you start and a place where you end. And so
we get there, they go through our bags, make sure we don't have anything we're not supposed
to have. No toothpaste. My toothpaste. We're dividing two samples. You can keep the whiskey.
The whiskey existed then. Go ahead. Here you go. Right? Yeah. They divide us into families
and we're all paired with a married couple that we have to call ma and pa. Gross. Boo.
Is there a way for Matt, Paul and I to become one of the people that they call Paul? Yeah.
Can I apply to be a camp counselor at this thing? No. I would bring my own fishbone record
with that "Hey ma and pa" song. Hey ma and pa, what the hell is wrong with y'all? I promise
I'll show up with the dirtiest mouth and the stinkiest armpits to apply. Oh, God damn it.
Does that help? God. Yeah, totally. That'll get you in for sure. Well, you want a side
tangent, but for girls camp, the LDS girls camp, they always want priesthood holder volunteers.
You don't have to have a girl going to the camp to volunteer. So just throwing that out
there. Super creepy. Of course not. Oh, what is creepy about that? Why doesn't anyone care
about young women? But he's got priesthood, so we're good. I like that Chuck E. Cheese
literally has better security. Chuck E. Cheese literally has better more guidelines about
who can touch the children and their establishment. I could be way off base here guys, but I feel
like there could be a correlation between these organized religious practices and the
fuckery that's going on at the top levels of our government right now. I might be missing
a beat here somewhere, but I think- No, no. Our president has very shiny teeth. He's got
some toothpaste. Those are his real teeth. Fuck off. And do I think he brushes them himself?
No. Oh, no way. No way. No way. Certainly not the bottom row. I think he just brushes
the top teeth and just ignores everything else. That's weirdly horrible. Okay. If I
found out that was true, I feel like that would be the thing that I thought was the
worst thing about Donald Trump. I got news for you. Okay. I'll try to speed this up.
I'll just mention a few of the most egregious things that happened. Please. All right. Okay.
So for the three days. So we start on this handcart trip. For lunch that day, we got
a cutie, one of those little cutie oranges. And that was it. Jesus. I was so hungry. I
ate the peel. Oh God. I was so hungry. And then for dinner, we got a little 10 cup of
broth and a roll. And then to sleep in, we got a tarp for the whole family. And we could
choose to either sleep on top of the tarp or underneath it. If it was going to rain.
Those are our options. And this was your real family or these were the people that you were
just instructed to call mom, ma and pa. Oh, I was called the big sister. I got nominated
to be the big sister and there was a big brother. So you are getting under a tarp with a fake
mom and dad and family after having a cup full of broth. And a cutie. And a cutie, Matt.
I have to tell you, I think the pioneers were better at it than this. I just want to say
it like I don't think. This sounds like someone who didn't understand history. I don't know
that they were that much better at it. How was this broth contained? Was this in a sealed
like canister? Was it like a soup canister? How was the broth contained? Oh, well, no,
they made it over the fire. Like they heated it up in like a pot and then laid it in the
pots. Okay. All right. So we had to walk along with our little cup and then we got a ladle
of broth. What was it made of? It was just like chicken broth. It was probably just bouillon
cubes to tell you the truth. Right, right. Just salty flavored chicken water. Yeah, yeah,
exactly. Good news though, the orange peel actually has more vitamin C and fiber than
the inner fruit. So you did yourself a favor by eating the cutie peel. Well done. You won.
You won the game. You won the survival game. Yeah, yeah. I knew that all along. I was just
testing you guys. Yeah. That's the kind of instincts we need a big sister to have. Yeah,
exactly. You know, I'm bringing, I am in real life a big sister. So I'm just bringing that
experience everywhere I go, you know, bringing that knowledge. Yeah. But a couple other things.
So one time it was supposed to be a lesson on faith. We had to be blindfolded and they
would tell us where to go with the cart and guide us, you know, with their voices, but
the worst one, and I even at the time, like, and I was, you know, I mean, I'm 17, fully
in it, fully believing, but even at the time I was so upset at this, they have something
called the woman's pool and stretch of time, you know, but there was a time. It's a wagon
washing fundraiser. That would have been a lot better. It would have been a lot more
fun. I'll tell you that. But it was supposed to commemorate this time that we're like the
men went away to do something and the women spent some time with the hand carts on their
own. And so we were supposed to like, it was like, in their honor kind of a thing, right?
So the boys were not permitted to help. They had to stand on the edges. They waited till
we got to the steepest, hardest part of the trail. Well, there wasn't even a trail but
of our area. And that the boys were allowed to do was like fan us with like their hats
and stuff. But then us girls, the, you know, women and the women's pool, we had to push
the cards of this huge hill all by ourselves while singing hymns. He had like a testimony
of how amazing and wonderful it was to watch you struggle. It was just so difficult. And
I can't imagine how those husbands must have felt leaving their wives. I just wanted to
help you guys. And I'm like, you little bitches. No, you didn't. You're just glad you didn't
have to do the hardest part. Did these little Mormon boys think that the Mormon pioneers
had just watched and fanned their wives with hats while their wives did all the work? I
don't know, man. I don't know. But they just kept going off about how like it was so hard
for them to watch us struggle so much. And I'm like, I'm sure it was. No, they're the
victims of this. Do you understand? It's good to be a lily white Mormon boy. Is there any
way that they could have stepped in? Like, was that a possibility that they could step
in and just help that or they were forbidden? No, they weren't allowed to. They weren't.
They weren't allowed to. What do you think would happen if somebody did? Oh, you know,
I mean, it'd be at least as bad as drinking coffee. Oh, you think that bad. I think that
bad. Yeah. Holy shit. I mean, I think somebody would have intervened and told them to stop
and if they hadn't outraged, I would have stepped out. It's been like, let's help push
this wagon. Also, I would have never done that stupid shit. Maybe. I don't know. I got
roped into some dumb shit when I was young, young. But I think I started a podcast. It
took me to like 20 to really free myself from this shit. And even then I was still kind
of fucked with it. Yeah. It's hard. I mean, yeah, I started questioning, you know, mid
20s, but then just that fear of like, right. I don't want to go to hell. Yeah. Okay. We
got to kill a chicken and learn square dancing and then I got my period at the end of it.
So, you know, yes. See pushing that card uphill. There's a plan for everything. There's a plan
for everything. Thank you, Captain James D Scoop. Amazing. Thank you for sharing. The big brother
had to kill the chicken. I was allowed to de-feather it, but I could not be had it because
that was a boy's job. But anyway, that's awesome. Yeah. All right, Captain James D Scoop. We'll
see you at the throne. See you at the throne. Thanks for letting me share guys. Oh yeah.
Also you, you look good as a Ranga. Now we've got you a more Australian slang. Perfect.
I'll say it. I think the Mormons got a couple of things wrong. I don't, I know, I don't
want to, I don't want to ruffle too many. I don't want to ruffle too many recently plucked
chicken feathers, but I think they got a few things wrong. Well, we'll see you at the throne.
I'm chicken feathers. Uh, guys. Okay. Uh, so I want to scoop baby. I want to scoop baby.
Just put in the, just put in the chat. Is that going to be a thing? The throne thing?
And I was just thinking like we've got, I need help salt pork as our, as our greetings.
Yeah. How about as our farewell, see you at the cone. That's our new, that's our new check
you later. Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Approve. We're going to workshop that. Approve. I think it's,
I think it's good. I think it's good. Turn the page likes it. Turn the pages in. So,
all right. Yeah. Well, let's just hear from the, uh, yeah. All right. Love it. We'll see
how it catches on. See you at the cone. I like it. See you. To every Orleans employee
you encounter at scoop fest, please end every conversation with. I'll see you at the cone.
I think people are down. I think people are down. All right. Thank you for this drink.
See you at the cone. All right. I'm running Joe. You could use it. You got to just come
out to a scoop event. Come on out, man. And hopefully there'll be some more scoop events
around the country next year. That, that'd be a great goal. I'm running into a time conflict
here. So let's, let's, let's, let's, uh, let's go. We got a scooper today from diamond scoop.
The categories are Oakland, Los Angeles, Las Vegas, and Raiders. Paul, you're up first.
What do you want? I will go ahead and try Las Vegas for 200 Las Vegas for 200. Everything
you think of when you think of Las Vegas, including the strip and the home stadium of
the Las Vegas Raiders is not actually in the city of Las Vegas. What is the name of the
unincorporated town? These attractions reside in. It is known as paradise. Nevada paradise.
Nevada is correct. Yeah. Me. I'll try a Raiders for 200 every year. There are stupid rumors
that the Raiders will trade QB Derrick car. Oh, this is an older scooperty from before
the Q the Raiders traded Derek. Derek is already played for the saints and retired. Maybe they'll
stop now that the Raiders traded for this player who is an all pro, a pro bowler and
cars former teammate at Fresno state. That was shit. Uh, Adams, uh, Devante Adams. Come
on. There it is. Devante Adams. Nice. Man, you're up. I got to test my vintage Raiders
knowledge here. Raiders for 400. We could use more scooperties head over to HeyScoops.com.
Just a reminder. The Raiders are one of the more mobile teams having played home games
in LA, Oakland, Las Vegas, and even San Francisco for their opening season while Oakland Coliseum
was being built. What year did the Raiders move to LA within five 1985 1985. That's right.
It's right in that neighborhood. 82 for sure. You got it. Safe. Well done. Uh, Paul Vegas
please Vegas during the last weekend of April, 2022 Las Vegas will hold this event with people
coming from all over the world to attend the festivities. Oh my God. Was this scoop fest?
It might've been. I'm going to go scoop fest. Let's try scoop fest. It was scoop fest. The
NFL draft does not count. Oh, that was the year that we had scoop fest during the NFL
draft. That's right. It's me. I'll try Oakland for 200. This former Oakland resident is known
for his comedy and political podcasts and his very sexy salt and pepper hair and beard.
He currently resides in Austin, Texas. Uh, I believe that would be the one and only Justin
Robert Young. Yeah. Jury if you're nasty. Jury if you're nasty. Matt. Um, Raiders 600. Daily
double. All of it, Jacob. I want it all. Raiders legendary owner, Al Davis is known for his
catchphrase. Just win baby. And suing the NFL so he could move to LA. Al got his start
with the Raiders in 1963 in this position. A doggy doggy position. Uh, yes, that's right.
Oh, it's a double daily double. So I have to come up with something. Well, she's a water
boy. Was she the guy that brought the waters? What's it called when you, uh, when you collect
the uniforms and stuff, uh, in Jersey, like the equipment manager, equipment manager.
That's my, that's my equipment manager is my guess. Oh, head coach. He went right to
head coach. Excuse me. Excuse me. The equipment manager for the entire team. Equipment personnel.
All of it. Yeah. Paul Las Vegas, please. The other daily double. Not diggity damn. Look
at you fellas. Vegas is becoming quite the sports town. It sure is. With the golden
Knights making the Stanley cup finals in their first year and the Raiders making the playoffs
in their second season in town. What other major team is rumored to be moving to Las
Vegas? The A's. Let's see. It is the Oakland A's. Maybe they're still rumored. I'm actually,
I'm actually draining my pool right now because we're going to build a stadium right, right
by backyard. Can you believe all that dirt moving around bullshit they're doing for nothing?
Yes. Yes, I can. They can afford it. Yeah, they can. I'm Las Vegas for 800. No, they
can't. In the year 2281 of the fallout universe, after the great war wiped out most of humanity,
Hoover Dam is the site of much turmoil. As depicted in Fallout New Vegas, two factions
fight in the second battle of Hoover Dam. Name one of the factions. Damn. Damn. Damn.
Damn, son. I don't have a single idea. I have to pass the mat. Oh, well as a fallout
player, I pass. Yeah. You don't want to reveal the secrets. Yeah. Paul. Vault Tech would
be my guess, but I don't have a guess because I don't know. I'll pass. All right. NCR, that's
the New California Republic and/or Caesar's Legion or just the Legion. Hey, Leann Casab.
Don't type the answers into the chat during the scooper, you jerk. Oh no. No, Leon's just,
he's too used to us playing our night games. He's playing with me. Thank you. Thank you,
Leon. I can't see the chat. I'm sharing the screen, so I'm not getting the answers. All
right, Matt, you're up. Los Angeles, 200. All right. LA is the home to a ridiculous number
of sports teams, including the surrounding suburbs. How many professional teams from
the big four leagues currently call LA home plus or minus one? Let's see. We got the Kings
in Hockey, Lakers, Clippers, and then we got the Chargers. There's a WNBA team there, I'm
sure. Yeah, but they don't call it. That's not part of the big four. Really? Big four
is Basketball, Football, Basketball, and Hockey. Seven. Baseball. Seven. Let's see. Eight. Rams,
Chargers, Angels, Dodgers, Lakers, Clippers, Kings, and Ducks. Ducks is what I was missing.
Plus two more if you include MLS. Ah, you didn't have the Anaheim Ducks. And now the
Ducks. But you got it within one. Wow. Paul, you're up. I'll close out Raiders. What the
hell? I don't know anything about that. What the hell? This head coach led the Raiders to
their first Super Bowl win, has the second highest win percentage, and revolutionized
sports video games by insisting the series with his name on it was the most realistically.
He tragically died in 2021. That is John Madden. John Madden, of course, the coach. Woohoo.
That's me. I'll try Oakland. It's a me. Oakland for 400. The Oakland Coliseum was the shared
home of the Raiders and the A's for many years. In its later years, it was known for the dugouts
flooding with sewage. What year was the Coliseum built within 10 years? Uh, 19. Within 10 years?
Let's try 1980. 1966? Holy shit. They don't build what they used to. They don't. I saw
a lot of games in there. It didn't seem that old. Matt. Um, let's do Oakland for 600. San
Francisco Oakland Bay Bridge opened November 12, 1936. Six months before the Golden Gate Bridge at a
cost of $78 million. The estimate to replace the Eastern span in 2013 was $250 million. With over
runs, how much did it actually cost within a billion? Pass. Passes to me. Paul. Pass. That passes
to me. Uh, let's see. Uh, the scores are Paul has 2000 and Matt and I both have zero. I'll,
I'll take a swing at it. I'll say it was supposed to be 250 million. I'll say 2.5 billion. Good
guess. 6.4 billion. Lord. That's, I'll say it. That's too much. That's that's an overrun
expected. Yeah, that's right there. Paul. Uh, that's worse than the sphere. Los Angeles,
please. Which is impressive. And 2028 LA will tie London and Paris for hosting the most Olympic
games. Name one of the two previous years LA hosted the Olympics. 84. 84. I think that's right.
84 and 32. That is me. I'll do LA for 800 in 2022. Will Smith slapped the shit out of Chris rock
during the Oscars held at this theater named after an American company specializing in audio
noise reduction, audio encoding, compression, spatial audio, and HDR imaging. Oh, sorry. That
question is directed at me. I was just reading the question and waiting on what are you guys to
answer it. I believe that is the Dolby theater. Got to be. It is the Dolby theater. Blinding.
Yes. Why aren't y'all talking? The Thomas Dolby theater. Uh, Matt Oakland or LA. If I get both
of these questions, I can get in second place. And right now I'm just in second place. No,
I'm in third place. Yeah. I'll take 200 points behind me for second place. Oakland for 800 to
seal a tie for second place. Let's do it. According to a random list. I found online the ATAT from
star Wars was inspired by the huge four legged cranes on the port of Oakland. It also says the
port is top five in North America. What does at at stand for or what's the largest port in North
America? Oh, geez. Matt, there are two very simple questions here. You can answer either
of them. Uh, artificial testicle, artificial testicle, because it's two balls. Got that one
dead on. Yeah. Yeah. Go for your bonus. I thought the largest port in North America was the port of
San Francisco, but I might be wrong. But I have to guess here because we're at the end of the time
here. Uh, I'll go with the port of San Francisco. All right, let's try it. All-terrain armored
transport or port of Los Angeles. Oh, port of LA. You're just a little north, just a little north.
I got all-terrain, but I couldn't put my finger on armored transport completely. Paul closing out
the category and the game. Los Angeles for 600. LA is the home of many conventions and trade shows.
This trade show covers the video game industry and at one time was the largest gaming expo of
the year. E3, which no longer exists. E3 or electronic entertainment expo. That's absolutely
right. And with that correct answer, Paul just submitted his win with 3000 points. I'm in second
place with 200 points. Matt is in a close third with negative 800 points. Port of Los Angeles.
Diamond Scoop, port of Los Angeles for the loss. Thank you, Diamond Scoop. If you want to send us
a scooperty, HeyScoops.com, head over there right on the homepage. Make us a scooperty. Make us a
Price is Right, Jack vs. Nerd. Make us an obelisk, Jack vs. Nerd and buy some tickets to Scoop Fest
all right there at HeyScoops.com. We opened up a couple of more whiskey barbecue tickets for
Scoop Fest. So there are a couple of them there on the website to purchase. Head on over there,
get you some whiskey barbecue tickets, get you some Scoop Fest tickets. Come join us here in
beautiful Las Vegas, Nevada at the end of September. My brother's coming. My brother's
going to be at the thing. So come and meet my brother. Yeah. And we're going to do it in the
Orleans. Call the Orleans. Use our discount code. Stay at the Orleans with us. I actually see Akshay
Mysore up there. I believe it was the first winner of the American accent contest at Scoop Fest.
Yes, I believe he was. Akshay, good to see you, buddy. Yeah, thanks for popping on, pal. Shoutout
to Wayne and Captain James T. Scoop for joining us here today. Thank you so much. If you want to
join us for a live broadcast, you should be a member of our Patreon. Join us at any level
and you'll get invites to our Zoom link and you can do that at PreachingFun.com. Oh, right.
Or if you, like Dead Lazlo in the chat, wonders aloud if Matt Donnelly will still be allowed
in the Orleans in September, head on over to fartsinabag.biz. See you at the gym. Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts. Go, go. Fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com. It takes you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. If you think this show
is worth more than $0, we would certainly appreciate you visiting PreachingFun.com
and/or fartsinabag.biz. You don't really have to go to both, but it couldn't hurt. Nope. All right.
Couldn't hurt. Well, thanks for listening, everybody. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you
at the Cone. We'll see you soon.
We're PreachingFun. Come together on the drums. Boom, ba-boom. That's the drum solo in Come Together.