yeah oh hello there I am so happy to see you because I'd like to thank you the
ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers it is a new
month we don't have a new list yet but we will thank each and every ice cream
truck driver before this month is through if you want to be an ice cream
truck driver and I sure hope you do share this fucking ice cream straight to
people's fucking ear holes head over to preachingfun.com preachingfun.com is
where you go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life
you save may be your own
oh it's a show hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice cream social yeah I'd love
to great let's go
I had a weird night last night you had a weird weekend too. I had a weird weekend I've had a weird life. Who am I fooling?
it's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social sitting over there in Las Vegas it's
Matt Donnelly sitting over there in Pittsburgh it's Paul Mattingly sitting
here in Las Vegas it's me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun we're preaching
fun hey everybody yeah how we doing everybody having a good day I don't care
here's a production meeting
blamo blamo is right right out of nowhere boom I just scared the shit out of my cat
with that blamo oh it was so much blamo oh man really woke her up poor kitty we
are our company gentlemen is restructuring we are restructuring our
company through somebody quit it our oldest our oldest friend and I suppose
employee although that feels weird it feels we paid very little but someone
yes but Annie is Annie is moving on from us our dear friend Annie is moving on
with us promise she has been with us since the beginning of patreon at the
very least yeah launch our patreon and then immediately expressed how
overwhelmed we are by our own creation yep yep and she emailed us and said I
will help organize this for you and then continue to do so for I guess I don't
even know how long I mean I have I mean it's really over 10 years I mean we
probably did patreon on our own for like a month before she swooped in and was
like yeah here let me just let me just take care of you sweet sweet children
lost in the woods and it's very important to note you know and I think I
really think is just Annie being respectful like I think she's just a
first-class person start to finish it's simply that like when we started we had
like seven tears we had a bunch of bonus rewards for people who were on for more
than three months right we had all kinds of different deliverables that we were
thought you know that we could do if we had all the time in the world and then
quickly realized that we don't have all the time in the world but Annie kept all
of these things organized for us all the time and more importantly fielded emails
from patrons yes I ordered what is happening I ordered all you can eat video
whatever hands-free eating video and so long ago when we were first figuring out
what our patreon was going to look like this is great we're just gonna go down
memory lane now that we're talking about any when we first figured out what our
patreon was gonna look like we just threw so many ideas at the wall and I
think Paul I think Paul said the hands-free eating yeah yes I'm sure I
did and Matt and I just went both of us like Paul explained to us what he was
thinking he said well we'll make a video where we go to a restaurant we will
order food and then we'll eat that food without using our hands and and Matt and
I just said like oh yeah yeah that is something we should do yeah no problem
and no thought about it no issue just right on there because our early patron
was like hey let's pay for our gas and a meal once in a while that was our goal
for the patreon and so yeah no I mean it was ridiculous and you know all the
things we've learned we've talked to other people who started patreon or
sort of podcast you know it's interesting and then now we've really
simplified things here on our patreon more than ever most because we kind of
discovered that we're such a community that like watching us do stuff or
making us do stuff it seems to be less interesting to our listeners than
making sure that we all hang out or create social opportunities for each
other like all you have to do to get us to do a hands-free eating video now is
convince us that it's gonna be funny and we'll probably just do it if we can if
you want a video for me you sent me the money to buy food you're getting the money
to buy an Aldi hot dog oh no no no no it's gotta be more money than an Aldi
hot dog I need a skateboard and a stick a set of jumper cables to create a ramp
of food that can go down towards my mouth oh a new competitor entering the
arena between team slide and team swing skateboarding skateboard with a skateboard
catapult yeah or the west was to your oh somebody else if we hit a goal we
actually came close this month to hitting a bonus goal for the first time
in a long time we felt everyone just short which would be maybe means a bonus
episode and just before we got on there we even brainstorming new ways to do
bonus episodes and what about so we're in good shape to work I think we had a
good idea we're in good shape without any to deliver a brand new bonus
episode should we get there so please don't let this reorganization hold you
back for supporting us we still need you and by need you I mean we are completely
reliant on you but yeah I mean you know yes we gave her a stipend but it was a
charitable stipend and so I mean it really was just her helping us out for a
decade and so she will be I feel like she wrote off the time that she worked
for us as a charity donation on her time yeah and that'd be fair we would back
that up at the IRS yeah I was sure I don't think any court would convict her
no we're basically when it comes to us running a company we're basically make a
wish but it's I just got a random link texted to me from a random phone number
wanting me to reset my Instagram password so I got that from Google today
too yeah I think I don't know you know I think maybe yeah maybe the one the US
infrastructure might be hanging by thread no I think we're probably fine
moving on thank you Annie you have been our champion for years we are going to
miss you in ways that we don't understand yet so so thank you so much
we're gonna run into issues over the next weeks and months and we're gonna be
like fuck Annie was just taking care of this and we didn't realize it I know
that's going to happen so thank you so much Annie we very much appreciate you
and everything you have done for us and for this community over the years she
was a huge part of making this the success that it is yeah and always will
be Annie Annie will henceforth be always welcome at any ice cream social event
yeah anything that we ever do for all time Annie is forever welcome yeah and
is just in yarn and sticks is saying I hope Annie gets free membership for life
I think we can get her she might be sick of us guys so it's not easy up on the
rewards but she wants to stay away from us I get that too well I don't think
we're you know I think she has access to the patreon stuff to a degree I don't
think we're taking that away so we're not we're not scouring to reset all the
passwords resetting the door codes this morning I'll need your keys in your badge
and your badge in your gun give me your gun give me a gun I don't care hand me
any gun any gun any badge in any gun Brogan is right and he's probably the
only one who remembers the passwords that's absolutely true she has not
received the last email or phone call from us that's for sure my last email to
her was expressing thank yous and all the stuff and like and maybe could you
just put a list together
thank you so much Eddie that was so wonderfully appreciated mm-hmm yeah so I
had a weird week I went to um went downtown the other night went on town on
Monday night we're not starting there I tell you where we're starting okay you
went to a football game with with pod therapy is where we're starting I did I
went on Sunday I went to a football game with pod there this is where
football why why football rules like like when you look at American sports
like football is just in its own fucking category in terms of success you I would
say I three three other friends JD who directed is directing the hey scoops
movie short from our friend Alice who has the offensive crayon purpose the
offensive crayons all went to this game and I went to bust balls with everyone I
think so maybe JD after the fact during the game because you were at what I
would think is the dumbest football game on earth so if you don't follow sports
it's the last week of the season uh-huh the Raiders were already the most
terrible team number one draft gets locked up they're bringing but at the
beginning of the day we didn't know that we thought the only thing that was gonna
matter on the day was that the Raiders needed to lose to lock up the number one
draft pick and then right before the game started they come over the PA in
the stadium they're like hey the Giants just upset the cow or just lost to the
Cowboys or upset the Cowboys or which ever one they did yeah Giants just beat
the Cowboys which solidifies the Raiders getting that number one draft pick now
that's not even on the table and that's anything on the table the Chiefs come to
town there's no Mahomes he's injured Patrick Mahomes is injured he's out
tells he's in probably because he's last game did they come to the game there
yeah homes yeah he was at the game I'm out there wasn't he I don't know I
thought he was there I thought somebody told me he was there I don't fucking know
I don't watch your breaks you asked us then Jacob and I were clarifying with
each other can you just give us a second I thought he was there I thought
somebody told me that he was there because it was probably Kelsey's last
game yeah both ever names started yes yeah Kelsey might retire retiring Travis
Kelsey yeah he's my age he's old he's also married to the good zillionaire
that Brady that's true that is true yeah but he's already made the second most
money and it but somebody made the second most amount of money in his
marriage and that did not stop him I don't know because he hated his family
he had to go back to my kids anybody hiring Giselle is a witch I'll spend
time in Tampa Giselle is a certified which careful also now as a black belt
buddy she'll kick your ass I ain't saying anything negative about it I was
wondering how powerful which Taylor Swift is in comparison I wonder I guess
pretty powerful under as well either way I feel like Travis Kelsey's gonna land
on his feet somewhere I'm saying there's absolutely nothing on the line Raiders
absolute worst team they're playing they are the worst both teams played
multiple not one but multiple backup quarterbacks oh so many quarterbacks and
no one could score a touchdown nope and it was just a field goal festival for
the first half and I'm texting you and I'm texting out and I'm busting balls
like alright happy field goals yeah like basically like why are you at this game
it's so dumb that sounds like an old that sounds like a Steelers game which
is Bosworth playing the whole game with nothing on the line it comes down to a
field goal and the Raiders win drill it 14 to 12 they scored 14 points with no
touchdowns which is a miracle they scored a safety at some point scored a
safety in there and people went fucking wild like it was great and all of my
ball busting fell on deaf ears because it was like whatever that was fucking
amazing and I was like this is why football wins like that is by far the
dumbest game like right now it's a Brooklyn Nets beat the Wizards on a last
second shot no one would give a shit right like like when when the NBA has
futility it is futility yes when you were watching the backup of backups play
against each other to win by a field goal kick and everyone is like best day
of my year yeah it's like what what this is why football has won this is how
football has won I mean we went in large part because it was a meaningless game
we bought the tickets she bought tickets that morning yeah yeah we were on the
13th row on the on the 40 yard line so we had killer seats right and yeah we
just had we went to we went knowing it was a meaningless game knowing that
neither team was gonna really care the backups were gonna be the ones that care
they are the guys they're playing for jobs they care and of course everybody's
professional so I mean they're they're still going out there and doing the
thing and yeah it was it was so much fun it was the most relaxed sporting event
I've ever been to there were Kansas City Chiefs fans sitting directly in front of
us we were just having nice conversations the whole game and would
like razz each other with that when our team did well of their team didn't do
well like just everybody was just having a good time just a quick check in with
our listeners here Jeff Loomis in the chat says I'm so disconnected from the
NBA this the first time I heard the Nets are now in Brooklyn and not New Jersey
Jeff they moved there before I moved to Las Vegas I used to be that's fair you
are behind on that I used to be a Nets fan and they and they moved to Brooklyn
and I'm such a Jersey guy that I was pissed because there was a superior deal
offered to them for them to play in Newark yeah and they took this really
shady real estate deal so this guy Bruce Ratner could basically own all the
property around the stadium and Bruce Ratner moved the team to Brooklyn and
immediately sold the team and kept the rights to the land and everything around
it it was such a fucking it was such a fucking piece of shit deal I mean I know
it moved them out of New Jersey but have you ever heard of a more New Jersey
deal than that they finished in style as they say they finished doing what they
love but yeah Jeff it's been at least before 2008 I don't know what year but
it's been a minute I always think that uh that they moved just so they could
rename their dance team you know the name of the dance team for the Brooklyn
Nets right I don't it's the Brooklyn Nets Brooklyn Nets you guys win you
guys just good job yeah that's wonderful all right dance teams for all the
football teams let's go for it let's go all right well the Raiders I just saw
them the other day they're the Raider at the Raider at there they're that work
they're just like Brooklyn I know the Saints I know the Saints ones they are
the St. Seychens so I've done this a lot all right oh bangles bang gals yeah
right the Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders that's just Dallas Cowboy cheerleaders
but they're a dance team as well right the Chargers are called a charger the
subtitle guys hate them are the Packers what are they the pack right fudge back
backers okay that's it the fudgies the dancing fudgies for the Packers the
bears the cubs yeah the cubs oh are they the cubs it's a buzzer it's a bunch of
young dudes so they dance the cubs and the twinks not to be confused with the
Dolphins they have the seals how awesome would it be to be in a football game
there's a you know time out and they're like all right making way the field
giving up for the Twinks it'd be great right let's go tons of cartwheels a lot
of backflips yeah yeah oh bears you have honey bears says we just do oh honey
bears is solid honey bears is nice yeah I'll tell you who else likes a good a
honey bear the following spot is just cut this off before we get to the
commanders and mark today's show is brought to you by al dente for its book
three al dente escapes the tickle hut that's al dente for its book three al
dente escapes the tickle hut that's from Dungeon Scoop in 2024 deep in it the
heart of the tickle hut al dente is tied up and it can not move you see he got a
feather somebody got a feather on his feet and he feeling it but everything is
dark so he don't know who he is give him a tickle so he have to struggle and
wiggle like a worm until he find a wall and then he were up against a wall and
then he's he feel a door jam and he squirm up to the door jam and he put his
mouth under the doorknob and he lick it open and then there's still no light but
he go through the door and he wiggle wiggle wiggle even more someone still
tickling his feet all the way he's so scared there's Cheerios on the floor he
can feel them his body crunching up against the Cheerios and he hears a
crying baby in the background then shards of glass that he wiggles on
shards of glass and broken Cheerios he realizes he will never escape the
tickle house or will he? Read my book! I tried to get out of the tickle house!
Who knows what's going to happen? Who can say? You know the difference between a door jam and a
door jelly right? What's that? I don't. I don't either. Okay. So Monday night we uh we
went downtown SJ and I we go downtown we had a rare night off together and so my
wife and I said oh we're gonna go out and hit the town we'll go find some
dinner we called a couple of friends and said hey we're gonna go down to
Fremont Street and walk around maybe find a little music find a little food
see what see what the night brings us so we went down we went downtown head down
to Fremont Street. What would we say gentlemen would we say this is version 5 version 6 of
Fremont at this point? It's a resting version 5 it's a it's a slightly slightly
adjusted improved like you know they do like the point the decimal points on
different versions of stuff okay I'd say I'd say we're like 5.5 of that makes
sense okay I think so Jeff Loomis you are not completely wrong I am I am in a
small minority of Las Vegas locals that goes and does stuff on the strip in
downtown that's true mainly I mean the strip part is because my my work takes
me there it's rare that we go to the strip without work taking us there but
downtown is a different animal but yeah so we head down we listen to a little
bit of music there's a band that SJ might work with a little bit and we
wouldn't listen to them a little bit which was nice and and then we see we
did a very Las Vegas tourist thing we saw a billboard for a special at one of
the steak houses at the I should give a shout out here the Fremont the Fremont
casino down on Fremont Street they had a special starting at 9 p.m. 1799 for a
steak and lobster dinner hey that is that's a nice old-school Vegas touch
right there can't beat that with a stick so we just because you can't beat that
they're trying to be old Vegas and we talked that we've talked about like
Vegas a lot on the obviously and there's a hearing this week local businesses are
trying to stop Las Vegas the town from raising parking prices and expanding
paid parking I follow of course our good buddy Troy heard who is one of the key
motivators down there in the Arts District yeah with with the theater and
majestic doing his thing and his you know his feed has just been so sad to
keep up with they are just trying to fuck the Arts District yeah and they're
just trying it's just nickel and diamond it's just the worst kind of nickel and
diamond and it is being done with it seems it sure seems like from an outside
point of view it's being done with zero for thought not only zero for thought
Jacob it seems with some level of malicious intent as there are now
security guards parking security guards out there who are former police and they
are carrying guns like it's one thing to have a meter made on duty it's another
thing to have an armed guard patrolling your parking spaces just me getting
pistol whipped as my as my chip won't scan on the parking meter right it's
like it's like I just came down here to watch my kid in a new version of
Cinderella I hear what you're sure I know what you're saying dance I hear
what you're saying and I appreciate what you're saying I don't see that as a
change Las Las Vegas security guards it is easy to have the to have the license
here to be an armed security guard and also it's an open carry state so like
having more having more guns around is what while I don't love it it's not a
surprise but do you do either of you recall running into that on the regular
in the Arts District I arts district is so new relatively okay but I mean but
like I I oh no no it's definitely changing I don't I'm saying I'm not
saying armed guards by the parking lots down in the arts district ever you know
that that's I mean the argument likely isn't like I guess I want to be able to
fucking pull heat on some you know scoff laws it's that right if you're gonna
send me downtown working late at night I would like to be armed is what they're
doing because it yeah outside I'd like to be armed everywhere I go but that's
not good well I mean I'm just taking a quick vote and nobody wants Paul to be
armed I've got my ad man tium claws that retract and you know so I can we're
actually gonna take those away from you oh no I'm not I'm not comfortable with
you having grafted to my bones nope sorry we're taking them this is on fire
in the chat today Jeff insists you know what raising parking prices means that
this might be a spot available and I'm willing to pay a premium for it Jeff if
you lived here I tell you to move but you don't even live here oh shut up and
get lost and Jeff I'll tell you the the downtown parking situation I don't think
again just looking at from an outsider point of view it sure doesn't seem like
it has been affected the business side of it has been affected by these parking
rate changes yeah it's the local businesses that are saying let they want locals to
come on down there breeze in grab a bite to eat see you see a show go home no
problem and that should be the way our arts district work it's us it's locals
it's for us also we are like our taxes already paid for the fucking streets
why I'm having to pay again to park on my street yes we're Jacob you're ready
Jacob no we are triple fucking taxed in this country it's insane yeah there is a
meeting happening today we're not gonna be able to go to it but there is a
community meeting happening in my neighborhood today about a new church
that is wanting to be built nearby people are up in arms
argument it should be I hope fuck off get the fuck out how close to your house
pretty close okay like other side of kind of the the block and everything from
me but like as the crow flies should this should this go through and get
squirrely in your neighborhood how much of a possibility is there for us as ICS
to try and file for church status try to try and solve some things I mean it
would it would automatically lessen our tax burden which I mean we would
definitely get away with it at least through the current administration
until the IRS gets beefed back up yeah you're right we'd have three good years
of skating so I would have minimum three good years probably more like 10 so yeah
let's let's fucking go I mean this is let's fucking also like the way your
neighborhood is set up right like you have a wall there and stuff you can put
whatever st. Annick sculpture you want like right there yeah yeah just have
like oh we could do anything I got I was genuinely trees and I have some huge
palm trees in front of my house and I have been genuinely considering hiring
somebody to come carve tiki figures into the living palm tree oh can that is that
safe for the palm tree I'm told that it is really I would I would look into that
a little more before doing it for sure I'm not this is this is an idea that I'm
playing with I'm just saying it to say that I just card ridiculous things out
in front of my house you can carve six six six into the trunks of those no
problem right in there it won't be too damaging all right not a cult ish
correct so we head downtown we enjoy our $18 steak and lobster which by the way
was delicious was it not was it like crawdad times or was it a lobster tail
nice nice lobster tail a little cup of the drawn butter which I mean who
doesn't love a nice cup of drawn butter that's right yeah a little ghee for you
I actually I poured water I poured butter into this can that's I'm drinking
right now good slicks your slicks up your blood vessel walls make sure makes
your blood move quicker keeps the vocal cords nice and lubed perhaps blue rib and
butter Jeff Loomis says in the chat cost more than 17 bucks to buy a decent
quality steak at the grocery store that is true this steak costs less than 17
dollars in the grocery store but I would put it I wouldn't put it on par with an
outback terrible not terrible at all it wasn't like like a street mugging kind
of steak sounds thin nice thick steak nice thick steak is that a full
measurement you put up with the screen is it also that that big round as well
inch and a half right yeah that's that's girth girth and width oh okay it's just
about just a cube it's just one cube it was a bite they said oh we asked the
waiter said what does it come with he goes oh it's steak lobster and a baked
potato so now great what's the big potato come with he goes butter and
sour cream said anyway you can uh can do anything else with that anything else
you can add to the baked potato he goes well I can load it up for you go oh
that'd be great load it up for me you didn't ask how much the loading would
cost didn't ask how much the loading would cost but it came out you know food
came out and the load-up was some shredded cheese and some bacon bits
right and caviar yeah caviar no problem that was five bucks I was gonna say
don't you do it man the only weird the only weird cost it was five bucks the
drinks were cheap we both ordered cocktails there were like eight dollars
for a for a drink it's like good job Fremont Street casino down here doing
doing this yeah so that's nice we we walk out of there we listen to a little
more music a couple of our friends come down and meet us so now we're all we're
all hanging out and moving around and they say oh let's go check out this new
bar downtown I'd shout them out right now if I remember what it was I'll find
it here in a minute Jacob I know so we went down we check out this new bar it's
It's a Japanese bar downtown in the arts district there.
Really nice.
It is called Pachi Pachi.
- Pachi Pachi? - Pachi Pachi.
P-A-C-H-I P-A-C-H-I.
It was lovely.
- Was that a Happy Days themed bar?
- It was not.
It was not, Paul.
- Oh, I'm thinking of Potsy Potsy.
- That's right.
That's a different bar entirely.
- Different bar, different bar.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- The jukebox is cheap though,
if you know how to work it. - Potsy Potsy.
- Potsy Potsy, you gotta order the Ralph Mouth.
- There you go.
- So we hang out there.
We have some cocktails.
Our friends have a little bit of food.
We pick off their food a little bit.
The food was really good.
The cocktails were delicious.
Oh, I had a wagyu washed old fashioned.
And just fine. - Wagyu washed?
- Just fine.
- Now what does that mean?
- What does that mean?
- Wagyu fat washed whiskey.
So they just, they wipe a steak in the--
- That's it.
They just dip a steak down in there and just,
they put a steak in the, those drink shakers,
they just put a chunk of steak in there, just whip it up.
- This is, I am also wagyu washed.
I replaced my soap with wagyu beef now when I shower.
- Wagyu washing.
- Just take wagyu beef across all my extremities.
- Anne loves an old fashioned.
- Between the beef and the butter with you, Matt,
you're really gleaming.
- Yeah, yeah.
I just, the only person who doesn't like this new look
is my cardiologist.
But other than that.
(Matt laughs)
- And he'll never tell.
- Everyone seems to think I'm shining and glowing.
- Your cardiologist.
(Matt laughs)
- The only man who knows my secret is my cardiologist.
And he'll never tell.
- He'll never tell.
He's like, "I'm drinking butter.
"I'm washing myself with beef.
"What do you want from me, doc?"
(Matt laughs)
- To not do that.
I don't want you to do either of those things.
- Name one thing I can do differently.
- Not wash yourself in butter.
- All right, fine. - Next, next, next.
Pass. - You're right.
- Pass, next.
- New solution.
- You got me.
- That's not gonna work for me, doc.
- So you were at the Fremont enjoying this meal.
- So we went to the Fremont, enjoyed this meal.
And then we go over to this new establishment
called Pachi Pachi.
- Where is it in reference to Fremont?
- It is a walk from Fremont, but just a walk.
It's just a few minutes off of Fremont
kind of on the edge of the arts district
between kind of the Fremont street experience
and the Las Vegas arts district.
- Is it like where the Griffin is and all those spots?
- It's on that end, but just a little bit past that
and one block over.
- There's always fancy little spots popping up over there.
- Exactly.
Over by like Carson Kitchen area, all that stuff.
- That's the spot where it's offensive
to charge for parking.
- That's why we walked.
- For us to, it's clearly built for locals.
Just pull on there, have a good time and get out of there.
- Yeah, that's true.
So we were in there, we're hanging out with our friends.
There are four of us in there.
And we are at the end of the evening,
we are the only people left in there
with the exception of one group of three guys
that's over by the bar.
And so we finish up and we're gonna head out.
We're gonna go, you'll probably find something else
and maybe a nightcap before we call it a night.
And so we stand up, we're gathering up our things.
And one of the guys from the group across the room
breaks off and comes over to us
and says, "You guys enjoy your night.
Thank you so much for coming by."
And our friend goes,
"Are you associated with this establishment?"
He goes, "Oh yeah, I'm one of the owners.
I just wanted to come over and thank you for coming in."
Lovely guy, we had a nice chat.
And he says, "Hey, I know you guys
are getting ready to leave before you head out for the night.
Would you be interested in having one more cocktail?"
And we all do the thing where the four of us
just do the look at each other and check in.
And we go, "Yes, let's have another cocktail.
This'll be nice."
And we all start to kind of shift towards the bar
in the place, okay?
And he goes, "Great, hold on just a second."
And he calls over to the bartender.
He says, "Hey, I'm gonna take these folks over
so I'll be back in a little while."
What?
Whoa.
Oh, hold on.
We're going somewhere else.
Never go to a second location, Jacob.
Never go to a second location.
Kind of interests you guys.
This is murderino101.
Never go to a second location.
We're gonna go to my apartment.
We're going to take these guys to my apartment.
In any situation, never go to a second location.
This is awful.
So we go, "Oh, we're going somewhere else."
He goes, "Yeah, it's just a little walk.
It's a couple doors down."
Go, "All right, great, we're in."
And so we head down.
We walk down the block.
- It's clothing optional, so you can leave your clothes here
or check out when you get into the place.
Whatever you wanna do.
- They have lockers, I think it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
- There's no charge for lockers here.
So if you wanna leave your clothes here, that's cheaper.
- Oh my God.
- It's two dollars over there.
- I'm scared for you.
I'm really scared now.
- Oh, no, no, no, it's not that kind of story.
So we go over, it turns out the bar that we go to
is a new bar in an old location.
The old location of this bar is a bar
that SJ and I used to go into all the time
when we first moved here.
So that was kind of exciting.
So we head into this new bar.
The owner from the Pachi Pachi, he comes in and he says,
"Yeah, these are my new friends.
Just met them down at my spot."
And we go, "Oh great."
And so we all meet, we all shake hands.
- Scoop or Nova Girl, Chad's asking,
did he ever prove that he was the owner?
(laughing)
- That is a fine question, Scoop or Nova Girl.
Because what happened at that point,
after he introduced us to everyone,
what do you think he did?
After we walked in, he said,
"Oh, let's go have a nightcap, a couple doors down."
We walked down to the other bar.
We walk in, he introduces us to the staff
and everybody who's there.
What do you think he does at that point?
We haven't ordered anything.
We just walked in, we've met everyone.
- It's a finger wag in the air.
Drinks for everyone, drinks for everyone, finger wag.
That's what I think happens next.
- Paul's on it.
He just goes, "Well, I gotta get back over to my bar.
Thanks for coming in, guys."
- What in the living hell?
- So is this the game that they're playing?
Is this the game that they're playing?
They're just shifting customers to each other's spot?
- I don't think so.
I was like, he left and we all looked at each other.
We were like, "Where are we hanging out?"
I thought we were gonna, you invited us here.
- Yeah, these are my new friends
who I don't wanna talk to. - You were on your way out
for the first time, right?
- We were leaving his establishment when this happened.
- So wasn't like he was trying to be slick
and kick you out of his place so we could close.
- No, I was like, maybe he wanted to close,
but that doesn't make sense because we were leaving.
We were like, we were up and putting our coats on leaving.
- That's bizarre.
- It didn't make a single bit of sense.
- It's really bizarre. - This is like a cab driver
taking you to a specific strip club, right?
- I guess, but I don't think anybody got anything out of it.
I mean, the bar that we went to
got us to buy another drink there.
I mean, it was great, we had a good time there.
We did have, I mean, he left
and we did just order a couple of rounds of drinks there
and had a nice time there.
So the recommendation was awesome.
- This is bizarre.
This is bizarre also because--
- I don't have a single bad part of this story.
It was just the weirdest fucking thing
I've ever seen in my life.
- But the weirdness matters, right?
Because how quickly are you gonna go to Hotsie Totsie again?
- I mean, I don't think it's affected
our opinion of that place at all.
- Here's the thing.
You went down for your bargain steak,
steak bisque plate and lobster tail.
- That's right.
- And decided to dial it up by going to Hotsie Totsie.
And what probably would have ended
as just like really fun night out downtown.
And now next time you have like friends in town or whatever
and they're still doing the surf and turf special or whatever,
you're not gonna do it again, right?
You're not gonna just go like,
"Oh, we should go do this and go bing bang boom.
This is a really fun night downtown," right?
- Well, the surf and turf special
and the Hotsie Totsie aren't connected.
They were just a walk from each other.
So the surf and turf was just earlier and then Hotsie Totsie.
Like I know what you mean though.
It is a weird nightcap on the end of your experience
at Hotsie Totsie.
- In other words, like if you, like a friend came down,
I was like, "Is there any old Vegas left on this town?"
And you would be like, "Oh, buckle up.
I'm taking you down to the Fremont.
We're gonna have a, don't get your potato loaded
and follow my lead," right?
Then down there, you might be like,
"Hey, there's also like a little bar.
If you guys want to get off the strip,
we can go around the town."
Like, you know what I mean?
Like you're very lucky to like replay that scenario.
But you're very much less likely to be like now,
to be like, "Hey, you want to go to this bar
where the guy weirded me out?"
Like, you're just not gonna do it.
You're just not gonna--
- You might be right.
You might be right.
- You know, like you're just simply not gonna be inclined
to treat someone else to that experience again,
because you're like, "This owner's weird."
- There's just a weird story.
And it is, like I say, not a single bad thing.
Not a single bad thing at any part of the story,
including the recommendation.
The recommendation was great.
- No, we only have to explore how flawed
this person's logic is.
Like we can't find all of the spaces
on the board game of decision-making
on this person's end.
- And I didn't even tell you
about the full length conversation
that we had at his bar before leaving there.
We stood there and all chatted and laughed
and had a good time for easily for 10 minutes.
Before he suggested that we go to the other bar,
we all stood around and laughed and had a good time
for about 10 minutes with him.
- He specifically said, "You guys wanna stay for one more."
He saw you leaving and said, "Let's do one more."
- He came over when we were leaving.
We stood up, we're putting our coats on.
He came over and engaged us in conversation at that point.
We had a nice, long conversation.
We all had a nice time.
And as that conversation seemed to be naturally
getting to a point where we could either sit down
and continue it or move on with our evenings,
he said, "I know you guys are leaving.
Would you like to have one more cocktail?"
- Right, and that implies one,
the cocktail happens in that location.
- Or at least that he's gonna have it with us.
- And two, that he's paying or that's a free round.
- Sure, the paying part, I was less,
I was less weirded out by the paying part.
- It is weird to escort someone to a bar
and not buy the first round.
That's just weird.
- Agreed.
- No matter who you are, owner or not.
And if I rally a group to move one location
and go to B location,
especially if I'm gonna ditch them, which he did.
- That's really odd.
- At least if he says, get them whatever they want on me.
Listen, I gotta get back to my bar,
but I wanted you guys to check out this place.
This round's on me.
Now you're doing some hospitality work
and now you're doing whatever.
But he literally just shoved you into somewhere else
and be like, "Buy things over here.
You're welcome."
- It is not, it's a weird move.
- It is.
- And you know what I really wanted to do?
You know, an hour later when we were leaving the second bar,
what I really wanted to do was go back to the first bar
and see if it was still open.
- If it had just vanished,
see if it was still even still there.
- There's not even a building here.
- Yeah, right, exactly.
- Oh, there used to be a building here years ago.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Are you familiar with the Hotsie Totsie building?
- And there's a painting of the guy and it's like 1958.
- Fuck, that's the guy.
- That's the guy.
Total ghost.
- How long was the walk between the bars?
- Oh. - Good question, Rob.
- 90 seconds, 90 seconds.
- It was right there.
- Yeah, right now, not out of the way at all.
Really a couple of doors down.
And in the same area, in an area we were familiar with,
there was not a single moment in this story
where any of us were uncomfortable at all.
- Because not to put too fine of a point on it,
but by making you go to another bar
and get another drink, which you didn't pay for,
you also had to pay for another hour of parking
that you were about to save
by leaving the bar in the first place.
- Back to the parking.
- That would have been true.
That would be true for other people.
We had parked with our friends at the valet
down at the Golden Gate Casino.
- And you have friends there?
- And we have friends there.
They take care of us.
But they're also-
- Connected.
- But it's also, it's also old school Vegas.
So it's free valet for anyone, if you can get in.
The hard part there is get again, because it's small.
- It fills up.
- That's it.
That's where I have friends.
- If we're up to Jeff Loomis, he charged $50 a car
than anyone who really wanted to pay could do it.
- Yeah, I mean, look at capitalist Jeff Loomis over here.
Capitalism will solve all our problems, right, Jeff?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell you who else thinks capitalism will solve
their problems.
And that's the following sponsor.
- Old money guns, Jeff Loomis.
Today's show is brought to you by Creepy Best Buy Guys,
part-time job as a professional wrestling trainer.
That's from Bear Scoop in 2025.
It's Creepy Best Buy Guy, part-time job
as a professional wrestling trainer.
- Hey, let's get in the ring.
Let's just go a couple and see what we can do here.
Okay, yeah.
All right, now first thing you want to do
is you want to put your arms together
with the other person's arms and hold on to them.
- So is it a specific type of hold?
Like what do you mean by which hold?
- Just get in there and start touching.
See what you touch.
- But like, is there a technique to the hold
that I should be using?
- No, no, no, no.
You've been punching rice, like I've asked you.
- Punching rice?
- Yeah, I asked you to punch rice.
That was part of the training.
- Yeah, yeah.
- You get a big old bucket of rice.
You just start punching that rice.
- Yeah.
- And it gets your grip strength growing, right?
Yeah, okay.
- Yeah, I used cooked rice though, so it was much easier.
It was very nice.
- Okay, I'm going to call you Panda Express.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- And her hay scoops are checked.
(laughing)
- I think that would very much defeat the purpose.
- Well, unless you cooked it and then refrigerated
and let it reset in there, then maybe, I don't know,
maybe it'd be sticky enough.
- That's why I remember I worked with this guy.
He was the nicest guy in the Virgin Islands
and he was a former army ranger.
And he said that they would jab their hands
into buckets of sand to build up their callus and strength.
And then you added rocks after your calluses built up,
after a while.
And then you added broken glass when the rocks
didn't do anything to your hands.
And you just kept jabbing them over and over again
into the sands or whatever.
And he's like, "That way, if you can only get two fingers
on someone, you can still..."
And he literally put two fingers on my neck
and I was like, "Jesus, those are callous and strong fingers."
(laughing)
He's basically saying that you just,
that way you still only needed two fingers for you
to kill someone who was trying to kill you.
And I was like, "Thank you for your service."
- Yeah, right?
- And then I went and I changed my pants.
- What was his army ranger?
- He was an army ranger, yeah.
- Yeah, I had friends like that,
a couple of ranger friends back in the day.
And yeah, they, I didn't fuck with them a whole lot.
Hardly ever, in fact, hardly ever.
We have an update on a previous story.
- I don't know if you heard it, a few weeks ago,
fella went to the old, what was the establishment
he went to, the haunted thing at...
- The John Wick.
- The John Wick. - The John Wick experience.
- The John Wick experience over at Area 15.
Fella showed up there with a real sex doll companion
and wanted to take himself and his real sex doll companion
through the experience.
And at one point, shenanigans occurred.
But Professor Big Scoop in the chat with us here,
in the room with us here,
in the Zoom where it happened, if you will, was there.
So, Professor, tell us your tale.
- If you have seen the video,
I am the tall guy standing to the screen right
of the guy playing the manager.
- That's it, we had friends send to our Instagram
the actual security footage of the events that took place.
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
- So you're working there currently, yes, Biggs?
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, along with, I mean, you know,
friends of Ice Cream Social, you know.
- Sure.
- Nicole Unger and Brenna Folger.
- Oh, lovely.
Brenna Folger is no friend of Ice Cream Social.
(laughing)
- Those names have nothing to do with
who may have sent us those videos.
- No.
(laughing)
So give us the skinny, Biggs.
What happens from your POV?
- All right, so we got the word
that this is gonna be happening like two days before.
- Oh, really, so he contacted the establishment?
- Did they call for permission at that part in advance?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
- Well, that's polite.
- Or is it polite, or has he done this before
with lots of places and finally realized,
oh, I gotta give you this? - Yes!
The answer to both of those questions is yes.
- Well, it's weird. - It could very well be yes.
It could very well be.
- He asked permission for the doll to be armed,
and we said, "This is an open carry state.
Go ahead.
You can strap heat under the torso of the real doll."
- My doll is coming straight from her job
as a parking meter enforcer.
(laughing)
- That's right, that's right.
So we knew way ahead of time,
and of course, all of the records.
Chris Brown normally plays the manager and the others,
but I was like, "Oh, come on."
I was getting ready to bump him in,
'cause I was also playing the manager that day.
And I was like, "All right, I need to go in there
and just kind of be his muscle, right?
Be the guy standing behind him."
- Yeah.
- And he was fine with it.
And the guy came in, very nice guy,
apparently been spending, you know,
about an hour or two beforehand out in the bar,
having conversations with-
- Yikes.
Oh, great.
- Yeah, with her and patrons that would,
or patrons that would come up and say,
"Oh yeah, so-and-so really likes the decor here,
blah, blah, blah."
And the whole time he said,
he said, "Now, here's the thing.
I'm not as weird as you guys may think.
I know she's fake, but I've had some really bad relationships
and this one with her is just, makes me comfortable,
makes me not crazy."
- Hard to argue with that logic.
- Who can argue?
- Yeah, and again, middle-aged guy would say it,
I would say probably 50 plus, you know?
- Okay.
Well, he's got that top of the line vag doll model money.
- Oh my lordy.
- That shit ain't cheap.
- And he-
- He didn't even want just the torso,
he wanted the whole thing.
- Exactly.
- He went with the huge tracks of land model as well.
It was, yeah.
- And if you lose it over the side of a boat,
you want it to be able to float.
(laughing)
- Right.
- Not as crazy as you think, guys.
- I'm just so psychologically damaged
from all of my relationships with humans
that I decided to forge my own.
- Holy shit.
- Now, I didn't see them, but everyone,
but some other people said,
it made me took them off once they got out of the bar.
Apparently she had elf ears as well.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- That explains why she was rolling for Thacko
before going to each room.
(laughing)
- Nice, Auburn haired young lady in a blue dress.
- Real horse hair, yeah.
- So he comes in.
So this thing is apparently heavy.
- They prefer sex workers.
- Yeah, it's heavy, right?
It's like-
- Oh, horse.
- Yeah, I would estimate it is closing in on 100 pounds.
- My God.
- It's somewhere between 50 and 100.
- How is he currently transporting it?
- That's Jacob's breaking point with real women.
He can't do it.
(laughing)
- How's he currently transporting the thing?
- So he has a truck that has a lift on the back.
- Great.
- Then she rides in the lift.
- Stop it.
- Lovers her to the ground.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- From the back of the truck.
- But then he just carries her?
- Yeah.
- I'm not-
- And that-
- You saw the video, Paul.
He was just carrying her around.
- I'm not as-
- That's what we, I mean-
- I'm not as crazy as you think, guys.
I just hired this vehicle
that normally transports aquatic animals from zoo to zoo.
(laughing)
- I transport her via this sling.
- Yeah.
- If you think you recognize this swing,
this is the one that SeaWorld used to use.
You've probably seen this sling before.
- Got a deal.
Got a real deal.
- It was actually like some sort of a chair once.
- Okay.
All right.
- Yeah.
- So we're in there and we get to work.
All right, he's coming through.
Blah, blah, blah.
So he comes in and because this thing is so heavy,
he's got it tucked under the armpits
and he's kind of waddling in with it, you know?
- Oh, scuba nova girl is saying roller skates
and somebody needs to get through to this guy
and get him a pair of roller skates.
- No, but roller skates, she just whoop, boom.
She'd be on her ass every five seconds.
- He'd be doing like those-
- That'd be a real problem.
- He'd be doing like those weird like Scott dances
with her, you know?
Just like two in the legs and up and around and-
- You get a tripod, maybe we can talk roller skates.
- What'd you call me?
- Yeah, you heard it.
- So he comes in, he puts her behind a chair.
He tries to, apparently she's got wires
or some kind of armature in the fingers.
- Okay.
- So he tries to-
- She's got bendy hands?
- Bendy hands.
- He's gotta come from grip.
And he tries to get her to grip the back of the chair.
- Is this a ride?
- And then he stands to the side.
(laughing)
- The grip was apparently not good enough.
And you guys have seen the security footage.
- Yeah, Paul, it's a ride.
- She falls backwards.
(laughing)
And both eyes, boop, boop.
- Just both eyes just pop right out of the head.
- Like champagne corks.
- It was just like, boop, it's like a cartoon.
- Oh, they just fly.
- And then it kinda went another way.
- Like Christopher Cullum.
- What are the other guys in the room?
- Now this is indeed where he is not as crazy
as I think he is.
Because if he was as crazy as I think he was,
he would start weeping.
(laughing)
- Oh, right, right, right.
- And he actually did just kind of start laughing.
And he was like, "It's like, okay."
And this one guy went to kind of help him
and he was like, "No, no."
So he went and picked up,
"Let me be the one that touches this."
- Oh God.
- Yeah, let me.
- You don't want this on your hands.
- And apparently-
- Yeah, you don't touch it.
- And apparently, don't do that, sir.
Don't help.
- Somethings can't be undone, sir.
Back away.
(laughing)
- Sir, she's dead.
- They're supposed to be the sockets or the sockets.
God, this is just, it's worse.
The sockets are kind of packed with cotton or something.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause one of the little cotton balls also popped out.
And so he gets her back up,
but then she's there staring at the manager.
And she's got no arms.
- Oh, oh.
- And of course, I'm sitting there.
It's not my show, it's Chris's show.
And I'm just like, all of my years of improv just failed me.
I had no idea what to do in this situation.
- What do you do?
This is beyond surreal.
- I believe I would have literally fallen to the ground.
I believe I would be on the ground,
just right next to her.
My eyeballs might pop out as well.
I don't know.
- Yeah.
- This for you, by the way,
has to be a huge curve ball
because you've already volunteered to do something
maybe above and beyond at work.
And you've decided to, basically,
you decided to hop on the soldier grenade, so to speak.
You will be the front and back,
depending on how you're operating the room muscle
to basically keep awkward, bad conversations
from happening, right?
That's kind of like your MO.
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm just gonna--
- So that drop must have thrown you for a loop.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
Yeah, because again, it's not my show.
I just wanted to be in the room.
(laughing)
And so I'm just kind of standing back in the corner,
looking stern, you know, all right, how are you people?
Are you gonna, you know, give my boss here, you know,
any trouble?
(laughing)
And then that happens, and I'm like--
- He's gonna give my boss any trouble, you eyeless freak.
(laughing)
- Well, 'cause he was in with another old group of people.
He didn't go through a lot.
- Oh no.
- It was even weirder, was it?
- He was in like a general admission group.
- Everyone else in the room said that looks like fun,
and they started throwing themselves on their backs,
hoping their eyes would pop out of their heads.
(laughing)
- And we're just like--
- Seven people died that day.
(laughing)
It's a real tragedy.
- It's like the '80s movie moment of I'll make sure
this person fits in, you know, like, hey guys,
I also felt my back and my eyeballs fell out.
(laughing)
- Throwing your eyes out of your head is the coolest.
- It's a customer service.
We're gonna make sure--
- It's not cool if you fall down,
your eyes pop out your head.
(laughing)
- That's right.
- Oh my God.
- So--
- So this is the show, quote unquote,
has not even begun yet.
- Oh, the show has begun.
- No, I think Chris got a line of dialogue out
before the thing fell back in time.
(laughing)
- And then he was just like,
'cause Chris, do you guys know Chris Brown?
Local Las Vegas actors worked with--
- Oh, I don't know if we know Chris, I don't know.
- I'm not sure.
- I think he--
- It works with--
- He put some work on Rihanna, is that right?
- No, different Chris Brown, Paul, different Chris Brown.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- I know, he did the Hamlet with Matt Morgan.
- Oh, I do know Chris, I know Chris.
- I know Chris.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So he was just, I know, you know,
waiting for things to get back to some semblance of normal,
and then he did probably the quickest version of that show.
- Right, it's the same, you have to,
this show resets like every 20 minutes, right?
Like you can just run people through it.
- It's an experience, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Every 10 minutes, there you go.
- So the show just resets and you do the same show
like many, many, many times during the day.
It's gotta be weird to do the show right after that show.
Like you have to, like, there must be like a weird thing
where you're just watching yourself perform
'cause you're like, I shouldn't be just doing another show.
I should be talking to a counselor or--
- There should be some on-hand counseling.
(laughing)
- You have suffered a traumatic event.
I will contact the eyes exploding out of the robots
and counselor for you.
- Oh my God, and so we sent the group to the next group.
- I'm around real girl accidents all the time.
Here's my card.
(laughing)
- She didn't land on you, did she?
- The door's shut, and again,
it's the end of Chris's ship,
so I was in there to bump him out.
- Oh, it's the end of his ship, all right.
- And he was just like, he was just like,
oh my God, the eyes, they pop.
And we just, we were both just like,
what were we supposed to do in that situation?
- Did he find the eyes?
- Oh yeah, yeah, they were, you know,
they're white and on a dark carpet, they were, yeah.
I mean, you can actually see them in that security video.
- And he just picked them up and pocketed them?
- Yeah.
- He didn't worry about putting them back
in her head at that point.
What do you think? - No, no, no, no.
- Is this a video that we can reasonably post
on our Patreon, do you think?
Do you think we can put it on our Patreon, I don't know.
I want people to see this video,
but I don't think we can like reasonably share it.
- I don't think we can put it out in the public,
that's for sure.
- Yeah, I don't think we put it out in the public.
I better go to the Patreon, yeah.
- Probably not.
- We've had the same conversation over, probably.
- I'm sure, yeah.
- It's like, what are we doing?
- Yeah, you guys have to sign favorite nations
to make sure you split whatever money you make
off of selling that video.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, it was, it was just wacky, and yeah.
Yeah, Kristen.
- I'll just tell you now, Scoops, you know,
we owe you high fives when we see you in person.
I have access to the video, okay?
So we can high five. - Oh, that's true.
That's true, when you see us in person,
ask us to see the video.
- Matt, he'll show you.
High five, and then we'll figure it out from there.
- Yeah, that's exactly it, here.
- I just sold five more tickets to Jokers of Magic
for people, just 'cause they're like, all right.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I was gonna go to Wabash, Indiana, but now, let's go.
- Let's hit it, we gotta see this video.
- Yeah, that's hilarious.
- There you have it, another wacky day at the old opera house.
- January 23rd, another wacky day at the old opera house.
I'll be there.
- Holy smokes.
Well, thank you so much for sharing
your inside scoop with us, for sure.
Did you have a company debriefing about this event?
- Everyone kept their underwear on at all times, Matt.
- No, but I mean, it might've been as a company
worth checking in, that's the only thing I'm like.
- Well, like I say, are you saying post?
- Yeah, three, he's saying, oh, post.
- No, no.
- We just, I mean, there wasn't a whole lot to do,
I mean, the guy apparently had a great time.
You know, he went to.
- Was there any word about the other people
who went in the experience with him?
- They, I don't know if they were friends or not,
but they thought it was interesting.
- Featured on a bug for the ticket value?
- I will say those people probably got a much different show
than most people did.
I know that the guy at the end playing the unseen,
he goes, all right, everybody, let's move.
You pick up that sex doll and let's go.
(all laughing)
- Did any of the characters have to talk to the doll
like it was a person?
- He, yeah, and he would do things like,
like, yeah, this is the blah, blah, blah.
Oh, she says, blah, blah, blah, blah.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, does she?
- She is what I would yell as the character.
(all laughing)
- Oh, does she?
- Oh, does she now?
(all laughing)
- I'm about tired of you speaking for that woman.
I want to hear from her, sir.
- Let her talk for herself.
- I'm concerned for her safety.
- Oh, my God.
(all laughing)
- I mean, she's already had her eye popped out.
- You've already popped her eyeballs out, sir.
- You, sir, have disqualified yourself
as a proper custodian for this maiden.
(all laughing)
- I will be taking over custodianship.
- Unhand her this instant.
- Oh, my God.
- That's it.
(all laughing)
- I demand satisfaction.
- Preposterous, preposterous.
- Whatever Britney Spears' dad's thing was with her,
that's what I've got with that doll now.
I'm going to take care of her.
I can give her a better life.
- What's a shame now is simply that you've peaked, right?
Like, this is it.
There's no other story coming down the pipe
that's going to be like, and then this other time,
like you're done now with stories from work.
- Yeah, yeah, that's, that's, that is, that's true.
All the celebrity appearances.
- Yeah, you have to go to all the other ones first
and just keep hanging that one back
until someone really pushes.
- I just can't get over him fucking carrying the damn thing.
Like, put it in a wheelchair.
- That, that, I mean, the eyes popping out was just,
oh, my God, what do we do?
Him hoisting her up and then waddling back
and forth between the rooms.
That, that almost broke me right there.
I was like, close those doors, close those doors.
- No, I find the writing to be the Herculean effort here.
I don't, I sure, you waddle around a hundred pound weight.
It is the constant fabricating of dialogue in your head
that you are translating to everyone else in the room.
That to me feels exhausting.
- Doing some work, man, doing some work.
- Yeah, and like I said, the gentleman was not a young man.
So I guess he's getting his cardio in.
- Young man can't afford those things.
- That's true too.
That's true too.
Young man can only afford the torso.
- Yes.
- Did you get a whiff of any thing?
- What?
- Whiff?
Whatever do you mean, Paul?
Did it smell like anything?
- The smell had just been fucked a bunch of times?
Is that what you're asking?
- I didn't say that.
- Then what else could you be asking?
Did he like shove soup down his throat?
Like, what are you talking about?
- Oh, I don't know.
- It smelled like soup.
- Give her a little shot of Chanel or something.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He probably had a smell.
It smelled like soup.
- Meat bath?
- If it smells like soup, I'm calling the authorities.
(laughing)
I'm not saying that, that doll is clearly--
- What is that, Campbell's?
- That doll is clearly leaking cream of mushroom.
Get the cops in here right now.
This is disgusting.
(laughing)
Oh my God, would it be too much
if she's leaking cream of mushroom down her leg
and he's like, "Oh, menses, what are you gonna do?"
(laughing)
- Oh, I don't like having Professor Biggs on here anymore.
- It's her time of the month,
but my time of the mouth as he slurps it up.
(laughing)
- It's sure, he's basically a walking lunchable.
He keeps--
- Sir, that clearly has not been cooked.
- He keeps his snacks in there.
- That is clearly raw cream of mushroom soup, sir.
- Look, it's-- - Please don't eat that.
- It's human grade.
(laughing)
It's fine.
- Professor Biggs, where can people hear more stories
from you?
- They can hear them on the Fabulous Geek Shock podcast
at geekshockpodcast.com, or just Geek Shock.
We actually were able to finally get the geekshock.com.
- Just took a decade, a little more than a decade.
Finally got it all cleaned up.
- Yeah, it's fantastic. - Oh my God.
- Anything worth doing is worth taking 10 years to do it.
- Yeah, well, somebody was sitting on it,
is what the deal was, and we were talking about it,
and we just, on a spur of the moment,
I wonder if that guy's still sitting on,
hey, guys, it's free, click.
- Nice, nice.
- I have a friend sitting, a guy sitting on
great eyeballs of fire, is just sitting there,
and I can't wait for them to just
sell it to me at a decent price.
- I got someone sitting on cream of mushroom cooch,
and I don't know what I'm gonna do until I get it.
- And it is leaking out.
(laughing)
- Oh, I really wish she would stand up.
- No, it's not the episode title.
- Cream of mushroom cooch is not the episode title.
(laughing)
- Oh, I begged to differ.
- Oh, and Paul, you'll be happy to know that
I have been carrying on the legacy of
our own versions of situational awareness.
- Oh, great, fantastic.
- We're good heroes.
- We've had a couple of initiatives.
- The Lord's work.
- I think we all caught something at the experience
that just occasionally gets us, that's all there is to it.
- Yeah.
- Space herpes, space herpes.
- Yes, that's right.
- Shit.
- Well, thanks, Professor.
- Biggs, great to see you, man.
Thanks for coming on, man.
- Yeah, you guys.
- Thank you, pal. - Have fun.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Good Lord.
- All right.
- Let's do a little jock versus nerd.
(audience cheering)
- Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
(upbeat rock music)
Time for jock versus nerd.
- Explosion of cream of mushroom soup.
(laughing)
- I'm pretty sure it's wrong.
- Call the cops.
(laughing)
I'm just upset now.
- We got a scooper to come and do this today
from Swedish Scoop.
The categories are retro dances, phone numbers,
penile slang, and Beatles.
Paul, you're up first.
What you want?
- Give me that 2,000 penile slang, please.
- I'll give you that 2,000 penile slang for sure.
A British term for a stupid or contemptible person.
This is really just the tip.
- A knob end.
- A knob end?
A bell end.
- Bell end.
- Oh, come on.
- Oh.
- Come on.
- Aren't you a bell end.
- Oh my God.
Oh, I got smacked.
- It's me, I'll do retro dances for 400.
Chubby Checker taught us to do this dance
before doing it again the very next year.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I believe that was the twist.
- That was the twist.
Let's do it again.
- You did it again like you did last summer.
- That's twist again.
I need another hit song.
- I will do a penile slang for 400.
- Oh, I'd love to be an Oscar Meyer this.
- Mascot.
Weiner.
- Truck driver.
- Weiner.
- Paul.
- Penile slang for 1,200.
- Sure, why not?
- Gallus dominescus is one of the most common and most,
domesticus is one of the most common
and most tasty birds in the world.
The male is often called this.
- A cock.
- It's a cock.
- Cock is right.
- Rock out.
- Cock of the block.
- I'll do penile slang for 800.
I swear it isn't schlort.
It is slightly above schlaverage.
You could even say it is this.
- That's a good one.
- Oh, well I have schlong.
- Schlong.
- I do like that one.
- Schlong, schlong.
Nicely done with the word play on that one.
- Matt, you're up.
- Penile slang, please.
- You dick.
- Well, make something up.
I'll do retro dances, 800.
Domo arigato as you do this stilted dance,
a sub-genre of popping.
- The robot.
- A classic.
- Beatles for 400.
- This Beatles supposedly died in 1966
and was replaced with a lookalike
with the band dropping clues in later releases.
- Oh, it's pole, don't you know?
- Pole.
- Nope.
- This is the old dead man.
- It's me, phone numbers, 400.
Daily double.
Now for 1200.
Tommy Two-Tone told us to call Jenny at this number.
- Come on.
- 8675309.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- The fact is a lot of people,
maybe of our generation and older,
will use that as their supermarket codes,
things like that,
'cause they don't want to go with their real phone number.
- Oh really?
- And so oftentimes, if you're traveling--
- Oh!
- If you're traveling and--
- You're just gonna discount, just use that?
- They want to discount the supermarket,
you can use that number.
- Just put in the local area code and that phone number.
- Yeah, local area code and that number, yeah.
- There you go.
- All right, Matt, you're up.
- What a valuable tip.
- Penile slang, please.
- Penile slang.
- You cock.
(laughing)
- I'll do--
- Mushroom soup tip.
- I'll do beetles for 800, please.
- Ringo Starr replaced this original drummer in 1962.
- Tommy Smothers.
- That's us.
- Smothers.
- What was his name?
I've got, that is the question, I know, I know.
- Literally, the question.
- Oh man, fuck both my eyeballs.
What is the name?
- Todd Glass, Pete Best.
- Pete Best?
- Yeah.
- That's it, Pete Best.
- Pete Best.
- Shout out to Ravi for the clues in the chat.
- Oh nice, Paul, you're up.
- I will go, phone numbers for 2000, I'm shooting the moon.
- Oh no.
- Sir Mix-A-Lot told us if the butt is round
and you want a triple X throw down,
dial this and kick them nasty thoughts.
- Not 1-900-Mix-A-Lot, kick them nasty thoughts.
- 1-900-Mix-A-Lot, I can't believe
that was the $2,000 question, though.
- Oh my god.
- Believe it.
- Someone call the cops, the moon just got shot.
(laughing)
- Fuck the moon.
- I'll drop phone numbers for 1200.
- Call Whitehall 1212 if you need
the London Metropolitan Police, better known by this name,
it's also the location of its headquarters.
- Mmm.
- The, what are they called?
- Scotland Yard. - Ghostbusters.
Or Paul can just give you the answer, that helps.
- Right.
(laughing)
- Thank you for the hint, Paul.
- Scotland Yard.
(laughing)
- I was trying to get the Bobbies
and then figure out Scotland Yard from there.
I was still two steps away from Scotland Yard.
- Whatever, if Paul's playing Lifeline, I'm in, let's go.
- Yeah, right?
(laughing)
- I will do retro dances for 1200.
- Daily Double.
- Badoo, badoo, badoo, badoo, do, do, do.
- Now it's for 2,000.
- This hip hop dance shares a name
with a hugely popular '80s doll.
- Paul, what is it?
- Well, it grows in a garden.
- Okay.
The carrot dance. - Grows in the sun.
- You get real stiff and orange.
- This would be the Cabbage Patch.
- There it is.
- The Cabbage Patch, absolutely.
- Yeah.
- Paul.
- I'm gonna do the Beatles for 2,000, shoot the moon.
- We're gonna do the Beatles for 2,000.
Nobody help Paul.
Paul can't get any clues at all.
- That's fine.
- On the cover of Abbey Road,
this Beatle is the first in line and wearing a white suit.
- Pete Best.
- It's gotta be John.
- John is correct.
- You know, I'm going across the road first.
I didn't want to get hit by a car.
(laughing)
- He was always safety conscious that John was.
- We didn't close the road.
We just took the picture, you know.
- Oh, let's see.
Score check with three questions left.
Matt is winning with 4,000.
Paul and I are both on his heels with 3,600.
- It's anyone's game.
- It is anyone's game.
We got phone numbers, retro dances, and Beatles.
I guess I'm gonna go retro dances
and get the $2,000 question.
- Shoot the moon.
- Nervous about it.
I'm shooting the moon.
This '60s dance, popularized by James Brown,
is more than a gravy-soaked Thanksgiving side.
Dressing.
- Do the dressing.
- It is, of course, the dressing.
- And you might put it in clothes
and turn into the side and look at yourself in the mirror.
- He did the sweet potato.
He did the sweet potato stuffing.
- The corned hash.
The green bean casserole, as everyone knows.
- I can casserole.
- Papa's got a great new casserole.
- I'm gonna do the pumpkin pie.
Here we go.
- If you soak your pumpkin pie in gravy,
we gonna have words.
- Oh, it's so good.
- We gonna have good words.
- It's so good.
- Nasty, nasty, nasty.
- Gravy makes everything better.
- I got permission to take a gravy-covered pumpkin pie
to the John Wick experience.
- Don't drop it.
The gravy's gonna go flying out.
- You don't wanna know what's gonna pop out of that thing.
- Oh, Jesus.
- It's the mashed potato.
- Do the mashed potato.
- I don't know what is the actual move though.
What's the actual, I don't know the actual move
of the mashed potato.
- I think it's where you got two fists
and you pump them up and down.
- I only know that because of the scene
in the Blues Brothers at the,
oh, Ray Charles' song at the music store.
They do the mashed potato and that.
Yeah.
Matt, you got phone numbers or Beatles?
- I need both questions to catch you.
So I will take both questions, please.
- Oh, boy.
Good call.
- Beatles' phone numbers.
- Smart strategy.
- What is Paul McCartney's phone number?
- Damn it.
Pass.
- I will do,
- Eight, six, seven, five, three, oh, nine.
- Beatles 1200.
- It's two, two, two, two.
- This TV presenter introduced the band
in their really big shoe at Shea Stadium
after they appeared on his long running TV show
a year earlier.
- That would be Chubby Checker.
- No, Chubby Checker.
- Dick Clark's Rocking Stadium Concert.
- Dick Clark's Rockin' Stadium Eve.
- That would be Ed Sullivan.
- Ed Sullivan, of course.
- Charges really big shoe.
- And Paul closing out the category
and the game phone numbers for 800.
Call 588-2300 to reach this company
if you wanna lay down some carpet.
- Empire.
- Empire Carpet is correct.
And that is the game.
Oh shit, I win with 5600 points.
Matt is in second with 5200.
I definitely wasn't looking at that the whole time.
Matt's in second with 5200.
Paul's in third with 4400.
That's from the Swedish Scoop.
Thank you, Swedish Scoop.
That was a fun one.
- Thank you, Swedish Scoop.
That was a very fine scooperty.
- We haven't done that well collectively
on a scooperty in a while.
- No, that was really nice.
I even lost a 2000 point question
and still came up in the pluses.
- Yeah, right?
- That's crazy.
- If you wanna send us a scooperty
or a Price is Right jock versus nerd
or an obelisk jock versus nerd,
head on over to heyscoops.com,
heyscoops.com right there on the home page.
You can send us any of those jock versus nerds.
You can send us some scoop mail.
You can do everything right there at heyscoops.com.
Check it out.
- I wanna thank Annie for all of her years
of helping us out on this podcast.
- Thank you, Annie.
We love you.
You've helped us out so much over the years.
I truly don't think we would,
we definitely wouldn't be what we are,
and we would not be anything close to what we do
on the Patreon side without having had Annie
in our lives for all these years.
So thank you so much.
- I wanna thank Penn for creating this podcast.
Penn, you've done far less than Annie
in terms of doing anything for this pod.
I mean, really, just not pulling your weight.
- I think we might've done less for this pod than Annie
now that I'm thinking about it.
I wanna thank all the people who support us
on our Patreon page.
It is indeed a new month.
Or did you send us?
It is a new month, and we're trying to figure out
who's gonna do Annie's job.
So we don't have the list, guys.
We just don't have it.
- We just don't have it.
- I do have a text here from FedEx.
My cat food is coming.
But that's not gonna help this podcast at all.
I wanna thank all the people who do support us
on our Patreon page at all the different tiers.
We really appreciate it.
This is normally the part where we thank people
at a certain tier and higher by name or by scoop name.
If you want to be one of those people,
then head over to preachingfun.com and sign up today.
(upbeat music)
Come visit preachingfun.com
It's better than hanging with your mom at her bed
- Or if you never wanna hear the words
Cream of Mushroom Soup Coming Out of Paul's Mouth again,
go over to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts
- Is it just the word Cream of Mushroom Soup?
Or Cream of Mushroom Soup Coming Out of Paul's Mouth?
(laughing)
- That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com,
it does take you over to our Patreon page
where for as little as $3 a month,
you can help keep this show on the air.
We are dependent on our Patreon supporters.
So please, if you think this show is worth more than $0,
fartsinabag.biz, preachingfun.com,
that's where you can go to show it.
You can do monthly subscriptions,
you can do yearly subscriptions
and save a little bit of money,
and you can gift subscriptions to other people.
I still really like the idea of obfuscating people
via gifting them a Patreon subscription to this show.
- Yeah, they don't even have to ever know
that they're a Patreon if they don't want to.
(laughing)
You could just sign up your email.
- That just seems wasteful.
- That's fine, who cares?
But it really does make a huge difference for us
in our bottom line, and look how close we are
to bonus episode territory.
We could get that in February
if we just have a few more people joining us
to the Obelisk Scheme.
Remember, if you don't have the current funds
or availability to jump on our Patreon right now,
you can participate in the Obelisk Scheme.
It's as easy as one, two, three, look around the room,
find someone who you think shares your sensibilities
or might find this podcast
in the least bit entertaining and educational or funny,
and point them to our URLs.
Get them listening to Ice Cream Social.
Just one person though, just one.
It's not a pyramid scheme, it is an Obelisk Scheme.
So just find one person, and again, I've said it before,
I will say it once more.
If everyone within the sound of my voice right now
would simply get one more person to listen to this podcast,
we could almost double our audience.
- That's just.
(dramatic music)
- Math.
- Math. - All right.
- My dreaded and sworn enemy.
(laughing)
- Thanks for listening everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
- We'll see you soon.
(upbeat music)
See you at the cone, see you at the cone
- Hey, do you guys wanna go over to this other podcast
over here and hang out with them for a little while?
- Sounds good, you can leave us immediately after you go.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, come on over.
I'll take you guys over there.
- No. - For a reason fun.
- He left us. - See you later.
- Oh, you asshole.
Oh well, this is actually fun.
I like this podcast.
- This new one is nice.
(laughing)
- Bye. - You wanna start
another news side podcast?
- Here come the Hawks.
Get your tickets today and get in on the excitement
that is filling the United Center.
(crowd cheering)
Visit blackhawks.com/tickets before it's too late.