Reggie, I just sold my car online.
Let's go, Grandpa. Wait, you did?
Yep, on Carvana. Just put in the license plate, answered a few questions, got an offer in minutes.
Easier than setting up that new digital picture frame.
You don't say.
Yeah, they're even picking it up tomorrow. Talk about fast.
Wow, way to go. So, about that picture frame.
Ah, forget about it. Until Carvana makes one, I'm not interested.
Car Selling Made Easy on Carvana.
Pick up these, may I apply?
Hello everybody, it's time. It's time to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, preachingfun.com is where you can go.
Preachingfun.com, head over there.
Carvana is so easy, just a click, and we've got ourselves a car. See?
So many cars. That's a clicktastic inventory.
And check out the financing options. Payments to fit our budget. I mean, that's...
Clickonomics 101.
Delivery to our door.
Just a hop, skip, and a click away.
And... what?
No better feeling than when everything just... clicks.
Buy your car today on Carvana.
Delivery fees may apply.
That's it for today's video.
Thank you so much for watching.
We'll see you next time.
What?
No better feeling than when everything just... clicks.
Buy your car today on Carvana.
Delivery fees may apply.
The life you save may be your own.
Here's a program.
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great. Let's go.
[music]
Woohoo!
I'm down to the bone in San Antonio.
Oh!
Making the sound more fun than they are.
Yeah. I wonder if that's an expression or not.
True.
[music]
It's time for Matt Maddly's Ice Cream Social, sitting in San Antonio. That's Matt Maddly.
Sitting in Pittsburgh, that's Paul Maddly.
And in Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
We're pretty much in fun.
Paul, you get a lot of action on the World Series.
Yeah, I made all my money back by betting on the team that spent umpteen bajillion dollars to get a Japanese man who is an unparalleled phenomenon to just stand up there and do everything for them.
That was a surprisingly knowledgeable breakdown of the World Series, Paul.
I mean, you can't deny Shohei Atani. That guy is a once in a generation talent.
I know, but now you blew it because it was Yamamoto who was the hero of the World Series.
Who?
Different Japanese player.
We're back in the correct universe on the right podcast.
Great. We're good.
We'll just start it over. Here we go. Paul, you know who you're talking about, right?
Back to one, everyone.
[music]
Shohei Atani was amazing, but in game seven, he really couldn't hold up on short rest.
Yeah.
Taking that again. He had two hits, I think.
I think so. Something like that.
He only won them four out of the five games they needed.
He was an incredible player, but they gave the MVP to Yamamoto.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Yeah.
Different pitcher. He came in and played really well. Also, like we're all on short rest and yeah.
Like the Super Bowl, I made a lot of bets on the World Series this year.
Okay.
I think I had 12 different bets going. Like the Super Bowl, I somehow lost all of them.
Wow.
I didn't win a single bet out of all of my bets. Not one.
And I had a range of bets, but not a single one.
From safe to long shots?
I had weird bets. I had normal bets. Yeah. I had everything. I had parlays. I had singles. Not a one. I'm bad at that.
Well, you should know that I was talking to my friend Ryre about making different Marvel character cards for me as a magician,
because increasingly, I literally am going to stop doing the intro of my trick with baseball cards, saying who likes baseball?
Because the answer increasingly is no one.
There's very few people.
No one.
Nothing like starting a trick off with a light smattering of applause.
I just heard the latest episode of Player One just dropped, and Phil was remarking how his son came to him, his 13-year-old son just the other day, and said, "Dad, what's the World Series?"
Oh, man. Also, my kids came home, right? I got them psyched up in the morning. You know what tonight is? Game seven.
Oh, yeah.
All teams have one, three games each, blah, blah, and my youngest fancies himself a Dodgers fan out of nowhere. I think probably his friend in school likes the Dodgers. We've watched zero games.
Yeah, yeah. They're close to us. They're fine.
When I was like, "Game seven, the World Series," this is the time to watch, right?
Yeah.
So they're playing with their friends. They're not home in time. I'm watching the game by myself. Finally, they're ready to come home. I pick them up from their friend's house.
It is like the ninth inning, and I go like, "It's the ninth inning of game seven," and the Dodgers have come back. They were down four to one. Now it's four to three.
And they go like, "Cool." And they watch for like five minutes, and then one says to the other, "Do you want to play basketball?" And they go, "Yeah." And they get up, and they go outside in the middle of the ninth inning and go play basketball.
And I was like, "Mother..." And then I just started making them dinner or whatever, and then it goes into extra innings. So then I'm now serving them dinner during the extra innings, and now they're interested because we're sitting and eating.
Right.
And now they're all in. And then it ends up being a very exciting finish, and they were like amazed. And to them, they had an amazing game seven memory with Dad of watching the end of the World Series. And to me, I was just like...
They started watching it around like the 11th inning.
Exactly. I watched 10 innings without them. And then they came in, just top roped it at the end there.
I like that your memory of watching this World Series and their memory of watching this World Series are going to be very different, but involve each other.
Yeah. So I literally last night, I did this thing where I put baseball cards in a bucket, and I had this poll, and I bring it out to the people, and I just had five people shake their head no with me.
And they didn't want anything to do with the baseball cards.
Yeah. And I was like, "You know it's just the first and the last name, right?" It's not like...
You don't have to be a baseball fan to participate in this trick.
You're not going to be called into the baseball fan's court tomorrow to sign an affidavit about your ability to love and admire every baseball player.
So annoying.
Baseball fan's court.
I was doing a show last night, it was Tuesday, and saw a smaller crowd, which is fine. I'm out in San Antonio, seven nights a week for the old Magic Saloon out here.
And so I'm doing the show, it's a light energy, it's like a weird energy, right? Because it's not that full, it's a big space.
Oh yeah.
And I'm experiencing what we're talking about here, and I finally was like, I literally was like, "Hey, I'm sorry, you're at a magic show, you're going to need to like, I don't know, do stuff, like you might have to read a thing or pick a card or like get up and touch a thing or say a thing."
And I know that this is a burden. I know that this is outside your comfort zone.
I know you all came in here expecting to be comfortable jurists sitting in the back and mildly observing magic from afar, and I apologize that only 20 some out of you have showed up.
I'm going to need you to get outside your comfort zone and maybe do a thing.
Yeah.
And I get this big laugh, and then I mess with a kid with my rope routine, and then I feel like, oh good, even though it's a small crowd, they're eating out of my hands.
I got 'em.
And then I finish arm chopper routine. I go into looking for a couple, and as I ask for a couple, six people get up and just leave.
Oh.
Walk out.
Okay.
Shit.
I wasn't ready for that part of the story.
Neither was I, Jacob, because I felt like I had won the crowd back.
If I don't have an audience with me and then someone's like, "Okay, I'm having that bad night," when you feel like you've done the right thing, and then they're still like, "Never mind."
And when it goes from 26 people down...
They all looked at each other and said, "Hey, you want to go outside and play basketball?"
Yeah.
They go from 26 people down to 20 people, it hurts the energy of the room, so to speak.
It's a notable percentage.
I was really in my head finishing my show.
Oh, no.
And afterwards, someone goes, "Oh, no. Those six people are friends with one of the women who work here."
And they came by to visit because they had dinner reservations, and she invited them to watch the show, and they said yes, but then they had to leave because they had dinner reservations at 8 o'clock.
There you go.
Wish you could have made that clearer to the magician on stage.
I was like, "Do you understand that I, for all the reasons of the world, they did say this, but then you said that, and so I figured all about it." Do you understand the difference between people leaving because they had an obligation versus people leaving because they were upset with the show matters tremendously to the performer?
The only thing I want is for the audience to not actively hate me and leave.
Was there a moment...
It's really at the top of my list.
And possibly leave a negative social media review that reflects on the theater that I'm playing and all this other stuff.
Was there a moment before they left that you thought could have triggered them?
No. Just so that the energy was... It was a low-energy room, right?
It was simply that, you know...
Well, you did have the new... You had the new bit in the baseball card thing, right, where you pulled out your own bat?
Yeah.
I just showed it off, helicoptered it around a little bit.
I tap my penis on Mickey Mantle, like I do, and then boom, it becomes Ichiro Suzuki.
The most magic wand.
Ladies and gentlemen, foreskin Joe Jackson.
Yes, I did put as many baseballs as possible into my foreskin.
Oh, God!
It turns out the answer is six. Six baseballs were possible.
Six baseballs into his foreskin.
This is an old baseball folk song.
And then I play Bing Crosby and I say, "This is my sack of oranges."
Jokes on them because they're red when they come out because of the blood.
I actually had one of my quickest jokes ever.
I tried to say one woman's name. She was like, "You're wrong. You're completely wrong."
I said, "Give me your name." She was foreign. I said, "Well, then break it down for me."
And then she goes, "Pre." And I go, "Pre." And she goes, "Ush." And I go, "Pre-ush."
And she goes, "Yeah." And I go, "Oh, that's like Sean Connery driving an electric car."
Yeah, that's a good one.
That's real good.
I was like, "No one can walk out on that. You can't walk out on that show."
On a pre-ush?
It turns out that was incorrect. Pre-ush.
Somebody said, "Leaf? What the fuck? What?"
The room manager was like, "Hey, I know the energy was weird tonight. I'm going to fill a show report. Is there anything you want in the show report?"
I said, "Maybe if we're welcoming guests via staff, they should stay for the whole show."
I said, "Maybe that should be a policy."
Or sit inconspicuously in the back where there's a place where they could sneak out easily or something at the very least.
Yeah, or just give me a really big heads up about it.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe a white board in the back that you can see where if anybody leaves, they write down the reason that they're leaving on their way out.
I would have wrote it into the show. I would have found a gag.
Yeah.
You know? Like I'm not going to work with a couple. If anyone feels like that marriage is rigged for the government, please leave now.
Well, that was a combo of situations, right? I mean, that's, you know, when it rains, it pours. You got weird energy, lighthouse, a couple of people bail in the middle. It's like, "What the fuck?" Yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, you could look at it and say, "These people are leaving because they have dinner reservations, and so it's really not that bad of a thing."
You could also look at it and say, "This magic show could have been so good that they could have decided to not go to dinner, but they didn't."
Right. It would be amazing if they hard sold it and got to be like, "Honestly, that is enough magic." Like that was incredible.
That was plenty.
I don't want to taint it with another trick. I saw perfection.
Jacob.
I'm afraid that the only thing that I can do now is like magic less, so I should leave.
I'm speaking purely for myself here, but a free magic show would have to be nigh miraculous for me to not want to go get food instead.
It would have to be something on the level of like, "Oh, that lady just apparated through a wall and ate her own shit and threw a monkey 50,000 feet in the air, and then a bomb went off."
Or simply say, "If I cannot find your food, I will hand you a one-foot roast beef sub, and then you hang in the balance."
Wait a minute. Are we talking like a Subway sandwich?
What would be the meal to dangle for you, Paul? What would be the meal that I'd have to hold back as a magician to make you stick around?
To make me stick around?
Yeah, you might win this meal.
Oh, a Bobby? What about a Bobby, Paul?
A Bobby would probably work. I mean, there's a lot of stuff that would work. Like a fresh bowl of chicken and dumplings. Oh, Lord. Let's go.
I went to a place last night. It had a Southwest chicken and dumpling soup.
So it had like corn and beans in it?
Yeah.
I'm in. I'm in, in, in.
That sounds pretty tasty.
It was one of the most delicious soups I've ever had.
That sounds really good.
It was the place called the Foundry, San Antonio's oldest bar.
I went to my buddy Oscar, who works here. Yeah, yeah.
I had the day open yesterday, so I got me a rental car and I bolted down to our friend Brian Brushwood's compound over in Austin, Texas.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
And I was like, I can't wait to sit in on great night with my pals Justin and Brian. And Justin Robert Young was occupied.
He decided that he needed to be in Washington, D.C. or something on election day and couldn't be out.
He had dinner reservations.
It was an eventful day.
He was meeting up with six friends. Six friends at a restaurant in San Antonio.
In San Antonio.
It was an eventful day.
You passed him on the freeway.
So Brian's like, "Yeah, no, I just couldn't make it. This is perfect. So you can do a great night." I was like, "Okay, well, good. You could have told me ahead of time."
I was just going to be the two of us.
But if you listen to the latest episode of Great Night, it's just me once again trying to keep up with Brian Brushwood.
He is a very intellectual and smart person.
And so it's me doing my best to keep up with him.
We're doing it.
I am -- it's going from covert to overt.
But I am trying to coax Brian out of retirement as a magic performer.
His kids are starting to grow up. All the reasons why he stayed home are starting to go away.
And his stuff is so original and different and is not performed by anybody else.
And I am slowly trying to coax him into just maybe doing a live event or two.
Maybe we can get a straight magic performance from him at Scoop Fest next year or two years from now.
He did, right? How many years ago?
It was a long time ago.
He did. Yeah. And yeah, I'm trying to figure it out. I think we should try to play comedy clubs.
I don't think we should try to play theaters. That's my pitch to him.
I was going to ask, are you -- so you're pitching a duo thing?
I think so. Yeah.
You're not just pitching that he should go out on tour separate from you.
Oh, no, no. Yeah, no. Self-interest involved completely.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Great.
Yeah. Because as you know, I discussed this.
I talked to a friend who's a manager and said, you know, what does it take to play comedy clubs?
And they're like, well, if you have 500,000 YouTube subscribers or stuff like that, that helps. Blah, blah, blah, blah.
And so I'm trying to build up all my stuff with social media.
And then I looked and I was like, wait, Brian Brushwood has two channels that are over a million subscribers?
Yeah. Yep.
Also, I feel like he's very funny and we haven't seen him do his thing in a while.
So I was like, I don't know. So I've got to -- he's -- he's -- he's harrumping about it, I believe.
I left him going like, oh, that would be a life change kind of thing.
Aha. We'll see. We'll see. But I don't really --
Ah, Brian, I think you should do it. I think it'd be great.
One vote for yes.
Yep. Brian, I talked to your kids. They want you to do it, too.
Rodimus Scoop is already saying that Josie and the Betacucks could be the live touring band with your act.
That works.
All right. That would work.
Yep.
No, but we get to do it. I would love to do it as a one-off as an experiment.
And if it could grow into something that happened more often, then, you know, do all kinds of things like Ed.
Do you --
Ed Paul of The Mix, written improv set, and, you know, all kinds of stuff.
I'd love it. I'd love it.
Do you think that -- that Bonnie is the -- is the big tripping point because of Bonnie's hatred for you?
Do you think that could be part of it?
She just doesn't want me in charge of the meals.
Ah, that's good.
She just wants to make sure that Brian's eating salads and stuff like that.
Sarah's married to that guy? Jesus.
She basically said, "Don't eat all of Brian's food if I go." She said, "Don't."
Now, Matt, Brian needs to eat too.
Leave some --
You take care of him on the road.
Leave some food for Brian.
Brian eats first. #BrianEatsFirst.
You know who else eats first before Brian Brushwood? And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show, "Matt and Manny's Ice Cream Social," is brought to you by -- oh, man.
I just got a text as I went to look for the commercial thing.
No, no!
And it's distracting.
No, I'm back on board.
This is from Chasing the Dragon in 2025.
"Rim Tobin's 3-day course on infinite wealth, extreme health, and super sexiness."
That's Rim Tobin's 3-day course on infinite wealth, extreme health, and super sexiness.
I feel like this is a bit on Jim Jobin.
Hey, everyone.
Oh, it must be. It's Rim Tobin here.
I'd like to advise you on how you can make your life better, faster, and stronger in every single way.
Are you looking for that perfect sexual partner?
Are you hunting for that great job that will bring you wealth but also give you time for a life-work balance?
Are you also looking to get a 90-foot penis?
I can do all of these things.
Yes, the 90-foot penis is the number one thing.
First, get the 90-foot penis.
Everything else falls into place.
If you get a 90-foot penis, then you will get a job.
Someone will hire you to be the guy with the 90-foot penis.
You can stand at the top of a mountain and drop the 90-foot penis down, and people will just watch it, right?
And people will pay you.
That will be your job.
Now, as far as sexual gratification, a 90-foot penis is very difficult to actually get erect.
That's what people won't tell you about the 90-foot penis.
It's really hard to get enough blood into a 90-foot penis to get it erect.
It's not impossible, though.
It's not impossible.
What we've figured out is that...
I don't fuck people.
I repel them.
No, we can use...
Like, you know, we talked about slap-cooking a chicken.
Well, this could be used for that.
You can just whip that clip.
Boom.
It's 90-foot.
Oops.
How did you cook this chicken?
Via mushroom stamp.
Two problems.
Two problems with the 90-foot penis.
First of all, it is nearly needle-thick, so girth is gone.
Girth is completely gone.
Just like those taffy strings.
Yes.
Oh, no!
It's going to get tangled.
It looks like basically somebody pulled out hair gel and just kept going.
I knew when the genie winked, I would regret my decision.
That's it.
So there is no girth at all.
It's sort of like one of those filaments that they use for optic cable.
So that's problem number one.
Problem number two, of course, if you do get hard, it will exsanguinate your entire body.
Everyone buckle up because we know there are 11 problems.
That's one of the things we have to explain away, 11 problems with this.
There are only two.
Only two problems.
Only two.
They didn't pay for enough ad space for 11.
Fiber optic thickness and exsanguination.
That's it.
Rin Tobin.
That made me think of the Mummy and the Skeksis.
I guess there's going to be another Mummy movie, which is exciting to me.
Starring Brendan Fraser?
Brendan Fraser and Rachel Weisz.
Oh, they're bringing back the original team.
They're both on board.
I was definitely being sarcastic.
They're actually bringing them back, though.
They're bringing them back.
Did they do that Tom Cruise Mummy movie thing that they tried that one time?
That whole thing.
Where Tom Cruise rewrote the whole thing in editing and that it was just really not understandable at all?
Dark Universe did not take off.
What were there, three movies in that Dark Universe that just all failed to show?
We don't know what you're talking about.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
That was their whole plan.
It was a Universal Monster reboot.
They were trying to do a Marvel Super Heroes thing, and they called it Dark Universe.
Oh, that's right.
They were going to do all of the classic Universal stuff.
I forgot about that.
It was Mummy and Wolfman, which was Benicio del Toro.
And then what was the one with fighting around the world?
What's his fucking name?
Oh, Russell Crowe.
Guy Ritchie?
No, Russell Crowe.
Russell Crowe, fighting around the world.
I'm Russell Crowe, fighting around the world.
That was Piff the Magic Dragon for a second.
No, it was Russell Crowe.
Russell Crowe did...
Which one did he do?
I don't know.
Buddy, you just keep laying these out.
We're not in them.
It's part of the cinematic world.
Anyway, he might have also been in the Wolfman thing.
I don't fucking know.
But anyway, they only got two or three of them down.
Oh, he was Hyde and the Mummy.
That's it.
Okay, so he was going to be a Jekyll and Hyde, but it never happened.
Anyway, yeah, it all just shit.
It all fell apart real fast.
These people trying to make these big, you know, cinematic universes.
It's lightning in a bottle.
We talked about it before.
You're never going to get the same thing that Marvel got, which is not going to happen.
Well, this, you know, people complain about superheroes and blah, blah, blah, blah.
The bottom line is that years from now when we're studying films, from Iron Man to Endgame will be one of the greatest achievements of a movie studio ever.
Oh, it's incredible.
They had more success with that run of films than most movie studios ever have.
Yeah.
And they were the first thing of like, oh, would it be cool if all these movies built up to one big movie with all of the stars and stuff?
And it just never was able to be pulled off.
But you're seeing a lot of different types of movies come out now.
You know, so, you know, even with your horrors from your sinners to your weapons, at first we thought horror movies were done because no one was going to see them.
But now they seem to be punching up.
And now you're just seeing, you know, weird movies like One Battle After Another and then, you know, whatever the Channing Tatum with a guy stuck inside the store movies coming out like we're seeing like real swings for like different types of movies.
Well, Matt, you see the Aziz and Zari Keanu Reeves movie.
Oh, yeah.
I did see something.
Oh, and what's his name's in that, too, right?
Seth Rogen.
Yeah.
I am.
I'm sorry to say, Matt, that first movie I've seen in forever in the theaters I saw with you.
And unfortunately, our contribution to that film's box office numbers did not did not move the needle.
Fortunately, our contribution to that film's box office is measurable.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
They can count our dollars.
The math is easy to do.
They can absolutely count our dollars.
We know how much we contributed to that box office.
Good Lord.
On a percentage level, we could measure what we did.
That movie lost so much fucking money.
Well, it came out on the month where everyone dumps movies.
Right, but like this is the worst October in recorded history or something like that?
Yeah.
So yeah.
If you look at what it takes to make people go to the movie theaters.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
Like I don't ever go any none of the boxes.
I haven't gone in front.
Holy shit.
I'm looking up the numbers.
Springs.
They deliver me from nowhere right now.
Uh huh.
Yeah, it's a bad one.
The latest dailies.
The opening day was eight point eight million dollars.
Yeah.
That's a lot of money.
Not for a major film.
What did it cost, Jacob?
That was eight point eight million dollars over almost thirty five hundred theaters.
You know, they should have done, you know, like what Kevin Smith did with Red State.
I can't find the budget yet.
I'm looking for budget.
Yes.
You know, Kevin Smith at first just went out and did screenings and Q&A and sold tickets that were higher than movie price tickets to go just kind of check that out.
And then once it made.
He did a big podcast junket on that one.
He was on like a Corolla's podcast when it was brand new back in the day promoting that.
Yeah, you're right.
Like Springsteen, if you noticed, he showed up everywhere to promote this movie.
Every event that they had, especially played a few songs and people went nuts and all that stuff.
They should have done like a marquee theater tour of the of the of the movie.
And then you have spring scene there.
He gets to talk with more humor and three dimensionality about his battles with depression.
And then we don't feel like we just watched one giant downer.
You know what I think?
I think they should have made a different movie.
I already know I would have rewrote the movie.
I mean, it was shit compared to compared to what you've told me about him.
Even just like what Matt has told better stories about Bruce.
That's what I'm saying, like as soon as as soon as he told me that that lady was an amalgamation.
I might get the fuck out of here.
I don't understand. I don't understand at all.
Oh, I'm going to make up this lady that I had a relationship with and I'm going to come out looking like a fucking bag of dicks.
I'm going to look worse than almost anyone in filmic history.
That relationship, he just looks like garbage.
There's a legendary story of Jersey Boys when they're trying to get it made.
Right. And they sent a script over to Frankie Valley and didn't hear from him for a while.
And then finally they tracked him down and were like, Frankie, we're trying to get you.
You know, we're trying to get the final sign off on this version, you know, the script for the musical.
And he goes, you can't do it.
And they said, what? And he goes, you can't you can't you can't make this musical.
And they said, why? He goes, because some of the stuff in it, I don't I don't I don't like.
And they go, what don't you like? We'll change it.
And he goes, I don't know.
And they're like, what do you mean? You don't know.
And they go, you guys faxed it over.
My wife read it first.
She saw stuff in there she didn't like and she shredded it and put it in the garbage.
Oh, boy. Do you think that's what happened? Do you think Frankie Valley's wife shredded the script before Bruce could read it?
I'm saying someone should have set that movie script to Paddy Ski Alpha before Bruce got to read it, is what I'm saying.
Fucking shit. Well, Philip, the SC scoop is saying they should have Muppets in it.
I think if you went back and reshot the Bruce elements or just did away, found a way to CG Kermit in for Bruce, man, it could be really, really funny.
That would be a knockdown, hilarious movie.
If it's just Kermit being Bruce. Yeah, it's just Kermit the frog going through all that shit.
Oh, my dad hit me. Oh, God, the managers, both Bunsen and Beaker.
Oh, boy.
No, it has to be from this eight track cassette.
You don't understand. No, the sound just isn't there.
It just isn't there. Oh, I'm sorry, Piggy.
I have to leave you here next to the dishwasher and moved to California.
There's no way. Oh, oh, you bitch.
I'm leaving this one. Dishwasher crumples billows with smoke.
Gonzo pops out of the top with a chicken.
You guys don't understand that the artistic force behind Nebraska.
All of the electric mayhem is basically out of focus in the studio shots and no one cares.
Yeah, nobody would care. No, it doesn't seem to bother anyone at all.
Listen, someone who's still down about twenty five million dollars right now with the worldwide gross, not counting advertising budget.
So far, they've lost about twenty five million dollars and flying in, putting a Bruce for all these public appearances, probably doesn't cost that much.
But that's probably very inexpensive.
But as someone who is this huge Springsteen fan, I it did cause the release of this Nebraska 82 album.
Which is great. It is awesome.
It's a four disc album and one of them is just him rerecording the entire thing with his voice as it is now as an old man.
Yeah, hey, little is your daddy home to go and it's my favorite thing that I've listened to in a while.
I got a bad desire.
Oh, Fozzie's fired. Sorry, Fozzie.
Hey there, Scooter, is it time for work?
You better tell us on time, you jerk. Oh, yeah, I got a bad desire.
What do you call the East Street band selling Christmas decorations around the holidays?
I don't know. Tell me, big man.
Bruce Springsteen. That's pretty good.
That's that's that joke alone is better than the movie.
Matt Donnelly has a better Fozzie the bear impression than I would have guessed.
It's really good. It's very solid, pretty solid, very solid.
Well, it would make sense that he would have a good Fozzie to my Kermit.
That's right. That's true.
There you go. That's right.
Now we now we have another bit we can do in our shows.
Now if we play Pollywood Squares, I'll pop over one of those squares.
No, Miss Piggy wouldn't have put up with Bruce's shit.
That's right. Oh, yeah, yeah.
First time he's like, I'm depressed and answering the calls.
Miss Piggy be kicking in that door and karate chopping at four track player.
I'm out of here, frog.
I have things to do. This is bullshit.
I mean, as we listen, I don't know how many more people tuned into this this this this Zoom.
I'm much more famous than I was yesterday.
What happened?
I went on San Antonio Live and performed a magic trick for the morning host.
Oh, that's nice. How did it go?
You did the whole. This was like a like a morning.
Good morning. Whatever town show.
Yes. Good morning, San Antonio.
San Antonio Live is a good morning San Antonio show.
And it's my second time doing it.
The first time I didn't talk about on there because I basically almost fucked up both tricks I did.
And I just was like it just was pretty pretty mediocre appearance,
except that I was funny and didn't help sell out the rest of the week because I was funny.
Oh, that's good.
This time, is this your card? You're doing the cups and balls, sir.
So what they do is they have you come on and do like, hey, if you have a quick teaser trick, you can do a quick trick.
And then go to commercial break and then do a real trick with you when you come back.
Right. OK. And so last time I was there, I had like what I thought was a quick trick.
And they were like a mega tease.
And they're going to do like me plus someone there for a dog shelter,
plus someone there advertising their new store or something like that in town. Right.
And so we're all lined up and I'm doing this card trick as fast as I can.
And something I'm taking up all the time.
And they have to I get I get I get the punch line of the trick in just the last second.
They cut the commercial and I just stare at the person who's been just holding this giant dog in their arms waiting.
So sorry.
And so Matt adopted that dog out of guilt.
And so now Matt has a Mr. Biffles.
So this time I'm there and I have this like pencil, I can put a pencil through a bill and it looks like I rip it and put a hole in it and boom, boom, boom.
It's all it's the dollar is fine. Right.
But I literally was like turned to my friend Mia, who drove me down to the root, the manager here.
I said, tie me on this.
And and I did it as fast as I could.
And she's like twenty eight seconds and I was like, I won't do it that fast on air to try to talk.
So that one's out.
Oh, the time for the old miracle harmonica sounds.
All right. Perfect.
I just grabbed her little index card.
She's reading her facts off me and I made it magically sound like harmonica and handed it back to her.
We went to commercial break. No problem.
This is nice and easy.
I get down there, Brian, it turns out Brian Brushwood is about to start selling the harmonica trick, the invisible harmonica trick on.
Oh, good.
Because I because I need one of these.
He was like, and so I just talked to him today and he's like, he's like, hey, are you willing to film a testimonial?
I was like, am I? I've just been doing I've been doing a testimonial for some magic trick for months.
The fact that you could profit from it's even better.
Yeah.
I think it's funny because the reason why Brian might be selling this probably because it's ruined popularity.
And I really think I am instrumental in the popularity of this magic trick.
You are definitely you have created a cult following for this magic trick for sure.
I really have.
Like I don't often take credit for things, but this one is like I definitely blew it up at Magic Live and sold it out at Magic Live.
And that's kind of created a wave of people using it or talking about it in magic circles that something they're using looking for more places to sell it.
They approach Brian.
So all right.
New business idea.
Every Magic Live, Matt decides what new trick is going to be the huge new seller.
We then sell said trick.
Matt Donnelly, the kingmaker.
Yeah.
This one looks like your nose is made out of rubber and it stretches out and snaps back.
All right.
Like a rubber booger?
You pull a stretchy booger out of your nose?
Stretchy booger is the worst clown I ever hired.
Stretchy booger? He was?
Aww.
Hi Matt.
Oh, stretchy booger.
Whoa, stretchy booger.
That was out of your pants.
I know.
You have some new material.
Oh, what material?
I'm afraid you've moved on from snot to some other kind of material.
Foreskin.
Foreskin?
Yours is more like fiveskin.
Did you have some kind of 90 foot penis going on in there?
Good lord.
Yes, but it's very thin.
Oh, yes.
I see.
Oh, I have to make a long distance phone call.
Can I use some of your fiber optic cock?
No.
Don't get roaming charges.
Oh, that's the least of my worries with your wiener.
You know who else thinks I have a dirty wiener?
That's the following sponsor.
Today's show, Matt and Manny's Ice Cream Social, is brought to you by Big Jerry's House of Hoarding.
That's right.
Store all your collectibles with me, Big Jerry.
That's from Dead Lazlo in 2022.
Hey everybody, it's Big Jerry. How's it going?
Somebody bring me some more cake.
Hey, anyway.
Come on over to my house of hoarding.
I've got nothing but places to put stuff and places to leave it.
If you've got something you don't want anymore in your house, come on and bring it by.
It'll be fine.
Oh, I just had a bunch of magazines fall over and kill another cat.
And her hay scoops a check.
Oh, that was my cat.
Meow.
Big Jerry.
That's a big guy.
So I did a bit I did when I do close-up, which is one of my favorite kinds of tricks for you.
Look at an envelope I put in my pocket. They pick a card.
Suddenly I'm not holding cards in my hand. I'm holding the envelope and in my pocket is all the cards.
And then boom, inside the envelope is their card. It's a miracle.
Something goes wrong with TV magic no matter what.
I described, almost messing up the last time I was on, even when I did the arm chopper, it got caught for a second and then went through and it was a moment of panic.
I'm trying to troubleshoot, I'm trying to brace them, all the little things that go wrong with this. There's a lot of little touches to this trick.
Anything that happens in plain sight, so to speak.
I'm anticipating all of it.
And then I just go to get the card out of the pocket and I just can't get the card out of the envelope.
I'm just sitting there like, pick, pick, pick, pick, just jammed in there, just can't.
It's an envelope that's like the size of a playing card, right?
Yeah, exact size of a playing card.
And so I'm trying to slide it out and I'm just like, oh, all the days.
The only thing that's going wrong is the actual punchline of the trick, the actual payoff, that's the only thing being delayed here.
I'm picturing dropping all the cards on the ground by accident. I'm trying to picture it accidentally.
I've done this thing where I've accidentally pocketed the whole thing where I'm supposed to keep a gimmick in my hand.
I put everything in my pocket like a fool. All kinds of things.
And then it's like, oh, it's going good, it's going good.
You forgot to grease up your card.
I forgot to grease up my card. Yeah, I got to butter up my envelope.
Well, everybody forgets something once in a while.
I had a little bit of time off after our trip to decompress.
And so I've been trying to, you know, just kind of straighten up the house a little bit here and there, got some stuff done.
You do look very decompressed.
I feel decompressed. But I went out and cleaned up the Halloween decorations.
Nice. And I was like, you know what? I better put the Christmas decorations out or they're not going out.
And I did it. I got the Christmas decorations out the same day.
Whoa! Wait, you've decorated for Christmas?
We are already decorated for Christmas. We've got our five illuminated corgis.
It's not crazy. It's not a big thing.
It's just five illuminated corgis and a little strobe laser that shoots on the house and makes sparkly Christmas colors.
And that's it. All right. Yeah, done.
And it's running? It's all cooked and lit?
Our neighbors across the street still have all their Halloween shit up.
I was like, I did it. I beat them to the punch.
And what's cool is now driving through the neighborhood, this is four days later, three days later, since I got my stuff set up.
I'm starting to see other trees. I'm starting to see wreaths on doors.
Oh, you started it. You started the Domino Hall day.
I put the word out. I was like, it's on this year, y'all. Let's go. Let's put it up.
And I also... Did I tell you guys about... The things that you two have influence over. Magic tricks and Christmas decorations.
Did I tell you guys about the goose that Ann got last year?
Yes. She refurbished it, right?
No, that was the gnome. So this was a goose.
Ann had always wanted a big old concrete goose because it's just one of those things, right?
Oh, thank God it's concrete.
But what can you do with a concrete goose except dress it up, right?
That's the whole thing, is you have a goose.
What can you do with a concrete goose? What can you do with a concrete goose?
What can you do with a concrete goose? I can put a hat on it.
That's right. Well, I finally got the set of costumes for the goose.
So now...
How does one shop for goose costumes?
Go online and type in "costumes for goose" and you will get unlimited replies because people dress up their goose all the time.
It comes up quick and easy. Jacob's going to the internet.
Oh, wow. It's up. There's a lot of costumes for goose.
And so I looked and found a reasonably priced set and I went for it and it has not let me down.
Yeah. As a matter of fact, I believe...
Yeah, I purchased one...
No, I didn't go there. That's just one.
That's just one costume. That's high end right there.
That's a Piff the Magic Dragon goose.
Yeah, that's pretty great.
It's a Goose the Magic Dragon.
Well, our goose now has full different stuff for every holiday.
So I already did the pumpkin on it, did a jack-o-lantern.
It was outfitted with a turkey. Now it's a goose that looks like a turkey.
Also, the goose is named Duck Duck. That's the goose's name. Duck Duck the Goose.
So Duck Duck was actually...
He is our memento from the Michael's Craft Store where we bought it.
And it's just one more sort of emblem of the fall of capitalism and the end of all brick and mortar mom and pop shops.
So, yeah.
So it's a turkey now? Do you already know what you're going to do for Christmas?
Oh, yeah. He's got a Santa outfit.
He's got a Santa outfit. Then he's got a winter snowflake for January.
Then he's got a big heart for February.
Then he's got a leprechaun suit for March.
Oh, God. There we go.
April, I don't think there's anything like April, May. I think it kind of gets sparse.
July, he's got a...
Oh, come on, Matty Glee.
I'm telling you, it's only so many costumes.
We need April and May.
Easter Bunny.
Oh, I'm sorry. There is an Easter Bunny. There's an Easter Bunny.
There's a Fourth of July Uncle Sam.
And for May, you should dress it up either as a stormtrooper for May the Fourth Be With You.
Yeah. Oh, that's good.
Or may dress it up like Justin Timberlake.
Just staple some ramen to its head.
God, that guy fell off so hard.
Nah, he's great.
What a chump. No, he's a chump. He's a chump. He's the definition of chump.
Come at me, Timberlake, you chump.
We actually didn't talk about Halloween yet, did we?
No, I was about to ask you about Trunk or Treat. Trunk or Treat and Trick and Or Treat.
Oh, man.
I think we talked about Trunk or Treat already.
Trunk or Treat, we talked about it, yeah.
I had an awesome Halloween, so my sister-in-law came up.
She brought a big old bunch of Dum Dum suckers, and we had enough candy.
We only had about a hundred...
You said, "No, I'm already here."
We only had about a hundred Trunk or Treaters, which was down from previous years, but it's still a lot.
Oh, you know, tariffs.
Dude. And then we surprised her, and we went right after the Trick or Treaters were done.
We put everything away, and we jumped in the car and ran to the Pittsburgh Zoo,
which was having their Halloween Jack-o-Lantern Festival.
Okay.
Jack-o-Lantern Extravaganza. I believe this is like the third annual one that they did.
It's like a giant ookie-cookie, but with pumpkins?
It was remarkable. This thing was incredible.
They had thousands and thousands of Jack-o-Lanterns throughout the zoo.
It was wild.
Okay.
You could get pictures taken.
There was a witch.
Paul has pictures of various Jack-o-Lanterns.
There's my spooky picture of our house. It turned out really good.
I'm going the wrong way here.
But yeah, there's me doing the classic with a skeleton doing the classic.
Okay.
They did these really ornate Jack-o-Lanterns sculpted by hand, and it turns out they had like 30.
What you're showing me is not sculpted by hand.
It is.
No.
What's that Pittsburgh sign?
Dude, these are cut out by artisans.
It's like carved into a pumpkin.
Yes.
It looks like somebody just put a picture on top of a pumpkin and it's lit up, but it's like carved into it.
It is carved into it.
They do use a stencil, but then they carve.
But yeah, there's like a marker for some of the darker stuff on it to make it really...
But there are like 30 artisans carving these fucking pumpkins every day.
And because it's the zoo, there's a lot of animals.
But it is wild. It is fucking wild.
It is incredible.
It's really beautiful.
I'm just wondering how much more care the animals could have gotten instead of taking all this time to carve these fucking pumpkins.
The animals are all away.
There were no animals out.
The only animals we saw were some flamingos that were sleeping in their own little thing.
The worst zoo ever.
Jules and Vincent.
Pulp Fiction.
Yeah, it was really cool.
It was amazing.
And I didn't even get any images of the grand finale.
It was too overwhelming.
There had to have been, I don't know, 10,000 fucking LED filled jack-o-lanterns that were timed out to music.
And they were playing shit like Renegade and stuff.
And it was all timed out to the music.
I'm telling you, it was out of hand.
They were playing Renegade.
They were playing Renegade and it was timed out to the music.
Yeah, Renegade by Sticks.
Yeah.
I believe that's the right word.
The word is out.
Is that how it goes?
Yeah.
The word is out.
They finally found me.
Yeah.
I'm a wanted man.
I'm a wanted pumpkin.
Yeah, it was out of hand.
And it was just this huge wall that stretched for like a half a mile.
It was nuts.
It was extremely cool.
That was pumpkins.
It was pumpkins.
The kinds of things, if you get a chance to look up the Pittsburgh Pumpkin Extravaganza,
just go ahead and look it up anywhere.
But the Pittsburgh Zoo Pumpkin Extravaganza, there are...
Do not look it up at work.
It is much dirtier than you think it is.
There is some NSFW stuff in there.
No, it was really, really cool.
It was good.
It was, I mean, like really, really fun.
And we went just at the last two hours of the show and it was nice and dark.
And so everything was super shiny in the light.
And then Ann kept telling me, "No, these are real pumpkins."
I was like, "Nah, these are plastic."
Because a lot of them were plastic.
But then she was like, "No, these are real.
These are real."
And I was like, "Bullshit."
Turns out every three days they have to reshave those pumpkins because they go south of cheese.
And so they got artisans in there just cranking out pumpkins all the time.
I am so far out on that gig.
And they have a huge crew of artists going and sculpting these pumpkins every fucking year, every fucking couple days.
It was wild.
Oh, that is painful.
And just like you, Matt, the guy who is the head gourd carver made an appearance on Pittsburgh Today Live or whatever it is.
And he was on there showing off his pumpkin carving skills.
So yeah, it was really something.
So I had a really fun Halloween.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
Also, like Matt, there was a guy trying to have a dog get adopted just off camera while the guy was carving the pumpkin.
They ran out of time.
They had so much good shit at this pumpkin fair.
They had a big s'mores spot with an open fire.
I know.
Six people from my show showed up at the pumpkin patch.
They left my show and went over there.
Well, they were excited.
They had s'mores to eat.
They had s'mores reservations?
Shit.
Holy shit.
I'm sorry.
We have reservations for s'mores in Pittsburgh.
It's only about a 25 minute drive from my house to get to the zoo.
So that was really great and really fun.
Are you going to start frequenting the zoo more often?
We've gone for a couple special events now.
And so I think we'll continue to do so.
They put on a real fun show.
Yeah.
All right.
I was overwhelmed by the amount of work and detail and fun that went into that pumpkin display.
I thought it was going to be ho-hum, but it was really...
I mean, I'm overwhelmed by your description of it.
So I can just imagine how you feel.
I wish I had it handy.
But if you get a chance, please look up Pittsburgh Zoo Jack O'Lantern Extravaganza.
Do not look it up at work.
And just look up that finale.
Yeah.
It's a very quick URL.
Falls very easy call to action.
Pittsburgh Zoo, pumpkin, Extravaganza, finale, LED, timed out wall, renegade.
Yeah.
.org.
That's how you got to look up.
But it was amazing.
Just amazing.
It's one of those things that when you're there, I purposely was like, I'm not recording
this.
I'm not taking pictures of this part.
I'm just going to experience this.
And it was really, really cool.
Rich Scoop in chat says, do not go to pittsburghblumpkins.com.
Oh, that's our new Patreon site.
Oh, shit.
Speaking of pittsburghblumpkins.com, you remember we gave away with our prizes galore, we had
some dude wipes that were holiday themed.
Pumpkin scented dude wipes.
Yeah, they were pumpkin spice dude wipes.
They were dumpkin spice.
That was the whole thing.
Dumpkin spice.
Well, they've got a new flavor coming out for the holidays that we just started getting
in at the Tarzai.
Oh, no.
Dingleberry.
What?
Dingleberry dude wipes are the holiday version.
And they're Christmas themed?
They're Christmas themed and they're called Dingleberry.
Oh, jeez.
It's kind of nasty.
I'm mad that they're skipping Thanksgiving.
I want stuffing scented wipes.
Stuffing scented wipes.
Oh.
Nice cranberry sauce.
It'd be cranberry.
C-R-A-M.
Cranberry.
You can just jab them up there.
Just call it giblets.
Oh.
It's better than fucking jingle balls or whatever the fuck they actually are using.
Dingle bells.
Yeah, giblets is better.
Matt, you had a fuck ton of kids at your house the other day.
Also, there was Halloween.
You came during a rush.
Jacob actually came by the place and we were running.
I did.
I ran by on my way to work.
Jacob came by right when I had about nine kids line up for levitation videos.
Oh, wow.
Not happening throughout the whole night.
But I did more levitation videos this year than last year.
I think last year me dressed like Satan really discouraged some people from stepping up and doing it.
And so this year I was dressed like Elvis and a bunch of parents got videos of their kids floating in the air with me running the hoop over their bodies and stuff.
That's cute.
I hung out with Matt's neighbor and we watched Matt doing the levitation videos.
Matt around kids and their parents doing these videos.
You can tell that Matt deals with school children on a regular basis.
It is spectacular to watch.
Yeah.
One is I don't touch them.
No, you don't touch.
I noticed that.
You don't touch the kids at all, which, you know, not how Paul would do it, but still fine.
Well, I wouldn't talk to him.
I get the fuck out of here.
Get out of my yard, motherfucker.
And then my buddy Tony was drunk with power running the clown jump scare.
He was.
So I think we last thought it was broken.
My neighbor, Gary, and I helped Gary, who abbreviated my car together.
He helped fix my clown illusion, and we discovered what happened, of course, was my fault.
So there you go.
So my buddy Tony's running the jump scare of my kids trick-or-treating.
My kids like running the clown jump scare when they got back from trick-or-treating.
Sure.
I don't think, Jacob, you weren't there when my oldest got back from trick-or-treating, right?
No, I was not.
I didn't see your kids.
The rule was basically don't jump scare little kids.
Sure.
Jump scare teens.
And even that backfired.
I tried to -- one kid I thought was older than he was, I made a kid cry.
I gave him all of the candy.
I just said, here, take any and all.
One was a group of teenage girls.
They came up.
We jump scared them with the clown.
And she literally just looked down and hugged herself.
And then four friends said, okay, we're going.
And the four friends just marched her off.
It was the weirdest dramatic reaction.
I am done.
I'm done.
I don't give a fuck.
I sit out in my yard.
I sit out in my place dressed up like a creepy fucking skeleton.
I was going to say, Paul does get mad that people aren't scared at Halloween all the time.
I do.
It's a fucking scary holiday.
It's supposed to be scary.
It's about the dead.
It's about the horrors.
I get so mad.
It's not Christmas.
It's all a fucking ween.
A couple of times we were going to go take a video of them levitating.
And also the jump scare happened with the clown.
And they went like, oh, wait, this is rigged.
I'm leaving.
And they pass on the levitation thing.
And I'd be like, no, no, no.
So at one point, I was levitating people.
And then a kid jump scared.
And then all of a sudden, my kid goes back for trick-or-treating at the same time.
It's like a big hubbub in my driveway.
And then suddenly a little three-year-old starts walking towards the candy, which is right next to the clown.
Next to the jump scare, yeah.
That's next to the jump scare, yeah.
And the parents go, whoa, whoa.
And I go, no, no, no.
We will not jump scare the little kid.
Right?
No, no, no.
And then Tony, my buddy Tony, was also going like, no, no.
We're good.
Have her come get candy.
Yeah.
My son--
Because Tony was drunk with power on the jump scare.
But I was watching.
He was getting the big kids.
Yeah, yeah.
We were just doing the big kids.
Yeah, no.
So he-- and so we do that.
But my son doesn't see the little kid.
He only sees the teenagers behind the little kid.
Oh, no.
And he wasn't paying attention.
So he slides over.
So in front of a giant crowd, of which we-- me and Tony, both were going like, don't--
No, no, no.
You'll be fine.
Do the jump scare.
And then boom.
You like sex a bit.
And then the one horn blasts some three-year-old kid.
Yeah.
To which we all just turned to Keeler.
We're like, yeah.
Just screaming at him.
Your poor son, I'm sure, was just mortified by it.
He was like, what?
We pointed.
He was like, oh, I didn't see them.
The table was above.
I couldn't see the kid below the table.
And I was like, it was all we were talking about.
Yeah.
So that was maybe the low point of the clown jump scare there.
Oh, disagree.
Disagree.
Did you get-- did you see our giant skeleton?
Did you see our 12-foot skeleton?
You have, on your property, something that you now own is a giant skeleton.
Wow.
My sons are begging me to just put a Santa Claus hat on it and leave it up through the
holidays.
It's the way to go, man.
It's the right move.
They're right.
Really, it's got to be a 365 skeleton.
You make him 11.
Also, you don't have anywhere else to store it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you got the HOA.
That's going to be trouble.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Unless there's a bylaw in there that says what kind of decorations you can have out
for holidays.
I think you're safe.
So at the end of the day-- this is the first Halloween where I decided to calculate how
many pounds of candy I bought.
I used to just measure in bags, and then I cost-code myself, and it turns out I had bought
50 pounds of candy.
Oh, yeah.
There was a question in the chat earlier about how much of your giant haul of candy do you
still have remaining?
I was able to unload between truck and treat, which turned out truck and treat, they actually
offered candy for you to give out.
Damn it.
Which I was like, that's something I should know ahead of time.
I wish that had been in the email.
Instead, I refused to be subsidized by the government for my candy supply.
I decided to lift my own trunk up by the bootstraps and provide my own candy.
I was able to unload 30 pounds of candy.
Whoa.
That is no small amount of candy.
That was like-- normally, you start off with a candy.
You go like, oh, just take one.
And then all of a sudden, you realize how much candy you have.
You're like, go ahead, take more.
I had it.
I'm all-- from the beginning of Halloween to the end, I was like, grab a handful more.
Go for it.
Be selfish.
Be a jerk.
And still, I turned out 50 pounds of candy was too much candy to have.
So you're ready for next Halloween.
How much was left over?
20 pounds.
20 pounds of candy.
All right.
Are you going to take it to the food bank?
Yeah.
Food bank meaning my mouth.
That's right.
Bank that food.
Bank it.
Go.
Yes.
So yes, I'm going to find a place to donate it.
I obviously go right up to San Antonio.
But I will find a place to donate candy when I get back.
Nice.
Yeah.
Funny thing, as a running bit, when it came up my house, I held up a bucket of candy, said,
trick or treat, just to keep giving it away.
And that was successful.
People still take candy when you offer it to them.
Oh, yeah, they will.
I was still unloading candy the next day.
I saw one of the best little TikToks I've seen in a long time was Black Barber Shop.
And the barber would get done with the haircut.
And then right before he takes the bib off, he'd grab a bucket of dumb, dumb suckers and offer a sucker to the client.
And the client would inevitably just crack up.
But then they'd take a sucker and they were loving it.
It was just the sweetest thing.
It was the nicest thing.
It's like we should offer each other candy in social situations much more often.
I remember, you know, when you went to your grandma's house, you got candy.
It wasn't a special day.
Exactly.
There's just such a dish.
We don't have such a dish for a reason.
Exactly right.
I think I need to keep a more active candy dish in my home that I specifically think about for guests, not just for me.
Yeah.
A guest dish.
A guest dish of candy.
Paul's stage in the world.
Not with the nasty stuff.
But he started his hero's journey.
I have, you know, I do this for the...
The biography will look back at this moment.
For the betterment of the world.
Rich Scoog, give me a good idea.
I should get in a white panel van, drive around, find kids who maybe don't have candy and offer them candy from my van.
Oh, that is, it's like a traveling food bank.
You know what ruined the candy dish?
Bitto honey.
Bitto honey ruined the candy dish.
That and that hard shit that just melds together into one candy glob.
Yeah.
That shit was nasty.
What my grandma had, which was great, was she had the little Kraft butterscotch squares.
Oh yeah, those are good.
Holy shit.
I used to eat those by the pound.
I know you can't tell, but I did.
I fucking love those things.
Yeah, my grandmother was a Werther's Original person.
I love me some butterscotch.
These were basically like Werther's Original, but you didn't have to work for it.
This was like, you just unwrapped.
They were the kind that you would use in baking if you needed to, right?
You just unwrapped a little square.
Oh my God.
I love those fucking things.
Excuse me.
You guys want to do a little Jock vs. Nerd?
More than anything in the world.
Let's do some Jock vs. Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Time for Jock vs. Nerd.
Explosion of butterscotch candy.
Biddle honey.
No, not Biddle honey.
We're going to Scoopity coming down to us today from Hoopy Fruits Scoop.
Hoopy Fruits Scoop.
You don't know what I got.
That's vaguely familiar.
What's that referencing?
Little Dooscoop.
Anybody know?
No, Hoopy Fruits.
I don't know.
Hoopy Fruits.
Hitchhikers, I guess.
Scoop Jesus is saying.
Hoopy Fruits.
Oh, okay.
After 12 years and 1800 performances, Rating the Rock Vault will close in Las Vegas at
the end of this year.
Less than 10 shows remain at the Hard Rock Cafe at the Las Vegas Strip.
Ticks available at ratingtherockvault.com.
To herald the end of the show, here's a Scoopity.
So it is a Scoopity, I guess, about the show Rating the Rock Vault.
Let's see.
The categories are Rating the Rock Vault.
All right.
Paul, you're up first.
What you want?
I'll go with Rating for 1200, please.
All right.
Rating the Country Vault ran for six years in what city?
Vegas.
Rating the Country Vault.
Yeah, I think it happened in Vegas.
Okay.
Branson, Missouri.
Okay, well, it didn't happen in Vegas.
Las Vegas of Missouri.
It ran in Vegas, though.
I think it showcased here, yeah, a little bit.
Let's see.
I'll try Vault for 400.
If you jump to the end of the show, what Van Halen song closes the show?
That would be Panama.
If you jump to the end of the show, the Van Halen song at the end of it is Panama.
I don't jump.
There you go.
It's possible that I have a bit of an unfair advantage on this Scoopity.
I might have seen Rating the Rock Vault more than you two gentlemen have seen it.
Well, yes.
I've seen it like three times.
No, you've seen it a handful of times.
Maybe four.
Yeah.
I will do "the" for 400, please.
Name any two Las Vegas properties that have hosted Rating the Rock Vault.
The Rio and the Hard Rock.
I love it.
Yeah, Rio and the Hard Rock.
LVH Westgate, Tropicana, Hard Rock Hotel, Rio and the Hard Rock Cafe.
Wow.
Absolutely.
Paul.
That show got around.
It did.
Rating for 2,000.
I've got to get back on the board.
What is the maximum capacity of Allegiant Stadium for a concert plus or minus 10,000?
35,000, isn't it?
I think you're low.
Oh, God.
All right.
Well, I'm going 35,000.
72,000.
Shit.
My butt.
Okay.
I would have been low, too.
I would have been 60,000.
72,000 people?
Yeah.
It's very big.
I guess.
I'll be the first to tell you.
It's very big.
Jinkies.
That's me.
I'll try Rating for 400.
Raiders of the Lost Ark came out in what year?
Plus or minus two years.
Let's see.
That would be 1980s.
That's '80s, right?
1980.
I think it is '84.
No.
You think it's '80?
Yeah.
All right.
I'll back it up.
I'll go '82.
I'll get the plus or minus four.
Two years.
'81.
Right in the middle.
There you go.
Matt.
The for 800.
I crushed the first one.
What year did Rating the Rock Vault start in Las Vegas?
Pass.
It passes to Paul.
Also, we couldn't get a window on this one.
2011.
2013.
Poop, poop, poop.
Oh, you were close.
You were close.
I was close, but not close enough.
Wrong, but close.
Paul.
Rating.
Why don't I keep killing myself on Rating?
Which year did the Raiders start playing in Las Vegas?
Plus or minus one year.
2020.
2020 is absolutely correct.
We know that one.
Yeah.
That was the year everything went to shit.
Well, how so?
The Raiders.
The Raiders moved to Las Vegas.
It's all took.
Let's see.
I'll try Vault for 800.
Who originally wrote and recorded My Generation?
Linda Ronstadt.
Linda LOD.
You want the name or just the band?
Like the name of the person or the band?
Because I don't know who wrote it.
Gloria Estefan.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's Gloria Estefan.
I guess I'll just say The Who.
Oh yeah, it's The Who.
The Who?
Lisa Lisa and Cult Jam.
Just Cult Jam.
Matt, you're up.
Let's do The for 1200.
And which city did Raiding the Rock Vault first perform?
City of the Mind.
The City of the Mind.
Pass.
Paul.
Does that mean it has to start with T-H-E?
I don't think so.
Somewhere in England.
Okay.
I'll say Liverpool.
Show me somewhere in England.
Liverpool.
I think it's actually somewhere in Mexico.
Okay.
Los Angeles.
We're both wrong.
The Mexico of America.
Oh, Los Angeles.
The Angels.
So it was The.
Oh.
Yep.
Paul got it right.
I mean, I got it.
Paul, you're up.
Great.
I got one right.
I'll go with The again.
For 2000.
Daily Double.
Yeah.
Oh, here we go.
I'm coming out of the hole, mama.
Lead singers Todd Currens, who's been on this show, and Travis Cormier are natives of which
country?
That would be Canada.
Oh, Canada.
That's true.
And Paul is back to zero.
He's still in third place, but he is back to zero.
That's all I asked for.
I'll try Vault for 1200.
What song is originally by a Beatle and covered by G&R, by Guns N' Roses?
Oh, oh, fuck.
It's "Live and Let Die."
Damn it.
Paul McCartney, "Live and Let Die."
I knew that one.
I just saw him at concert.
I should have known that.
You just saw that.
Yeah.
I do love that cover of it, too.
Matt.
I will, I got to catch up here.
Oh, yeah.
Score check.
I'm winning 2800.
Matt is in second with 400.
Paul is in third with zero.
I will do rock for 2000.
All right.
Daily Double!
Do-do-do-do-do-do.
Drummer Blas Ellis of Rock Vault Tours with this holiday-themed rock show.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Come on.
You can get this one.
I know, I know.
I just had instant cognitive dissonance on it.
Yep.
Nicholas Newman, his wife drags him to it every year when they play in Jersey.
You know, this started in the really cold areas of Russia when they first started doing
the show.
Manheim Steamroller.
Trans-Siberian Orchestra.
The Manheim Steamroller.
The Trans-Siberian Orchestra.
Blas drives a steamroller in Siberia.
Paul.
Vault for 2000, please.
Name the other Deep Purple song in the show besides "Smoke on the Water."
You know that other Deep Purple song.
Oh, it's "In a God of the Vita."
"In a God of the Vita," the famous Deep Purple song.
I don't know.
Is it not?
You want me?
Is that your guess?
Yeah, that's my guess.
Okay.
No, it's "Space Truck."
What the fuck?
"In a God of the Vita."
I'm in space and I'm truckin', baby.
Don't you know that I ha ha ha ha ha.
You remember when we used to make out to this hymn?
Oh, won't you truck with me?
That's me.
I'll try rock for 1200.
Name a song that S.J. sings in "Rock and Roll."
Oh, come on.
Your mama don't dance.
Oh, what does she sing?
She sings, I don't know.
She sings, "Here I Go Again."
Is Barracuda in there?
My white snake.
Barracuda.
She sings some white snake.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Oh, she sings some Rolling Stones.
What's that song called?
"Gimme Shelter."
Start me up.
Sing "Start Me Up."
She does "Start Me Up."
She sings "Brown Sugar."
She does "Gimme Shelter."
"Dreams" by Fleetwood Mac, "Gimme Shelter" by the Rolling Stones, "Heartbreaker" by Pat Benatar, and "Alone" by Heart.
Nice.
What a comprehensive list.
Yes.
Yeah.
It did take me longer to figure out what are the songs that she sings in that show that it should have.
That did seal the game for you, Jacob.
Oh, how nice for me.
Yeah.
Matt, you got rock for 400 or 800.
Well, it's tough.
Fighting for second place.
Yeah, if I get it right, then I'm in second.
If I get it wrong, I'm in second.
It's tough.
That's right.
I'll go for 800.
You could get the third daily double.
It's the third daily double.
It's not.
Todd Kearns of Rock Vault regularly performs with this top hat wearing member of Guns N' Roses.
Buckethead.
Yeah.
A young person brought up Buckethead to me a few weeks ago.
I was like, how do you know who Buckethead is?
Like somebody in their 20s brought up Buckethead to me.
They're like, oh, he plays all this great guitar stuff and everything.
He's really good.
He's a great performer and everything.
Yeah.
And I said, did you know that he was in Guns N' Roses for a while?
And the look on this guy's face got hilariously huge.
He was the guitar player in Guns N' Roses.
Yeah.
Not back, but forward slash.
Forward slash of course is correct.
And Paul closing out the category end the game rock for 400 former ICS guest and Rock Vault guitarist Rowan Robertson was a member of this metal band.
Oh God.
In excess.
Was he with Dio?
That's literally what the question is.
I think he was with Dio.
He was with Dio.
Yeah, I got it.
Oh, I'm so proud of myself.
Oh, Paul got the secret $8,000 question correct.
So that means, oh shit, that wasn't the $8,000 question.
No, I still win.
I win with 4,000 points.
Matt wins with $3,200 and Paul has negative 1600.
That's from a Hoopie Fruits scoop.
Thank you Hoopie Fruits.
Yeah, that was great.
If you want to make us a scooperty or any other kind of jock versus nerd or just send us in some email.
HayScoops.com is where you can go.
HayScoops.com.
Head over there.
Make us a scoop mail.
Make us a jock versus nerd.
Do a scooperty.
Do a Price is Scryte.
Do an obelisk.
You do all those things right over there at HayScoops.com.
We are running low on the jock versus nerds.
So go over there.
Make us one.
Yeah.
In fact, pick a different Vegas show that just closed and write a whole one about that one too.
That'd be great.
There's a lot more to choose from.
Keep them more every day.
We could just do a string of Las Vegas shows closing.
We can do Las Vegas shows close that we've been part of.
That's right.
Good Lord.
That'd be like two weeks of material.
Or some would say maybe 1260 episodes.
But it is the true story of this show.
Vegas shows closing.
I want to thank all the people's supporters over on our Patreon page.
Absolutely.
It's a new month with another list just yet.
But this is the part where we thank you by name.
It's one of the rewards that we offer.
So go to our patreon.com/hayscoops and check out the tiers that fit your budget today.
Both monthly or yearly options.
Yearly comes with a discount.
Was that web address too hard to pronounce?
That was a very long web address, Matt.
Just Google Pittsburgh extravaganza lantern zoo animal.
Pumpkin jack-o-lantern zoo.
No, go to preachingfun.com.
Sticks.
Come visit preachingfun.com.
It's better than hanging with your mom out of the bed.
Or if you've already applied to be the new pumpkin mold scraper at the Pittsburgh pumpkin zoo extravaganza doohickeything.org next year,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
Farts, farts, farts, farts, farts.
Fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com.
It does take you over to our Patreon site where for as little as $3 you can help keep this show on the air.
If you think this show is worth more than $3 a month, you can do that too.
It would really help us out.
Over there at preachingfun.com.
And of course, fartsinabag.biz.
Thanks, Penn, Jeff, for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Penn.
And thanks, everybody, for joining us here on our Zoom.
And thanks, everybody, for joining us on Twitch.
Yep, that's right.
Stay safe out there.
We love you.
And we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you on the phone.
See ya.
Bye.
It's the bonus material for being a Patreon.
When everything just clicks.
Buy your car today on Carvana.
Delivery fees may apply.