Two reasons I build a Greenwood, I'm a massive fan of Mid-America, St. Louis Airport.
I love the convenience minutes from downtown.
The parking lot right there is just $9 for 24 hour parking.
Are you kidding me?
And speaking of that, the affordability as well, great prices on flights at all those
flights, all those destinations nonstop.
That's huge when you travel with kids like I do, and they take you to ideal destinations
from sugar, white, sandy beaches, to the bright lights of Las Vegas.
You want to find out more about Mid-America, St.
Louis Airport, go to flymidamerica.com.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go!
It's time for Madden Maddly's Ice Cream Social, sitting in Las Vegas, it's Matt Conley, sitting
in Pittsburgh, it's Paul Maddly, sitting in Las Vegas too, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy.
Just got a video message from my friend, Alex Ramone.
Oh yes?
Because he's out in New Jersey at something called ProfitCon, nothing scratches me wrong
about that in any way, heading out to the old ProfitCon in New Jersey.
P-R-O-P-H-E-T?
No, no, no, no, oh that'd be, yeah, I wouldn't have outed him if he was at ProfitCon, you
know.
Alex Ramone is the returned Profit board group in New Jersey.
I think if anyone could pull off a cult, it's Alex Ramone.
That is true.
Let's not get it twisted, MJ can pull off the cult.
Well he knows where his bread is buttered.
Well MJ would be on all the merchandise.
Profit like money, profit like money.
Profit like money y'all, that's the name of this episode, profit like money.
They should have just called the con Step 3.
Right, we can start doing a Step 3 con, super expensive tickets, nothing really happens,
it'll be great.
He said, he was a magician and one of them goes, "Do you know someone named Matt Donnelly?"
And he goes, "Yes."
And she goes, "Well I know him but I really know his wife Sarah."
I was really good friends with Sarah and her friend Jen and so he pulled out his phone,
they made a video, shot a video to me and it is the woman who booked Sarah and I on
a Valentine's Day morning show when we were first dating.
Oh wow!
She was a TV producer.
I remember this.
Yeah, she was a TV producer.
Because SJ and I were supposed to, I don't know, this was a different thing, right?
Oh no, this is way earlier, this is way earlier, yeah, this is back in New York, like we were
literally...
Because there was another thing that happened like this in Vegas, that's what I was...
Didn't you and Sarah shoot like a Valentine's thing in Vegas one time?
Yes, yes.
Okay, okay.
And Jimmy and Robin were in it.
That's what I started thinking of immediately, Jacob, I was on your page but then this is
even earlier.
There have been conspiring forces all around you for decades to make sure you and Sarah
are a thing, huh?
I think it's the only, it's possible but it's the only reason Matt and Sarah are together
because the universe forced Sarah into it.
Yeah, I mean the second one of her friends goes like, "Sarah, seriously?"
And then she might just like come out of it like a hypnotist, like just go like, "Oh shit."
"Oh God, what have I been doing for all these years?
I have children!"
He's hideous.
No, no, so when we first started dating, we were hanging out, having drinks with our friend
Jen, who we're still very good friends with Jen, Jen and Andy.
Her husband hired me to do handiwork when I had that job destroying offices and painting
walls.
Oh, right.
That's a good friendly close up.
And Jen, Jen was in Miami with Sarah out here in Vegas.
She later did Miami on Broadway, did Kinky Boots on Broadway, still is in New York, good
friend of ours.
Definitely tried to cock block us on our first date, which I always think is very funny.
Just really not, not like she wanted me, but she just wanted the date to get awkward.
She came and met us, she was at the bar and she got hammered and kept being like, "So
you really like Sarah, you're going to mess with her, what are you going to do?"
And really out loud in front of Sarah and I trying to destroy the date, all the chemistry.
And I doubled down and go like, "No, I really like her, yeah, no it's great."
And I just turned to Sarah and was like, "I really like you, I really want to keep dating."
And so I just was eating all of her things to destroy it and be like, "No, I'm going
to stay confident," and be like, "I like this gal."
So then we ended up becoming all drinking buddies as I continued to date.
And then we had beers with this woman, Liz, who is a producer, and she goes, "Oh, I need
couples for a thing on Thursday for Valentine's Day, we need couples competing for a travel
sponsor.
We want to do a getaway or whatever."
And so I was like, "Well, we're not close to married, we've been dating about like six
or seven months or whatever."
And because we'd only been dating for six or seven months, we crushed it.
Oh, because you just knew everything about each other.
We knew everything about each other.
We knew everyone's favorite color, favorite movie, favorite whatever.
All the things that you forget over time.
Gun to my head, if you told me what Sarah ... I could not tell you Sarah's favorite
color or favorite movie, and she could not do the same for me.
Oh, Sarah's favorite color is blue, and her favorite movie is being John Malkovich.
All right, Jacob, you and Sarah going away to Maui.
Ann's favorite color is red.
I don't know that she likes movies enough to have a favorite, but I don't know.
Maybe Step Brothers like me.
We both love Step Brothers.
So we one tied with another couple, and so we had a tiebreaker, and I lost the tiebreaker
because it's for a travel website, and they asked, "How many destinations does the travel
website go to?"
And I was like, "I don't know, a thousand?"
And the sponsor was like, "What?"
And it was like, "The answer is like a hundred."
I was off by an order of magnitude.
You paulmatically sponsor.
I did, I totally paulmatically sponsor.
So instead we got ... I don't know, all of them?
Spin the globe and just hit ... Just three places in Arkansas.
It's only three places in Arkansas that our company goes.
Oh my God.
Throw a dart at a map.
I don't know who this guy is.
So we ended up with, it was something like a $300 voucher or a $500 voucher or something
like that.
Oh, that's pretty nice.
Second place, yeah.
First place was like thousands of dollars in a real vacation.
And so- But you probably had to pay taxes on that.
Maybe, yeah.
Maybe.
Yeah.
All I know is that I think it was like $300, because Sarah and I were so broke that we
couldn't use the $300 as a base point, we had to use $300 as our budget.
Yeah.
Right.
You now have a budget of $300.
You've gone from having a budget of zero to having a budget of $300.
Exactly.
We did a getaway to a hotel just outside of Philadelphia from New York, and we spent a
weekend in Philly.
Ah!
Perfect!
That's pretty good.
The Paris of Pennsylvania.
Yeah.
Good Lord.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
We did it.
We did have a good time.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
I miss the days of just like, "Well, we're going to do something."
"We don't have any money.
There's a hotel down the road.
Let's go stay there."
Yeah.
I know.
It really is.
I do miss those days.
Yeah.
That was the plan in Vegas.
When you're living in Vegas, what else are you going to do?
Go get a hotel deal.
Right.
That's right.
Yeah.
Staycation, baby.
The weekend, it was one of my son's birthdays.
Okay.
He and his friend, when they were young, they used to always do joint birthdays because our
friend Danny and Jason, their kiddo, there's no popular person on earth than their child.
Every time they start saying a new expression, it's like, "Oh, you've been hanging out with
Danny's kid again," kind of thing.
Suddenly they want a new game, and the best was, "Okay."
We're being coy about the names because it's people's children, but we know these kids.
This is Danny's oldest son that you're talking about, right?
No.
They're the youngest.
Oh, the youngest?
They think he's cool as hell, but he doesn't spend a lot of time with him.
Right.
But he's a little older.
He's a little older.
Yeah.
Their youngest son is the same as my oldest, and they're only nine days apart.
Right.
And so they used to do joint birthday parties, then different schools, different whatever.
We finally decided, "Let's get together and do a birthday party."
But I'm going to take a side note here to be like, I've now officially encountered my
first ... I've been out of touch with slang that we brought up on this show, but my kids
have now just started saying this expression that I am like, "What?"
And they won't stop saying-
Are they saying for shizzle?
They're saying for shizzle?
Can I take a guess?
Yes.
Is it 6'7"?
Oh, they do that before every photo and I ask them what it means and they don't know
what it means, but they do say 6'7" before every photo.
I love kids saying things that they don't know what it means.
It's my favorite thing.
Yeah.
Do you know what 6'7" is from, Paul?
I have dug up a couple things.
Yeah.
So it's LeVar Ball's height or LaMelo Ball's one of the Balls.
LaMelo Ball.
LaMelo Ball's height.
From Charlotte.
And then it's sort of like, "Oh, I would like to be that."
You know, like to be 6'7" or whatever.
Yeah.
Like that would be cool.
But it also can mean mid in certain situations.
Okay.
Like it's only 6'7" out of 10?
Yeah.
It's been co-opted to that sometimes, but also, Jacob, mostly it's people don't know
what the fuck it is.
They just say it.
Yes.
Like if it comes up like in a thing, "6'7", "6'7".
Yeah.
They just yell "6'7".
Like if you guys take a photo, they go, "Okay."
And everyone goes, "6'7".
And they laugh.
Yep.
And we don't know why.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's a reference to basketball players height and some other weird meanings that have been
attributed to it, Jacob.
So they say, "Bet."
Oh.
Oh yeah.
"Bet."
That's back now?
That's back.
Oh yeah.
Bet's back.
You know what else I heard that was back the other day?
I was watching a video of kids getting their hair cut.
What's that?
You know what this kid said?
Getting haircuts has been around for a while, Paul.
Okay.
This is a viral barbershop where the kids on their summer vacation can spin a wheel and
get crazy haircuts.
Okay.
Oh, I like that.
And they dare their friends to spin the wheel and go for the crazy haircut, like half shaved,
half on.
Or, you know, old man.
You know, where they cut off all the back hair and just leave the horseshoe rim and
all that kind of stuff.
Good, good.
So these kids, these young kids are getting these wild haircuts, this thing.
But this one kid spun it and he got the half on, half off, right?
Yeah.
Good.
Right down the thing.
But then the fry tuck, that's one of them they're getting.
So as he's getting it done, he's liking the look and he says, "Oh, that's tough."
Tough is back.
Whoa.
It's back.
Fucking greaser.
I haven't heard tough in forever.
Sorry.
I have to go fight with the socias.
Dude, like for real, tough.
That was such a thing when we were kids.
For me anyway.
Everything was tough.
Yes, it's from the outsiders.
No, but no, it's even before that, it's like, "Oh, that's tough."
It was like, cool.
Yeah.
I mean, it was written about in the outsiders though, in the famous book, The Outsiders.
Oh, I guess.
Yeah.
And it was kind of immortalized in that.
But yeah, I mean, it was around, the author wrote about a thing that was just around at
the time.
Yeah.
So my kids started saying, "Oh, bet."
Like, yeah, good.
Let's do it.
It's on.
Right?
Yeah.
Which my kids were already saying dubs or W, like win, like that's a win.
Uh-huh.
Getting some dubs.
Yeah.
And also just going like dubs.
Let's do it.
Be dubs three.
And then it starts saying, "Oh, bet," well, a couple of things about that was one was like,
we had the quintessential what happens with parents.
I couldn't believe this conversation was happening because it's as written as every parent should.
Yes.
We said, "When did you guys start saying bet?"
And my oldest was like, "I've been saying it forever."
No.
Forever.
No, you haven't.
That is simply not true.
We're very aware of your speech.
We have paid, over the years that you have been alive, we have paid a lot of attention
to you.
Exactly.
I was like, "What?
No, you have not.
You have not."
That is simply false.
That was '80s-
You weren't saying it yesterday.
That was '80s hip hop slang.
Oh yeah, bet's been back for a couple of years.
Bet's been back in a hard way for a couple of years.
Crazy.
Yeah.
Anyways, we just had to do a joint birthday party.
We went out to Sandy Valley, Sandy Valley Ranch.
Oh, not the strip club?
No, no, no.
I mean-
Oh, okay.
It was just across the street.
Yeah.
But it was actually driving up.
I did see Ranch, Ranch, Ranch, and I was like, "Wait, where am I?"
And I was like, "Oh, I'm in California.
No bunny ranches.
No whatever here."
But you drive out the Gene Goodsprings Exit off of the 15 on your way out of town, and
then you just drive-
On the way to LA?
Forever out in the middle of the desert, and then this is suddenly you pop a bunch of ranches.
I think we would categorize it as glamping.
Yeah?
All right.
Okay.
Yeah?
We had a giant teepee where the kids all piled in and stayed there or whatever.
Good.
Sarah, Danny, and I had the covered wagon, and we gave our friends, the younger couple
with the two more kids, a mini house, full mini house for them.
Great.
Are these-
Outdoor little kitchenette areas where it's a gas stove, propane tanks for showers.
Yeah, perfect.
So these are pretty permanent structures.
They're not like tents.
No, no.
These are permanent structures.
That's it.
That's what I mean.
Do they have locking front doors?
No.
Oh, yes, actually.
Yes.
Not the teepee.
You can't lock down the teepee.
Oh, really?
Oh, shit.
Not with that attitude.
No.
You're out, Paul.
If you can't lock the teepee, you're not going?
If I can't lock my teepee, I'm gone.
I'm gone.
Because I used to have nightmares about-
That's the line.
I used to have nightmares about that all the time.
How about people breaking into your teepee?
Well, people would break into my teepee, and then they'd break into my wigwam, and I was
like, "Fuck, Doc.
What am I supposed to do?"
And the doctor said, "You're too tense."
You know who else was just made a little sad by that joke?
The following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Bobby Butt Stick's Blue Lingerie and Lingerie Shop.
That's right, from Dave Sorensen in 2024, that's Bobby Butt Stick's Blue Lingerie and
Lingerie Shop.
Blue Lingerie?
What's Blue Lingerie?
I think it's a type of restaurant, but let me look it up for you, Bobby Butt Stick's.
Thanks.
I'd like to advertise my establishment, but I need to know what I am.
It's a Belgian bakery.
There we go.
It's a bakery.
Okay, great.
Yeah.
The Lingerie.
Hello.
I'm Bobby Butt ... I'm Bobby Butt Stick's.
Where did this voice come from?
It came from me, Bobby Butt Stick's.
I started a French bakery years ago, and I had nowhere to put my buns.
So what I decided was I would also sell lingerie, and I dressed my baguettes in badonkadonk thongs.
That's right.
You can buy the finest loaves and tinny holsters at my place of business.
Bobby Butt Stick's Lingerie and ... Come get it.
Lingerie Shop.
Yeah, that's right.
You heard me.
You heard it.
You know what I said.
So also I have sweet buns.
I have hot cross buns.
And if you're lucky and you buy something very tantalizing, you'll get sticky buns.
That's the Boulangerie Bobby Butt Stick's Boulangerie guarantee.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I'm getting notifications from the ugly old woman in the kitchen that something is
cooking and done.
Hello, ugly old woman in the kitchen.
What do we got?
Oh, my God.
The ugly old woman found the lingerie, and she put it on, and she's transformed it to
a beautiful lady.
Oh, she's gorgeous.
We're going to go and get married.
I'm sorry.
I'm closing the restaurant and lingerie shop to spend the rest of my life with the ugly
old woman who was my cook who only needed some TLC and some nice lingerie.
Oh, boy.
My life has changed forever today.
Thank you, me, for selling the things that made the ugly old woman in my shop pretty,
and I can marry her.
Happy Thanksgiving, everybody.
Don't enter Hayscoops at checkout.
No.
The store's closed.
The store's closed for marriage.
Yup.
We're turning it into a house.
This was an odd commercial to pay for.
We charge a lot of money for these commercials.
It's weird that they're paying for this commercial just to tell us that the store is closed down.
I'd like you all to meet Mrs. Bobby Butt Sticks, AKA the ugly woman.
There she is.
My sweetheart.
Hey.
How's everybody doing?
Oh, she's so beautiful now.
It's a real pleasure to be here.
Now, don't you give her sass, because she's wearing lingerie around the town.
That's how she does it.
It's the only way I look good.
That's right.
If she takes off her sexy lingerie.
Until this, I was an ugly old woman.
She takes off her sexy lingerie.
It's like a magic spell.
Did you guys watch any of the newest fight of the century?
What?
Oh, it's Canelo Crawford.
Canelo and Bud Crawford?
Who?
I don't get to watch any of it, but it was the big fight that was on Netflix, big boxing
fight.
Yeah, it was the big boxing fight.
So you had Canelo, the reigning defending champion, and you had Crawford, who came up
in weight to match Canelo to do the fight at all.
It was weird.
They were talking about it because it's like the end of both of their careers, but it's
the biggest fight that Crawford has had to date.
Yeah, he's been a really, really renowned fighter and a crazy respected boxer, but never
had any star power.
This was his third weight class.
This is a fight that they've been trying to make this fight happen for a few years.
It was the first boxing fight in years, though, that has actually lived up to the hype that
came into it.
It was actually a really good, fun to watch event.
Yes.
Well, I didn't watch the whole event.
The whole event was like six hours long on Netflix with all the pre-fights, and our friend
Mitzi was texting us during the first fight and saying there were more people in the ring
than there were in the stadium, because it was in Allegiant.
It was in the huge stadium.
They set a new attendance record in Allegiant Stadium where the Raiders play, 70-some-odd-thousand
people.
Oh my God, though.
I really liked this fight.
I watched the whole main event fight.
You had all of this Saudi stuff, and the Saudi Crown Prince got introduced before the fight.
They did a special thank you to the Saudi Crown Prince who was in attendance at the
fight because I think he had given a lot of money to make it all happen.
I think he was part of it.
The crowd of 70-some-odd-thousand people loudly booed the Saudi Crown Prince live on Netflix,
and it was pretty hilarious.
This is a very strange thing that's happening.
Did you guys see the announcement that WrestleMania 43 is going to Saudi Arabia?
Yep.
Dude, Tom Brady just signed a flag football thing to play flag football in Saudi Arabia.
Good grief.
I need a Saudi Prince to get into podcasting, improv, and magic like yesterday.
Yeah.
Oh, it'd be great.
I don't know.
It seems really scary, all of it.
I mean, it seems like there is enough money involved that no one who is tempted by that
money remotely gives a shit about the optics of it.
Well, I mean, they got CM Punk.
He flipped.
Well there you go.
There's the proof.
What more proof do you need?
No, but I told you about that a couple years ago when he was out on the outs with WWE,
and he had an argument with one of the other guys who was going to go perform in the Saudi
Arabian.
Okay.
Yeah.
And he said, "Go suck a blood-soaked dick in Saudi Arabia," and he had to apologize
for it this year when he went.
Because he's taking money.
He went to hell with money.
Yeah.
It's weird.
There just simply is an amount of money where we don't care about the murder of a journalist.
That's it.
It is, "I murdered a journalist, but I would like to give you money.
I'll give you $50 million, and you just won't mention that I murdered a journalist anymore."
Well, I mean, I still go like, I can't believe that Dana White being on film smacking a woman
did nothing to him.
Nothing.
He didn't apologize.
He didn't have to apologize, and it didn't stop him from being invited to speak at the
Republican National Convention to speak at least higher.
He gets these high-paid speaking engagements.
It thwarted him in no way from accomplishing everything he wanted to do.
It's because his name is Dana, and when your name is Dana, people feel like they can't
pick on you about other things like beating women because you've already had too difficult
of a life being named Dana.
They just don't want to make it any more difficult for poor Dana.
It's so strange to me, but yeah, that's it.
We cared about Jamal Khashoggi for like six months, and then we're like, "Ah."
The same thing ended Ray Rice's career.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All-pro football player did exactly the same thing that Dana White did, and it ended his
career.
Yeah.
As it should, by the way.
As it should.
As something that should be an outlier, that's how that should work.
Yeah.
No way.
You act like you still didn't draft Ray Rice on your fantasy football team in case he came
back.
Come on.
Drafted him this year, motherfucker.
This year.
Don't call it a comeback.
He's been here for years.
But yeah, no.
That fight was supposedly a great fight.
I haven't watched it, but it apparently was very good.
Yeah.
It's really good.
It's really fun.
Watching this audio, watching him get booed, and he got booed while he was standing in
the middle of the ring.
They had invited him in the ring, so the camera's just on him, and he's got this deadpan expression
trying to ignore 70,000 people booing him really loudly.
He literally whispered to someone, it's like, "How much to pay the people to applause?
I'll pay it.
$1,000 a person?
Yeah, yeah.
Let's write checks right now.
Let's do it."
I think for the ticket price that was at that event, I think it's more than a grand a person.
Yeah.
That's true.
Based on how much those people paid to be there, it's more than a grand a person.
There were so many people in town.
Now, how many people were booing because of Saudi Arabia's policy towards women and other
disparaged minorities?
And people that they fuck with?
Yeah.
For some people, just out of racism, just saw a brown guy in a turban and were like,
"Boo!"
What do you think?
Like, it's not 100% to 0%.
I was saying, "Boo-earns."
I was like, "Oh, oh, was anyone else saying, 'Boo-earns'?"
Nick Newman in chat says they were saying, "Bruce," because he was Prince Bruce.
Prince Bruce.
Prince Bruce from Saudi Arabia.
I want to hear that version of my hometown.
You know, maybe the solution is, the next time they introduce him, they start playing
old Ray Stevens, and he had the A-Rap.
That's his intro music.
That's it.
Not just the streak.
The Sheik of the Burning Sands.
Oh my God.
I had to, I didn't have to, but I did.
I took my wife to the airport the next morning because she had an out of town gig, and neither
of us really thought about it.
She had a 7 a.m. flight out of Vegas, and so driving her to the airport, there was suddenly
a line for miles of cars trying to get to the airport the morning after that fight.
Oh, jeez.
That early, too?
We pulled in, and both of us were like, "Oh, oh, shit.
This is a thing."
And then I went to pick her up.
Did you do the old Mattingly Donnelly flip around?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, we did all the back things, and we were in the truck so I could get off the road a
little bit.
We did the dirt patch and everything.
We did the whole thing.
But yeah, go ahead and pick her up the next day.
It was just as bad, and I was trying to get to the pickup area.
I'm on the phone with her, and now I'm stuck.
So now I can't do any kind of flippy or go anywhere else because I'm stuck on the road.
But I'm texting with her, and she's like, "The passenger pickup area is empty.
I don't know what you're talking about," and it was all people going to long-term parking
in the valets and all of the wealthy— People getting out of town.
Muck to mucks.
Yeah.
Just getting out of town.
Yeah, yeah.
That happened the same.
Yeah.
I went to pick me up, and I was like, "Passenger pickup.
There's no one here."
She was like, "I cannot get in there."
And I was like, "Weird."
Yeah.
And it was just—I was coming in on a day when most people were leaving town, so all the
locals were clogging up the affordable rates of overnight parking at the Vegas airport.
That's right.
The very affordable rates.
The bad thing is there's one road that leads to passenger pickup in the A terminal, the
main terminal.
There's one road that leads to passenger pickup, but that road also leads to long-term
parking and economy parking and valet, and then there's one fork off that goes to the
departing flights.
I mean, that thing was designed for when we—
When you got all those things going.
We were still calling Vegas hotels "carpet joints."
Do you know what I mean?
Like, that's how long ago that place was designed, and it's not—
Yeah.
I will never understand—I mean, I understand it, but man, they should have put that monorail
to the damn airport.
And now it's—Elon Musk is taking on the cab union.
Of course.
Yeah.
He's trying to get the boring company to make it to the airport.
Are there like two people left in the cab union now?
That's a—but they are mad.
Those two people are really pissed.
Maybe the power has shifted.
Maybe they are coming back, because I know there's been a lot of backlash with Uber
and Lyft, too.
Nah.
So I don't know.
We're not going back.
That's not how things work.
"Chaotic" is right.
You got to play "Vegas Parking and Weather."
We're crushing it right now.
Oh, that's true.
"Vegas Parking and Weather, no one does it better than ICS."
Ho!
You know who else knows everything about Vegas Parking and Weather?
Hold on.
We're going to come back to that.
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by—nope, that's me looking up a laundry.
Today's show is brought to you by Henry's Hobo Cafe from Dead Laszlo in 2024.
That's Henry's Hobo Cafe.
Oh yeah, all right, uh-huh, all night.
My name is Henry, I'm a hobo.
I got hungry sitting on the street.
I said, "Henry, time to grab some gumbo and find a place to eat."
So I grabbed my gumbo and my bindle, and I went on down the road to find a spot.
I happened upon this old abandoned hotel full of ghosts and a cooking pot.
So I asked the ghosts, "You want to work for me?"
My name's Henry.
They said, "We'll work for free."
So now you can come into my house.
That's not really a house.
It's a place on the middle of the street.
It's full of ghosts and me.
You can get some old cooked meat.
Come on down to Henry's haunted house, Hobo Havel.
That's right.
It's full of ghosts and also garlic toast.
Come on down, get your fill.
Henry's got ghosts that will kill.
That's right.
I didn't mention, but they're deadly.
These poltergeists will eat your soul.
They also make you into food and you are what becomes in the bowl.
You're what we serve for lunch and dinner.
If you come to eat, you get eaten.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Anybody who comes to my place can kill and eat.
That's what happens.
I'm a cannibal.
I'm Henry the Cannibal.
Henry the Cannibal.
Come on down and get eaten up by me and the ghosts.
One of the ghosts is little girl.
Do you think she'd be fine?
But she's not.
She's mean.
She's meaner than anybody.
Oh no.
I hope it's not the girl.
I'm just here for lunch.
Can I get seated for lunch, please?
Come on in.
I'll be happy to see you.
Oh no.
Now it's a little girl ghost and she's murdering me.
Oh, she's eating me.
She's starting at my feet and eating her way up.
Oh no.
Oh man.
Enter Hayscoops to checkout.
There you go.
What were you saying, Paul?
Oh, I was saying, speaking of weather.
Uh-huh.
Speaking of biggest weather.
How's our outlook looking as we approach ScoopHead?
Oh, I think we look great.
I think we're looking really great.
Yeah.
Here.
I'll pull up the actual Vegas parking and weather.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
We're in the middle of it.
So yeah.
Actual Vegas parking and weather.
Uh, yeah.
No, it looks like we are, oh, mid to low 90s, mid to upper 80s.
That's great weather out here.
That's gold out here.
Yeah.
No, we're going to be perfect.
Sunny.
Sunny the whole time.
It's going to be so nice.
Very, very nice.
It's not too late, by the way.
ScoopFest.com.
Go ahead and buy your tickets.
Come join us out here in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Enjoy that fantastic weather.
Come hang out with us for all three days.
Uh, there are barbecue tickets available.
There are VIP tickets available.
It is going to be a blast.
I was talking to, uh, a performer last night that is going to be performing at part of
ScoopFest and they were super excited about it.
It is going to be so cool.
ScoopFest.com.
Uh, head over there.
Get your tickets to ScoopFest.
Come see us.
I can't wait.
I can't wait for you to have.
I don't know.
It's soon.
It's soon enough that, uh, I am no longer getting anxious when someone mentions ScoopFest
to me because I am already in that anxious cloud.
There you go.
We're there.
We're in it.
We're dialed in.
Yeah, yeah.
I just live in it now.
Yes.
Same.
Um, yeah, yeah.
It's going to be fun.
We have some surprises on top of the surprises.
It's going to be great.
It is.
It's going to be so fun.
Oh.
Jacob, hold my calls.
I'm doing a podcast.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm busy right now.
He's doing a podcast.
Professionals, everybody.
Pro aficionados.
We were laughing the other morning, the whole family were having breakfast, and, uh, my
wife told a story about her dad doing the pull my finger gag.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
She said she pulled his finger, he farted, and she was shocked and upset as a nine-year-old
girl was just furious.
Like why?
Absolutely not.
That is not appropriate.
You monster.
We were laughing because I said, you know, it's funny now that we're older, you know
that later on he was like having a beer with a buddy going like, man, daughters are different
than sons, man.
Yeah.
Daughters just don't.
Not the same thing.
Like she was not, she didn't think it was funny.
No.
Right.
Well, did she think she caused it?
I think so.
I think she didn't want that responsibility.
Yeah.
I think she was like, I don't want to have this power.
And, uh, I mean that also, I think, uh, for girls, again, I can't speak with any kind
of authority or experience, but I've, you know, girls have a whole different road to
go down when it comes to discovering bodily functions.
Yeah.
And if you suddenly throw into the mix that the pulling of a finger can cause a fart.
Can trigger.
Yeah.
It's like one more thing.
It's like, what the fuck is this flesh cage that I am trapped in?
What kind of disaster area have I been born unto?
How many booby traps are in this thing?
You think this child was upset because she had learned something about the human anatomy
that she didn't know previously?
Right.
It's just too much.
This is one more fucking thing, one more fucking thing that can go wrong with human bodies.
This is just add it to the list of the terrible shit that goes on with these meat puppets.
Chaotically clumsy.
What the fuck is the flesh cage I'm trapped in is when I yell every time I'm in a store
changing room.
No, that's not even what we're talking about, the reputation of women and wives watching
true crime and true crime podcasts and true crime documentaries.
Right.
I was like, let's just straight up staying coached up on their most likely natural predator.
This is all it is.
This is all just, it's just absolutely just staying on top of, it's like why men watch
shark week?
The same exact reason.
We're just staying coached up on our predators.
That's all.
When I get in the water, when I put one toe in the water, I am no longer at the top of
the food chain.
I need to educate myself to watch shark week.
Or in the case of that little girl, shark week.
But I was like really, really meditating on this pull my finger gag.
I was like, wait, someone did it first, right?
Right.
Someone was like, oh, I got to fart.
I can't come up with the noise.
Let me just, if I come up with a joke, I can fart in public no problem.
This is, it's a little known fact.
It is the second most famous thing that the Earl of Sandwich did.
He invented the sandwich and he invented this bit.
But that's it, right?
How old is the gag?
Right.
Because that guy could be very old.
I just saw a crazy TikTok with this lady talking about, she came home and her husband said
he had a surprise for her and the afternoon before she had eaten a bunch of beans at a
taco joint.
Oh, no.
She knew she shouldn't.
This is the kind of humor that my wife does not enjoy.
She knew she shouldn't, but she did it.
She ate a bunch of beans.
And he blindfolds her and sits her in a chair in their dining room.
And she's sitting there and the husband says, oh, I'll be right back.
I forgot something.
And she can hear him leave and she's like, oh, I got to let one go.
So she lets out a toot and then and she's like, oh boy, that's a that's a that's a real
winner there.
That's a woof.
And then she does another one and she still doesn't hear him come back yet.
And then she has like three or four and she's like, oh, geez.
So she keeps the blindfold on, stands up and gets like a pillow from her chair and starts
woofing it around to try and dispel the stink, you know, and then sits back down.
And then finally, her husband comes back in, she's still worried that he's going to smell
it or whatever.
He takes a blindfold off and it's her whole family there for a surprise birthday party.
Yeah.
She's been sitting there cutting biscuits.
Oh, man, what is this unsliced cheese doing here?
Oh, my Lord, can you imagine?
Can you imagine?
Oh, according to this, the first time the pull my finger gag happened on film was in
1959.
Oh, right.
But I'm saying we're going to get some like, you know, oh, yeah, half a man out of ice
one day to revive him.
Someone's going to do the pull my finger gag in front of him while they're studying him
in a cage or something.
And he's going to be like, you guys are still doing that gag?
Yeah.
Is that gag still alive?
And we'll be like, yes, unfrozen Brendan Fraser, it is still alive.
No, like we as comedians, we don't, you know, we say like, oh, we do is silly.
It doesn't matter.
We don't change the world or anything.
We just make that make the day a little easier for everybody.
Right.
That guy changed the fucking world.
That guy created a fart joke.
For better or worse, just as just the world is a different place from the one that he
found.
It's the truth.
Yeah.
He left it better than he found it.
And Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Yeah.
I put that right neck and neck.
Basically the same.
Jesus.
So I've been watching.
Yes.
I've been watching a lot of weird reality TV lately.
Okay.
Especially bad reality competition shows.
This has become my late night watch while I'm sending emails and half paying attention
to it.
But it is fantastic.
Okay.
I've been watching one.
I finished watching it now on Netflix called Outlast, which is they just take a bunch of
people and drop them in the Alaskan wilderness and they have to form teams and they survive
out in the Alaskan wilderness until the other teams give up.
And so it's an open-ended game.
It lasts as long as it lasts until enough people give up.
And then there's a group that wins.
There is one dude who was on this show though that all I could think of the entire time
watching him was if Paul Mattingly were really good at outdoor survival, this would be him.
That's a big capital I, capital F pal.
It sure is.
It's a whole big old if, but I'm telling you, if Paul Mattingly had made a couple of different
decisions in his life and we're now just an outdoor survivalist guy, this would be him.
And I'm going to tell you why.
So to win the game, one of the rules, one of the only rules is to win the game, you
have to be on a team.
So a team has to accept you in to be even for it to even be possible for you to win
this game.
Got it.
So at one point he is changing teams.
All of his team is gone.
He's the last person remaining on his team and he's going to change teams and he knows
that one of the other teams is going to come along and loot his camp that he and his team
had built up for themselves.
They're going to come loot his camp and get his resources and everything after he leaves
taking what he can to the, to the new camp.
And so this motherfucker in, I believe what would be the ultimate Paul move burns his
house down so that the other people can't come in and get it.
Now hold on, you think that's what I would do?
I think if you had made the turns in life to become this person at all, I think you
might have a little bit of this in you.
Oh, I don't know.
I think you'd be, I think you'd be like it go cause it's a game.
So it's all, it's all a game and it's a game that now people are taking a little too seriously
because they're in it and they've been doing it for weeks and they're starving and they're
outside and so they've, you know, part of their brain has forgotten that it's a game
and that it's not really real.
I don't know.
This guy just struck me as, I didn't dislike him either by the way.
Was he a, when I watched him, when I watched him burning his house down, what made you
think of me?
It was, it was his mannerisms and just everything about him that it was, cause it really wasn't,
there wasn't an A to A line to draw between the two of you because you're, you're so,
you're so very different.
You just think this is alternate universe me.
I think it's just alternate universe you.
And he was, I should say too, I should say too that I liked this person.
Okay.
So he was, he was burning his house down.
I got it.
Yeah.
I understood why he was doing it.
Everything about it.
I was like, this is, I like this guy, but he is on a different wavelength entirely from
where I am.
I'd like to think that if I really put my mind to it, I could survive in the wilderness.
Oh, I think you could.
With a couple of tools and whatnot.
I don't think you're a useless person.
I would hate it.
Yes, you'd be so mad.
I would hate it so bad.
You'd be so mad the entire time.
That was just it.
That's why I quit Boy Scouts after getting Life Scout.
I was like, I can't in good conscience even go through with this Eagle Scout shit cause
I despise the out of doors.
I can't in good conscience become an Eagle Scout.
That really, as a kid, I was just like, I was like, this is like, this goes against who
I am as a human to even purport to enjoy camping in the least.
I don't.
I hate it.
I hate everything about it.
So, yeah.
I want you to watch this show, Paul.
You should come to Sandy Valley, Paul.
It's outlast.
Oh, I'm sure I'd have a great time.
Paul is a clamper.
Temperature controlled covered wagon.
I don't think I've been camping in 30 years.
Yeah.
I could say...
Is it 30 years ago you drowned that kid in a lake?
Was it that long ago?
Holy shit.
I didn't consider that a camping trip.
Oh, okay.
That was just an afternoon.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah, it was just an afternoon.
Yeah, it's true.
You didn't sleep outdoors then.
No.
You just were outdoors.
I was just working.
Yeah, that's true.
You're just taking out the trash.
Yeah.
My wife asked me to take out the trash, so here I go.
That's good Saudi money, man.
You can't pass up that Saudi money.
I didn't realize she hated that neighbor kid so much.
Saudi prince was like, "Drown that kid."
You got it, Paul.
I was like, "No way."
And he's like, "Here's a dump truck full of cash."
I'm like, "Okay."
Do I get to keep the dump truck?
Yes.
I'm in.
It's a tax write-off.
You had me a dump truck.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just don't...
I don't like camp.
I don't like anything about camping.
Well, when we got home, we borrowed sleeping bags from my neighbor, Gary, who loves to
camp.
He takes his own tent and sleeping bag on a motorcycle and just goes out in any direction,
just finds places to camp.
He loves it.
Oh, I've got a sleeping bag you guys can borrow.
I've got a big double, like a two-person sleeping bag if you guys ever need it.
We did.
We should have gotten it.
Yeah.
And it's zero degree too.
It's fucking hot.
Okay.
Yeah.
Perfect.
I'm really surprised Paul hates camping.
Leon Casab.
Leon, he's talking about that.
It's the only time I've ever been able to read sarcasm.
In the chat, no problem.
Yeah.
Now, you know what I...
Do you know what I do like?
What's that?
The idea of having a sleepover.
Oh, okay.
In the house.
I like the idea of people setting up sleeping bags on a nice cushioned floor, watching TV
until you fall asleep, playing video games until the wee hours.
I like that.
Speaking of camping, I was just talking to somebody the other day about Airbnbs, and
they were saying that they had had some bad luck with Airbnbs.
And I said, "Yo, Matt and Paul and I had bad luck with an Airbnb one time.
I think it was in Jersey."
Yes.
And it had been listed as like a three-bedroom.
And we got there, and one of the bedrooms was just a child's room with a pair of like
Ninja Turtle bunk beds or something.
Yes.
Now, that was Austin.
We would have been so aggravated.
Was that Austin?
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, because Brushwood paid that.
We would have been so aggravated if it wasn't for the fact that Paul was there and was more
than happy to sleep in the children's bunk beds.
Oh, yes.
The Turtle bunk beds were in Austin.
We did have bad luck with Airbnbs in Jersey.
We had a weird Airbnb in Jersey.
I think I'm conflating it.
We were on the third floor of a house, and the people were definitely living in the house
below.
We were trying to leave.
Oh, that was just the three of us.
Yeah.
We were in and out of that place in like seven hours.
Yes.
Yeah.
We used that place to barely sleep and take a shower.
That's because we took an overnight red-eye flight home on Spirit Airlines on their deck
chair that they call first class.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We were trying to leave to go to Tierney's, and it was like they had a birthday dinner
or something, like one of their kids or something.
Yes.
We couldn't leave.
We felt like we were going to their backyard.
We had to leave.
We had to walk through their children's birthday party to get to our car.
We had to walk through the party.
It was terrible.
No good.
Oh, so funny.
We returned our sleeping bags to Gary, he goes, "Do you like it?"
And they both go, "Yeah.
Yeah.
We love it.
It was our first time camping."
And I was like, "Oh.
Oh.
Bad dad alert.
Bad dad alert."
It did not occur to me that that was the first time camping at all.
And that the first time camping was this really nice Sandy Valley Ranch glamping.
I was going to say you have ruined your kids now.
That's not bad dad alert.
What are they?
Eleven and ten?
Seven and nine?
What?
They're twenty-four.
No.
You take kids much younger camping.
You risk a hawk stealing them.
It's not, you know, this is not...
That is true.
Yeah.
Good dad alert.
Good dad alert, if you ask me.
Exactly.
Snakes could eat them.
Hawks could snatch them.
How many of your children got stolen by hawks, Matt?
That's zero.
Good dad alert.
I mean, seriously, you watch some of these, what was it, the missing 411 stuff?
All the people that go missing in the woods?
That's scary.
Yeah.
All those hawks.
Paul's drawing from experience.
He went to drown that kid and a hawk took him away and Paul was like, "Fair dinkum.
Fair dinkum."
I had...
Well, he pulled the...
"Fair dinkum."
The kid grabbed him out of the water thinking he was a fish, I guess, and the kid wasn't
drowned.
So I was like, "Ah."
So I had to train on the hawk until it got high enough and I was like, "All right.
This fall is going to be fatal."
So then I shot the hawk, he dropped the kid, bam, done and done.
You know, that was the original ending for Lord of the Rings.
Almost exactly.
It was Gandalf up on the eagle, bang.
One shot.
There's stories like that that make me think you could run UFC, Paul.
No problem.
Oh boy.
Well, I guess you get that government contract, do the big fight on the West Lawn.
Oh right.
Fuck.
That is actually happening.
That is going to be...
That's the thing that's so fucking crazy.
That's a big part of why I'm...
Yeah.
That's it.
Well...
That's the one thing.
I...
I can't really watch wrestling anymore.
I've stopped listening to my wrestling podcasts.
I don't really watch live.
I watch Botchamania and that's about it.
But it's just, you know, it's too crazy.
It's the same...
It's the government...
That's our government now.
It's the government.
It's WWE.
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
That's them.
Yeah.
I...
Well, on the way out, we knew one of the women who lived in that area, she came by to visit
on a golf cart and the kids took turns driving the golf cart.
Oh, fun.
Now, that's fun.
Good.
And I was like...
I turned to Sarah and I was like, "This is all they're going to remember."
This is all...
Yeah, yeah.
They're going to be like, "I love camping because we drove a golf cart around."
In a couple of years, your youngest son in the middle of a conversation is going to mention
that he's a really good driver and you're going to be really confused why he's talking
about that and then he's going to mention the golf cart and you'll be like, "Motherfucker,
you're talking about that goddamn golf cart."
Yeah.
We got to feed...
They were feeding the horses, we fed donkeys, goats, chickens, pigs, and they're these horses
that look like cows.
They're fat horses?
Are they ponies?
They look like they were trying to disguise themselves like it's a cow patterned skin,
a cow patterned...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Like a mottled, a mottled, mottled...
Palomino.
Palomino?
No, no.
Is that what it's called?
That's the club, Paul.
They're called a pal...
That's the club that you love going to, Paul.
You're confused again.
It's called a palomino, right?
Isn't it a palomino?
No, I believe so.
Newman says, I don't know, he says, "I quit."
It's not a palomino?
I was going to say, we're getting palomino and of course, any cheap guest courses, which
is also a great name for them as well.
Is it a calico?
It's a calico horse.
Calico horse.
A palomino is a horse breed characterized by a pale creamed golden coat or a white and
silver mane and tail.
So that's not it.
It's not a palomino.
I know.
Nick Newman was saying, we host a horse podcast together.
It's true.
Yeah, but I don't know from a fucking palomino.
That don't mean we got any horse since.
El Camino.
It's an El Camino.
There's an El Camino because of big cow sized horses.
Newman unmute yourself.
There's a sway back El Camino right there.
Yes.
There you go.
Is Newman, can you unmute yourself or no?
Who can say?
I can unmute myself.
Hi guys.
I'm not mad.
I'm just disappointed.
Newman, tell us about these cow looking palominos.
The front is like a horse.
Those are beautiful.
The back is like a truck.
The front is where you ride.
The back is where you fuck.
Is the picture in the chat what you saw?
Similar.
It was maybe more brown and black skin based and it was more of a, it wasn't a race horse,
but it looked like more kind of athletic looking than that.
A horse with spots is most commonly called an Appaloosa.
You either saw an Appaloosa or you saw a good old fashioned American paint.
Oh yeah.
American paint.
And that's, and that's not because they actually paint it.
It's because that's what they call it.
No, that's a Sherwood Williams, they call it.
That's it.
That is an American.
You probably, what you saw was an American paint.
Okay.
That is, okay.
Cause I didn't, what I didn't get into is that I met a guy who'd been working around
the ranch for 27 years who called himself Bones and I need to know everything about
Bones.
Everybody shut up.
This is the rest of the show.
We're going to talk about Bones.
I need to know about this man.
And he was like, so I said, Oh, we've got to head back to Vegas.
I was sorry to hear that.
I got out of that city for some years ago and never went back.
Came out here to help my friend move and never left.
Oh my God.
My spirit animal's got any bones.
Well, she was an American paint had a face like Sarah Jessica Parker.
He had like, he was joking around with me so much, you know, when someone has so many
bits in their head and then like, I laughed at one of his bits.
So that was something that he was like rapid fire, but it wasn't like, yeah.
So in, in, in, in a hurricane of information, he'd use the word paint.
And I literally was like, are you saying paint like paint?
And he was like joking, like, yeah, we paint them or whatever.
And he was like, and like, I couldn't get to like, I needed the real answer.
I couldn't get him to stop doing bits.
And so when he said paint, I was like, I think he's fucking with me and I don't know what
he's saying.
And I can't believe I now can't believe any information he's telling me about this horse.
But he was saying what it's called.
It was called an American paint.
That's what it was.
And, and here's where it gets more confusing.
American breeds can also be classified as paint horses by the American paint horse association
based on their coloring.
Okay.
So like, so we have, yeah.
So we had a thoroughbred named market tree, okay.
And market trees coloring on its leg, his leg went above the knee, which is part of
their requirements that the judges for this paint horse thing have.
So that, so he actually was dual certified as a thoroughbred and a paint horse.
Wow.
I know.
He was special.
His name is market tree.
And it was a bad joke because that is a French woodworking term for when you use glue made
from horses to do inlays.
Boo.
Boo that name.
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
Isn't that bad?
We didn't name him that.
I like it.
It's macabre.
It's like a rabbit named possum.
I dated a girl that had a, a rabbit in a room in a cage.
And first of all, there's an odor.
It's mostly, it's mostly cedar chips, but there is an odor.
This Nick was this one of those things where, as I've heard in apocryphal, um, Aerosmith
songs that she perhaps utilize this rabbit for birth, for pregnancy test.
The rabbit done died.
That's right.
Is it, is it, is she, was she so promiscuous that she had several bunnies by her bedside
to test, rapid test, whether she was pregnant.
Is that what's happening?
If I made it up the bedroom to the, if I made it up the stairs to that bedroom, I'm sure
I wasn't blazing any trail.
That's what I'm saying though.
But so she, do you think that's what was going on?
She kept the rabbit.
She, well, I did not, I had, that's definitely what was happening.
I have not read nor have I seen a, a, it's still to this day, a work called Watership
Down.
You've ever seen Ridership Down?
No.
Is it, it's a book or it's a book and an animated movie and the name of break you, it will it,
the name of the rabbit was a reference to that.
Was it a number?
It was a number.
Okay.
It was a number?
This is my rabbit.
Unban scooped in the, and the chat says Fiverr.
That's that's the name.
Do you know that girl?
See, I wasn't the first.
There it is.
No.
Okay.
He knows that girl too.
Yeah.
The chat knows everything.
Well, I got those rabbit girls.
And she was kind of shitty that I hadn't seen this.
Yeah.
She's right to be shitty on that.
You need to see that.
And then you need to see plague dogs and then you'll never have to smile again.
I'll save a lot of time.
No, I just listened to that REM song.
Everybody hurts on repeat in my car.
Seriously though, plague dogs is the same animation house did Watership Down and it
is the most devastating thing I've ever seen on film.
Plague dogs.
Yep.
Okay.
Thanks for having me.
All right, buddy.
Thanks, Nick.
We appreciate your horse sense.
Let's do a little Scoop Mail.
We got one here from the Salt Lake Scoop.
Hey guys, I thought I would share something from a recent Vegas trip to let you comment
on it.
We went to Brad Garrett's Comedy Club recently until we're in the MGM Grand.
Just a quick summary of the format of the show.
Brad comes out and tells some jokes.
Then he introduces the first comedian.
Then Brad comes out and tells a few more jokes.
Then he introduces the second comedian.
Brad told a few jokes indicating that he was not a big fan of Trump.
He did a Trump voice and did the Trump dance and said it looks like he's jacking off two
guys.
Brad made a few other jokes at Trump's expense.
He did more Trump material than I thought someone would do at a Vegas show.
Yeah, Brad is a very anti-Trump fella.
We were at the show two days after Charlie Kirk was murdered during Brad's second set
that a woman across the room stood up and addressed Brad.
I thought I heard her say, "Can we have a moment for Charlie Kirk?"
Is this Brad Garrett?
It's Brad Garrett, yeah.
Is Brad Garrett on stage at the Brad Garrett Comedy Club?
I thought I heard her say, "Can we have a moment for Charlie Kirk?"
Brad responded by saying, "A moment of silence for Charlie Kirk?
You know this is a comedy show, right?"
Then he quickly followed up.
It is tragic.
Everyone should be able to say whatever they want without that happening to them.
With that comment, about 70% of the crowd applauded and Brad had won the crowd back.
At this point, the staff began to move toward this woman.
Brad said to the staff, "No, no, no, she's okay.
Just leave her," indicating that he didn't want her kicked out.
Brad then went on with his jokes.
His show was almost completely derailed by that woman and he got the control back so
quickly.
It was fascinating.
It went from cringing to applauding and back to laughing in less than a minute.
A few questions for you performers and Vegas insiders, was there any chance that this was
staged?
No.
No, no, no.
No way.
You're just looking at a guy who has dealt with this shit.
I just saw Mark Maron talking about hecklers and crowd work in general.
I can't recall who he was talking with now.
But he was talking about crowd work as it being something that's currently hot right
now.
A lot of comedians are being praised because they do awesome crowd work.
And Maron was like, "Hey, it's important," to the degree that you're able to quickly
address a heckler and get your shit back on track.
But I don't think making your career on crowd work is really that laudable, per se.
But I think what you saw there was a very experienced professional who was able to very
quickly turn it around and get it back on track and reset the mood.
But that's experience, man.
I mean, that's the goal, too.
It's just a reset.
And the brevity of it, that's the other thing, able to do it quickly, just like done.
You don't even realize.
Yeah.
No, I mean, it's a weird...
The internet makes things change so fast.
And so at first, standups felt like they were really hampered by social media because they
couldn't put their best material online because they consider it burned, something they can't
do again, right?
And so then they started realizing that younger people started reasoning faster.
They just did crowd work and put crowd work clips up, then they could protect their best
material and just do crowd work.
Right.
But then crowd work clips just became so much more popular and so much more viral, then all
of a sudden you had all these people purposely putting comedians on the spot and doing those
kind of contests.
Those crowd work shows and all kinds of other examples of it.
So strange.
And so crowd work just has become this version of it and even stranger, and I've talked about
this with magicians and comedians, is how much the audience now is just prepared to
talk to the person on stage.
Right.
Yeah.
Right?
Oh, it's amazing.
They're ready.
Back in the '80s and '90s and even early 2000s, if a comedian started talking to someone
from stage, that person would be embarrassed.
Yeah.
Yes.
They would recoil.
That person didn't want to have that conversation.
And now it's just like, "Yeah, yeah, I'm ready to talk.
What are we talking about?"
No.
That's why they're going to comedy shows to become part of the show.
It's right.
Fucking weird.
Krista Hendricks, who's crushing it, right?
She figured it out.
This is something that happened to her.
She wanted to do crowd work, so she went with the burner magic tricks.
And people liked her crowd work so much, she had to keep eliminating magic tricks in her
show.
Right.
She had to do less and less magic tricks.
And you can watch now in her more recent clips, when she goes to talk to the audience, they're
just ready.
They're ready to talk to her.
They're ready to have all the answers.
They're ready to talk about their occupation or the specifics of the situation they're
writing about.
Right?
No problem talking to people now.
They know their job.
So it is-
They know their part.
It's wild.
It is bizarre.
Nope.
Oh, that's from Saltlick.
Thank you.
Thank you, Saltlick Scoop.
Did Newman plug his podcast before he went?
Sorry, I had to take a call that I was gone for a minute.
Oh, no, he did not.
He's re-launching-
What's Newman's new podcast?
He's re-launching his podcast, Newman Unleashed, on September 25th.
You can start listening to his solo pod.
There you go.
Check it out.
Listen to Newman if you hate yourself.
Get that horse sense.
Wait a minute.
Here's some Jock vs. Nerd.
You want to do a little Jock vs. Nerd action?
Oh, am I?
Fuck yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Oh, that sucks.
We got an old school Jock vs. Nerd coming at us for Nesticles!
I'm on the hunt for balls.
We got an old school Jock vs. Nerd coming at us for Nesticles, Scoop!
Nesticles sent this in a while ago, he reconstructed it for me because I missed it back then.
Here are a dozen episode titles from our show, from our very own beloved Matt and Mattingly's
Ice Cream Social.
Here are a dozen episode titles.
The question is very simply, figure out which of these titles are real and which ones Nesticles
Scoop made up.
That's it!
Easy game, fellas.
Easy game.
I'm going to tell you a title, you're going to tell me is that a title of our show that
the three of us produce and put out on the air?
You're just going to tell us, is that a title that we produced or is that just a made up
thing?
First one.
Paul, I'm thinking of a number.
What is it?
Two.
That's it.
That's exactly right.
You're first.
Bleach Thy Crevices, Bleach Thy Crevices.
Is that an ICS title or is that made up?
Made up.
Matt, is that an ICS title or is that made up?
Say it again.
Bleach Thy Crevices.
I think it's made up.
It is made up.
Good job both of you.
All right.
We played a game like this before and I have an unfair advantage in that I go back and
forth with Slaking Fool about titles for each episode before they go up every time.
I'm the one who uploads the episode, so I type it twice before I put it out into the
interview.
This is on a curve.
I usually retweet it and I usually see it.
That's true.
Oh yeah.
I usually pay some measure of attention to it.
Rich Men Knit, Rich Men Knit.
Real or fake?
Rich Men Knit.
Matt, you want to go first on this one?
Rich Men Knit, K-N-I-T.
Fake.
Paul.
Sounds real to me.
Point for Paul.
That was episode 602.
All right.
Rich Men Knit.
The twerking disaster.
Real.
Shout them out.
You know them.
Real.
The twerking disaster.
I'll say fake.
It is fake.
Two points for Paul.
Pete, Pete Seeking Missles.
Real.
S-E-E-G-I-N-G.
That's real.
That's episode 780.
Yeah.
So Paul's up.
Shalali Leg.
Paul's up by two now, yeah?
I think so.
I think Paul's plus two.
Yeah.
Shalali Leg.
True.
Yeah, that's a real one.
That's a real one, 733.
The Moist Horizon.
Oh, that sounds like us.
It does.
It really sounds like us.
But it doesn't ring a bell.
Yeah, right?
I'll say fake.
Okay, Matt.
I still say fake.
I should do it for gamesmanship.
I should change it up.
I think it's fake.
It is fake.
Good call, buddy.
Good call.
Good work.
You put us on a deal.
The Androgynous.
Fake.
Oh, I think that might be real.
It is real.
1081.
Yeah.
That's lazy.
Ah!
That's a lazy title.
That's exactly what I thought.
I was like, "The Androgynous.
That's not real."
I scrolled down.
We have a show called The Androgynous.
The Gospel of Jacob.
I mean, on a chat GPT level, we must have, right?
Right.
That just seems like at the end of 1,000 episodes, we must have done that.
The Gospel of Jacob?
Yeah.
The Gospel of Jacob.
Did you say real, Matt?
I said real.
I'll say real.
It's fake.
We never did The Gospel of Jacob.
Out of town.
Let's call this episode that one.
The Gospel of Jacob and the moist horizon.
We didn't use both of those.
Chili Chilis.
C-H-I-L-L-Y.
C-H-I-L-L-I apostrophe S.
I'll say that's real.
Chili Chilis.
That's real.
Oh, that is fake.
That is fake.
What?
Stop it.
I know.
That's three that we have to use now.
My brain is confused.
Porn sniffing dog.
That's real.
Yeah.
That's definitely real.
That's episode 679.
The fifth nugget hits rock bottom.
I'm already upset with how poorly I'm doing on this, by the way.
Three wrong is unacceptable.
It's not like you gave a speech talking about how you had an advantage in this game at the
beginning of the game, though.
I think that's real.
Exactly.
That's why I was putting myself on blast on purpose.
I wanted to stay sharp.
Yeah.
I'll say real on the nugget.
What is it?
Oh, Paul says real on the nugget.
The fifth nugget hits rock bottom.
I'm going to say false.
It is real.
Episode 1133.
I'm running away with it, Matt.
I'm running away.
That's a recent one.
Yeah.
Paul's destroying me on this.
At 1133, you say recent, Matt.
That's like three years ago.
Maybe four.
It's a year ago.
No, it's like six months ago, right?
No, no, it's not.
Yeah.
I don't know what number we're on now.
What number are we on now?
What number is this show?
We're on 1240 something.
Yeah.
So it's been about 100 episodes.
It's been a year.
It's a long time.
Yeah.
This is the last one.
And of course, as tradition dictates, this one is worth 18,000 points.
Don't leave me gross.
That's real.
You both get 18,000 points, but Paul wins by three.
That was episode 454, and that is from the Nesticle Scoop.
Thank you so much, Nesticle Scoop, and thank you for rebuilding that Jock vs. Nerd that
you had made a while back.
We really appreciate it.
If you want to send us a Scooperty or a Price of Skryte Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk Jock
vs. Nerd, or just send us an old school Jock vs. Nerd like Nesticle Scoop just did, or just
go over there and send us some Scoop mail.
You can do all those things over there at Hayscoops.com.
Head over to Hayscoops.com.
Do all those things.
It's going to be great.
Buy yourself tickets to Scoop Fest.
Yes.
You don't have to hear us plug Scoop Fest a whole lot more coming up in the next couple
of weeks.
Get them now.
Do it.
You're going to miss it.
Awesome.
Who sent that in?
Nesticle.
Nesticle Scoop.
Thank you, Nesticle Scoop, for making me doubt myself.
Really now, I'm a terrible podcast host.
I don't think that's why you're a bad podcast host.
Thank you, Jacob.
Those were great, though.
Even the made-up ones were really tricky.
Oh, there were the made-up ones.
I'm just upset that we haven't already used them.
Jacob, you're right.
Why I am a bad podcast host is I muted my Zoom because I had to take a call, but then
I didn't mute my recorder.
So in the middle of the Newman interview, you have to figure out ...
That's where Newman's talking, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I got you.
I'm just going to make a note about that right now.
It'll be fine to just hear Matt's rando conversation in the middle of the interview.
With my corporate magic booker.
That'll be great.
Yeah, that'll be great.
Professionals.
That's right.
Nicholas Newman in the chat, great time to take a call.
Yeah, yeah, Richard wants us to leave it in.
Thirsty Scoop wants us to leave that in.
There's a Patreon level.
I do notice, and I don't know what to do about it, because I don't know how to mute the recorder,
so I just leave the room.
So it's only the beginning of the conversation before I leave.
It will not be hard to find.
When you hear a different voice on the phone on my audio, you'll know.
That's it.
Holy shit.
That's why I'm not a good podcast host.
Other reasons.
I want to thank Ben Jalef creating this podcast.
Thanks, Ben.
I want to thank the following people, all of whom, consider glamping their first time
camping.
Yeah.
Dan Martin, Daniel Loeser, Daniel Matias Ferrer, Danny Olwein, Darren Cunningham, Darth Scooper,
Dave Serial, Dave Hanson, Dave Slusher, David Johnson, David A. Small, David Gravel, David
K., David Peterson, David Sorensen, David Walker, Dan Laszlo, Derek Josier, Dole Whip
Scoop, Dippin Dots Jack, Dirty Old Scoop, and Distiller Scoop.
These wonderful people refer to themselves as paint horses.
Edward Bender, Alyssa Walsack, Elkton Magic Scoop, Eric Nilsen, Erotic Scrape Scoop, Evil
Monkey, Fate Out Scoop, Fifi, Finn Steffensen, Flat Kidney, Frankie's Tiki Scoop, Freehold
Scoop, Freeze Dried Scoop, Frozen 49th Scoop, Frozen Cusser, Fudgy the Whale, Galusha Scoop,
Galactic President Scooper Star, McScoopsalot, Galen Diggs, Garrett Godfrey, Gas Man Scoop,
and Gaspacho Scoop.
I want to thank the following people who know the old song from the Half Cow, Half Horse
show.
Of course is of course, of course, of course.
That's Doc Scoop, Don Donnie, Don't Say Scoop Name, Doug Lay, Dr. Science Scoop,
Dr. Scoop Little, Dr. Tobias Scoopay, Duck Flambe, Duke Scoop, Dwayne Webb, Ed Shortarms
Marcus, Ed Ondrick, Ed Wagner, and Ed Les Scoop.
Big thanks to these individuals who have far better bathroom luck than Jacob usually does.
Even though we didn't have a fun Jacob bathroom story this episode, I'm sure we'll have one
very soon again.
The Gospel of Jacob.
Yes, Gelato Problems, Gelato Steve, Gene Zink, Genetic Scoop, George Guskov, Gerardo Garcia,
Gizmo Scoop, Greater Sunday Scoop, Gravel Scoop, Green Wolf Scoop, Grill Sergeant Scoops,
Guy Wade, Gwarthok, and Hatchet Scoop.
And I'd like to thank the following scoops.
I'd like to thank Heather Divine Hansen, Holly Marshmallow Lightly, Horse Dad, or House Dad
Scoop, not Horse Dad Scoop, that's a whole different person, Hylian Scoop, I don't have
a Scoop name, Ian A. Chapman, Ian Soto, Ice Cream Manwich, Ice Blue Scoop, I want a Scoop
baby, Jacob Dinklater, Jake Schneider, James Dawson, James Hubbell, Jameson Fisher, Janine
Lankard, Jason Klepper, Jason Horkostas, Jason Specklin, Jason Street, Jason Vasquez, Jason
Victor, Jason Yenowitz, Jay Shapiro, Jed Taxon, Jeff Faust, Jeff Harris, Jeff Libby, Jeff
Loomis, Ginny E. Barb, Jeremy Hudson, Jesse Rain, Jill Short, Jimmy Sloanina, John Carter,
and John Bloor, thank you all so much, we sure do love you.
Thank you so much.
If you'd like to be thanked on air, if you want to hop on our Twitch broadcasts, all
you have to do is get on over to "Why can't I finish this plug?"
It's literally the thing that pays us.
Go to PreachingFun.com so that we don't do this for free.
Or if you want your kids to sleep in a teepee while you sleep in a chuck wagon, head on
over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz, that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
Like Matt said, that is how we do the show, it's what makes the show possible.
So if you think this show is worth more than $0, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those
are the places that you can go to support this show and get some cool stuff.
Like you get to hang out in the Zoom with us.
Our Zoom attendance today got full on spoilers for ScoopFest this year, just in the pre-show.
So there is something worth coming over and hanging out in the Zoom chat with us if you
are on Patreon, so do that.
Look at your Patreon messages, we send out the Zoom link twice a week, every week, no
matter what.
Well, unless we're not going to do it, then we wouldn't send the link out.
But other than that, no matter what.
Yeah.
Right.
All things considered.
Pretty much all the time, though.
Alright.
Usually.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
We'll see you at the cone!
Generally, Tom had no problem hitting his opponent with the supremely epic ultimate legendary
long-range blaster.
But with his spotty Wi-Fi, his target skipped around like a second-hand CD.
The story you're hearing is 30 seconds long, which is the amount of time needed to unplug
and restart your modem.
Take better aim and get Gateway Fiber that's always friendly, fast, and fair.
Check availability at gatewayfiber.com and don't forget about your first month free.