Here we go
Stop it solar scoop. Oh
Hello there people are putting emojis of tits up in the chat now. I zoom here. It's very distracting, but I like it
I want to thank you the ice cream truck drivers. Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers
Let's see who are the ice cream truck drivers boy see I'm so distracted
Who are the ice cream truck drivers? Those are the folks that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes
I don't have a new list yet
But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver before this show and a future episode this month
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver
And I sure hope you do preaching fun commas where you can go preaching fun comm head over there sign up to be an ice cream
Truck driver and who knows?
The life you save
May be your own
Oh a show
Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
Shout out to win Matt Donnelly discovered the best
Manual nose hair trimmer that I've still ever used the eagle
It's time for Matt Maddenly's ice cream social sitting in Las Vegas. It's Matt Donnelly also sick in Las Vegas
It's me Jacob the audio guy sitting somewhere. We'll figure it out later. It's Paul. We're preaching fun. Yeah
Paul's not here
You know, it's funny. We got a couple of
Compliments recently this thing our recent episodes have just been have been on a good in a good spot
We've been out there
What better way to bring it to a screeching halt than simply not knowing where Paul Mattingly is on this earth?
I think it's maybe a good way to just slow it down
We'll show you but the chat is continuing to find different ways to portray boobs in emoji form in the chat
It's very exciting
Lori else off the two sunny side eggs. Very nice. Very nice
Everyone so creative. Oh, it's got text from Paul breaking news. Oh, hey
Be home soon, so it wasn't sleeping. Oh
Well, we don't know that you might have been like on a park bench somewhere just just dozing
Just feeding the birds and just
Fetch in the middle of January in Pittsburgh, no
It's so nice out it is freezing for Las Vegas, right? It's 44 degrees
40 degrees
It's got down to 38 which is Celsius for our foreign listeners. So I don't know five
I've were terrible at converting Fahrenheit Celsius. I have no idea
But it's negative 30. I don't know. Yeah
But I go to the gym and I'm my gym right now
It's just like our little community center because my actual gym gym closed my gym gym closed
Oh, oh Jim Jim top of the morning to you my Jim Jim closed
So my my regular gym closed it's gonna be taken over by a crunch Jim eventually
It's a coming soon what thing which is also funny, right? Like pizza places just become other pizza places
Right like Jim's like what else you're gonna do that space it has like it has a pool and workout equipment
Are you just gonna so it's gonna be another gym? Oh, yeah, I forget about the pool. Sure. That makes sense
Yeah, it's why I had joined that particular gym is because all right
Cuz you could go in there and and and and stare at the young ladies who were swimming exactly
You can go swim exactly but I have those glasses that look like eyeballs that are looking up
And so therefore you can't tell that I'm staring at the spring ones
Yeah, but I taped them so they just look like they're looking up good smart. So that way that way I'm not creepy
That's why he's the best and I
Go, so what I do is I go to the community centers called the multi multi multi Jen multi Jen center multi generational center, right?
Okay, so they have you know kids camps. They got swimming lessons. They have like classrooms for to teach classes for adults
it's a big it's a big big outfit over there and one of the has is a gym in a walking track and a pool but
A big like okay. It's like where the where the competitions are where the swimming competitions are
locally for for the schools
Gotcha, and so I go to the gym in the evening around like 530
Which means the Sun has just gone down and spit was super windy yesterday like really windy crazy breezy yesterday
And I look out the window and there's a fucking swim meet happening
Was like what fucking hell on earth
Where why it's it's still January. I know we live in the desert
But it's still January
Why on earth is an outdoor swimming meet happening?
I mean best case scenario in the pool and I assume an unheated pool in the desert in January. It's not pleasant
It's not nice
No, like without a breeze. It's just it still was a cold day
But it was like that means like, you know, like oh man when you get wet and then there's a breeze
I mean, that's all right. Yeah, I couldn't believe I just all these kids
It's honestly the reason that I don't swim half the time. I don't swim
It's cuz right now I'm just not swimming in case a breeze comes up. I
Mean it's been a minute, but I that story where I was hired to be a
Bathing suit model by accident. I think I told the story on there
It's been a while. It's been a while though
But yeah, so so they'd cast just off of headshots and then it was me three male models and four
gorgeous women models and then a bunch of bathing suits that didn't fit on my fat body and then
Right. I forgot they had the bathing suits
So I stuffed into one of them like a sausage and then yep
Good
We had it to go do like a pool shoot and there's literally like two pools like a giant lap pool and this beautiful kind of
circular fountain pool for like
Hanging out and renting cabanas, right?
Mm-hmm. So they set this really fancy camera and they art directed me to the furthest place away from the camera
They put a fake that
That is good art direction
They put a fake drink in my hand and put me literally 200 yards away from the camera
All right, so they had the hotter people closer to the first pool
I was just supposed to be decorative like background and the second pole
Here's what they did. They put all the they put all the super hot people in the close-up pool and they put me behind
the camera with a jib
Can you you hold this this bounce this light bouncer this reflector? Can you hold it?
I don't think I'm even on camera over here. No, you are you are don't worry about it. You're fine
The look I remember still the art dressers face when I was trying to squeeze into a bathing suit and him just going like why
Why are you here?
What have I done to deserve this hanging out in the tent and listen to all the hot people talk about all the different
Things they have for their veggies and vegetable smoothies and which blenders they use and stuff
I was like I know what a blender is
I
Just put snakes in mine
But it was freezing cold. It was like a freak. It was it was like it wasn't as cold as today
But it was it was probably like 50 degrees still very cold to be in a pool. And so I
Being the only person in pool B
Really took my time getting in try to not even let it ripple
He's like even if I just got up on my on my stomach like the wind was blowing and it would just freeze, right?
So I was saying like perfectly still in the water to like not like to establish a level and not change it, right?
That was yeah, that's what I was doing. And then at one point they want to shake things up
I'm gonna shake things up and said I move people around
Except me. They said to keep me right where I was
I
Had taken the first shoot to a build a wall
They set the wall up between me and the camera. It's all one of the hot guys pretending your friends with fat
So back there, right? So they sent him back there
And you said that's not how you pronounce my name
And
And he was a big old beautiful dummy. So he ran great and just jumped in the pool
Yes ran and just left into the pool and I was like, no I've established
You're rooting for both of us
He gets up he's wet and then we start saying still pretending to talk and gesture one another while they do this right and
And he is like man. It sucks. It's cold
Sure does buddy
He's like cuz the winds blowing I was like, oh no one of us has already figured that out
Yeah, the other of us knows which blender to have to make the best vegetable smoothies and the other knows how wind works
on cold skin
But we both got this game
We're both getting the same check buddy
I
So remember that shoot came out it was it was it was not I was not in the pool stuff
I was in the at one point they like decided like
Set her attention on me and like do things with like they were pushing me in the pool, right?
And that was oh, okay. Those were the those are the final shots. The pool was me getting pushed in the pool
while girls with their dad showed up
Give us money and let us gamble go away
The those those didn't make it because they probably looked over things like it just looks like we're picking on someone
Now I was just fat this time I was still young so I didn't come off as their dad
I just came off as like I don't know their gay best friend or
You know someone they went to high school with you know that kind of a thing
Who's with us for the day
This is a make-a-wish guy that said he wanted to hang out at the Caesars pool before he died. I
Didn't know they did exchange students to the Caesars pool, but I guess they do. That'd be great
Like you're dying like you want I want to you want to hang out with famous magicians
No, I want to know what it's like to get bottle servers and have bottles hang out. That's my I
Want you to just buy me a table at Omni
Craziest nightclub make-a-wish is like we can't afford this. I want a poolside cabana at towel
Right give it could we just buy you a pool just buy you a pool
Someone in chat saying they're trying to distract me with their zoom background their zoom background is the crucifixion
It's just it's it's three people on crosses on a hillside, but I'm not sure if that's the real one
Cameras back then I mean
You know not to put the car before the horse here, but that's a beautiful sunset. I mean, it's perfect
Perfect sense. How could you see that sunset behind three people hanging on crosses and not believe in God?
Wait, someone said do you see the letters the letters on there? Oh, it just says it says titties or tits. Oh good. Oh
The cross of the crosses spell titties now I get it
Great boy. Did that take me too long and
Not help the audio version of this podcast at all
All right, but yeah, I think we're doing great
Hey when you were growing up Jacob did saying the word it sucks like that sucks was that considered like extreme oh
That was definitely considered that was a that was a word we could get in trouble for yeah me too
Yeah, my kids throw that like it's nothing all the time
Really? Yeah
Do you smack him just give him a taste of the back of the hand at one point?
I was like, you know, I offered to make a breakfast whatever they're like
Oh, do we have it? You know, do we have waffles? I look I was like, no, we're out of waffles and my youngest goes
Well, that sucks
and I
Didn't go like hey timeout
Was an extreme thing to say when I was a kid you guys start out like it's nothing and when you directed at me
It's very jarring and it makes me really angry
Sorry, I'm making you breakfast are you spoiled asses don't have waffles today mother
But yeah, so my kids say sucks like no problem to hear other kids say it so I guess it's okay to say sucks
maybe maybe um, I
Definitely have a memory of me saying something sucks to my dad and him stopping and just just looking at me and saying something along
the lines of sucks what?
Go ahead
What does it suck?
You're like it was definitely something along those lines was like I put point-taken titties dad titty
Yeah socks
Saying something blows definitely couldn't say shut up. Although you can't you still can't say shut up. My kids know just say shut up
We got in trouble when we were little for stupid if we if we called somebody stupid
We got in trouble for that. I
Remember really getting in trouble
The first the first time I thought I had to like get caught cursing and had to confess to my dad
I said up yours
Which I don't even think
I don't even think that's like even on the radar as an insult anymore
That was huge. I I said up your nose with a rubber hose
Mattingly is here Paul Mattingly everybody everybody everyone Paul Mattingly. Hey guys
Well Paul, you're late. So up yours, buddy. Oh boy. Now I'm getting it now
You know what it's absolutely fair the boys told me we adjusted for the time I wrote it on my calendar
For some reason this morning I woke up and I go. Oh, yeah two o'clock podcast
Do do do do do fart fart fart just tootling around that was part of it
Okay
The other part was I'm doing my morning business
Getting ready to take a shower
uh-huh, and I'm scrolling on my phone and
What to my wondering eyes should appear but the local toy shop going business sale
Oh, we never have everything we never
Everything must go
the fact that he came back is just
It's only ten minutes away from my house, so I was down there is basically the bad signal went to the sky
Yeah, I had no choice
They entered the siren call and went to the toy store and just was zombieing out for an hour. Just oh
What can I get? You know, I got I got a couple good little little trinkets. Nothing too crazy and go too crazy
Local toy stores also go get a business. So pour one out. Yeah
No
this was a
This place called Toyland
Anyone has ever thought Paul isn't that selective with his rage? Okay. No, I this place is
Okay, you guys have you guys don't have you guys don't have ollie's on that side of the world
No, I don't always so ollie's for the East Coasters is this discount chain?
That's sort of like big lots was in its heyday
I'm from the East Coast. Okay, like a newer East Coast thing. I think so. Yeah, okay, so
You remember big lots when it first popped off yeah get some really
May as a kid you could get some amazing deals
You could take five bucks down there and come home with something significant. Yeah, you know, oh, yeah. Yeah, so
Ollie's does this they get warehouses full of old toys and things and put them at pretty deep discount and sometimes they
You know clearance them out even there
What this toy store Toyland was doing was clearing out the best of Ollie's sales
Bringing them to their store and repricing them above and right at MSRP or higher
So I was kind of like well, this isn't a business
I mean
So their business plan was take things out of the bargain bin mark them up and then try to resell them. Yes
That's already called eBay. I know
It's basically like an eBay but but not as many
good
Items now occasionally I found some deals at the win stores start doing corporate dumpster diving
Things are bad all over things are bad all over and I hate to see a small business go under but I also know
That they are straight-up just resellers and they put everything at a price that no one could deal with and they were doing big-time
Pokemon scalping as well. So I'm just like man
Do you think it's possible that they're just faking the out-of-business sale and they're just gonna be one of those stores
That's perpetually going out of business. That's just their new thing
No, I the owner was there and I heard you guys are listening to the last episode of Matt Madley's. Oh
Now the owners the owners were there and they were talking about
The next chapter or whatever. So clearly they've got some other scheme up there 11 is the next chapter
11 you're right. You're right. That's yeah, there's two locations in the Pittsburgh area that are going under
Again, it it makes me sad but you know
Not that sad because it was a dumb model and I would go like I'd been there like four or five times
They'd only been open about a year and I'd been there a couple times to try and support them and the last time I went
I just walked right out with nothing because I was like there ain't shit here
You know, it's just sad did you ever talk to him? Like did they properly nerd out about toy products where they know?
It's not like that. They're not in it for the love. He's not in it for the love. He's just a scalpy. He's a scalpy scalp
This is it Paul need some heart in there. I
Imagine he has I imagine he has probably one
Fixation. I don't know what that might be
You come back to Vegas you always go to the same toy spot around the corner from my house
Yeah, Ralph's his name, right? Well Ralph's is the comic book shop. Okay. Oh, right
And then and then Ralph's just happened to have a new toy store rogue toys built
Place right in that same slot. That's a total nerd cave now, man. It's got rogue toys. It's got that
Smashing ground rogue toys has always been in that in that ballpark though
They've always like when they were downtown and everything they were always that like real nerdy spot
Like yeah, no rogue toys is great. I had wonderful
I always I always knew that if Paul got a divorce and then got remarried I could go get his remarried gift at that rogue toys
You could you could buy half my collection. I sold nearly four thousand dollars worth of toys to them and
And that was at a loss for me
You know when I was moving I had to get rid of so much stuff
But they were cool about it. The only thing that really bugged me is I went back in and I'd sold them some of my
Mega blocks turtle stuff and I I let go of a piece that I came back and I was like
What are you charging for that that I gave you for ten dollars?
So, yeah there were there one or two go back and look again
Well, I mean well that was the thing I went back and I was like, oh look, it's my entire collection on display
That's what SJ will do SJ will do that when we go to concerts
She'll be like we'll be in our spot and then she'll I'll see her on her phone and then she'll be like hey
What what did we pay for these tickets again?
No, I mean hey look no regrets you gotta if you're a collector, you know collections come and go
That's what it is, you know
It's it's just and I've I've been so fortunate to build back so much cool stuff here in the new space
And I don't know. I showed you guys last week last time the amazing
Enterprise that I just got which was you know a lazlo I showed them the video
Of the enterprise that I've set up. It's just it's a gorgeous
So I've got I've got more collectibles and I know what to do with it's lovely, you know, it's just fun spending time
so I apologize that
My forgetful brain and my blindness in toys led me to be a half hour late. So
we all assumed you were dead and
That's the right assumption to make you know, and we started a podcast anyway
A wellness check at your door. Just the
Matt text to me is like I can't knock on your door. So good luck. Hope you're not dead
Yeah, I'll stop Paul might be dead they would add into the podcast anyway, that's the following sponsor today's show
Oh, I just had it up. Where'd it go? God damn it
Today's show is a lot. We go to Toy Story. I'll be right back
All right. Today's show is brought if it's 50% off. I'll let you go
I'm sure no off for breeze flavored vodka presents booze cruise on the trash barge
That's from Nathan's hot dog scoop in 2021 Paul I'm sure I
Shouldn't speak for Nathan here, but I think Smirnoff for breeze as his practice is also good enough to be its own commercial
But if you want to also just commit to the booze on the track, I agree
I think we're good with Smirnoff for breeze. Yeah for breeze is our sponsor
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da ta
Hello comrade. Do you have horrible breath in morning from drinking from?
Urinal where only water is available?
Then solution I am having for you. We are providing new smirnoff smirnoff Febreeze
bringing
delicious clear booze right to face and then
No stinking mouth from from Febreeze chemical to wash your teeth and tongue. Oh
So good spray on furniture when done spit on pet and children to make less smell horrible
Whatever need smirnoff Febreeze now available in pino colada and linen crisp
Take choice what want linen crisp pino colada shot you tell you tell me I know your boss
I know your boss you air control have drink have great breath
I I guess I'll take the pino colada one pino colada coming up sir good choicings here you go
to whole big bottle
That is to I get two bottles of vodka for that's that is the shot that is what we call shot out here
in Georgia
To whole bottle of vodka is shot one shot
He scoops to check out
Georgia
Huh, is Georgia still around hey, it's still intact. I don't know hour to hour
We don't know we don't know right now. What do we know? Whatever we know is God's will whatever's happening
It's what the Lord wants it Leon in the chat. He's rushing out to the liquor store to buy a case. Hey
There you go, I already have
JD
Maker of the scoop documentary. Uh-huh says he is coming out to see the show
That I'm doing with your wife Jacob on on the 14th with Sarah has to go good
Wednesday January 14th the composer's room come see a nice variety lineup with Sarah's to Ross
SJ Shayna Christmas and more
JD says he's coming just because he wants me to show him the the doll video from the John Wick experience. That's why he's
He's paying money to see a show to hang out with me so that I can show him my phone and I can just show him
The video that's why he's coming. I mean that's a piece of Vegas history right there
Checks out that's real Vegas insider history. We've got that's pretty awesome
It is a very valuable commodity to have for sure
I
Leave tomorrow for a gig in South Bend, Indiana. It's a private show. It's a corporate show
So if you're oh in Indiana, so I can't come kick rocks. Yeah
You come see me in Chicago on the 27th or in Wabash Wabash, Indiana
I forget which day but jokers of magic that that last week of January into February
We're doing a and nine shows. So so sorry corporate gig. I will come right back. It's a corporate gig
Yes for cool company
I had to I still haven't done my homework on them yet, but first. Yeah company. Well, I hope it goes
Like a white supremacist group. Yeah. Yeah something about like pure race and
Sure controlling the banks. I forget but yeah
All the companies are that way nowadays
Can't tell one from the other
Hoochie they're throwing a party and they're throwing the throwing the letters DEI into a burning dumpster
Damn it to hell
Damn it all
But I yeah, so I got a flat there and I'm flying in Chicago and driving from there's a two-hour drive
And I figured with the weather and stuff
I'd be better flying to a major airport and I wanted no connections because of my baggage. So I'm yeah
He has a name and it's Sarah
But yeah
New Year's resolution was to start learning Spanish and piano. I haven't started piano yet. Okay
Cuz I but you're studying Spanish now. Yeah, I've downloaded two apps
All right, Matt
Let's see
Good number of apps. Let me grill you Matt. Go ahead Juan es alto como es Juan
Juan es alto see
Alright, okay you've passed level one you've
For people who aren't on the video side of this podcast Paul was so genuinely happy
He was so pleased with himself
I don't they call me Paul duo lingo Mattingly. Okay, they do call you that
I've done one is jump speak and one is duo lingo. Yeah, okay
and
They both it's a 21 jump speakers
21 jump speak right and this is eventually the goal is that I can go
Undercover in a Spanish high schools and hunt down drug dealers. So that's what happens if you graduate
You go into a recruiting program
Hola fellow students
Don't they a star like cocaine factory
Como es Juan
We we speak English
They not you're clearly an old white guy
Come on I'm trying out for the track team tomorrow. Oh, sorry, but
Thank you, you've got that Benjamin button shit
so one of the things they ask you is they say, you know, can you want us to
Download your contacts to see who else is doing this. Oh
And they could partner you up do that and normally I say no to all of those. Yeah things
But they're gonna barge your friends with shit. I was like, oh, let's give it a shot. No
And I haven't heard from anyone else yelling at me yet
But I woke up to my first kind of social aspect to text from Duolingo. Oh
Hey
Your buddy Rick Passanio is studying Spanish on here. Do you want to connect with Rick and
I couldn't write back to do a lingo to be like Rick's been dead for six years, but sure
Like oh my god, if you can connect me to my dead friend Rick like yeah
Wait a minute. It's like a fucking Ouija board kind of feature the dual
Promising if the only way to talk to ghosts is Spanish then yeah, let's let's commit. Let's do this
What is the Spanish word for ghost?
Have you been wanting to talk to your dead friends and relatives?
Come try Duolingo
Duolingo we guarantee that you can talk to your dead friends and relatives
- oh, we go. It's a it's a side. It's a side
App called you will linger
It keeps you in contact with all your dead friends after you expire you will linger lets you chat
You will linger yes, we use AI generative
Bullshit to make your friends talk back to you from the grave. It's not as scary as it sounds
Except when the AI takes over and starts talking all kinds of racist trash because that's what they do
All of your dead family members will be racist
They're all racist now. Oh my god. It's what happens when you die you become racist. I guess so
I'll tell you who else became racist and that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by
Stiffy's wood service. That's right from kiss me where it smells funny in 2024
Stiffy's wood service. Are you there? I'm Stiffy. Don't you know I got me some wood for you
You want me to bring some over to your house. Mm-hmm. I'll sell to you for a good price
I've got a bunch of wood bunch of wood in my back trunk
Stiffy puts wood in the trunk
If you know what I mean, you want some of Stiffy's wood from the trunk come and get it Stiffy got wood
Stiffy got all the wood you need
Stiffy got sticks and twigs
Stiffy got half trees
Stiffy got wood
Stiffy got wood Stiffy got wood
Wow break it down
What the fuck is happening
Can't row my brain our brains not working well today
Well, maybe one of us cause this first had to be a little late in the program. Oh, oh now we're shifting blame around
Well, okay
We're not shifting it around. I think it's been the same place the whole time. Oh, really?
All right, Matt. All right, Matt, let's let's let's shift some other things around. How about this one? How about this one?
Don't they a style of Bibliotheca?
See one as Bibliotheca sure great
One as Bibliotheca
In the chat look at motherfucker
Take a look at
You stack of books. I'm not you over like a stack of books. I take you out like a stack of books
Fucking why I'm always looking like a bibliotheca new fucking and rice collection looking son of a bitch
Stephen King novels
Section and then in the Bibliotheca looking so do we decimal have an asshole?
You card catalog located motherfucker
Do they even have card catalogs at the library more good. Yes, I don't know sure because we've all been to the library recently
Yeah, I have why I was late to the podcast. I have
50% off I take I take I take my kids at the library
But we rarely we don't usually use the Dewey decimal system over there
No, I guess most of its all been transferred to computer
But I wonder if they ever I guess did they I know there's no reason to keep all that data. I guess on cards. I
Wonder what the I should look online. I'm just asking questions into the fucking void, but
What can you consider a good repurposing of those Dewey decimal card holders?
Oh those huge those huge very specifically sized drawers
well, what would you imagine would be a good second use for those spice rack comes to mind a
Very large spice rack. I mean for a for like a for like an industrial kitchen. I
Mean that's a lot of spice. It would take a lot. It does take up a lot of space gun rack
Could you fit a rifle in some of those long boxes?
Probably oh be kind of cool to just pull out a shelf of guns. I've got it. I've got it. What do you got?
Don't even move them out of the library
Turn them into beehives
In the library just in the library
Beehives an apiary. I mean they would work as hives. I
Suppose. Yep. No, no, I think that's figured it out
Can I bring crystal saying business cards?
Ravi's a storage of Chinese medicine. Yeah, that's how yeah, I think rhino penises would slide in there pretty good
Mm-hmm
Well, once you dehydrate them
Of course, I wasn't talking about non dehydrated rhino penises
Those are what you're always talking about hydrated rhino penises, Paul
You won't shut up about hydrated rhino penis just because it was my band in college
You'll add that one single we did have that one single there's good the shirt was the thing that kept us going
We had a really cool shirt for hydrated rhino penis. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Oh, there's a three-dimensional aspect of it that I think people really appreciate it people liked it
It was made of that pup. Remember that puffy paint. That was such a rage back in the late 80s
It was all puffy paint
Puffy paint dehydrate or hydrated rhino penis shirts were all the rage at my school
Modern-day apothecary tables. Yeah, that could be cool. Oh my god that could store
Pokemon and magic cards. Holy shit that'd be an awesome way to store your Pokemon and magic
I like all these suggestions like we have a giant card catalog. What could we repurpose this as Oh a card holder?
Okay, all right. Yeah, you're right. All right. What else what other thing could you do?
But I already said beehive already got the right answer. What about a bunch of weird long ways aquariums?
But that would have to be just fish that like living in the dark most of the time or
Oh eels
You don't want to turn around drawers of eels and snakes
That don't want to turn around
Eels that hate turning around
Oh
My god, oh it would be great for organizing Lego. Yes
Would be awesome for that I keep waiting for Paul to move on to anything else
But he just keeps listing off things that people are saying that you can do with a card catalog
It's a great topic
We're not talking about enough because think about the thousands of libraries that are out in the country right now and think about the disused
Uh-huh. Dewey decimal card catalog holders. I mean your universities those probably took up a room
Sure, right. Oh, and did those this is the problem we need to be
Destroying this furniture. Are we just throwing these out? Is that what's happening?
Repurposed at a very long aquarium repurpose recycle reuse
Very long aquariums for eels that don't need to turn
Right. Yeah, we could you need directional eels. We could put beta fish. They don't move around very much
Or is that cool to them the who kind of fish the alpha fish
Alpha fish don't don't aren't that's not real that the guy who wrote about the alpha fish regrets his paper about the alpha
Teaching alpha fish how to talk to people I did I did
But I misconstrued it and I thought it was part of the whole alphabet
I thought it was alphabet fish, but you do love a bit. I do
Yeah, don't get me started omega fish the alpha fish
Omega me. Oh, I can't believe I'm gonna move on from this, but let's do some
You you can move on all you want
I am continuing to come up with repurposing ideas for disused card catalogs
Continuing to use Greek letters with aquatic animals
Next up zy dolphins
Zy dolphin sounds like a fucking new medicine for Edie
Like introduce everyone to this my epsilon seahorse
I was like I get targeted on Instagram for
Like basically like don't get the wrong Edie meds if you have to pee urgently after you have an orgasm
Do you like do you sprint to the toilet after after you have an orgasm?
There must be there's a greater. There's a greater scientific
Area of concern
Going on and I was like wait wait isn't that isn't that the whole thing you orgasm and then pee like that's the whole thing
It's like it's your doctor Paul. It's your doctor. It's just one continuous stream, right?
You don't wait for you for you guys orgasm begin peeing is different
Why is the world spinning do you think you're into golden showers? You're not you have a scientific health issue
Boy oh boy that the the amount of
Treatment for that shit. I mean I guess it's whatever well. I know it doesn't for me. I was like wait
I'm not I'm not even a step one of this medical thing yet
So like why are we how did I end up how'd you get on that targeting on the long end of the arc of that?
Yeah, that is very specific like yeah, do you find?
Yeah
Have you experienced slight green discoloration and your balls after ejaculating using this?
Medication you might be using the wrong stuff
You have food coloring
You've been eating green eggs and ham
We got an email from scoopy Ramon
Hey gentleman of the churn and possible guest nope
There was series of random middle connections not worth detailing here
I recently found myself regaling someone with a story of enthusiasm over experience from my past
It made me think that one or all of you might have a story that fits this category
My stories are enthusiasm over experience
Are we are we insinuating that our enthusiasm?
Outpaces our experience well when we say I love boobies. What does that sound like it sound like we have experience or does it sound like?
Yeah
In that respect my
Base is my experience
So here's my example of enthusiasm versus experience in high school
I first caught the acting bug by doing the school plays a friend of mine
I'll call him Chuck because that was his name had played an extra as a freshman and had told me repeatedly about how much fun
It was and how many girls were in the school plays one of those two things convinced me to audition
Fast-forward a bit and Chuck and I are now both extras in the next school play the play was the crucible
Oh as freshmen
We were both relegated to extras in a scene where two or three other characters are talking Chuck
And I were to play jail guards or something, but they were of course non-speaking parts, but shouldn't we do be doing something?
Dumbass attention starve sixteen-year-old me asked that exact question
Fine, just don't steal focus was the reply
In the production of the crucible in my high school there were two
Puritanical jail guards who so fervently believed that the rest of the world was too chill about
Armageddon and stuff to stay in England
Did their best to not make any noise as they shot dice in the background of the Salem witch trials?
also, I
Can't tell if it makes it better or worse that we all my cause
I
Can't tell if it makes it better or worse
then we fashion our own dice out of clay from the art room so that they would be period in hopes that the director would
Let us do more and that is
way worse
Definitely worse
Hilarious that is how lair period dice
No way those dice rolled true right so they could have rigged some kind of gambling scheme
Because they certainly always rolled, you know six or something like, you know, right? There's no way they built a great
evenly weight distributed clay dice
Probably you are you guys want to get into my dice game here. I got a I got a dice game going on over here
I got a special homemade dice. I just got to sell them hard
Gonna sell them hard on the crucible thing and that these are, you know era appropriate gambling
That's right
What's that? What's a priest me for craftsmen? We could take him for all the money we have you remember how back in back in the day
It was all
Dice in the alleys down those puritan streets
Anyway ever get it over your head on something with enthusiasm
For something that now you have some more experience than it was an obvious rookie mistake much love FYI t f y da t f o
W i a t f that's scoopy Ramon. Thank You Scooby Ramon. Thank you, and I appreciate this on a deep level
I had this experience when I was in kindergarten and
Was in a school play and I was an elf
Sneaking on to the stage
backing up and I was to bump into Santa Claus and be surprised and I insisted I
Insisted that I hold a toy and then drop it in surprise and shock
I was like, how about I tell you I was like I was giving I gave myself business
I was like, how about I take a toy and I and I well when I bump into Santa. Oh, that's good
That's good. I dropped the toy and they were like fine. Whatever, you know
I was obnoxious and I was you know, 18 19 is my freshman year and only year of college
We did Rosic Reds a gilded also your senior year
We did Rosic Reds a gilded are dead. Yeah, I got cast is just polonius, right? It was just really in that show
like not, you know in the hamlet a vital character, but still like a
Tertiary role kind of thing and rose goes are dead. I really just came in to illustrate that that's happening
Throughout the hamlet, right and I did so much
Business and I tried to get so much laughs
Like a baddie old man, like I was obnoxious looking back
I'm like so ashamed like if I if I were me now in a play with me then I would be like
Can you chill the fuck out and play your part? Can you just?
Accept that you didn't get cast as Rosencrantz or gilded turn. Can you just move on?
You know, it was it was it was it was obnoxious I
Got to bust out during a ride. Oh, Matt. Donnelly has a question. That's correct. That's exactly that's exactly the level it was at
During my college freshman year. I got to play rolling mall and present laughter and I had that character is just annoying and crazy
And so I just got to go
ballistic as a young
Ham and it was fucking glorious and I killed it
It was it was really really really fun. But then also I was like well fuck
I that I was in a main
Production with all the graduate students. I think I'm done here
Boy, I was like, I don't know. Seriously. I got like third for the top billing like what the fuck what else?
What else is going on? It's six more years to do this again. No, thanks. I'm fucking
That was really one of those things I took away from that experience was like, okay, I can go do other stuff now
And he did I sure did indeed go do other stuff and
Still is doing other stuff and unless he's died between the recording of publishing of this episode
you never know and I'm still doing the
More enthusiasm than the experience when I got to do the the warm-up gig for P&T
Yeah
Exactly. That was ridiculously crazy, but it worked out worked out real good
But I was just very lucky
Right place right time and boy. Oh boy was that guy previous to me just tanking it
Yeah, you just she had like a different job right or whatever we were you there when he got fired or I yeah
I was there as pen stand-in. Yeah, I was doing that's right. Yeah, you were doing standard work
Yeah, I was doing standard work and then I kept doing standard work and the warm-up right for that season. That was wild
That was a lot of work
Fun though. I think every job I've ever taken was definitely taken with enthusiasm over experience. Yeah
Yeah, I mean at least up until I was 35 right
Including including when Matt called me and said you want to do a podcast I
Mean, I would say that would definitely be enthusiasm over experience for all three of us. That was Paul that well
Yeah, I mean well, but not not really I don't have any experience. I had experience talking into a microphone. That's about it
Oh, I don't I still don't know diddly squad about putting together a podcast properly. No, I mean I know a little bit
But not not a ton
Don't get on the feeds. I don't
When other podcasters ask us for advice they are disappointed often
Like I don't know record it and throw it in the ether
Yeah, release the episodes on time. Oh, yeah, right. Yeah, I can't I can't don't show up a half hour late. I
Can't start off my TED talk with be friends with Penn
Why not be a hard one to do
It's not easy to execute advice but it is that it is advice that can be executed can be can be done
We got an email here from Anonymous, here's a what would you do story?
We had a little what would you do action?
Well, it starts when I visited a dance scene that I hadn't gone to in about 15 years
I hit it off with a guy I used to know and like a scene from a film
We danced together for most of the late-night blues party
It was romantic and incredibly hot when we left he carefully asked I might be reading this wrong
But would you like to have coffee sometime to reassure him on several levels?
I answered. Yes, that is the perfect thing to say that is much better than my suggestion
Which was to go to my hotel room and fuck
Whoa
It's a good answer. It's a solid answer
When we met for a date, I was glad to find we were both vaccinated atheists
He's 15 years older than me though, which put me on edge because of a bad experience. I had with an older guy
I started worrying we wouldn't be compatible and saw a red flag when he mentioned a right-of-center newspaper
Still he was kind and empathetic and the chemistry was hard to ignore at this point. What would you do?
But this point I could continue on the day you keep on each other, right? Do we know the gender of our writer?
We don't okay
I feel like gay or straight if an older man came to meet you if you want to say let's let's cut through the
Bullshit and go fuck. I feel like they would do it
Well, I think the writer was was saying that to be funny more than more than like an actual suggestion
The other person the other person they had been dancing with said like hey, you know, we've been dancing
We were having a good time tonight
Would you be interested in going to get a coffee and they're like I am interested in getting coffee
I was gonna say we should go fuck but yes, let's go get coffee, right?
So then the question is how we feel about if they start mentioning right-wing newspapers
Yeah, like kind of just where we're at at this point with it, I guess
So there's a little bit of a little bit of stuff that they're worried about a little bit of stuff that writers worried about age
It made the newspaper I guess
But still kind and pathetic and had good chemistry
So, yeah
We did our best to be respectful and with full consent that it might be a one-time only thing. We spent the night
Okay turned out. He's good in bed
Oh, yeah, and we have a kink in common
So I got very excited at the potential to explore this which would be a first for me. Okay, big, right?
That's what I'm guessing. So it's like the shrimp
Let's go
We spoke on the phone a few times
In an impressive backfire of complimenting me
He said he only wants to date women at least 10 years younger because women his own age look old
What?
Casual sexism and he apologized guys
Know that I'll be breaking up with you in nine years. Yeah, right. I said good day
Don't get comfortable universal all women age the same all men don't don't worry about it
Wow, no problem I
Called him out of this casual sexism and he apologized next it came out that he voted for a political party that I don't like
But I don't want to be and I hate people who vote X person
Finally, like he was quoting a soundbite. He said it's hypocritical to believe in global warming and still fly
Yep, he doesn't believe in global warming. Come on
I got the feeling he didn't always think before speaking most people wouldn't call their promising sex partner a hypocrite
with a sell-by-date
Oh with a sell-by-date, right and this is all just making this sex hotter. Yeah, you know
Sure, that's the kink the kick. Oh
Tell me more horrible opinions. Oh, yeah
Shut up and keep fucking me you big dummy go
Having my first period menopausal mood swings. I crashed hard
Don't be I with your tongue on my toes go
Hey, that sounds like a good night
Having my first period menopausal mood swings. I crashed hard and ended things. Damn it
I get very uncomfortable with debates and didn't attack his beliefs. I spoke my piece
He listened and it and it didn't become an argument
He apologized properly and was shaken by how much he had upset me
It was the most respectful breakup call I ever had shortly after that time three people I knew got terminal
Diagnoses and depressing political stuff was happening. Oh at a low point. I asked myself
What would I do if I only had six months left? Oh, my reaction was I would call that guy and tell him
Don't say anything about anything
Let's just have some fun
This is really hard right it is this is really hard because it's hard to meet anyone that you're
Sympathico with in general. Oh that kind of hard. Yes
And then to try and navigate especially currently just how polarizing opinions can be
Sure, but what how important like we've made everything so important
when I was a
single I
Remember being an atheist like factored faster than I thought it was
Like I was certainly willing to not give a shit about that person being Christian
And the early dating parts. Yeah, and it just it kind of it would come to a head faster than I than I thought it would
Yeah time, you know, yeah, that's just a younger generation thing
I mean, they don't they don't view blowjobs as a thing that you need to wait on as much anymore
but it's it's true in relationships if you
You know if you find out that your partner is prone to magical thinking
then
It opens up other doors and if you find your partner is prone to saying off-color possibly bigoted shit
there's probably other shit behind there too, right like that's
Well, I mean maybe if you you know, I think it's I think it's hard to examine like
male loneliness white male only this has like its own thing, but like the truth is like this is an example like
Wherever this guy is getting his echo chamber. Yeah, there's no yes global warming, right?
You're breaking up with him sends him back to that space. Yeah, but but yeah, but I don't know
Yeah, but it's not and it's not your job responsibility to save. Yes
Right to save all of stupid white male America like I mean, you know, I've been having I've been out of the game guys
No, but you know, whatever
But we want we want I found a woman who would save me the thing that I do for my single friends is you know
Like write down everything you want in a man, right? So in this case if you want to say
Awesome in bed believes in science like, you know, like like what happens is like we write that list down
It is not crazy to look at that list. That list is not like there's no one on earth who could fit this bill
No, and like and I did I did that before I ended up
Dating and I made my specific list of things
I wanted in a partner and it not only does it reinforce what's important to you
But it narrows your field of vision and you don't just go wild off the handle looking at people who it just quickly
Nullifies possible bad choices, right? It sharpens your head man
It's it's it's what I talk about an improv all the time too. You know, the the real key to improvisation is focus
That's it. Where's your focus?
Okay, and so that's it. That's it. It's really just focus
like I can teach a lot of different stuff, but focus is what it really a lot of what it really comes down to and
with anything
decide what's important decide what you're truly looking for get clear about goals and
things that are important to you and
The bullshit falls away. Yeah, but it's hard to keep focus
It's that and that's especially true now and that's why we see a lot of what's going on within our political spectrum
It is designed to destroy
focus
Sure. Yeah. Yeah for sure
I don't want to I'm gonna go back to other point, but what you're I don't want to no no no, no
Yeah, that point is valid
but I think so many times like our ability to be flexible to be giving to want to
Put things on the line to like our willingness to possibly change to help to bend for other folks. Yes
I think you get lost in that ship. Yes, and and then and then you combine that with the sunk cost fallacy
Yes, good example. My yes. Yes. Yes, I envy
I've been in this shitty really you're like I can't get $3,000 in a month. I can't do it
And you think you're gonna get out of relationship you're gonna be embarrassed you think your friends are gonna think oh my god
You put so much time in your friends won't care at all
You know
It's it they'll care about you, but they won't care that that that you put more time or less time in
they don't
You you you anytime you take a step towards being healthier your friends are going to be grateful that you're in a better space
No matter how long it took you to do it
That's worth saying on its own also
If they're your real friends, right good and not your frenemies and that's it
Those were talking about also you can be you should be also be more selfish about your friends
You should be you know
if you if you have a dysfunctional relationship with your friendship group or you feel like you're you know not truly a
like
Jive is not a mute. It's not truly mutual with your friends group. You should get new friends
You should get to find it any kind of hobby any kind of club any kind of meeting. Yeah, you're right any kind of bar
Oh, there he goes. Here we go. You know what he can do better than us Paul
Jacob can do better than us and I'm glad he's gone. I
Wait a minute. I looked around I turned out I couldn't do better. That's a double-edged right there
I'm glad he's gone
Then I'm saying as a guy who lives in like, you know an urban and suburban environment
You know, we have numerous scoops right us
You know where they have basically stayed in their religion longer simply because they would know they'd be completely alone in their community
Sure, right become atheist like I understand that this is an uphill battle and bigger things
I'm only saying in your heart
don't think that like
Compromise compromising all of your wants is the only way you know, right? Right?
I think you made the right choice in put the kibosh on it
Because fool me once shame on me shame on you fool me twice shame on on me
And wait, what do you what kiboshes has happened here? Well, she she broke it off
And the writer you they broke it off what I
Haven't finished reading this email yet. Oh, I thought I I thought they broke it. Oh shit
We've just got we've gotten sidetracked
What would I do if I only had six months left my reaction was I would call that guy and tell him don't say anything
About anything. Let's just have some fun. Oh, no, that thought stopped me crying
I asked myself seriously am I that shallow and my brain said yes
Oh, you asked what I want and I told you if you can broker that deal
I'm in after a cooling off period. I arranged to call him
We agreed that being friends was a disaster and I said I had heard of the concept of sex clubs
Where apparently you don't discuss politics, how would he feel about meeting as if we were at a sex club?
He said I can be there in an hour and a half
He added if I turn up and you decide no, I'll drive home and I'll not sulk about it, which was a helpful reassurance
This guy definitely had a had has some reassuring qualities to him. Sure. This is smart. This is yes
We had a better night than the first at the time of writing
We meet every couple of months always checking. We're still okay with it and enjoying it while it lasts
We've had some amazing times and he said and done some very kind and thoughtful things
The kink exploring is going very well. I can't believe it took me this long to buy some sex toys
I found he's a fan of Tim mentions poem
Storm and of Penn and Teller's bullshit. So he has critical thinking awareness
It's just well behind the times and certainly not helped by the media and politics that he follows
Maybe some of my attitudes will rub off on him
Maybe some other things will rub off on him too
Hey as I try to avoid generalizing or being negative and I really try to understand rather than judge
So am I naive?
Liberated morally challenged making the world a slightly happier place or all of the above
Thanks for reading fucking with the faces in a private sex dungeon after a good spanking tied with easy escape cuffs. That's anonymous
Anonymous. Thank you so much for sharing and being so open with us
That's this is a lot of fodder here to think go through those options again
Am I go ahead Jacob am I it was it was a BC and date? Do you remember?
Let's see. Am I let me find here
As I try to avoid generalizing and or being negative and I try to understand rather than judge so am I am I naive
You want to go to a one at a time am I naive no, I don't think so
Liberated yes. Yes, you're liberated. Yes. Definitely. Am I morally challenged? No, no
Don't think so making the world a slightly happier place. Yeah, I think so. Yes. Yes, that's it. No like yes
I don't think you're naive. I don't think you're morally challenged. I think you are liberated
I think you I think you are making the world a slightly happier place both for you and your companion
Yeah, the like look you said you have kinks and fetishes, right?
Like that's a it's often a very difficult conversation to broach on in a regular dating environment. You found someone who fits that bill
You want me to put this light bulb where and they agree to everything right you put out everything you want it again
You just did we just talked about without whether we didn't got to it
You were like if it could be this and not that and always this and never that and he said yes you both
Intelligently made an agreement. Will that get sloppy at some points or we end up in the conversation at some points sure
But that happens in every relationship no matter what you're doing. Anyway, so like what you did do was actually you literally
Came up with your most selfish list for this person to still be in your life
And this person said they'd happily fit those parameters. That's awesome
You laid it out this person accepted and it seems like it's going okay
because now you might need another guy who's also dynamo in the boudoir and
And then decide I don't need to meet this
This this is this right winger for for private sex anymore that might happen
But you you've actually allowed yourself to leave that door properly open, right?
Right, if you were dysfunctionally dating this person and you were going to meet someone to be like, oh, but I'm dating someone
Oh, but it might get messy now. Now you're fucked up, right?
But you you have the exact sexual relationship you want with this person you want to use this person. He says use me
You're in that spot you've appropriately set expectations
Yes
And now you if you would now encounter someone you could have a more fulfilling rich with you'd be able to move on to that thing
No problem, right?
Now, I think this is a nice thing. I think this is a nice thing anonymous
Very much so speaking of nice things. It's gonna be nice. How about I beat Paul Matt and Chuck versus nerd?
Yeah, I'm on the hunt for balls
The hunt for balls
Oh
It's possible I just discovered that we've already played the scooperty that oh
Well better discovered early. Yeah, I better find it now than eight questions in
We're pros everybody
Game coming to us today from yarn and sticks in the chat
Thank you so much. Oh, yeah, the yard and six in the chat. Nice. What up?
This is the one where we have the double downs. We have the steals
We have all those things in this obelisk game that I had definitely planned for before this moment
That you're hearing all the better right now here to see it. That's great. Here we go
All right, so we got a $200 question all the way up to $5,000 questions. We have double downs
We have steals we have stupid super steals and we can do a 50/50 lifeline one time a Matt has control starting off
Matt the category is celebrities. It's the $200 question. I don't think anybody's gonna steal from you. Let's go
Name the supermodel who had a talk show from 2005 to 2010 Cindy Crawford Kate Moss Tyra Banks or
Christy Turlington, let me see Tyra Banks
Tyra Banks
It was Tyra Banks. Okay, I was gonna guess that but I was I part of me thought Cindy Crawford maybe
It's any crowd. I feel like you see Crawford did shit something on empty V. We're yeah
I was like a style show. I don't Cindy come in here. We got questions for you
It turns out that mole has overtaken 90% of her face. Oh my god. It was it was a guado all along
I'm Cindy Crawford now, baby. I'm the crawford
It's a sport
What you're not stealing sports, are you?
Nice deal sports. No category sports Matt on November 23rd
2025 the Raiders played against the Browns who won the Browns the Raiders the Colts or the line
As a reminder you have a 50/50 lifeline that you can use I'm gonna go with the Browns the Browns
Is correct. It is the Browns. You know, I know the Raiders only won two games
So I had to figure out whether that was one. Oh, yeah
Six-hundred dollar question food food anybody do anything
Name the main ingredient in a typical salad
Lettuce cabbage chicken fries in Pittsburgh answers D
I'm not kidding. They put it in all of them. They put fries on things that go gourmet
Manny's
Manny brothers. Yeah
To the devil's lettuce a please. Let's see it is a
Well done, Matt. You're on a you're on a tear. Yeah, it's going pretty well
$800 question. What am I? Oh, what am I?
What if I contain flour butter salt nutmeg ginger cinnamon eggs
Brown sugar condensed milk pumpkin puree then what am I?
your mom
Jack Lantern a pumpkin pie a pumpkin roll or a pumpkin head. I
Let's see pumpkin pie is obviously the lean terms we should it's not a pumpkin roll
Our butter salt nutmeg ginger cinnamon eggs brown sugar condensed milk pumpkin puree
It's got a little pumpkin pie pumpkin pie pumpkin pie
It is a pumpkin pie
All right, but nothing's not good job. No one can stop my little pumpkin pie
Thank you. I'll steal damn it
Apollo stealing super steel or steel regular steel
regular steel
What am I part two my scientific name is
Dihydrogen monoxide and I can kill you in many ways. What am I ethyl alcohol?
Also, ethyl alcohol mercury or water water D water
Yeah, Paul loves that D keeping it wet loving the D sweet D. Yeah
What am I part three
Okay, I am widely distributed I am a widely
Distributed animal with a pointed muzzle and bushy tail. I range in color from black white brown and red
Vulpus vulpas vulpas is my scientific name. What am I wolf dog fox or mouse? Oh
I
Think that's a wolf, but I'm not a hundred I'll go with wolf a wolf. Let's try wolf
It's a fuck shit. Ah, boo. Oh, what does the Fox say?
Question earth and it's going to Matt now fuck that I'm stealing it. Whoa
How dare you this coarse-grained igneous rock is found in kitchens and driveways and has a
What is that? Moe's Moe's Moe's hardness of six seven. Yeah
Diamond shale sandstone or granite
Found in kitchens and driveways, I mean granite gotta be granite
I think so. I think I'll go granite D granite. Yeah
The moon it's a $1,600 question and it's the moon
Approximately how long does it take for the moon to rotate?
360 degrees on its axis an earth year an earth day an earth minute an earth month
It's oh wait the the rotation is that one
Wait, is it wrote
Is the rotation of the orbit? I think it's the full year because we always see the same side. So it rotates along with us
Right, I think you maybe sure earth year I'll try y'all go here
No, it's a month. Oh
I'm wrong. There you go. Yeah me too
Paul riddle me this who's a
$2,500 question let's riddle me this I'll double down. Oh
Paul doubling down why not I?
Run but never walk have a mouth but never talk
I have a head but never weep and a bed but never sleep. That's a river
rubber or volcano
It is a river a
River runs through it a river does run through it a
$3,000 question. Oh
Steal oh no
Oh is right Matt stole it
This author is known for the novels of mice and men grapes of wrath East of Eden and the winter of our
discontent to name a few
Douglas Adams here's Anthony John Steinbeck. I wish it was Piers Anthony
I can imagine a Piers Anthony grapes of wrath. That'd be something right? I believe this is Steinbeck. Oh
No, I'm sorry. It's Orson Welles Orson Welles. We were looking for Orson Welles there. We were looking for Orson
Well, no, it's course. It's time big
Let's see $4,000 question snacks
Super steel damn it
What year were spaghettios first sold with the slogan the best invention since the napkin Wow, that's a beating
1882 1975
1965 or
1860 I'm gonna use my little 50/50 action right here. Good call
That got rid of 1860 and 1975. Oh, thanks for getting rid of the fucking
spaghettios release
motherfuckers, I
Mean it was at 18 hundreds Jesus fuck no
Can't be I mean, we're gonna go 65 1965 got a final answer
It is. Yeah gotta be
$5,000 question
I have to try is super steel. Wait, what happens? Oh Paul gets a super still first
Don't I get to double down first still hungry for the $5,000 question
Paul did say it first
Which two candles were named after horses and candies candies
Which two candies were named after horses baby Ruth and KitKat
KitKat and Snickers
lollipop and saltwater taffy
Snickers and lollipop
50/50 me, please. Let's see here
That got rid of baby Ruth and KitKat. Yeah, and KitKat and Snickers
So Paul has lollipop and saltwater taffy Snickers and lollipop
Which two candies were named after horses boy, oh boy, these were the two I was debating over anyway
Wait, how do I zero it? Oh someone super steeled me. God damn it. Someone did super steeled you
I'll go see let's try lollipop and saltwater taffy
Snickers and lollipop Paul got it wrong
Snickers
Jacob will
400 points Paul and matter both tied at 0 Paul and matter tied which also means Jacob wins
Yarned cats if you want to sit as an obelisk jock vs. Nerd or a scooperty or a hey scoops all the things over there at
Hey scoops hey scoops calm. That's where to go go to hey scoops calm
Thanks. Thank you so much. Thank you so much obelisk yarn and sticks. I should have super stole them. So I get the hang of this game
Well, aren't we all I don't know. Could you do it? Did you know Snickers?
No, I knew Snickers you knew Snickers was a horse. I knew Snickers had been named after a
Was named after a horse. Yeah was the horse named Snickers. Yes
Wow
Let's begin the bed I have to get going so that I can do a podcast with him
Oh, yeah, there's no more. We thank people always sports on patreon. It's a new month
We're still trying to figure out who runs our patreon
And so we'll get a list together. Hopefully by the next recording next week. Oh sure
We can figure this out
But if you want to be thanked on air or get other kinds of rewards from us
If you just want to support our podcast in general and have the room in your wallet to do so
Please head over to preaching fun calm. It's like the feet a tear that fits your budget today easy for me to say
Oh, I'm sorry, I was at the toy store go to farts in a bag that bit
Oh
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun calm
It takes you over to our patreon page before as little as three dollars a month
You can upkeep this show on the air. We are dependent on our patreon supporters
That is how we are able to do this show. So yeah show is worth more than zero dollars preaching fun calm farts in a bag
Dot biz those are the places that you can go to show it three dollars a month
That's all you have to do to help keep this show going you can either do it by the month
You can do it by the year and you can gift
Subscriptions to other people you can do all those things right over there at farts in a bag dot biz and and preaching fun calm
Yeah
Absolutely. Thanks for listening today's show. Thanks for listening any show
That we make I should say not just any show in general
Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
Thanks guys
See ya!