That's what it supposed. That's what it was. That's like that's why the the 12-month calendar has
Months that are all jibbly jubbly with the days
Mean case closed case closed Jacob
More date all you ice cream truck drivers out there. You were the only thing keeping Paul from
I don't know
Good stuff. That's true. I want to thank all of you, especially right now
I want to thank the Elkin magic scoop Fifi Frankie stinky scoop collective president scooper starving scoops a lot ice blue scoop
I want to scoop baby Jake Schneider Jason Klepper Jeff Harris Jonathan
Laurie Ellsraw and Leon Casab if you want to be an ice cream truck driver
Just like these fine folks preaching fun commas where you can go head over to preaching fun comm
Sign up today to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the life you save
Maybe your own
Here's a show
Do you ever thought about how many months of extra days and how many months don't
Are preaching that fun
Sorry, we got interrupted by the start of the show Paul, please continue your case for the 13-month calendar
Anyway, you were gonna say something and you're like wait, I'll save it for air. Oh, I was talking about
The new spawn universe comic book that just came out
Called I saw Santa
It's a two-parter. It was very holiday themed. It's wild
It's a wild fucking book. So Santa Claus is doing his thing
magical shit, you know and
He runs into this kid
Who basically booby traps?
his house
To kill Santa. Oh
He's gonna catch and kill Santa
All right, and Santa has to deal with this kid and then it's this whole
story of how this kid gets away and
Becoming Santa is like trying to kill kids or is it said it's just being Santa Santa's just being Santa and this evil child
has tried to kill Santa and
Being Santa and this kid thinks he's at a home alone movie, but not not just a home alone movie. He's a bastard
He's like he's like Santa. Why didn't you give me the one thing?
I wanted and he's like I just you're you're five or whatever. You're six or whatever
And he's like all I ever asked for is a bone saw and and and he's like
I'm sorry. You've not been you've not been behaving well and this kind of thing and he's like
No, you ever give me his coal and he has this wagon full of coal and he sets it on fire
And he kicks it over and he sets his whole house on fire and he's killing his
You bring up a good point Paul. I'm glad you bring this is this is our
New Year's episode our post Chris Bosh episode and you bring up an excellent point
I've always been confused my whole life when I was a child now. I've always been confused
Why does Santa bring coal to the bad kids? The bad kids are going to start a fire. Yes, they're bad kids
You're giving them coal. You're absolutely right. He literally added fuel to their fire
Coal is delicious. It's delicious. Right, right. We don't talk about that. Well
Just like I've learned in that latest
Or one of the most recent last podcast on the last last lot podcast on the left episodes
Hey, Paul, let's go back to one buddy. Let's start it over. Okay. Yeah, we're gonna edit that out
Just like I wormed on the blast hotline on assess paper
That was closer that was closer buddy
We're gonna do it one more time as I just experienced in the SAS POM on harsh harem bin. I was tired of fear
No, fuck this is gonna save us a ton and overdubbing costs no last podcast just had a whole thing about chimney sweeps and
Of course, they are covered in coal dust and soot and soot
Even more dangerous than coal more combustible. That's why they had to have chimney sweeps
Japanese would light on fire. Yeah, so these kids were covered head to foot in soot and
People they were smoking what like two packs a day easy packs a day easy
People thought that they had great dental hygiene for some reason
simply because
When they would smile the contrast exactly. Oh
And so people had all these myths around oh what well chimney sweeps must know what would be what to keep your teeth
What in it and no, of course not? I'm sorry, sir. I didn't understand what you said. Look we want him sweeps
Right now you've been going up and down up and down Bob's you're right. We'll get your thing clean taking a suit
I come out. Give me a grin boom boom boom sparkly sparkly. I'm thinking all right, but the first mr. Pipples died, right?
Well, he died, but he didn't leave let me tell you what he left a little bit of a DNA
Little ribonucleic acid met and I'll got that motherfucker on lock for the next 1500 years
Burying a tomb with me you will be
Well, there you go wait so like I remember this I've still seen like there's like the like the more of the
If you don't like fluoride, you know and and Robert Kennedy has taught me not to
Yeah, clearly he's he's the one to take advice from you see
You see
Charcoal-based toothpastes and right super. I think that is holdover. I think I think that's a holdover
I think so because it doesn't make any damn sense. You could do the same thing with the power of pumice
I guess fuck if I know you know, just that's what I do with my teeth
I take a pumice stone and just take a bar take a bar of lava soap
I
Remember watching the passage of time in his tooth shrinkage. I remember watching someone on tik-tok. Oh man back then I such long teeth
I remember we were talking about she was using it was really long in the tooth. She was using magic erasers
She started using magic erasers on her teeth
Because she's like well, I think the principles the same and I sure she she kept posting for like a week and then she stopped
I think she probably did she probably did a reprobable harm to her teeth. Yeah
Or just poisoners
With like gum cancer and stuff microplastic. Oh my god. If you guys heard that joke from it
I don't I tear my fault by the way. I want to made this bit another one like creeped out right now, but I don't know
I don't I don't know the comedian. I did it to myself
It's terrible that I can't remember the comedian, but he says, oh, yeah, you know
Microplastics are in everything now, right?
Mike there's microplastics in semen detectable levels of microplastics in semen
Mm-hmm, and he's like even lower even even billionaires
Even billionaires have detectable levels of microplastics in their semen and he's like that's not good
Kids eat that
Oh
This made me laugh and laugh and laugh yeah, yeah, it's a great joke. It's a great joke
It is a good joke. So yeah, we're all we're all dying with
Poison in ourselves, but yeah, I don't know
It's all that's a big way the spawn book. I don't want to spoil it because it turns out really cool
But it's he's basically Santa Claus in the second book
you go and you see he's in his workshop and his study has become a
Charlie from always sunny
Maps and you know
Yes, the conspiracy room because this kid has gone on to murder people every Christmas and
Santa
being and a
Creature of the spawn and not last pet cast on the left, right? I'm talking about spawn now. I'm back on spawn
So guys from last podcast on the left have gone on to murder someone every Christmas
So Santa is within this is within the spawn realm. And so
Santa Claus
He tried to call 9-1-1 when he he ended up at a murder scene
That this kid had set up for him, you know, yeah, and of course, they don't hear him because he's Santa Claus
he's magical and so he grabbed a speaking spell to try and type out help and
Make it, you know say the thing so he could guess but he didn't get it in time and he got whisked back up
And it's just it's a it's a really interesting well-done story and the end the ending is quite satisfying and interesting, too
so I would highly recommend if any of you are into a little bit of gore a little bit of
Creepy gore for your Halloween or Christmas
As happy as an ending as any any spawn book yes, and how much plastic isn't that happy ending
Ask the children, okay
Ask the children
Minor don't someone minor don't think of the children double poly mylar bag. So quite a bit of plastic smart smart
Yeah, Matt you have a whole rock band in your house now I do I do yeah
you did it to yourself you idiot you did the thing that uncles do to
Other families. I did I am my brother with this for years
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so my
one can actually already had a drum kit for his
His birthday, so we just he just he wanted an extra splashy crashy
Symbol he wanted a splash symbol
and so he got it he got us he got himself a nice symbol for for
Have you discovered the the indoor like basically the practice symbols that are mute symbols yet
There you know the ones that come with the original kiss the kids kits
They have like a bunch of holes in them, so they still make a noise, but they're not like crazy loud. Oh, that's okay
That's that's getting closer to them. We have we have mute symbols in our rehearsal our rehearsal room at the house here
Yeah, yeah, they're metal symbols. They've got a fuck ton of holes drilled in them
Yeah
You can hit them as hard as you want and and they don't just deafen you because you're in a regular sized room right and so
That my kid was that was not enough for my kid, and so he asked for a deafening symbol and got it good
He was like oh, I make so much noise. It was just flashing. I was pretty sure that
Where I come from the mute symbol is a slash through a speakers
Yeah, that's we got one of those and he hits that he hits that and it's sponge
So just because he just taps it with a drumstick and then that's that
Symbols when he hits it it takes out all the sound for all of the drums
And then they can't hit they can't hit it again. He's got to hit it hit it twice
Twice
Yes, that's same same band bossy
What is it zell zell jan or whatever it's zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill zill
Yeah, no, you spend say it some more you spend a zill gin on that well his his grandmother spend a zill gin on that whoa
That's a real that's a real symbol. I think I think she's great on the x-files
Zill gin and she's the other son. Yeah
Do you think her and scully really did in real life her? I hope so
But it's my youngest her and scully is my cup of tea her and Mulder whatever but if it was her and scully
Whoa, don't be your pleasure. Don't be your fun
She's scully when you just make a stupid sex joke
And then Paul goes all nerd and gets horny on it. I
Apologize Paul. What happens on page eight of the spawn book you describe detail. She gets scully fucked
But my youngest he started taking electric guitar lessons over at the old school of rock
And at home in an acoustic guitar and he was like, nope
This shall not stand
Dad I'm I was put on this earth thrash
Play coffee houses. That's right a little more Dave Mustaine a little less John Denver, huh? All right
So he's left-handed is a Southpaw. Have we discussed this on air? Oh
Have we talked about this on air? I
Feel like we must have but yeah, you're your youngest is a lefty
That's an original less poor Southpaw with a sunburst finish Jimmy bitch. Would you look at that guitar? I don't even play that guitar
No, no, no, no, put it down put it down put it down. Leave it low lately
Youngest are you doing a Taylor Sheridan monologue? That is a classic bit from an old
teaching
That I have clearly
Had yeah when I was a kid, yeah, it's useful useful Bozzie in the chat knows where this is going. So we started
Giving him lessons and they try to teach him initially school of rock try to teach him right-handed. Oh
So that's the that's the that's the easy easier thing to do and so what happens is that basically if kids are remotely ambidextrous
Okay, the world is much easier for right-handed guitar player wherever they go. They'll have a right-handed guitar player
right-handed guitar that kind of stuff and
Most people like it's just it's just a one-to-one
Kind of a easier to teach or whatever
but and we wanted to have him go off to the school of rock to do it there before we committed to buying him anything because
we want to make sure that he really liked it and you know, whatever just you know, and
After the first lesson the instructor came out and goes well, we learned a couple things today
I was what's that? He goes you sounds pretty good. He goes and
He's definitely left-handed. He is left-handed. There's no
There's no teaching him right-handed I said, okay, you guys have left-handed guitars here they go we do we do we can teach him
I'll tell the guitars. I said, okay
So then you know, we're gonna go now now he's into it
He's been into it for a while. And so we're gonna actually gonna get him a guitar for him to play at home
So we go over to guitar center and I walked up to and turned out the lessons booth
I thought those customer service booth was a lessons booth. Ah, and I said
Yeah guitar center doesn't really have a customer service booth. No, they sure don't Jacob
You should go to a different store
And I said, uh, I'm looking for a guitar for like a left-handed guitar and he goes did you start teaching him?
Yes, did you start teaching him?
Same opinion
And I said, oh, I've been extra so much easier for the rest of his life. If he learns righty one thing
He even had a substitute teacher
for his guitar lesson at School of Rock and
The guy was like again like and now he's like a month's of lessons in and the guy's like you
really think about learning how to play right-handed guitar because if you ever had a party and someone busts out a guitar and
You play left-handed guitar. You can't you can't play or whatever and then he came home and told us a story and my wife
And I were furious
Yes, I said, do you know what you should say back to that person when you if you should you have him again?
It is like my kids like what I was like tell him Kurt Cobain Paul McCartney Jimmy Hendrix
That's a you that's what you say back to him
People it turns out are able to play the guitar. Yeah, they can they can make their way they can struggle through somehow
I'm willing to bet if he gets good enough. He's gonna have that guitar with him at that party
Right and or you know if you actually get skilled enough like Jimmy Hendrix actually would take a right-handed turn
Just flip it upside down and play it. Yes. I told Matt the move is you learn how to play guitar
Like he just learned how to play guitar as he's doing now as it gets good enough
He'll be able to flip it in his head and then he will just be able to take a
Regular guitar and flip it over at a party. It's a fucking power move
Yeah, you know, the only the bag is the pickups and stuff on the top
But I think if you're if you're if you're an artist, you're I think you like all that stuff
You like like you like trying to navigate that stuff
But anyways, I don't care about any of that. And so so guitar center it would turn out the guy was like
Oh, I just teach lessons here. You got to find the salesman anyway, and so I said, okay
And I found a salesman of roaming luckily. We don't have a booth where they hang out
Yeah
They just they just roam and I found a guy roaming and they're kind of dressed the same way that everybody else at the store is
Dressed anyway, they just have longer hair. That's that's what gets them away
The teachers have the longer hair than the sales force. No, no the my guitar centers
There's just you know, people who work there are just around the floor just walking around
But they look like they look like every other dude shopping there. They don't use it's really hard to figure out who works there
Yes, so we found the guy you get approached all the time, right? Jacob
Hey, man, you helped me out. You're you're you're basically like wearing a red shirt at Target
The bad thing is I usually know the answer. Yeah
It's usually easier to just be like, yeah, it's it's it's something. Yeah
Yeah
so I I
Found a guy and I was like you have any left-handed guitars because oh jeez
Here we go
No one can keep this opinion to themselves. He's like he's like we don't really like there's not like a section for it
So you have to walk around and just kind of find one and so we're playing this game. We're walking around
And
It's the only one like I can't go to like guitar world, right? Like there's no yeah, like I have no competitor. I can't
And you're trying to be like I'm trying to not shop online, right? I'm trying to like I'm trying to shop
You're trying to brick and mortar it you're trying to be a good guy
Yeah, I'm trying to be the one is this the one inside the center. Yeah town square. Yeah town square. I know it well and
So it's like there's one
There's one and then I'm realizing I'm looking at it and like
On electric guitars the the was it not the frets. What's the we what's the things you turn to tune the tuners the tuning?
Yeah, the knobs. Yeah the knobs the tuning knobs, you know on an acoustic guitar. There's three and three on each side, right?
Oh, you mean the the the tuning
Shit now I can't think of the word
Stretchers yeah, those guitar string stretcher. Thanks. Thanks. Oh, that's a whole different thing
Yeah, so it is so this guitar teacher's trying to pay all he's old enough
Circles in circles, I'm left-handed when it comes to pegging
Left-cheek dominant. Yes, it used to hold the top of the headboard is your left hand when you're getting
Yeah, that's well cuz it's cuz that cuz I loop I loop one leg around
You'd be surprised. I can actually you know, what do you think happen to that old hip? I can pretzel up a little bit
She said she no she does she we got code she looks at me and she give me a wink
She'd be like you ready to get mr. Salty with it
That's how she that's how she rolls
Well back to the story about my ten-year-old, thank you. Oh is it 10 now he's 10 I
Know too old for most billionaires, but um count things
So I'm realizing that the the pegs on these left-handed guitars that it's it's arbitrary and some of them the pegs are on the right
Of the guitar, right? Oh
So they just choose to string like two guitars left-handed and they choose to string the rest
Right-handed and that's that and that's the end of the game. So shopping for a quote-unquote left-handed guitar is really just about
Stringing them right? Yeah, is that right? I guess that's right
This is what I mean. You yeah you get into like some of some other minutiae and stuff
But you can definitely just do that. You can just string a guitar up to Z down Z
Yes. Yeah. Yeah now I'm thinking about it
Yeah, cuz the two the two left-handed guitars we found one the pegs were on the right side one on the left side
It's just about you know, but you still but then but then it's it's a bet. So it's not about the frets
It's about that where the knobs are
Right you want the knobs on the bottom
So once I realized it was about the the like all the other little things you have electric guitar that are on the physical
Instrument you want that below the strings and not on top of the strings when you're right. I
Was like, oh now now I see but I was looking at the shopping just got a lot easier. Yeah. Yeah
So he's trying out a couple things
I finally grab a right-handed guitar that looks good and I let it just go like here just put the strings on this one
and we'll find out if they make a left-handed version of it, yeah or whatever and
and and so
Basically a beginner's
Stratocaster called Squire. It's made by the Stratocaster. Oh sure. Yeah. Yeah
That's been around for a long time and and it's a little more expensive than like a total starter guitar
But it's not as expensive as some crazy electric guitars, right? And so
He gets it. He goes. Oh, I like this a lot and he's really nice playing around with it. And so
We go online guitar center. They have a left-handed version in inventory. We should be able to pick it up by Christmas
great and
Then we get notices or other kids concert. We're getting email notices that it's on backorder won't be there before Christmas
Oh
Okay, listen the story it's about to make me a terrible person, okay
We're in the middle of it is the holidays we're in the middle of my oldest kids Christmas concert
So we don't want to handle this right now, but I go ahead and open up Amazon
Look for left-handed guitars
Squire Stratocaster I was gonna say now, you know the making model
It can be delivered to my house tomorrow
Yep, I was like, sorry guitar center and then
Boop done cancel the order guitar center and and gave gave gave more plastic to that seaman monster
Jeff Bezos and yeah, and then my kids playing an awesome guitar downstairs
If you're quiet right now we can we can hear Matt's youngest playing the guitar in the distance
Well, I tell you what's neat about school of rock is that they teach him rock songs right away
Oh
Yeah, no, they make it so much fun
Yeah
And so my kids just playing songs like it's just like he's already just off just playing like tunes
And so it's like it's actually really fun to have in the house
And my oldest son was like let's go out in the garage and jam and I was like he just
Got a good car. He doesn't know how to tune it yet. He doesn't do it. I don't cares. Yeah
Let's go time to jam you time to jam you just triggered a memory. I meant to talked about this a couple weeks ago
I forgot. Yeah, so Anne and I were going to the local Walmart
this was two weeks ago, maybe not even and
We had snow flurries coming down. So there was a dusting. It was early in the snowfall
Right before things really got kind of hairy
We're heading up towards the Walmart and as some of you may know
Walmart allows for the Salvation Army to post up at their doors
Okay, with their cat the bell guys. Yes
On this day the bell guys had been replaced with a band
Okay
This a bell band no
these were
people playing
wood instruments horns
Okay. Yeah, and
as we got out of the car
Walking towards the thing they were
warming up
and it was and I was like
And I was like who the fuck is skinning that cat it was
Atrocious
Atrocious but but hilariously bad like so bad. You're just like this can't be real and
then
Sir, and they go one two, three four
Paul you're gonna get us demonetized
We go inside we walk inside and I'm just looking at and we are giggling our asses off
idiots because we
Stop it and I'm just losing my shit and we get inside and she's like what the fuck was that and I go
That was Mariah Carey's all I want for Christmas
Fuck you was not
It fucking was I hear that song on loop in Target eight day eight times a day
That was what they were trying to play. Fuck you bullshit. That is not what was asked. That is that sounds like they successfully played it
Oh my god, it was so and then as we were coming out
They were doing another one and it was just as horrendous and we get in the car. She's like
They must have been special needs
That were there for the Salvation Army
I'm like, I don't know. I don't know. Let's say let's say fine. It was fine. But holy shit. I
Just like it was
Unbelievable. I wish I wish I had the temerity to have I think there's probably more than Salvation Navy than the salvation
I should have sucked it up. It was maybe I've been like I'm gonna give this bigoted rat fuck organization a dollar
Just so I can videotape some of this ear fuckery that is going on right here because it was maniacal
maniacal the sounds that were coming out of these instruments and
We were beside ourselves like how did how who who said yes who said yes
I know it was it was my tongue with the bell ringers of people. I'd be like, you know that organization
Sponsors female castration in other countries, right? Right. No, please do not ever donate anything to the Salvation Army
They are garbage people. It's a garbage organization
But yeah, but I would have told that band I think
Yeah
It was out
rages
It was outrageous
I'll tell you who else really got in the holiday spirit walking into Walmart the other day
And that's the following sponsor a squirrels guide to breaking and entering Paul's basement. That's right
That's from 2025 cup of scoop get the squirrels guide to breaking and entering Paul's basement
Hello. I am how you say a squirrel. I
Am wanting to get warm, but I am cold
So I am thinking hey, I will break into someone's ass and still they're warm. And so what I do I
Get into the basement
which is a
fully furnished and as they say in the human circles
Finished is a finished basement. Okay. I'm not I am NOT in Finland. It is a finished basement
I go inside and I find a hole and I
Squirreling, you know how you do a squirrel into the squirrel hole. He's slowly becoming Louisiana
And it's it's a slow transition here I go into we get him into the squirrel or
And I'm inside and suddenly I am there and I am warm and I am looking for a few
It there is no
There is only spiders
Just a spider
That is it and I don't want to eat spiders. So then someone puts a nut roll in a cage. I
cannot resist
Go and I eat a nut roll. But then the tello then the cage it closed
And I am in traffic. Oh
No, and
My balls stick out of the cage because I have huge squirrel nuts
and
There it is. I am trapped
like a squirrel
Then I am set free back into mother nature
To look and cry at the trees. I must now inhabit it
instead of the warm
basement
But if you stay in the tree long enough, it gets warm
Enter a scoops to check out despite all his rage. He's still just a squirrel a nut roll in the cage. It's true
We are all that nut roll
So when we leave town we usually have friends stay at the house and then house sit for us and everything
Yes, they watch the dogs. We have we have several friends that we enlist to do this
Have roommates or whatever and yeah, they come they come stay at the house. They watch the dogs. They have a good time
Whatever this last time when we left
Is the holidays and so all of our friends had shit to do all of our friends that usually come and house sit for us
They all had shit to do so they didn't stay at the house. You're gonna have so we hired a
Professional we had we had multiple friends recommend this professional house sitter to us and she works
She's she is a solo and she's from a service or she's a solo house watcher
She is a solo house watcher. She is not from a service
So she must work on just recommendations. All they then how does I believe size? How does one advertise? I will I will watch your house
Trust me. It's a trust me. I believe she works entirely on word-of-mouth. I believe it is entirely an obelisk scheme and
she also works in a
Vet she works in a veterinary clinic and so she is a she's good with pets
She's good with pets and she's more than just a like she doesn't just do
You know civilian work in the veterinary clinic. She works with with the medicine and works with the animals and everything
Does she do surgeries? I think she assists
So I think she's kind of like the veterinary version of a just cysts. I think so. Yeah just cysts
And not even removal placement just placement. That's the fucked-up thing people want that now
They're asking can you make my Sharpe look more like a Frenchie? That's right. Can you just jam his head full of sis?
Just cyst it up. Ain't no plans for sure Myra. Paul. How old are you picturing this person that Jacob's hiring?
Good question. I am picture picturing her
She
the license the license
Says 29
Okay, but she's a road-hard 38 looking
Contrast between her. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She is she's a world-weary individual with lots of tattoos
Just from staying aware and other people's houses like see leathery skin splotchy hair
perimeter sweeps, you know
Relaxed. Yeah
Rambo and hide yourself in mud
She's had to fend off home invasions a couple of times that's unsettling
Just once I can leave you with the PTSD. Oh, this is a 29 year old
Like a rifle across her back
Randy I travel from house to house and as a someone needs me I just appear zero incidents
That never had a fast know your neighbors. You know your neighbors real well
Yeah, we know our neighbors. Sure. Yeah, I need a list of names cuz when they come to the door
I call out names and if they don't respond quick enough, it's a 22 right to the esophagus
I don't I don't take it. I don't take a chance
So, you know, you know my house
Shoot twice ask questions later
That's what I do. No dogs get stolen on my watch never Oh double-cap Sally
Never lost a dog. I've lost neighbors, but I've never lost a dog. I
Mean I can yell dance, but they can't dance by the time I'm done with them
No, and and it's it's stand your ground. I'm just standing my ground
You could you came on my property. Well, it's not my property, but by stand your ground laws it is
I'm responsible for this for your property
Yeah, so who is she she rode hard put away wet Jacob who we're talking about here
Matt how old do you think she is? I think she's like for mid 40s. Oh
Matt's closer. I think she was she was probably late 30s. Did you check did you check her?
I did not check. She might have been 19. I don't know
It cut off it cut off her thumb and count of the rings
But she has a she's like set herself up weary look yeah
Thousand yards there
Just walking around whistling this tune from the good the bad and the ugly
Hi, nice to meet you. My name's pts, Diana
Did she did she have to come over the house
To like be in the house to be with you guys before she before she watched the house. She did she did how
Dogs your dogs usually go after the new ones. So did your dogs go nuts when she came in?
They they go nuts a lot less than they than they did when they were younger these days anyway, right?
Also, you certainly condition them. You're like look we have people over kids. There are people coming by
Does she get her get her scent all on him I
Didn't notice her
Purposely getting her scent. Did you did you guys dogs or otherwise? Did you guys leave some dirty laundry for them?
Do you do that? Do you do that for the puppers?
Do we leave go ahead we answer the question
Do you leave dirty laundry for a stranger or rubbing your dog's faces to calm them down?
Here's our pile of dirty laundry when you want to rub it on the dogs you leave your dirty laundry
You leave a shirt or or two in the in their sleeping quarters so they could still smell you when you're gone. It works
Well shame on you
I've learned shame
Now did you realize that there's two people that have spent a lot of time around my dogs
You know how deprived they are
I don't even get me started. I'll tell you all about my fucking dogs here a minute, but fucking
Did you realize that that is how dogs measure time?
What yes through scent
Dogs measure time through scent. I just so I read a poem when you leave the house
Your scent is in the air
Yes, and as the day progresses the smell of you being around your scent is in the air
Not this scent not me buddy
I forgot I was talking to a man with an unwashed ass. Yeah, it is a pungent. It is a pungent odor that stays
This is the thing though. That's the scent in Matt's house. Matt is always there
My cats have an easy day
But that's how they can tell you've been gone for a while is the scent is less so you've been gone
Having I can't smell you
Yeah
Yeah, that song was written for a dog and of course dogs don't understand the sun goes up and goes down
They don't understand like light and day
No, but no like I was saying man dogs are idiots. They they absolutely understand town
Night and day they understand circadian rhythm, but i'm saying as far as
Look
Uh, I I would even emotionally be measured by scent. What do you mean?
I I miss my I was trying to make a kelly clarkson as a dog joke and I lost it anyway
Because she's not because she's not she's hot business whose husband just died
Poor thing
And it was strange
Poor everyone were they ever
As strangers in the night
So she's there. She's got her guns comes by how many guns she's got her guns. Oh too many to count
It shows up like schwarzenegger's commando the end of commando
just
I'm going to have to use your refrigerator a few times. I hope you don't mind
If it's if this food in the fridge you don't want me to eat and eat it labeled labeled with the security deposit
Put something on top to say do not eat
Otherwise is our fair game because i'm one of these people who believes you're going to be gone for a week
You don't want the food to go bad again moldy. Anyway, I can eat it. I can use it. I can get the value
Won't you let me have that food?
Why don't you let me have it?
That's fine. You can eat anything in the fridge. Great. Uh, everything is off limits now to you and your wife
For the next 10 hours before you leave the house. I call dibs on everything in the fridge
This is part of our arrangement dibs
No, also, I see you have a lot of drinks up there in this place. We're outside
We've heard dibs has been called if you do not respect dibs, we will arrest you you better get out of this house right now
It's not your house anymore. It's not your house squatters rights dibs dibs
Police there's a person yelling dibs and saying they have squatters rights in my house
That's right, I called it it's dibs I shit in the bedroom when you weren't looking so it's technically mine
Oh god, she did shit in the bedroom
Ha ha
You should never let a stranger in your home unless you don't want your house anymore, but that's the lesson you've learned
Goodbye get the fuck out
Thank you for participating
Tough but fair tough, but fair is right. You're stupid. You're so dumb and your dogs are mine
Oh at least something good came out of this
Could you use some dirty laundry behind so I could comfort them?
Yeah, you better leave a stinky shirt or a pair of underpants so I can stick it in the crate
Let it dissipate slowly over the next few weeks
Yeah, she came by she met the dogs
Uh showed showed her around the house
Yo, I did I was like here's the bar
Uh, and I was like anything that's open on the bar
just
Knock yourself out. Whatever whatever you want
And she goes she took a bottle and hit herself on the head
Knock myself out there. You've been roofing all these beverages. I know what's going on
I've played this game before
This is roofy roulette
Then she goes well, I don't
I I don't drink alone is the only problem
with that dude
She and I was like she and then you 24 and then you pulled out 45
And then you and then you pulled out the torso you bought a week ago for
There you go, this is also open do whatever you want with this
And I was like well if you do if you change your mind if you want anything go ahead and
If you change your mind
She goes oh no to her credit. She goes. Oh, yeah
If I want to just sit around and be sad one night, maybe i'll do that
Did you not just say well you could have someone over
No
Okay, listen
No, I didn't I didn't propose that she did she have people over and like
Entertain at my house. No, I didn't I don't think I don't think if you don't drink alone
You want to be used some kind of filthy you don't have to entertain at the house
But yeah, exactly you can do easily a hundred people in the backyard. That's true
We've got rolls of visqueen in the garage several times. That's it
If she lays down some plastic all bets are off. That's right. That's right
dibs respect dibs
I tell you what so she we uh, we left uh, we left town
She told my wife, uh, because of course she and sj are the ones who put all this together
Uh, so, uh, she told sj. Oh i'll send you you'll update pictures on the dogs
Uh, it'll it'll be great. There won't be any trouble with the dogs. Everything's gonna be gonna be real good
she sent
Multiple update pictures to my wife every day so so that sj knew that the dogs were were being taken care of
We got back to the house
It was so much cleaner than it is when our asshole friends house it for us
It had been vacuumed the dog shit in the backyard had been picked up and throw it away
I was like this is incredible and I had told her I was like the dogs are small enough
The yard is big enough
If you don't pick any of it up because she was like, oh is there a trash can for the for the dog poop from the backyard?
I said, yeah, there's trash can over here. Uh, really though. You don't have to sweat it. They're not big dogs
Uh, so unless the mood just strikes you honestly, you don't have to worry about it. Yeah
And uh, but yeah, like the the yard was completely clean. It's like man. Are you sure?
Asshole friends got thrown away and she didn't eat it
You sure she didn't straight up tootsie roll all those nuggets
That's her whole scheme, right?
Jacob, can you actually send her a text now whether she tootsie rolled all those nuggets?
Oh
She's got a couple blacked out teeth
She just wrote back up. She's she's replied
Busted
Oh, yeah, she
How
How many licks could oh no different
Oh, she wrote back
It said I oh
Oh, she got too drunk. She got too sad and drunk
That just gorged herself
I did it again. I said I wouldn't do it
I eat all the shits at the place. I was
Of watching the dogs
But in order to actually eat all the dog feces and that is the following sponsor
Today's show is brought to you by creepy best spy guy and ray ramanos improv training classes
Okay, so um
Who here is familiar with the concept of yes hand
I am
Yeah, great. Okay
I'm gonna turn it over to ray
Uh, yes and uh
Okay, so
Everybody up. Let's do a little zip zap just to get us going. Uh, you know get to get it loosen up
uh, so okay, uh
The most important thing, uh is making or maintaining good eye contact with your partner
honestly, because
If you focus on that then you can't miss moves that are made or you won't miss here
words that are said
Usually and i'm sorry. Is that is that also creepy best buy guys?
Number one rule is eye contact as well. It's my number one and my number two rule
Both number one and number two number one and number two. That's my number one and number two rule is eye contact. Yes. Okay
What if I don't want eye contact for my partner like the way could be guessed best by guys looking at me
Like I want him to stop looking at me. Ray. How would I get him to stop looking at me? Uh,
Invite your brother over to fuck your wife
And her hate scoops to check out
Wow
Is that a plot point from the show or from his real life?
both
Right what you know, she tootsie rolled his fiance. No, uh
Matt did you know that those are my those are my first two rules?
I did know that I didn't know that your number one number two rule or eye contact you set me up for it
It was nice. I did I did. Yeah
and it's true
It's the most important
If you ask me
This is before the holidays right because you came back for the holidays, yeah
Yeah, it was right before the holidays got it
Okay
Because it was it wasn't like a special rate to make a woman because I if you're making her work christmas
Then I imagine it is sad drinking time
I don't know. I mean she got up uh every morning and uh, all right
But she told us her her grade to mecca matt you racist not everybody celebrates christmas
She would get up every morning and light the menorah
And she was very happy about it. She's very conflicted. She was she was not a smart person
Well, she's out there just to tootsie roll them nugs man, that's right, that's all she came for
No, she'd get it because she has a job so she'd just get up in the morning and go to her job at the at
the vet's office and all and then
Come home in the evenings, I guess and and let the dogs out and have dinner and go to bed who?
Did she stay at the house
Yes, she stayed at the house she sleeps over, huh?
She sleeps over that's that's part of the deal
Did she leave behind a pile of dirty laundry for the dogs when they missed her?
She did does she sleep upside down like a bat?
I
Not that I know of you don't know though. I didn't ask you showed her guest quarters. She's like no. I see this chin up bar
I'm good. I got my brought a chin up bar. She's really into health and no I sleep upside down
See these hooks on my shoes on the heels of my shoes
I use them to lock on to chin up bars and other protruding bars
I oftentimes
Find myself sleeping at gymnasiums and or playgrounds which can be troublesome
That's why I keep this I keep this tarpaulium with me at all times
To wrap myself
If I have to sleep at a playground, I wrap myself in the tarpaulium so I don't arouse suspicion
people think it's just a tarpaulium over a
Reportedly broken piece of playground equipment not a human woman sleeping upside down. I emphasize human
Well, it's i'm doing a little jock versus nerd
You're gonna do a little jock versus nerd action. Oh am I fuck yeah
I'm on the hunt for balls. I do cut several holes in the tarpaulium for free
Quit saying tarpaulia
Explosion of tarpaulia
We have a christmas scooper to come into us today from the og scoop the categories are peanuts
Songs more winter holidays and pine potpourri. I'm sorry matt's dying. So you're up
We're all crouping. Uh
I'll go peanuts for 200
Let's see here
This is from og so it's gonna be a good one. Here we go in the peanuts of charlie brown christmas
This was the famously low fee lucy van pelt charged for psychiatric help at her booth
Five whole cents. I love nickels. Give me those nickels shiny nickels. Listen to that jingle jingle jingle
Five cents and paul of course recounting lucy's, uh catchphrase. I just just watched it
That's me i'll try. Um, I don't know more winter holidays 200
The number of candles on a menorah when all have been lit
I think it's eight right i'll say eight
Is it not oh there's the extra one it's nine
I knew it. There's nine. I knew it. It's paul looking out for you jacob
You almost got answered wrong and paul intervened to make sure you got it right. It's a christmas miracle. I'm intervenous
You are intravenous matt. I'll take uh more winter holidays for 400
The year quanza started within five years, uh
Pass
paul
I'm gonna say
60 oh no
Uh 59
66 shit shit my dick
Oh piss my ass
Shit, I was so close
You were close
I definitely thought it started later than that
Uh paul you're up get those points back. Give me them nuts for 800 peanuts
peanuts for 800
In the peanuts television special at charlie brown christmas. This was the color of snoopy's iconic dog house. Oh boy
Well, it got all decorated
All right
I'm trying is that your final answer? No, i'm trying to think what the color was before it
Oh boy now i'm conflating what I actually saw
Oh red and white
Red and white. Oh my
I'm sorry. It's blue. It was blue. Shit my dick. I knew I knew that was tricking my shit
Is jewish he's celebrating hanukkah. That's right
Uh, it's me. I'll try. Um, I don't peanuts 400
Daily double
Let's see here
This tomboyish peanuts character known for her freckles does not appear in the television special a charlie brown christmas
Pippi long stocking a little redheaded girl
The very current reference pippi long stocking little redheaded girl
Uh, that's um
But wouldn't that peppermint patty I think it's peppermint patty
Yeah, peppermint patty, yeah, come on chuck it's time to celebrate christmas chuck
Oh, yeah, she called him chuck. That's right. I like her
Matt you're up. I will do uh peanuts for 600
This jazz pianist and composer created the iconic score for the tv special of charlie brown christmas including the timeless classic
linus and lucy
Mike jones
Mike jones michael the jazz demon jones. I don't know pass
paul vince garaldi
Vince garaldi is just correct paul's just right. Yeah
Uh paul you're up
Oh
You got songs more winter holidays or pine potpourri. I'll go pine potpourri for eight. Let's go. Let's get it going for eight hundo
The spitting top played by jewish children during hanukkah dreidel dreidel dreidel. I made you out of clay
I'm, sorry. It's just dreidel. It's just one dreidel dreidel dreidel dreidel. I will play
Uh, it's me i'll try uh pine potpourri 200. It's the other daily double
At christmas time the this live tree is the most popular a douglas fir a scotch pine
A balsam a balsam fir or a frazier fir
Uh, this is my daily double, huh og?
Uh
I mean
A douglas fir is kind of what I was thinking. I guess i'll say douglas classic
But is that the one that people can afford?
I don't know i'm saying douglas fir
It's a frazier fir mostly grown in my home state of north carolina. I prefer a niles fir
Good for fucking you
The niles and daphne fir
Matt you're up
Um, I will take uh winter holidays 600
This cultural observance on the 26th of december is a holiday in the uk canada and australia. Is it boxing day?
Well, that is literally this question. Is it boxing day?
Boxing day
It is boxing day boxing day at the time of this recording
Let's all fucking fight. Yeah. Yeah at the time of this recording. It is currently boxing. It is boxing day today
When the show comes out, it's boxing monday. I sure as shit had a boxing day unloading a 2600 truck. All right, uh,
It was only like a 2200 today wasn't too bad. All right, i'm going to scale it back
Like son of a bitch. Hey, it's christmas. That's the time for lies. I'm about to ride in the street
So christmas is always a time for lies
paul your turn
Uh songs for 800
I was gonna say we're all avoiding songs the song that holds a guinness world record for having been covered the most
In what?
This song has been mukake the most of any other song
Oh, man now i'm trying to think
Oh
Silent night or
Some rock and roll song
I'll have to pass
Oh that passes to me. Um
I don't know pass matt. My guess is jingle bells, but i'm gonna pass also that might be right
Silent night was my guess right the first one
Oh silent night. Did that say get silent night paul's on fire with his passes. He's doing amazing. Yeah, i'm the best loser
I'll do more winter holidays 800
This festivus tradition takes place as soon as dinner is served
Is that the airing of grievances
I just saw jerry seinfeld do it a bit the other day
He was talking about how festivus was the uh, like the the main takeaway from that show
He's like that is definitely the bit that has continued the longest from that television show is just people talking about festivus
Well, it's because it's jerry stiller
Exactly the immortal fucking jerry stiller, right? Yeah. Oh and that's the credit that he gave
Absolutely, i'm paraphrasing what he was saying about it
But yeah, he was like jerry stiller's speech about festivus is one of the best moments from the entire program
Um, i'll do that you're up i'll do songs for 200
Let's see here
Paul knows the singer of white christmas quite well. If not, he gets backhanded
Uh, that'd be uh being the south paul crosby
Oh being south paul crosby. There he is. How you doing there david bowie?
Don't you sass me none while we do this first take we're getting it done in one son
Got a bag of oranges to beat you with tonight
Paul you're up, uh songs for 600, please
The diva making approximately 2.5 to 3.3 million dollars for her inescapable song during the holidays. That's miss mariah carrie
Mariah carrie miss carrie if you're nasty
Miss carrie
Moving on pipe ovary for 600
This is where i'm gonna go instead of making a joke
The type of animation employed by raken bass productions and rudolph the red-nosed reindeer and santa claus is coming to town among others
Uh, this would just be the uh, the claymation right like stop motion claymation
Yeah, there you go stop motion. Good job, right?
I believe claymation only applies to will vinton's
Specific studios. Yeah, I was going to say, uh,
Yeah, yeah, it's that it's not the tank. Yeah, whatever. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I was gonna say the same thing
It's like muppets instead of puppets
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah claymation with uh paul de anderson. Um, that's uh
I'll do a
Uh song for 400
The song that you are avoiding if you participate in whamageddon last christmas
Last christmas
Is correct. I think I didn't give it away
I I I i've sold it you gave me your heart and I flipped it for a profit. I don't understand my man
I'm a i'm a heart flipper last christmas. I needed a heart
You denied me a heart
And I died
Fine, but we're over 400
Category end the game. It's for the win
What does bruce springsteen ask the band in santa claus is coming to town right after he asks if they have been good
Clarence clarence you're gonna get a new saxophone
He immediately asked slarence lemmons about his instrument says you guys want to see a really depressing movie about me
Just wait
He's weeping cuz he's lonely he's an awful lot like me
He's got threadbare marks on his elbows because he can't afford a suit because he works for free
Can't afford a suit because he works for free. Oh, you better give him money because he's poor as fuck
He's down on his goddamn. Mary ass. Look
Santa claus is broke as hell
Santa claus is broke as hell santa claus needs money
pay his ass
Not really think he asked about a new saxophone. No, there aren't any questions in there at all are there?
Saxophone is your final answer? Yeah
If they've been practicing real hard you guys been practicing real hard
I have I got a rager on right now
I always practice hard. I practice hard keeps the blood out of my brain so I
I miss that girl who I liked a lot and I don't want to talk about specifically
I'll amalgamate the bitches that I fucked in the 70s
Yeah
Amalgamated bitches that I fucked in the 70s
How many amalgamated bitches you fuck?
I fucked many bitches in the 70s. These are all amalgamated
It's just that's the game. I win with 1400 match in second with 1200 falls at third was 600
That's from the og scoop. Thank you og scoop
If you want to send us a scooper to your price of scryte jock versus nerd or anomalous jock versus nerd head over to hey
Scoops.com hey scoops.com. You can make us any of those things
You can send us some email right there at hey scoops.com do all the things right there. It's awesome
It's a great website. Oh my god, you guys one of the best
I don't know. I don't know. I just can't check out some websites, but it's one to check out for sure. Yeah
Well, yeah, I gotta say I mean
Big shout out to everybody joining us here on the day after christmas
We got a really nice audience in the live chat and it's been a lot of fun
To tune in and tune out and to check out everybody that's commenting with each other. It's a party over in the chat
While we're doing the show
It's pretty great. Oh my god
Das boot is throwing up a wharf. Did you get a signed wharf?
Is that a signed dorn?
Amazing. All right. Uh, i'm gonna thank some people who make this possible sign dorn
um
Quit saying sign dorn
All of these people leave a punch in odor for their dogs to tell time
That's uh scoop dave ill scoop it real good scoop jesus scoop lord tristan scoop mefa scoop nurse
Scoop of saltwater scoop t scoopaholic scoop paul's drag race scoop aluga scooper metroid scooper nova girl
Scoop it or ascending scoop neon black scoop o metrics scoop o hazard
Scoop check the experience scoopy dooby-doo
Sebastian robbins shoe the scoop sir scoopy mick scooperton the third esquire
Sola scoop spring loaded scoop strap a chicken on scoop technical scoop port and the bad humor man
Big thanks to these left-handed les paulers ajb
akshay mysore
andrea anderson
andrew j. Hughes
andrew conig andrew ossichuk andy cheek ant foods
our miss sarr
avan zarlez bart vonk base camp scoops bb hermit bj joyer ben ben dennis ben gow
Bobby becerra brendan light brendan allen brendan maddox aka an arco scoop
brian traves buster kamikaze cameron hall cassie rice charles eaton charles thompson charlie thompson chelsea far
chris spartchi chris ellis chris fisher and chris jackson
All right, these following people all try to call the cops using a speaking spell, but then they're covered in microplastic ooze
Uh, that would be the sensei scoop the civic crew scoop the diger reduce the lapis lagomorph the nano scoop the salty squid
The scoop lachian the spirit of the latin club the upside down scoop the dirty scoop the man the myth the scoop
Tk 421 scoop, please tony scoop rano
tuba scoop wacky tabaki scoop who that scoop wheel beardy dan wind walker scoop 23 for shaping
One small scoop for man aron aron boyd aron wentling and adam goff
The following people you ask them real nice and they will totally tootsie roll them backyard nuggets
christopher hayworth cj magnata colton salt salt mary colton sat mary, uh
Cory, did you marry? Yeah, we know where that's going sat mary not salt mary
Craig little daniel daniel lozor daniel wine dave hanson dave slusher david johnson david a small
david gravel david k david peterson don dotty dr tobias scoop a duck flan bay
Dwayne webb and ed andrick
And the following scoops have also made me realize that all of my other friends are disgusting
It's ed waggoner eric nelson finn steffenson galen digs garrett godfrey jing zinc george gustav
Warthog heather divina hansen ena chapman james dawson james fox james hubble janine lancard jason street jason
Vasquez jason yanowicz jeff libby jeff lumas jeremy hudson jesse rane jill short jimmy slow nina
john jacob schuppenheimer schmidt jordan campbell joseph foster joseph palero josh roberts josh
Wattar joshua wilson juan galvez keester sunday kelsey kendary ken fargy ken sodo kevin chamberlain kevin dory
Collin tony kristin claddock kurt egder lance amand lee drummond linda brandmere luke melon m hurts maple raisin scoop
Mark sad whiskey mark draiden mark madison mark uh picking him maybe and i'm aka stormer gatton
Yeah picket heim
Mark picket heim there you go
Yeah, i'm showing everybody in the chat that my son got me this for my for christmas
It's very oh, that's nice
It's that i've got your back shirt with two stick figures and one of them is holding the the stick
That would be the other one's back. Yeah
Without knowing any of the improv stuff. It doesn't that's an improv phrase very much is
But anyhow, I want to thank all those people and if you want to have your name read on air
If you want to join us for zoom chats if you want to look at all the other rewards we offer
Go over to preaching fun.com and select a tier that fits your budget today
Oh
Or if you just want to go in the garage and jam with matt's kids head on over to farts in a bag dot biz
That's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching fun.com it takes you over to our patreon page
Where for as little as three dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air
We are as always dependent on our patreon supporters. Uh, the new year is coming
You can subscribe for the full year. You get a little bit of a discount if you do that
You can also send uh subscriptions to other people as gifts
If you can't help out over at the patreon we get it help out at the obelisk scheme
Tell one person and one person only about us
Find somebody who is gonna dig on whatever this thing is
And uh, and maybe maybe tell that person about it. Maybe be smart about who you tell about it
Uh, but yeah, that'll be great
Uh, oh and if you wanted a little a little merch a little merchandise a little matt and mattings ice cream social swag if you will
Head on over to matt and mattingly. Uh, nope. That's wrong. Hey scoops.com slash shop or you can just type it in this little nugget
Store jingle door a big door song. We got a store
Oh store jingle.com
Merry christmas to you and me. It's right up there with mariah carrie's all over christmas is you just the caribbean christmas for all
Um, all right. I want to uh, I want to thank you all for tuning in stay safe out there
We love you and we'll see you soon
Like I got home and there wasn't anything to pick up there wasn't dog shit in the backyard the house was clean
The dishes were done. We're preaching fun
Check her teeth. It was amazing check her teeth
There's a series of riddles as to the whereabouts of my wife
It's perfect
Oh the old right wife riddles after christmas
Where's sj
With my family tradition we don't even start looking until after new year
[BLANK_AUDIO]