I'm here on a job site with Tim who owns his own electrical contracting business.
Three employees and two work trucks.
Tim traded up to Geico Commercial Auto Insurance.
We're positively here where he needs us most.
They sure are.
With step-by-step help on all his insurance needs.
All for shockingly low rates.
Shockingly low, huh?
It's just a little bit of electrician humor.
Do you get it?
I got it.
You know, it feels like we have a real connection.
All right, I'll stop.
Get a commercial auto insurance quote today at Geico.com
and see how much you could say it feels good to Geico.
Hey everybody, Jacob the Audio Guy here.
Tierney's Tavern, Thursday, October 23rd, Montclair, New Jersey, 7 p.m.
It is going to be great.
The doors open at 7.
Make sure you get there.
Tierney's Tavern, Thursday, October 23rd.
Doors open at 7 p.m.
It's a night of improv, stand-up, magic.
Matt Donnelly and Paul Mattingly.
That's right, Matt and Mattingly will be there.
Kurt Braunler will be there.
Dion Flynn from The Tonight Show with Jimmy Fallon will be there.
The Didgeridoo Scoop and so many more.
It is going to be amazing.
If you can get to Tierney's Thursday, October 23rd, 7 p.m., get there.
It is going to be a night to remember.
I'm a little jealous.
If you go and I'm not there, just know that I'm jealous of you.
That's right.
Here we go.
I've been working all day already.
It's fucking bullshit.
That's the thing about you.
Oh, you want to go to bed?
Yeah, I'm ready.
I want to thank all the ice cream truck drivers that have joined us today.
Thank you, all you ice cream truck drivers.
I don't have a new list with your names on it yet, but we will before this month is over.
And we will thank each and every one of you by name here at this part of the show.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I sure hope you do,
PreachingFun.com is where you can go.
Go to PreachingFun.com, sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and who knows?
The life you save may be your own.
And now, a program.
Hey, Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
What would you do?
Show of hands, everybody who's doing this show from a balcony on a cruise ship.
Hey, it's Boogey Matt Donnelly.
One goes up, that's doing it.
It's time for Matt Donnelly's Ice Cream Social.
Just sitting in a regular room, it's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in a different regular room, it's me, Jacob, the audio guy.
Sitting on the balcony of a cruise ship, it's Matt Donnelly.
We're PreachingFun.
I don't like being called Boogey.
Boogey Matt Donnelly.
I feel like nothing about me is being Boogey at all.
Matt Donnelly is wearing a bright pink hoodie modeled after the Beatles' "Sergeant Pepper" album.
Which one are you? Which one is that?
I don't know, the pink one? Mr. Pink.
Is that John?
Yeah. I think that's Paul.
Why would you get the Paul outfit?
Because the John one is the yellow one that none of the three of us wanted.
I think you would pick the Ringo one, and I think I had the George one.
Makes sense, all right.
I'm here to give sage wisdom.
What a large hood.
It's great, because you want to know why?
It's so windy, but I still want to get my steps in.
I can put my headphones on and put the hood on over the headphones and then tie it tight,
and I can walk around with my headphones on.
You're fairly incognito, eh?
Yeah.
It is a bigger deal than people realize for large-headed individuals
to have a hood on a hoodie that actually fits our head.
And same goes with those, you know, I use real headphones because the little ones that go in
the ears, again, when you have a large head, you also have large ear holes, and so those things
will fall out.
Earbuds just fall right out of your head?
Yeah, I can't wear earbuds.
Like throwing a hot dog down a hallway with your earbuds, huh?
I can do the-
I have a gaping, slutty ear hole.
Matt with his lobe gashes just completely wide.
Good Lord.
How do you think he gets that gig?
Oh, some serious aural stimulation.
The earbuds fall into his ears.
No, gross.
Little tweezers.
He's got four Raycons stuck in his-
Hurry, I just keep hearing Spotify ads.
Help me, help me.
Oh gosh, how many of you?
That's a loud helicopter.
Is that what it is?
The helicopter is coming by Matt right now.
It's great.
I'm sure they're not looking for him.
It's no big deal.
Citizen, are you on Twitch?
What is the content of your creation?
Twitch is really cracking down.
Airwolf, it could be airwolf.
It could be airwolf.
It could always be airwolf.
Stringfellow Hawk coming through.
So yesterday is this-
Is that a jet?
That's a jet.
I think we're right next to the airport.
They're gonna be done with my room so soon.
I'll go back inside so soon.
Why?
This is great radio.
Apparently there's a drawback to doing the show outside.
You'll never convince me.
A hovercraft, I'm just gonna keep-
I'm just playing an old sound effects CD.
Just modes of transportation.
Mode to transportation.
It's an old Spike Jonze bit.
They're invading Normandy right behind Matt.
We've got an airplane, a helicopter.
Next comes a slide whistle and a cymbal crash.
And a chicken squawking.
So I was supposed to be at sea today.
Because yesterday we were supposed to spend the day in Maine.
And one of the things that's interesting about Virgin is that they-
Basically when you go to ports that you can't dock at because your ship is too big,
you have to take boats, little boats from your ship to the shore, right?
Okay.
Those are called tender boats.
I prefer dinghies.
And it was really interesting because I didn't know that.
And everyone's like, "Oh, are we gonna tender?
Can we tender tomorrow?
Are we gonna tender?
Or how do we tender?"
And I was like, "What is going on?"
You didn't know what?
You didn't understand the lingo, eh?
I was like, "I brought plenty of gasoline.
Let's do this."
Let's rock and roll.
I'm an open-minded individual.
I assume my wife is as well.
But either way, she's not here.
She wanted me to do it.
She wanted me to do it tender.
That's what I know her.
So then we were in Maine and the seas were too rough.
And the current too strong to tender boat from the ship to the shores in Maine.
Oh, no.
So that means none of their excursions got to go through.
Right.
So excursions are over that kind of stuff.
And then also it meant that for the time being,
we were just spending the day sitting and looking at the shores of Maine.
Oh, look, there's Maine.
Was it kind of rocky even while you were docked?
No.
Not too bad.
Because you're lassoed in pretty tightly.
Yeah, because it's also more of a current issue
and currents weren't affecting the anchored gigantic boat.
Interesting.
But it's different when you're at sea and you're moving.
You're like, "Oh, it's a sea day, but we're going."
It's a different thing when you're at sea day and you're like,
"We can't go there and we're going to sit here."
Right?
And bless their hearts.
I'll say it.
Bless their hearts over there at Virgin.
They made some calls and about two hours into everything being canceled,
they're like, "Hey, we're going to Boston right now."
So we're supposed to be in Maine, go at sea for a day,
then be in Boston in the morning.
And they're like, "Nope.
We're going to haul ass right now and go to Boston right now."
And so you're going to have an overnight two-day Boston excursion.
And so I thought that was pretty heads up on their end.
It caused chaos.
Yeah.
It caused chaos in the entertainment department.
Being scheduled to the show.
You got to have shows going.
If the boat's moving, you got to have shows going, right?
Well, yeah.
Also, if we're at sea, your show is a primetime show.
Right.
If we're going overnight in Boston, it's the only overnight of the journey.
Boy, is no one going to your show.
Right.
Where did you fall?
I was not on either way until Monday.
So I don't have to worry about it, but yeah.
So I'm off.
Speaking of that, how is your life of leisure going between your one and a half shows a month?
I'm going fucking nuts.
Okay.
So now it's time for you to get a handheld console of some kind.
That's your next move.
I don't, I just think, yeah, yeah.
I'm all caught up on my boom beach of nailing.
Yeah.
You got to get a proper game boy or some kind of, yeah.
We got to get you a modified game boy.
That's got like thousands of games on it.
I watched some weird with Wyatt Russell in it.
I watched.
It does sound like a weird Western.
Wow.
I'm binging task, which is not a real heart warmer.
Not really.
It doesn't really warm the soul.
Anne and I, Anne and I bounced off of that on the first episode.
We got 30 minutes in.
She was like, Nope, I can't do it.
It's dark.
Oh, that's how, yeah.
What was that?
I single part of that show that looked, uh, that interested me enough to even turn it on.
Well, it was just, it's just so, it's so depressing.
Yes.
Anne just said straight up, she's like, there's enough happening.
I don't need more made up depressing.
I'm good.
Yeah.
No, no.
When you're, when you're living as a little cabin boy with room service,
looking at, looking at, uh, people living in a total hellscape with no hope is really,
really makes those eggs taste extra delicious.
Speaking of, uh, Matt, uh, sitting in living as a little cabin boy and other
people living a hellscape.
I saw Matt's wife the other night after we got done recording.
Oh, poor, poor hellscape to say hello.
This is, this is the hard part, right?
Like I'm doing four shows in two weeks and my wife is doing, like, uh, she is handling
the speaker world pride parade.
Yep.
She is hosting auditions for, uh, the show girls musical at Troy's theater.
Uh-huh.
She is running an afterschool program for the children.
She is also, uh, uh, basically some sort of manager of the disco show.
Some sort.
I don't know her exact position, but she's, she's, she's, she's a,
she's a managing member of the disco team.
Sure.
And, uh, there are people down at absence.
And so Sarah is filling in for two people and covering everyone's shifts over at absence.
Uh, right now I'm doing all the shows and getting my boys to soccer practice and band practice.
And I have to do four shows in 14 days.
I feel like such an asshole.
I can't.
I saw her on, I saw her on Wednesday evening and, uh, she comes over, we're chatting and
somebody, uh, also asked how you were doing and she went, oh, I think he's doing.
Actually, she looks at me, you saw him this morning. How's he doing?
I said, he's fine.
Uh, he's a little stressed about, uh, just sitting in the cabin while you're running life, uh, here.
And she gave me the biggest eye roll that I have seen come out of.
Oh, boy.
I'm familiar.
Luckily for you though, luckily for you, it was her birthday.
And, uh, show it was on her birthday, but everyone at the show was just coming up to
her and telling her happy birthday and singing to her. So everybody at the show went really out of
their way to make sure that your wife had a good birthday evening. I think that was, I think that
was really good. That was, that was a good ending of the day, especially for Matt Donnelly.
Who was it? Some of Amy Poehler was interviewing, uh, a woman and she's in that Leo, Leo DiCaprio
movie that's out right now, Paul Thomas Anderson. Um, who's that lead actor? I forget her name.
And, uh, she was joking. She was like, you know, every man in their marriage says their
wife is their best friend. But if you ask the wife of their best friend is they have a list of friends.
She's like, men don't know how to have friends. She's like, well, women have friends.
And said, good thing that you have this podcast, cause you've got male friends.
My wife was, uh, was showered with, with cards and gifts and people take her out to lunch and all
that stuff. And, uh, I sent some, uh, a vegan dark chocolate, uh, gift baskets from far away.
Oh yeah. I wanted to thank you for that. That was really good.
Jacob, it's supposed to go to Sarah. I was so excited about the school mail.
Man, I wasn't going to mention anything. I saw that dark smudging all around your mouth hole.
I thought that's probably chocolate, but I don't want to, you know, put him on blast.
It's mostly chocolate. It's 85% chocolate. Jacob have asked, we'll eat at Smith.
Have asked, we'll eat Brogan. There's your sticker.
Oh my God. I'm straight up delirious today from work. I just, yeah. Yeah. Just work just makes
me delirious at this point. Is it all Christmas stuff now that you're dealing with? Uh, we're,
we're about to hit Christmas. Yeah. We were getting, we're getting Christmas scented shit.
Meanwhile, a scented foreshadowing of what's, yeah. Yeah, exactly. We're getting like pine needle,
uh, glade plugins and we're getting fucking, uh, leaves, leaves and autumn soap, hand soap.
Like today, like we got the Christmas scents before we got the autumn scents is weird.
And that doesn't make horse sense. It doesn't make a damn lick of sense, but it does. Oh boy.
So yeah. And then just being up so early today, but then I couldn't sleep today because I had
stuff to take care of at home. So I haven't got my nap in. So I'm kind of just in that,
and then it's true. Well then right before, right before we record at about a half hour ago,
Anne calls me. She says, Hey, can you look over this resume I put together and do some,
you know, uh, edit, you know, just edit and copyright or not copy copy editing resume.
It was a, it was a Tinder resume. So she sent me a resume. And so I really, sorry,
I'm just refilling from my recently refilled vase of drinking water. You've got a fucking
fresh carafe, fresh carafe. Oh my God. Uh, life is tough, man. Cruise life is tough. I've been there
for all the trappings, not for the guilt. I would be loving it. But this is the thing. I
had the exact same or similar situation, but mine was even crazier because I couldn't get off the
boat for four or five months. Oh yes. So like major life events would happen and I was just stuck.
No, you have, I could only call Anne once a week, sometimes once every two weeks.
No, there are people that are on here like that for like forever. Right. And so, uh, I heard things
like, I just get the burger of the day, just experienced something different. I don't care
whether I like it or not. I just get the burger of the day. I was like, Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I know it's got pear on it. It doesn't sound good, but I'm interested. Some vinegar dipped pear
Gruyere. Oh Jesus. It looks really pretty in the picture. I know it's not going to taste that good,
but I'm going to try it. He's got something a little different. Barf. Oh, that sounds good.
So you were, you were tasked with punching up a resume. Yes. I was tasked with, uh, doing a quick,
um, you know, what do you call it? Cop? Not what? Editing, editing? Yeah. Copy, copy, copy. Yeah.
Doing like copy, editing a resume and then they went and whatnot. And I think I, yeah, copy edit.
And I did a, uh, I did a bang up job if I say so myself. Yeah. As long as the words copy edit
didn't have to be in there anywhere. Thank God. Thank God. She's not a copy editor.
I barely am, but, uh, you know, I agree Paul. You are barely a copy editor. Yeah, I barely am.
Was it her resume or someone else's resume? No, it was her resume. So yeah. So exciting things.
I was going to say, I was like, inter company. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't know if it was
like, uh, everybody keep your fingers crossed for all the applying for the role as ICS host.
Yeah. She's coming. She's coming on. I would, I would cross my fingers, Paul, but I have so much
to do. I have so much going on. I get it. So I get it. I'll get around to it. Okay. Oh, he's halfway
there. This is good. This is good. Don't rush yourself. I don't want a rush job happening.
Not going to, it doesn't mean as much if it's, if it's hurried. You want quality. Yeah. Quality
finger crossing over quantity finger crossing. But so yeah, I was just doing that right up to the end
and then, uh, you know, shifting the dogs around. Cause I got, I gotta run the giz and, uh, Adora
warden. So I got to switch them. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. One has to be away while the other gets to
roam free and then back and forth, back and forth. You got to balance yard time. They still don't get
along. No. Oh, I thought it was like, I thought it was like a temporary growth. No, no, no. This
is a forever thing. This is not something that I would be okay with as a pet owner. It's, uh,
it's simply not be okay with some of my pets being like, no, no, fuck you. No. Yeah. It's
agger damn bait. And that's for sure. Uh, either she is on my lap next to, uh, or next to Ann.
Okay. Uh, or she is put away or one of the other one has put away. Uh, but so yeah, I spend
Nope. All the time. No babysitting is making sure gives is there and safe. And then, and then she'll
start going, because she needs to go out or want some water or whatever. And then I had to go and
lock up a Dora and then put her out and then take her back and get a Dora back out.
And when Ann's home, you have to put her up too, right? Oh, forget it. They are vinegar and water.
Just, I think that's right. Is that right? Vinegar, vinegar and water. And also that's
going to be on the new burger of vinegar and water. It does not sound good, but I mean,
it is going to be on there. It will be something different. And water actually do mix there. I
believe it's oil and water. Oil and vinegar. I don't know. Why not oil and vinegar? It's,
you know, it's the reason these oil spills are a problem is because they don't mix snow and not
snow. That's it. As your copy editor, but I ask if you want to do oil, oil and vinegar instead of
water and vinegar. He doesn't know what copy editors mean. I do though. I do. I just don't
remember what the phrase is right, but it was. Yeah. Oh boy. So yeah. Fingers crossed for
whatever she should. She will crush whatever it is. Yes. Yes. I only, uh, you know,
shake my head in disbelief anytime she's passed over for anything because fools, fools. They know
not the power of Ann McPheeters. Yeah. That's right. Get shit done. She gets to put Matt and
I down as references. Okay. I'll do that. I'll do that. I'm sure she'll do that. I'll FaceTime
with whoever wearing this sweatshirt. Oh, I'll be ready. Where, where are the fish head? Uh,
Ms. McPheeters, we were going to hire you for this. We called one of your references.
He was sprawled nude on a cruise ship balcony during the entire zoom call that we had with him.
We couldn't really hear him over the helicopters. Yeah. It was just a lot of helicopter sounds
and we couldn't tell if it was from an actual helicopter or just the way he was rotating his
wiener. He was harpooned by someone in a lifeboat to make sure that he jumped.
It seemed effective. It seemed effective. Tender that man.
I'll tell you who else wants to get tendered. And that's the following sponsor. Today's show,
Matt Madley's ice cream social is, Oh, come on now brought to you by use without the internet.
Come on. Oh, I thought you, I thought you read something, uh, scary. No, no, no, no. What,
what could be going wrong in the world now? Um, well, I have one. Yeah. My, my phone's being a
Dick one second. Oh yeah. I've got one. Say that one for the next one. Okay. We got one for crazy
Jeff's propeller hats for corgis. That's from street scooper crazy Jeff's propeller hats for
corgis. Hi, my name is crazy Jeff. Uh, I've sell propeller hats for corgis for a long time.
I couldn't maintain a job or a relationship at all because I was crazy and, uh, I just could,
I couldn't get it together for anything except the thought of putting propeller hats on small
Welsh corgi dogs. And I started doing that and they let me know how I got these hats.
Let me tell you,
my first corgi was a fee. He was slipping farther and farther into that Joker impression.
Well, spoiler, crazy Jeff was eventually going to go totally crazy in that, uh, commercial.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It was definitely, it was going to be a slow burn for sure. For sure. He was, you know, he, you know,
he was coming off as relatively St. Jeff for a pretty long while. So yeah.
Yeah. So, yep. Uh, I saw, so those show their production shows here on board. Oh good. Oh yeah.
Those are always a trip. What's, what is the title of one now? This was one's called out of time.
Oh, good. Is that, is that banking on the whole, um, musical musicalization of back to the future?
I see why you would think that Paul, it's actually a, a Jersey boys style musical
about Huey Lewis and the news. You're close. There you go. Yeah.
You know, I just sat in there on the street, like with my friends,
I didn't want to share that with everybody. So I was like, do I go Italian Huey Lewis or how do I
Lewis? I went Huey Lewis on an arena stage. That's why he's speaking a little slowly and loudly.
Don't take money. Don't take fame. Don't need no credit card to ride on this train. Hey, hey,
you know what I'm saying? It's very sudden. It could be cruel sometimes, but it might just change
your life. They say that all in love is fair. Yeah, but you don't care. You know, Joe Pesci
is also in my musical. Yeah. Well, you know what to do. We didn't get told to you with a little
help from above. You'll feel the power of love. It turns out Joe Pesci knew all musical stars
before they became famous. Joe Pesci is also, he's actually a key component into making Huey Lewis.
That'd be great. Yeah. Uh, anyway, uh, no. So, uh, Paul, Paul's right. It's a, it's about a time
machine thing. It's a time machine thing. Ooh. Oh, it is just about a time machine. Yeah. It's
Raiding the Rock Vault. It's Raiding the Rock Vault. Back when Raiding the Rock Vault was still
conceptual and had a giant Mayan temple. Those of you who don't know, Raiding the Rock Vault
started off as astronauts invading a giant Mayan temple and discovering ancient hieroglyphs of rock
and roll. Federal archaeologists. Yes. They were talking about the federal archaeologists.
That was when they were having auditions and our friend, uh, uh, who was our friend? Uh,
SJ. It's my wife. Brandon. Brandon, uh, got in, um, Brandon. Anyway, someone told me I had to
audition right away. And I said, I'm in LA with my family. And I said, well, they're only, yeah,
I was in, I was in fucking California at the same time. We were both fucked for the DJ. Yeah. I, uh,
so I flew home to make it to the audition time. And he said, oh, just kidding. I'm not seeing
anyone else today. And I was like, okay, thanks for having me leave my family in California and
fly home to do this audition. Thanks, buddy. Who had you do that? Uh, our friend, our friend,
who later on was like, yeah, our friend later on, it was like, Hey, can you get pen and tell it?
No, not Brandon. Brandon didn't do it. Brandon actually got the gig eventually. Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yeah. No, no, it wasn't Brandon. Sorry. Yeah. Yeah. Ryan, Ryan. Yeah. Right. Right. Ryan was
in it for a long time. Right. Had me fly home and said, just kidding. And then, uh, uh, and then
later on I was like, Hey, can you get pen and tell her to do this thing? And I was like, you know
what? I can't. You know what? No, no, I can't. You know what? Give me, give me, give me 180 bucks
back and maybe we'll talk $180 and some time with my children, which has a price. Let's be honest,
not. It does. It does. It does. I'm sitting in a cabin. The price is here. The price is right.
Motherfuckers prices. Right. My little golden bottoms glass of water.
That's just there with magic fish, scaring housekeepers, too much, too much rating. The
rock vault is finally closing this year in Las Vegas. Yes. I think, I think, I think just like
a couple of years past this will be the year we're talking about a lot of shows closing. Uh, but yeah,
my sincere hope touring, but yeah, they're going to, they're going to close at the old hard rock
cafe here in Vegas. Finally, at the end of the year, after I think like 12 years, my sincere hope
for rating the rock vault goes to the old wrestling adage. How can they miss you if you never go away?
And I really think that maybe three years from now, they can come back and really,
well, let's see 20, 28 provided things are still intact. She's shaking out in a certain way. Let's
say 20, 28 maybe. Yeah. Okay. Just as a, just as a arbitrary. Gotcha. Yeah. Okay. I'm not picking
that date for any specific reason. No, and again, we, we, we, a little Vegas and parking weather,
they're trying to do a couple of things for some, because you know, so you're like not going to
charge for parking for locals. Other people are trying to buy deals. And the whole point is just
like, man, Vegas is a town of bold swings. So if you kind of inch back little things and expect it
to have a big impact, you're a fool. Yeah. Uh, Cosmopolitan. I just got an email, uh, about three
minutes ago, uh, a report about Cosmopolitan. They are doing a new special to try to entice, uh,
locals and quote unquote, industry people to come to Cosmopolitan. And what they are doing
is they are offering free parking to these people every single Monday.
Mondays free parking to locals on Monday. When I was in my twenties and Monday was my night off
after I worked on a Saturday and Sunday, I started a thing with my friends called Monday's the new
Saturday and we would go nuts on Monday nights. I'm not even saying that I won't take advantage of
this ever. I'm just saying it's a dumb promotion. It worked in a very small group of friends in the
nineties and two thousands, uh, uh, early two thousands. I would like you and that group of
friends to hang out at the Cosmo on Monday nights going forward. Let's see how long they keep this
going. What the Cosmopolitan is missing in this calculation is there need to be industry people
employed in Las Vegas for the discount to apply. And if all the industry people are getting let go,
here's an example of what I think would, uh, would, would be fun. Okay. Free parking and
free valet again, because it used to be free valet when you first came here. Right. For an entire
month for an entire, if, if, if all of November, it was just free parking and free valet because
that would make people I think from Los Angeles and stuff go like, Oh, maybe it'd be fun to just
roll in there and toss the keys and go into Vegas for a weekend or whatever. Like they might, like
that would be something that would at least make people go like, Oh shit. You know, like, you know,
like there you go. Scoop. Jesus has got it. No fee. November. I was going to say no pay November
November to go along with no nut November as we all celebrate. Of course. Yeah.
I've been celebrating that in October. I'm getting a jump on it.
That was low hanging fruit. That's why I can't resist touching it. Boy. Yeah. That's a good
idea, Matt. It does need to be a big move, right? There are still a couple of casinos that have
free valet or stupid. It needs to be like, Oh, like, Oh, what? Like it needs to go like, Whoa,
like it needs to like make people go like, Oh shit, cool. They just back. That's what that's like. So
like these little inching things of like, Oh, well, you know, we're not charging for this over here.
We can give this much and maybe that will get enough people in the door to move the needle a
little bit. Yeah. But we won't change too much. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But they won't do it. Well,
I don't want to give away too much production stuff here, but I feel like our dealings with
the Orleans reflected very much sort of the zeitgeist of what's going on in Vegas. And I
see this quoted by local Vegas and Las Vegas locally and, and, uh, uh, you know, some of our
favorite, uh, Twitter bloggers and whatnot, how, you know, this vicious cycle of, Oh shit,
we're losing money because no one's coming. Let's charge everyone for everything, right? Every little
thing because everything's that used to be free. Now our, our, our charges, things that used to be
just considered complimentary. Now our charges, things that we used to be able to make a deal on
now, we can't negotiate a fucking penny, you know? And then that gets even worse because you start
to tighten the strings on the people who are actually paying to utilize your space. And then
they don't want to utilize your space. And then it's like, well, yeah. Yeah. Sorry. I wasn't
listening. What'd you, uh, could you start from the beginning again? So I don't want to give too
much away here regarding our interactions. Yeah. I was just saying you wasn't talking about the
always the time I think as a whole. So Jacob and I both leaned in and leaned out. Yeah. No, I wasn't,
I'm not, I didn't want to give too much away. I don't mind telling the audience that we had a
very fucking hard time dealing with the audience this year. Oh yeah. Yeah. No, they were tough
this year. Yeah. And I think, but I mean, I think it's part, not just for us. I talked to other
people that had events there and everyone had exactly the same complaints. And I think it's
in no small part due to that whole effect of the tightening of belts all the way around and the
rejiggering of employ employees to where people who aren't familiar with their prior roles, you
know, and if you don't want to give too much away here, but we actually had kind of a hard time
dealing with the Orleans this year. Okay. I don't want to spill all the beans, but this year our
relationship with the Orleans was strained. It was. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But not to give too
much away. Let's keep some cats in the bag here, but let's also say so far as us go into the Orleans,
that was tough this time around. That was a real dick kick. If only there was a free place for me
to park on Mondays, then it would all be better. Then I'd hang out on the strip some more. Yeah.
And, uh, yeah. And they get a whole casino full of people wearing our robes and fezzes. Good point,
Laurie Elsroth. Like we add ambiance to that. That is a win-win. I mean, I'll tell you who loves
us at the Orleans is our bartenders. The bartenders love us and the production guys love us. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But, uh, every day I would check in with the bartenders and be like, how'd you do
today? And the bartenders would be like, fuck me. These scoops are awesome. I'm telling you. Magic.
There it is. I've seen the bars. Ultimately, those motherfuckers who are working, those are the only
people I care about actually making happy. I do want them to be happy. That is absolutely true.
And one of the bartenders said it was like, I can't wait for you guys to come back. And we were like,
Ooh. And then he's like, Oh, don't, don't wait in one hand and not shit in the other because
you're going to become a constipated motherfucker. Like one of the bartenders, uh, he had been with
us, uh, for our two previous shows or our two previous scoops. Oh, really? So he made a point
to get sure to get up here. Uh, I saw you guys on the schedule. I made sure to get up here.
Yeah. He, he was, he was having a fucking, he remembered it's a good time, right? Yeah. Yeah.
Um, I'll tell you who else remembered that it was a good time. And that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by sweat house, roofing company, hot shingles, just waiting to be
nailed. That's right. Sweat house, roofing company, hot shingles, just waiting to be nailed. That's
right. It's time. You know what time it is time to check your papers for openings and try them to
check your openings for papers. Go ahead and look into class asifieds. That's right. Right
under the asifieds. You're going to find our sweat house, roofing, hot shingles in your area,
ready to be nailed anytime. Yes, indeed. Whether you like it hot or whether you want it wet,
even if you need it metal, we got you covered. We always got you covered at the sweat house,
roofing company. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. How about a little Colombian tile? If you know what I mean,
huh? Huh? How about some, huh? Do I know what you mean? Do you, do I, do you,
do I? I'm talking about doing drugs and having sex. Oh, okay. That's the secret of our roofing
company. It's actually a front for drugs and sex in a van. Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah. We'll come
right to your house and fuck you. You can fuck me in my own house. Why do I have to go in that van?
Oh, a van just pulled up in front of my house. Somebody's ringing the doorbell. Hey,
how's it going neighbor? Your roof looks like it needs some help. Wink, wink, exaggerated wink,
deep, deep exaggerated wink. I'm saying it for the benefit of the listening audience,
but I'm also doing it. Wink, wink, exaggerated wink, innuendo hand sign. Wink, wink. Would you
like a new roof? Wink, wink, innuendo hand sign. Yes. Oh yeah. No, I would like a new roof. Yes.
Great. Get in my van and take off your clothes and give me your credit card. Oh, I see on it.
Okay. Now you get it. It's a fraud protection thing. Yes. Also, would you like some Colombian
tile? Oh, I know what you mean. Do you? I do. Do you? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So I just confused the
first and now, but you got it right away. Yeah. Yeah, no, it's Colombian tile. Okay. Fair. Yeah.
Enter hate scoops to check out. I guess I'm just slow. You'll get it. First, you get the mortar,
then you get the pestle, then you get the Colombian tile. So is that the order? I don't know.
First, you get the pestle, then you get the mortar. I guess that's probably the better way.
Because how are you going to transport the mortar without the pestle? First, you get the pestle,
then you get the mortar, then you get the tile. Say hello to my little roof. Oh, hi. Wink, wink,
deep, deep wink. Yep. I was watching the time traveling show. There's a time machine. What is
it? What is it? Top of a rack. What is it? It's a microwave sitting on top of a rack that's spray
painted. Wait a minute. Yeah. Do they get inside? Why are you in disbelief here? It's a pushcart,
and you put stuff in it, and then the screens go all crazy, and then they go to a different time.
And I was laughing because it would just go to 1950 something, and then it was in a diner,
and then they had to get fuel each time they needed to leave. So the different fuel had to
go in the microwave to power the time machine to go to different times. 21 gigawatts and whatnot.
In the diner, there's this elaborate bit during a dance number to steal a cheeseburger because the
cheeseburger is the fuel needed to go. That was enough fuel. And I was like, it's a diner. Just
order a cheeseburger. You don't need to steal that one. Just order a burger. What are you doing?
Right. It's a 1950s diner. Your dollar will go really far. And I was laughing because it
all of a sudden went to 10,000. Spoiler alert for those of you who want to go see the show.
Thank you. But it goes to 10 million BC or something like that, right?
And I was laughing because, yeah, I was laughing because when it went to very far in the past,
very far in the future, there were people around me that were like, whoa. And I was like, really?
They were in. They were bought in.
Oh, this is not squirrely.
Well, I mean, 10,000 to get out of this one. Well, this is this is pre humans, right?
I believe so. Yeah, not in this one. No, no. OK. There's some tribal dancing.
Wait, because because humans have been around. This is the biblical one. 300,000 years.
Yeah, they I didn't write them. I didn't write the years down. Maybe they got it right and I
got it wrong. I don't want to despair. The musical don't come to me for exact dates.
I don't fucking know. But I mean, I'm a sapiens.
Scoop Jesus is putting on the chat like I've noticed some plotholes in this cruise ship
jukebox time travel musical. No, I get it. That part's like, no, it's ridiculous. Of course it is.
I was bringing the story to the people just be like, whoa, like it was blowing people away.
I was ready for time travel, but not extreme time travel.
What do they think of next? I don't know. The most logical thing.
Did they do jungle love? They did not do jungle love, although.
Did they do walk the dinosaur when when it featured tribal people? It did go into more
ethnic and rap songs. Oh, no, no, no. Suddenly it's a Busta Rhymes video.
Yeah, yeah. I was kind of like, maybe don't maybe don't put those two together like that.
Well, you know what? Kudos to them for really addressing our troubled past.
In the 50s diner, everybody was definitely a lot of races all getting along and everyone
got to sit wherever they wanted. Now, there's a chance I could add some real commentary.
I don't know what I would like to see on a cruise ship more, a cheesy song and dance
show where they're traveling through time or a show where they really examine all of the problems
in America's racial history. Hey there, Daddy. Oh, where'd you zip in from? I'm from the future.
I'm from the future. I'm from 2026. Wowzers. What's that like? Well, it's not too far off
from the 1950s. All the racism and segregation, but none of the prosperity. Fuck us, right? Yeah.
How'd you build a time machine? God knows. Why don't you want to stay here? I'm ignorant. I'm
going back to where dinosaurs are because I've got a better chance of making a life for myself
in the time of dinosaurs than I do in my time. You're right. I do want to see the educational
show on the cruise ship. I want to see the exploration. It's Saturday night. I'm going
to go to the Rosa Parks musical. Let's do it. Look, man, I'm a tyrannosaurus Rex, not a
tyrannoracist Rex. Everybody gets along in my time unless you're prey.
But you could still sit anywhere you want in our dino diner. Oh, the diner is still there. Oh,
yeah. Of course. The diner is the through line for the diner show. The dino diner.
It's always been a diner. No matter what time period they go through, it's always a diner.
This show writes itself. I would love to meet you and Sarah and maybe even Jacob and SJ,
honestly, all of us. I think it'd be really fun to take a swing at trying to come up with a cruise
ship show that we could put together. A jukebox musical for cruise ships. I think we could fucking
crush it. That might be the next episode of this show. We could just be us coming up with one.
Seriously, we could crush one. The four of us all together with all the experience we've had on both
sides. Jacob could come at it with the tech stuff, and we could come at it from a writing
perspective, and you can come at it from a performance perspective. We could make something
really interesting, I think. All right. We're going to stop doing this podcast. From now on,
we're just writing cruise ship musicals. Step three, profit. All you need is one. All you need
is one. It'll play forever. You have these young people who are crazy talented. You have to do so
many dance numbers and sing so many songs to get on these things. They have their songbook and they
can kick ass choreography. Then you put them in these musicals that are so strange, where every
costume's a million dollars. I was going to showcase myself, but instead of playing a
secret spy scientist wearing a dinosaur tail. That's where I'm doing. That's where I'm living
my life, my best life right now. That's where the money is. Yeah. It was fun. It was certainly
worth seeing. Did they go to the far-flung future eventually, too? Yes. They went back before the
big bang. No lightsabers. What indicated future? When they were hanging out before the big bang,
I was like, where are you hanging out and where are you standing? Where were they? They went to
before the big bang. They went to before the big bang. Now, wait a minute. They said that was before
the big bang. That's where they had some real soul searching, Paul. That's where they really
started to discover who they were and their feelings for each other. Well, it's because they
didn't have any lights. They just went to pitch black. They're like, oh, this is before the big
bang. All matter was condensed into one tiny particle. I was like, how was our sound traveling
from my mouth to your ears before the big bang? Again, I don't want to poke holes in a cruise ship
musical. I was curious about it. There's so much happening here before the big bang.
A really great image of dinosaurs dressed up like line cooks. Pretty great.
I'm just thinking of different scenes that you can do before the big bang.
Well, the diner, it's sort of like Hitchhiker's Guide, the diner at the end of the universe,
right? Yeah. There you go. Yep. How is this diner even here? Who knows? Before the big bang.
Who the fuck knows? We're all just hash browns. Can I get some pancakes? Not before the big bang.
They don't exist yet. We don't even have moons over Miami because there are no moons. Hey,
how are Miami? How about Miami? Welcome to Miami. Benvenido. How about the Giants beat the Eagles
last night in football? That was pretty fun. That was pretty fun. What happened? Giants beat the
Eagles with Jackson Dart. The New York Giants looked like the best team in the football league.
That's what happened. I only bring this up because Jackson Dart absolutely is the
boyfriend of the daughter from Landman. I was watching him at a press conference. I was like,
oh my God, it's just the boyfriend from the show Landman, the high school football player.
Oh yeah. He's totally the same guy. Paul went away, but Paul... I'm here. He wears like a black
splotch on his cheek. Yeah, he doesn't do the black face paint below both eyes. He just does
like a big splotch below one eye. He does it because it's a tribute to Anakin Skywalker.
Is it really? It is. He was playing in high school and he was inspired by Anakin Skywalker
and then put a little black splotch on his cheek and it looked pretty cool. So that became his
thing from then on. It was so funny because Herb Street and Al Michaels... Al Michaels is
like almost 80 years old. He's done all the greatest kids, called the miracle of ice in
the 1980 Olympics. Herb Street's like, of course, it's a Star Wars reference. Mike, you want to take
it from here? Al Michaels goes, "Al, you want to take it from here?" He goes, "No, no, no.
I love me some Star Wars, but no, you go ahead, Kurt. You break it down for the audience."
Al Michaels was like, "Do not make me talk about Star Wars." He just went, "Nope."
Wow. Well, I mean, that generation, they really did love the prequels.
It was very impactful for them. That was their big movie going experience. I got to say Hayden
Christensen was doing a lot of heavy lifting. He tried with that shit script that he had.
Props to him, but I guess the blotch is to indicate when he got burned up in the...
Yeah. Oh, it's the scar. It's the scar. Okay. Now I see. I thought it was just on his cheek. Oh,
no, it's the scar. Okay. Okay. Yeah. He's like blacked out one eye. Yeah. He gets a scar.
Okay. Well, he's a handsome little Hayden Christensen looking dude himself.
He really is. He is a gorgeous man. The quarterback of the New York professional football team
is very attractive and is going to do just fine in his life. Yeah. I bet you he's going to be
okay. He's going to have some really nice Star Wars memorabilia. I'll bet he already has some
really nice Star Wars memorabilia. New York transfer, not known for their looks. Eli was
never... You hold your tongue, Eli Manning. Apparently he did. He often would sit on the
sideline and just hold his tongue. He's not a smart man. I'm Eli Manning. I throw ball. I make
touchdown go happen. I hold tongue. Hey, I hold tongue. Hey, sideline man, you hold tongue for a
minute and make phone call. I can hold that for you. Thank you. Make phone call while someone else
hold tongue. Hello. This is Eli Manning calling from Eli Manning's phone. Not since Paulman that
he's done such an accurate impression of a person. A large cheese. That's right. Deliver it to Eli
Manning, please. Good night. Well, that went good. I expect to eat pizza later. I'll hold tongue now.
Thank you. Yeah. So. Yeah. Eli Manning holds on tongue. That was about how good looking Jackson
Darn was. That's all. Let's do some Scoop Mail. Message for you, sir. We got one here from Bus
Driver Scoop. Dear Matt, Paul, Jacob, and the entire Scoop community, how does an introverted
extrovert that is unbelievably damaged mentally by life express how incredibly loved and accepted
they felt at their first Scoop Fest? Oh, how does said person express the amount of confidence and
self-worth they obtained simply by being in the presence of this community for four days?
I really do not know where to begin with the thanks, the hugs, the heartfelt face fuckings.
I really can't find the right words to tell each and every single person that I crossed paths with
that you are amazing. And I am infinitely grateful not only for your existence, but also for you,
for your acceptance into this spectacular group of humans. Thank you from the bottom of my heart
for being all that you are. Love and licks. That's Tracy, the Bus Driver Scoop. Oh, yeah.
Whatever. That's a bad prank. This is like that. This is wonderful. This is wonderful. Yeah. Yeah.
We got to pass that on to JD for yet another Scoop confessional. Or maybe it made it into
a Scoop confessional we didn't even see. Oh, yeah. I don't know. We aren't privy to any of that. We
don't know. No. I hope to see them at some point. We got one from Masshole Scoop. Dear gentlemen,
in episode 1244, you guys discussed the song Darling Nikki by Prince. The first time my mother
ever heard that song was in April of 1985. I had been born in March of 1985. My name is Nikki.
Jacob gave a good rundown of the song on that episode. But for context, the very first lyrics
are I knew a girl named Nikki. I guess you could say that she was a sex fiend. I met her in a hotel
lobby masturbating with a magazine. My poor mother was completely horrified. She said that if she had
just heard that song a month earlier, there is no way in hell that she would have named her baby
Nikki. My name would have been Sarah. And that would have been weird. So I'm glad it all worked
out. You're right. People named Sarah are weird. In the same episode, Matt talked about the band
G love and special sauce. Oh, yeah. Coincidentally, they also have a song that references a girl named
Nikki performing sex acts on the singer. It's called kick drum. And it's actually a really good
song. It is a good face. That's a mass hole scoop. Who is a brand? That's a brand new scoop name.
Oh, fantastic. Yeah. Thank you. Mass hole scoop. So that's another question for the ages. And I'd
love to get the popular opinion. Matt, Jacob, what is your take on Nikki's actual physical situation
during this scenario? Is she reading and perusing a magazine and diddlin the beam?
Or is she rolling up the magazine to some sort of phallus and inserting it?
You know, Paul, they're by masturbating with a magazine.
I have to thank you, Paul, because I thought I was going to have to ask that question.
And so thank you. Thank you for being one of the eternal burning questions.
Nikki actually doing with that magazine option B is eternally burning. That's for sure.
And then ML Kennedy says the magazine was also masturbating, right? That's another reading on
it. It could have been joining in on the magazine's master magazine. There's masturbating.
I think Prince forgot the word for reading and replace it with masturbation.
Do you think he just did a search and replace? He forgot the word for reading.
Better than a hotel lobby reading a magazine.
I wonder what that word means. I don't know. Let's replace it with masturbating.
Reading too few syllables doesn't work. Linguistically, he knew what would shove
that magazine back up your hoo-ha and get back to writing. Also, you would hope that that's a
very glossy tome because if it's just straight newsprint, he's going to disintegrate. You're
basically, she's going to have a paper machine. Check your openings for paper.
Well, luckily it wasn't glossy magazine. When you read the lighter notes, it said,
do not try this at home. Do not utilize lighter notes for hoo-ha insertion.
When I read the lighter notes, they were all smudged from being in my hoo-ha.
We got one from Trav. Hi, I have over a decade of professional experience in kitchens,
not to mention my continued learning and growth in the 20 plus years of my adult life
that I haven't gotten paid for cooking. I say this to only say, unfortunately,
Paul is right about microwaving hot dogs. He's an absolute potato when it comes to
microwaving bratwurst though. You see, cooking a hot dog just involves warming it up. Most of them,
you can eat it raw. For the most part, they're cured and fully cooked. Therefore, the only thing
that needs to be done is to make it hot to be tastier. The traditional method for a ballpark
hot dog is boiling. Cooking a hot dog in a microwave is essentially the same thing. It's
akin to steaming. As long as you don't overdo it, a microwave hot dog is perfectly acceptable.
One could argue even efficient. I'm not saying you microwave the bun. Never microwave bread.
It makes it tough. Now, there could be arguments that grilling a hot dog adds more flavor and a
bit of texture. That's not wrong, but that doesn't make a microwaved hot dog unpalatable. It just
makes those options better. Let's not pretend that a hot dog is some culinary masterpiece.
It is a way to dress up the leftovers and sell some cheap ass shit. Love y'all. Fuck you in
the face. That's Trav, AKA I-D-H-A-S-N. It hasn't. I don't know. I appreciate that, Trav. Thank you
for coming to my defense. Yes, I agree. Well, he did say that you're a potato for microwaving
bratwurst. Look, I did it once. Okay. I've learned my lesson. Potato. Yeah. It's just a convenience
thing. Yeah. Tell that to my intestines. The science is tight on this. It does not.
It's not the same. The science is out.
And we got one here from Robert. Hi folks. Loved episode 1227. Rob's story about his
heroin neighbors reminded me of our old family friend, Tim. He was about 60 at the time and this
took place back in the '80s, back in Poughkeepsie, New York. Every fall, Tim would wander into our
woods and collect giant "basketball mushrooms." Not a nickname. They were literally the size of
basketballs. My gosh. He had the foraging know-how to tell the good from the deadly and had sliced
them like bread and fry them up. Said they were delicious. We weren't brave enough to find out for
ourselves. Then one year, Tim just stopped showing up. He was dirt poor and had no phone. So we had
no way to check on it. Our best guest, he finally grabbed the wrong mushroom and joined the network
in the sky. Years later, surprise, Tim reappears. Turns out he had gone to prison. He did what?
He went to prison. He did what? There's no expanding thing on this. He just went to prison.
For mushroom thieving? Who knows? I like to think it was for mushroom thieving.
Fast forward, he's turned things around, got a place, even a phone. He calls my grandfather
and asks if I, the family's designated pre-teen tech wizard, can help him set up a fax machine.
Grandpa and I head to his sketchy apartment in one of Poughkeepsie's less than great neighborhoods.
I plug in the brand new fax machine and ask if he has anyone to fax or someone who might fax him.
Then we spend 20 minutes explaining what a fax machine actually does. He seems surprised by the
concept. Then he says, "Thanks for coming over. I got something for you." He leads us into the kitchen
and there, stacked like techno Jenga, are 50 brand new fax machines. I decline. No thanks.
I don't need one either. Tim nods, "You're right. I've got something better for a kid."
Into the bedroom we go, and now there's a stack of 50 boom boxes. Brand new. Shrink wrap still on.
I shoot grandpa a look. Grandpa just shrugs. We both left with a boom box. Mine drains deep
batteries like it owed the Energizer Bunny money. Baby. That is from Robert.
That's amazing. I tell you, the best not stolen boom boxes in the '80s still drained those fucking
deep batteries like they were going out of style. Yeah, it was crazy. You could not run them on
batteries for very long. You get like five or six good hours tops. Yeah, tops. Yeah, it's a shame
Tim had to go to jail for a little while. He was always such a fun guy. Yeah, I wonder why.
Well, I asked him, I asked him if it was for stealing mushrooms. He said, "More or less."
You can't get a straight answer from that cat.
It's time for Jog vs. Nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time. Time for Jog vs. Nerd.
We got a scoop coming to us today from the OG Scoop. The categories are brands in song,
Nurb words, noun verb. Oh yeah. Noun verb words, I guess. Homophones five and before and after.
Matt, you're up first. What do you want? Oh boy. I'll take homophones five.
Look at all the pretty flowers all in neat lines.
Wow, he's pretty flat. Oh, rose. Rose and rose. Rose. Yeah, rose, rose. Yep. Rose,
rose, rose. They grows gently. That's me. I'll try Nurb words, noun verb for 200.
A cleaning chore where what you are doing is removing something that is known by the same name.
Oh, to dust, like dusting. Yeah, dust. There you go. Yeah. All right. I got it now.
We're all on board. I'll try. Now we know what these categories are. Brands in song, please.
For 200, what gas company is mentioned in Bruce Springsteen's Jungle Land?
Oh, shit. I'll pass because I don't know. Matt. God, that song is long for me to go through all
the lyrics in my head. Is it Shell or something? It's like a jungle land out here at the Texaco
station. Is it like people's gas like we have out here for our natural gas? Is that what it is?
No. It's the people's gas. It is the people's gas. For time, I'll just pass. Dwayne Johnson came
right to my house and said, if you smell rotten eggs, evacuate your home. I'm passing. Exxon.
They'll meet neat that giant Exxon side that brings this fair city lights. Yep. Yep. There it is.
Matt tried to get your Springsteen song in there. I know he's always looking out for me before and
after. For 200, Daily Double. All of it, Jacob. All of it. NCAA Basketball Tournament with Frankie
Valley. The Final Four Seasons. Of course. Final Four Seasons. Our good buddy Noah was just on that
tour. That's right. Your good buddy. The Final Four Seasons. Take a bet. Let's see. I'll go back to
Brands and Song for 400. What car manufacturer is mentioned in the song American Pie by Don McLean?
Okay, so the Springsteen song was too long for Matt to go through all the lyrics. I'm just going
to go through American Pie real quick. This comes up pretty quick in the chorus.
Excuse me. Oh, Chevy. Yeah. Yeah. I wasn't going to make you go through that whole
fucking thing. Long, long time ago. Time ago? No. Galaxy far away. Naboola's under attack. Galaxy.
Ford. I thought me and Qui-Gon Jinn could finally talk the Federation into maybe cutting them a
little slack. Let's go to Brands and Song again. I like it. For 600. What camera company is mentioned
in Haya by Outkast? Polaroid. Polaroid. Picture. Shake it like a Polaroid Nakia. I still feel like
that song is new-ish to me. Yeah, it's not. I know it's not. And that reference was old when he made
that reference. Yes. Yes. People were like, what? What is he talking about? And we were all like,
Polaroid. Polaroid cameras were already gone by that time. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean, they're out
there still, but yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. But now it's like, really, they're gone, gone. Now they're
just a Lego set. Oh, that reminds me. We talked about doing a Polaroid camera thing for ScoopFest.
I'm just now remembering that. I'm going to order some Polaroid cameras for ScoopFest.
Fuck you guys. I for one vetoed that shit. That's true. Matt, you're up. That's why I'm not going
back to the Orleans next year. I'll do before and after 400, please. The Boss and Blondie combined
these 75 and 78 tunes. Awesome. Blondie. So this is a coming and going thing? Yeah, yeah.
75 and 78. Heart of Glass. Springsteen have something with Rapture at the end of it.
Oh, shoot. I'll pass. That passes to me. I'm passing too, Paul. I feel like this is going
to be very simple once we finally see the answer. I think you have to know the Springsteen song.
Oh no, that's the trick with these questions is you do have to know them.
Yeah, it's the entire trick with the questions. I'll pass. I'll pass. All right.
She's the one way or another. She's the one way or another. That's a good one. Yep. That is a good
one. I'll try. I'll close up Brands and Songs for 800. What technology company is mentioned in Mr.
Roboto by Styx? Accio. Hmm. I don't know. I don't know. I'll pass. Paul. IBM. IBM. Oh,
my heart is human. My blood is boiling. My brain, IBM. My brain, IBM. Yes. Good job. Paul. I ate a
sandwich. I am a robot. I have IBS. Let's go with the NURBOARD's noun verb. Make the connection.
Ollie and cardboard. They're both boxers. Boxing. Okay. Boxing. The box. Yeah, yeah.
Paul, our math. Before and after. 600, please. Daily double. All of it, Jacob. All of it.
Rowling magical novel with a new character, a stunning wrestler. Oh, I mean, Harry Potter.
Who's the stunning? I got it. Who's the stunning wrestler? Would I know the stunning wrestler,
Paul? Yeah. Who does the stunner? That's his move. I don't know. Most of the administration has
suffered at the hands of this wrestler, a stunner. Like a good, like over 50% of the administration.
There was a great picture that came out last week of what's his name. The guy who, one of the guys
who runs WWE now. Triple H. Yeah. Triple H. Yeah. Him and his wife, who's Vince McMahon's daughter.
Yeah. And her mom, Linda McMahon, who's the secretary of whatever it is in the Trump
administration right now. Yeah. Yeah. And the thing went out and was like Stone Cold Steve
Austin has stunned all the people in this picture. Oh, who? Who, Jacob? Stone Cold Steve Austin.
Oh, right. I forgot we were talking about that. For the record, I still don't know the answer to
this question. You got it. It's Harry Potter and I don't know the stone. I don't know the stone.
It's a Daily Double, so I guess I'm going to say. It's a Daily Double, Paul. So I'll also say Harry
Potter and the Stone Cold Steve Austin. Let's try it. Harry Potter and the Sorcerer Stone Cold
Steve Austin. There you go. So close. Wow. In my defense, I got 80% of the words. Yeah.
You stunned 80% of it. You did. I'm kidding. Go ahead and mark me right.
It's me. I'll try noun, noun word or nerve, nerve words, noun verb, securing a box for shipping.
Securing a box for shipping. Closing it. Oh, tape, tape. Yeah. Yeah, there you go. Paul.
I'll do homophones for 400. Upgrading the offering table.
Upgrading the offering table. Let's see. Let's see. Oh, altering the altar.
Alter the altar. Alter the altar. Oh, there you go. Alter, alter. Well done.
Matt, you're up. I will not have gotten that one. I will do before and after 800. A Bond theme song
plays as John McClane kicks ass in this movie. Live and Let Die Hard. There it is. Oh, live and
let die hard, of course. Yippee-ki-yay. I'll close out nerve words for 800. Sometimes on a wall or
used to beautify something hung on the wall. Sometimes on a wall or used to beautify something
hung on the wall. Picture. You could picture a picture. I'll try picture. I'll paint.
You could paint a picture. That was a stretch, I think. Paul.
So was picture in fairness. Homophones for 600. A rough path. A rough path. A rough path.
Trial and trail. Are they spelled the same? No. No. They're not. So it can't be a trial trail.
You did make me spell both of them in my head though to answer that question. Yeah, right. I know.
I had to too. Rough path. I don't know, but there was only one set of footprints. A road road.
A road road. No, I'm sorry. It's a course course. Course, course. A course, course, course, course,
course, course, course. And we got homophones for 800. Matt closing out the category and the game.
I think it's the other daily double, right? No, he already got both of those.
Oh, if I get this, I'm in second place. And if I pass, I'm in second place.
Right. I will take them all, but not that one.
This is homophones? This is homophones, yeah. I will take them all, but not that one.
Oh, I think I've got a guess. I don't know if it's it though. I don't feel super confident.
I will take them all. They're not the best I've ever had. Not even close. Something like the lot.
Not that one. I just don't know. I'm going to pass.
It passes to me. I'm going to, I'm going to try for second place here. I think it's except, except.
Yes. Look at you. I couldn't think of a good way to give a hint on that one. That is the game.
Paul wins with 1600. I'm in second. Thanks to accept, accept with 1200. Matt's in third with
600. That's from the OG scoop. Thank you. Thank you. That was great. I'm only very good at the
before and afters and I didn't get any of them or maybe one of them. Good job, OG. Good job, OG.
If you want to send us a scooperty, head over to HeyScoops.com right there on the home page.
You can send us a scooperty. You can send us a jock versus nerd, an old school jock versus nerd.
You can send us the obelisk style. You can send us, what's the other one? Price is straight. You
can send us a price is straight jock versus nerd, or you can just send us some scoop mail. You can
do all those things right over there at HeyScoops.com. Also, if you try to send us some scoop mail from the
forum there at HeyScoops.com and you have a hard time or you have a hard time with attachments or
anything like that, you can just email your scoop mail directly to us, admin@mattandmattingly.com.
Oh, Brogan has already made a sticker for Paul's computer. It is me telling have ass will eat
Smith. It says remember your password. I can't tell what my hat says. What's my hat say in that
picture, Paul? It says eat ass, suck a dick, and sell drugs. And your mouth has a suspicious stain
around it. Are you eating my wife's chocolate? It's suspicious to you, maybe. Yeah, it's clearly just
chocolate. You ate my wife's chocolate. That's amazing work. It's chocolate mayonnaise. Amazing
work, Brogan. That makes me laugh. I want to thank all the scoops who joined us here on our
Twitch feed here. Hell yeah. Absolutely. And so I want to thank all the scoops who support us over
at our Patreon. We'll get the names up for the next episode. Just know that this podcast will
not be possible without the amazing support that we get from so many of you. You know,
if you're out there and you have a little bit of room in your heart and your wallet for us,
check out all the different tiers that fit your budget over at preachingfun.com.
Hanging with your mother.
Or if you, like and McPheeters, don't get along with all of Paul's dogs,
head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
Your dog just did this or that. Your dog just brought a dead bird in the house.
I get the same thing. Yeah, I know. I know how it goes.
Oh yeah. They're my dogs when they're bad.
Fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com. It does take you over to our Patreon feed where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air. How else can you help keep
this show on the air? We can go to our shop. You can go over to haste scoops.com/shop. There's a
lot of good stuff over there. If that URL is too long for you though, just listen to this.
Store jingle. Store a big store song. We got a store.
Store jingle.com. That's right. One take not only.
There it is. Just go, baby. Just go.
It's hard to believe that. That was embarrassing at the time.
Where's your poetry?
But thanks for this, everybody. Stay safe out there. Thank you,
Pam, for doing this podcast. Thanks, Pam. We'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
[Music]