Oh hello there, I am so happy you're here because this is the part of the show where we thank you, the ice cream truck drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers. We are actually having trouble with Patreon right now to get all of the lists out.
But we will thank all of you Patreons out there, each and every one of you before this month is over.
In the meantime, I want to thank each and every ice cream truck driver out there for delivering that fucking ice cream straight to your fucking ear holes.
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver, help support this show.
Head over to PreachingFun.com. PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver.
And who knows, the life you save may be your own.
It may be.
Or someone might call you on a phone.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
I feel like we've brought this up before, but what are you guys' current stance on Cologne?
I actually have something that happened yesterday.
Okay.
What did you mean the city in Germany?
No.
It's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social.
Sitting over there, it's Matt Mattingly.
Sitting over there, it's Paul Mattingly.
Sitting over here, it's Jacob the audio guy.
We're PreachingFun.
I had a friend's mom buy my kid Cologne for his birthday.
Oh, and your kid is 11?
12.
I mean that's the age.
Cologne age.
That is Draconwar age.
I went through a brute phrase, not Draconwar.
Jacquard Noir was definitely the Cologne of choice when I was in high school.
I grew up thinking that Cologne was an old fashioned notion.
When I hear the word Cologne, I picture--
You don't use Cologne?
I've never used Cologne.
You don't use Ascent?
No.
Neither of you?
I went to Walmart yesterday with my lovely wife.
Your anniversary trip.
Our anniversary trip.
No, we're going and getting our stuff.
Every time I'm in Walmart, I make a point to go over to the perfume aisle and there is generic CK1.
It's called You.
And I always grab a bottle of You because that is the scent I've been using for damn near 30 years.
And I use it every day.
And it's just been my scent of choice.
And it's cheap-ish.
I always like CK1 because I started with CK1 and it's just what I chose and it's been my thing.
But I don't go without-- as soon as I step out the shower, I hit a little something,
spritz a little on the clothes, rub the old hands together, boom, boom, boom, freshen up.
You said hands and you showed wrists.
What is it?
Wrists, wrists, wrists, wrists.
Yeah.
Because putting colognes in your hands is really weird.
That's gross.
Yeah.
No.
Right on my hand.
I like for everything I touch to smell like CK1.
Put it all on my face.
Everything out of the fridge.
Everything just like everything you grab.
What I like is that--
Paul's coffee cup just reeks of Calvin Klein.
No, no, no.
Here's the thing.
You two have spent an inordinate amount of time with me.
And you've never noticed some overpowering odor coming from me.
That's correct.
Don't you tell me what I've noticed.
I don't have the greatest sense of smell.
But that's not to disqualify you not being a stinkeroo.
But on the other-- I mean, not me being a stinkeroo, but not even me-- I'm not sent forward.
Like, you don't go, oh, because there's people that wear cologne.
And you're like, they were here five minutes ago.
Or maybe they're on their fucking way.
Like, you can--
Famously, we called-- you know, Wayne Newton had a crazy--
Oh, lord.
Had a crazy, billowing--
Yes.
A pigpen-style cloud around him.
A pigpen cloud of scent.
Absolutely.
It was like, choo-choo.
The Wayne train came through.
And that's it.
When I hear cologne, I think of old-fashioned parties I was dragged to in Monmouth County,
New Jersey, where all the men put on dinner jackets and had their own stinks on them while
they drank a lot of alcohol.
And I got bored.
Well, that's it.
It's a disguise for stinks.
And I don't have to use much because I don't stink.
And I don't drink.
And I don't smoke.
That's the other thing, too.
If I drank and smoked, I'd need something more powerful than CK-1 because that does not hide
shit.
Right.
But I am curious, I just personally never thought to ever wear it.
My wife never mentioned it.
She doesn't do a lot of perfumes either.
She might do a little bit of something.
She does nice lotions and things like that.
Sure.
And then I use--
Well, your wife has a pleasing natural musk, too.
That's what you always say about your wife.
That's what she says.
That's all people talk about to her.
It's just her musk.
Yeah.
Her pleasing natural musk.
And when I try to talk about her musk, she's like, get in line.
So many people just talking about my musk all day.
It's easier if you send me an email.
Is she selling her urine for Hunter's boots?
Is that what's going on now?
Yes.
Attracting dancers in the wild that they can shoot with a bow and arrow?
No, it's Hunter Biden.
She's putting her piss on Hunter Biden's boots.
Go to huntingbootspiss.vegas, and you'll see my wife's website right there.
[LAUGHTER]
.org.
No, but I'm curious.
What I'm curious about is if--
I'm in my late 40s, right?
So we do late 40s, early 40s, late 30s.
Are more people wearing cologne in general?
Or am I wrong in thinking that it was an old-fashioned notion?
Because to see it come back with younger kids is interesting to me.
But maybe I'm just wrong.
And a lot of people wear cologne.
So I want to know in the chat.
We have enough people here.
I wear cologne.
Paul's a cologne guy.
Jacob, you get spritzed up when you go out, too.
You never think to go cologne.
No, I never do cologne.
I'll do maybe a little aftershave or something.
But even that, I don't want an aftershave that smells.
I don't like having a scent.
In high school, there were times that I had cologne.
I definitely put cologne on in high school and stuff.
I think by the time I was in college, though, I was done with cologne.
So it sounds like there are some-- three guys have chimed in.
They all wear a little cologne.
They're talking about Paul style, a very little amount of cologne.
All right.
A little dab will do you.
Do you do the cloud?
Do you walk through the cloud?
No.
I use it-- honestly, it's kind of like aftershave.
Because I dry shave.
I'm not dry, but I use a little bit of water.
I use a little bit of water.
And all razors now have a little lube strip on them.
So it's not really dry shaving.
Nobody likes a lube strip more than me.
So a little bit of that.
And basically, after the shower, it's almost like aftershave.
Just a little something.
Keeps the bumps chill and whatnot.
And I spray it right on.
I don't do the cloudy walk-through thing, really.
OK.
According to this, Gen Z is big into cologne.
Yeah.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
It's definitely the young people-- it's back in, for sure.
So it skips a generation, perhaps.
That's a wondering.
Or it skips a generation.
Or it skips Gen X.
And also, this is talking about having a fragrance wardrobe,
which is apparently a popular thing,
which is multiple fragrances in your collection.
And you select the fragrance that you feel is most appropriate
for that day.
Well, that feels like something that happened to me.
I never get one of anything.
Oh, you would be a collector.
I definitely feel like it.
My wife was like, maybe you could do a little laughter.
I was like, I have eight beard oils
I don't use in my house at different places.
Go get the purple bottle off of daddy's smell shelf.
You haven't gotten into the beard oil habit yet, Matt?
My wife didn't like it.
I kissed her once with beard oil on, and she was pissed off.
And I was like, all right, well--
Oh, is it too much?
Yeah, it's easier to have beard dandruff
than it is to put accidental beard stink on my wife.
I like doing the beard oil when my beard is a little longer.
I've got my beard trimmed very short right now.
I like it when I've got it a little fluffy.
Then I like the beard oil.
That's part of my daily regimen, too.
Sebastian Menescalco-- am I saying the name right?
Sebastian Menescalco, I think, is a stand-up comedian.
He did a live episode on Amy Poehler's podcast.
It's really great.
I highly recommend.
And he wears two colognes, one on the front
and one on the back.
Sebastian, come on.
He has a different--
Oh, so this is what I want to talk about.
This is coming and going.
I can't imagine-- I mean, that's a lot of work,
to build up a cologne wardrobe.
A fragrance wardrobe.
Because everybody's body chemistry
reacts differently to scents.
So you've got to find the one that hits home.
And for me, one just doesn't rock the boat.
CK1.
Whatever I got going on jibes with CK1.
But there have been times when I've tried a little Burberry
and whatnot, and it's like, the vibe is off, kid.
I think I'm going to start just taking Tiger Snake whiskey
and using it as aftershave and just letting that be my musk.
All you have to do is take one drink of it,
and then it will just ooze out of your pores for a day.
I can't tell you how much that fucking Duke Cannon shit
that I stock on the target shelves every day.
Yeah.
It's all bourbon barrel infused shit.
So you might as well--
It's all bourbon--
This is another cologne?
It's soaps.
It's aftershaves.
It's shampoos.
I was going to say, same with beard oil as well.
Yeah, it's beard oil.
It's all of it.
All of it is oak wood bourbon barrel infused shit.
Yeah.
Everything smells like a basement in Kentucky.
It kind of does.
Yeah.
Well, that's interesting.
So are you encouraged by your son getting into scents now,
or are you worried?
No, I was way too early.
Fucking 12, fuck off.
No, I hated that.
What are you talking about?
No, that's too much.
You hated it because it's your kids growing up.
Exactly.
My son was starting to look so adult.
Yeah.
And then he had to get braces.
And I literally picked him up from the orthodontist.
And I was like, oh, thank God.
Oh, he looks like a kid.
Oh, thank goodness.
Yes.
He was literally just starting to just look like just a man.
Yeah.
And it was really, really taking me.
That'll happen.
I know.
He sold me insurance the other day.
Well, he's been doing that since eight.
[LAUGHTER]
I guess first, he convinced me that my current insurance
was not good enough.
I was just saying.
He's a good neighbor.
Healer is there.
He is unlicensed.
And that is not FDIC insured, just so you know.
[LAUGHTER]
Like the FDIC is going to be existing in two minutes.
I feel like your son will pay out, though.
If I get into a major automobile accident,
I feel like your son's going to take care of me.
[LAUGHTER]
That's true.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
I think that's going to be fine.
Aguirre Scoop has said braces, the puberty and virginity
extender.
Yes.
[LAUGHTER]
That certainly helped in my situation.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
It does not seem to be a deterrent socially at all.
Not anymore?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
No.
That's great.
I mean, everybody-- like, all kids now have braces, right?
Yeah.
At some point.
They do.
Most kids do.
And I--
I feel like it's a much more common thing now.
It wasn't completely outrageous for me.
A lot of people still had braces.
No.
But they do them younger.
Yes.
Ah.
That's for sure.
Yes.
It's very rare that a kid in high school has braces now.
They do them all in the middle school years.
Yeah.
They do that because younger gums, it works faster.
Teeth move around.
Yeah.
Oh, Aguirre Scoop is saying, are braces smaller than they used to be?
Maybe.
Aguirre Scoop in the chat is saying that braces are super tiny and minor now.
Or that they're asking.
I think the--
They're super tiny and minor now.
They're able to stick to the teeth.
Yeah.
They seem smaller to me.
Mine's just shining.
Mine's just got a big gold grill.
It's just a big-- it just holds so the teeth are just moving around.
Oh, god.
Have you seen those people that wear their grills too long and it fucks up their teeth
forever?
Oh, my god.
It's the nastiest thing.
They just keep--
Well, it's just--
They keep them in for, like, months.
And it's like, what are you doing?
Well, because it's a visible version of Invisalign.
Oh, no.
But it's not even-- no.
Not Invisal-- it's like just-- they're not medically sound.
No, I'm saying, like, the grill-- no, that's what I'm saying is.
The grill is acting like just a visible Invisalign.
But it's just not even helping anything.
It's just correcting--
Right.
That's jacking them up.
Oh, it's so gross.
It's just doing what braces do, but in the wrong direction.
Oh.
[INAUDIBLE]
Oh, Matt, Galactic President Scooperstar McScoopsalot has a great question in the chat.
Did the boys convince you or did the HOA convince you to do anything about the giant skeleton
in your front yard?
The giant skeleton is still up in my front yard.
That's a win.
We keep joking that we're going to put a Santa Claus hat on it.
I have a feeling the HOA will not approve of that.
Most of the problems--
But you can't ask permission.
You can't ask permission.
Oh, no, no.
We're not going to ask permission.
But I just-- I think we just still get fined is what I mean.
The skeleton's head is bigger than mine.
So I have some big Santa Claus hats, but not big enough for the skeleton.
So I got to go out.
I'm sure it's just a quick search on the internet will get me a giant Santa hat for the head.
But plus, I think it put a little sac on his back there.
But the problem is simply that it's a two-person operation.
And my wife-- first I was away, and then my wife's so busy that we literally just huddled
up right now for just to finally have an hour to play out the next two weeks.
I have no idea when we're going to have time to take that thing down.
Right.
Oh, good news.
Home Depot sells a Santa hat to go with that skeleton.
Yeah, there's no doubt.
There's no doubt about it.
What about putting him in the pool?
I did a Google search for giant skeleton hat, and that popped right up.
Could he just live in the pool?
Yes.
Put him in the shallow end of the pool, so he's just out of it.
That'd be funny.
Yeah.
That's pretty great.
Those bones will probably dissolve, and the chlorine in your pool will become toxic.
I don't know.
That's probably not good.
That's probably not good for the--
Or it'll activate the spell that lies within the skeleton, and he will simply grow and
animate it.
One way or another, something's going down.
Yeah.
It's not going to be--
One way or another.
It's not going to be safe.
Oh my god.
No.
It's going to be unfortunate.
Well, I got through yet another round of eyeball testing on Monday, and it was kind of crazy.
Went in.
Yep.
Eyeball.
And yeah, I'm certified eyeball, and we've done every test that we can except for the
dye test.
So he was like, "You want to just do the dye test and get it done?"
And I'm like, "Great."
So they could detect any possible swelling or whatever.
I'm like, "Sure."
Yeah.
So they had to put dye in me, and then quickly get a bunch of pictures of my eyes, and then
we looked, and, "Oh, there's no swelling.
Okay."
So everything's written off except I have crummy veins, and there's really nothing we
can do about that until things go catastrophically wrong.
So I'm going back in in seven weeks to see if things are better or worse.
The yellow dye.
Yes, it was very yellow.
So as they're doing it and everything, they're like, "So you're going to notice discoloration
in your urine and stool.
That's going to last a day or two."
I'm like, "Okay, cool."
But then I'm getting ready to go back to my car, and I'm like, "Well, I better hit the
head before I go."
And I swear to God, it was the secret of the ooze.
I fucking was so ... It was fluorescent.
Fluorescent?
I mean, that's what it's supposed to be.
It was fluorescent.
I was like ...
It's still upsetting.
Kecto Cooler is shooting out your urethra.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's used to that.
I'm afraid of no ghosts.
It was ... Well, okay.
God, should I share this?
This is too much.
Wait a minute.
What's happening?
Hold on.
The things that you've shared without this question has been paramount to this podcast.
I can't believe ... Whatever you're about to say seems ...
This is terrifying.
I'm going to share it.
I'm going to fucking share it.
I don't care.
I'm going to share it.
I almost don't want him to do it now.
I'm too scared.
I had been peeing for a day, basically, and it was still pretty bright.
And I was like, "Well, this is throughout.
This is corrupting everything."
So in the interest of science, I had to bust one out and see what was going on.
And I'm here to tell you that it permeated everything.
So I literally fired off some straight-up ectoplasm radio.
My no-nut November was done a while back.
But I also thought, not only in the interest of science, but also I thought, probably good
to get this out of every part of my system that it could be lingering in.
Yeah.
Time to flush.
Right.
Yeah.
Just general maintenance was what was going on.
That's it.
I'll tell you who else only does that in the interest of general maintenance.
But here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
As I'm doing this, as I'm thinking about it, how many times have… because guys are
the worst.
How many times have guys had a die situation and then had a romantic interlude not long
after?
And what does that do to the possible children conceived, let alone the kind of intimate
moment you're having?
Oh, I didn't realize that's where you were going with this.
I thought you were concerned about the fluorescent pearl necklace that I was giving out to all
the peoples after getting my eye digest.
I thought you were worried about your gym socks glowing in the dark when you tried to
go to sleep or something.
Here's the thing.
Yes.
So this is the other thing too is like, is this dangerous?
And if it's not that dangerous, then I think we've found a weird porn subculture thing
here maybe.
You found a kink.
Yeah, right.
People who fire off multicolor shots.
Upside down Spider-Man.
I'll tell you who else has fluorescent semen.
I want to tease go through this commercial break.
After this commercial break, I have a bunch of new tour dates coming up in 2026 for the
Jokers of Magic.
It's all officially on the Jokers of Magic website and I want to talk about all the cities
I'm going to when we come up after the break.
Every single city on the Jokers of Magic tour will be jizzed on in fluorescent semen.
That's the Jokers of Magic guarantee.
That's right.
Guarantee.
Also, here's a sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by, oh, Matt Donnelly.
There we go.
From Kevin Chamberlain in 2022.
It's brought to you by me.
So yeah, I'm going to be going on the road.
Go to jokersofmagic.com.
Okay.
Next commercial.
Today's show is also brought to you by Leftover Lobster.
That's right.
From LAJ in 2022.
This product is Leftover Lobster.
You see, Ariel, sometimes people can't finish their entire meal and they need to take a
basket home.
Don't forget to have an extra cheddar biscuit.
Why not?
Ah, under the tin foil, under the tin foil.
I will be waiting down on the shelf under the tin foil.
You'll put me deep back in the fridge and you'll forget I ever lived.
I was alive once.
Now I am frozen under the tin foil.
You leave me there for a week and then I start to reek.
You remember only far too late that it was something you were going to eat under the
tin foil.
Under the tin foil.
I am a stinky mess.
The germs have coalesced and it's mold all over me.
You spent 25 dollars on the plate.
You weren't going to let that go to waste, but you should have left me because now I'm
just scrudsy.
Look, I'm covered in mold here.
You don't want this, dear.
Leave me, I'm rotten.
All kinds of nasty under the tin foil.
And eight scoops of checkout.
Yes.
Oh my God.
We found a, at work the other day, we found just somebody's coffee cup that they had put
somewhere and then it apparently had gotten hidden.
Like other people got put in, other things got put in front of this coffee cup and the
coffee cup got hidden and then, uh, long story short, several months later, a coffee cup
was found.
Oh, what?
It was like a fancy cup, no, like a paper coffee cup.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Good.
An at work, an at work coffee cup, just right into the garbage.
But it was, it was disgusting.
Sure.
Yeah.
Life.
Disgusting, Matt.
Speaking of disgusting.
Life finds a way, um, I'm going to be in, uh, Chicago is actually a preview jokers of
magic.
It's Chicago magic lounge is going to be Mike Mills and I, so it's two of the jokers of
magic or we're playing together in December 18th, 19th, 20th and 21st, uh, that's Thursday,
Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
Oh, happy birthday.
How about a show in Chicago just for you?
Thank you.
I won't be there.
I think we'll be doing six or seven shows.
So check out, check out Chicago magic lounge, uh, for, for that.
Uh, but yeah, no 2026 starting January 23rd, Lexington, Kentucky, baby, uh, unless it's
an opera house.
I'm so excited.
Um, and then we're going to Cincinnati, Ohio, January 24th and January 25th, we're going
to Bloomington, Indiana, January 28th, Green Bay, Wisconsin, January 29th, Madison, Wisconsin,
January 31st, Wabash, Indiana, January 31st, still Wabash, Indiana.
Then, uh, in March, March 19th, we're putting Saratoga Springs, March 20th, Newark, New
Jersey, baby and JPEG.
Yeah.
And then, uh, fishing up in Eastern Pennsylvania, March 21st.
So yeah, go to jokers of magic, get some tickets there, come out and see the show, get your
purple chips.
I'm so excited to be doing this show.
Yeah.
This is great.
We saw this on a Dittleman's, uh, Instagram last night.
Yeah.
I believe I'm doing all of them with Dittleman and then, and then there's going to be a rotation
and Mike Mills will be doing all of them.
And then we'll be rotating between Derek Hughes, who I'm so excited to be doing a show with
Derek is Matt King's number one filling guy had an awesome run on America's Got Talent.
If you're watching our stuff, he, he's just killer everywhere.
And uh, we're also going to Nick, the fats coming back for one of the legs of the tour.
So Ruben Morland, who a lot of people don't know he's, he's actually been killing it in
a fringe festivals.
One of the nicest guys, uh, uh, it's the big goofy redhead.
I love Ruben.
I've hung out with him a bunch of times.
I'm so excited to be sharing my first shows with him.
He's so he's super funny.
So yeah, very, very excited.
Each shows a four magician lineup, uh, of comedy magicians and it's going to be super
fun.
That sounds wonderful.
Yeah.
The magicians, I watched the most recent fool us, uh, the other day and, uh, that cat with
the, with the fucking card trick, who, uh, who was it, uh, close talk to him like the
day before or something like that to get him on Paco, a groudo, a guard.
Yes.
Uh, I wasn't even going to try to remember his name.
He was amazing.
So I was going to, this is a abracadabra spoiler, so I, but I guess, you know, we're here, uh,
that is the reason why you don't see me on this season of I was in the chamber as an
emergency guy.
We had lost a couple of people to different, for different reasons.
And uh, I was being, uh, primed up to do some kind of version of my card stab or ring trick
routine for fool us.
And then all of a sudden it was like, no, nevermind.
We got this guy and of course I was like, you know, and uh, and then he came out and
he was, he just killed, he just killed.
So yeah, he was there just as a friend, uh, helping out, uh, John Carlos Scalia, uh, who's
who aired an earlier episode this season and they was to have done a two person show with
each other in Spain.
And so it was another thing.
It's like the same way they got, uh, uh, Danny D or T's on.
They simply said like, you're here.
Like you're right here.
What are you?
Why are we not doing something here?
And so he showed them a couple of stuff and yeah, he went on there and fooled the shit
out of them.
So yeah.
Uh, and so did John Carlo.
So, and I've worked with John Carlo a bunch on the princess cruise ships.
He's the nicest guy.
And uh, as someone said on, uh, abracadabra, maybe the only person who can just totally
successfully use charm as misdirection, just, just totally can just be so charmingly goofy
and whatever that you just, you just take your eyes off of everything he's doing with
his hands.
Uh, it's, it's really, they're, they're both just killer killer guys.
Yeah.
They're great.
He was amazing.
I've seen a fool us this season, man, they, it is, it is a good season to fool us.
It is.
We don't know what the future holds, uh, couple, you know, we, they took the season and split
it in half, right?
So the air 10 episodes and they gave like a big four month gap and then now they're
airing the other 10 episodes.
Um, the reruns get the same exact ratings as the new episodes, which is usually a bad
sign for TV things.
Uh, we've done over 140 episodes, so there's certainly enough to syndicate till the end
of time.
And that includes getting rid of three seasons of, uh, the COVID seasons, which they don't
seem to re-air as much, uh, without the studio audience.
Uh, but I think those episodes are now covered with the last two seasons.
And so I don't know.
And also what is CW in this modern media landscape, uh, it's, it's a really weird, uh, is not
been gobbled up by any of the major streamers.
It's still its own app.
Uh, it's still a network television show, which is still airs on rabbit ears.
Um, and so I don't, I don't, we don't, we don't know.
So we, so it's all, it's all up in the air.
I just don't, I don't know what anything in TV means anymore.
I know that point now where like all of our experience in television entertainment doesn't
mean anything at all.
The models certainly aren't there anymore that we came up with.
It's so strange.
It really is a very strange time, uh, specifically for television and, and yeah, it is, it is
weird.
And so, yeah, I, you know, uh, would Penn and Teller wants to do another season would,
would they want to maybe try a new show somewhere else?
I don't know.
You know, that kind of stuff.
So I mean, we did, uh, 11 seasons and secretly like 13 and a half seasons if you do it by
a regular episode count.
And so that's the whole lot of TV and the whole lot of cool stuff.
So I, I, I don't know.
And how it's that many seasons over how many years now?
Gosh.
Uh, I mean, it's over a decade.
Yes.
It's definitely over a decade.
Yep.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think when I started.
Well, yeah.
So my kid was born.
Uh, yeah, it's been a decade.
It's been a decade.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah.
So my kid was born.
My second kid was born during the first season.
So, oh yeah.
They're a supernova girl.
Season one was 2011.
Yeah.
So I mean, it's, that's, that's a run.
He's coming over.
We'll talk about the original season of air in England too.
So season two is where I kind of start the American, uh, season.
Oh, right.
Sure.
It's been 10 years since it was refired up in season two and it goes on.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Are they thinking about a new show, Matt?
They're always are.
They always are.
Um, yeah, the new show that they're talking about doing, it's not going to be as difficult
to get a trophy.
It's just a full Matt Donnelly.
Yeah, it's just, it's just going to be like, if you don't get one, it's going to be like,
what's wrong with you.
It's just embarrassing.
Cut piff's hand.
Injure piff.
Yeah.
No, it's strange.
It's strange to be busy enough that I don't need it.
You know, I think, I think that was always like the weird thing of like, anytime full
scale, I was like, oh good.
That was always a nice, nice thing.
And I think also like, I've really gotten like, like I heard, I heard me something about
another magician.
They're going to put, they're putting together a TV special for a magic thing and I'm not
necessarily on this magician's radar, but like people around him are.
And I am actually like, I think because we're going to show, like I have, I understand magic
for TV versus magic for magic sake pretty well.
And it's like, and I was like, I should be at least get a phone call from one of these
people.
It's like, and so I am a little bit like, oh wait, if this shows over, I need to figure
out how to put myself out there more as a possible, like, you know, lower level producer.
Yeah.
Cause of like, I really do.
I did learn so much from that show and I think it could help a lot for something like that.
But yeah.
Yeah.
We'll see.
I bet you could buy the CW.
That's probably, that's probably true.
It's on the block.
Yeah, uh, my, uh, improv classes are going great.
I just got done with my first, uh, level one four week, uh, class and I had a couple of
students who were so jazzed that they wanted me to keep teaching and go on to level two.
And I was like, well, I don't have a level two class scheduled right now, maybe next
year.
And they were like, Nope, let's get this going.
And so they contacted, uh, uh, and, and made a, made a thing and, and, and got, uh, got
things moving forward and holy shit.
Uh, Justin was up for it and they've got five students registered so far out of my class
and they're going to get a couple more hopefully and by the, this next month I'll be teaching
two classes a week.
So yeah.
Whoa.
Yeah.
I'll be doing a level one.
I'm still doing my level one again and a level two.
So it's great.
So we are doing what I was hoping to do, which is build out, uh, improv community in Pittsburgh.
It's going to take some time, but it's going to happen.
Uh, I believe we'll see.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
So that's going really well.
Uh, thank you, bossy.
Uh, yeah, it's, uh, it's just, you know, it's what I've been hoping for and I'm, uh, still
teaching the occasional free class over there at the pod duty network.
So that's going to happen.
Uh, so I'm going to do, do that next Tuesday, then the Tuesday after that provided everything's
lined up, we'll be rocking and rolling with, uh, Tuesday classes too.
So very encouraged with that, uh, making some more, uh, yeah, making some more headway with
getting, getting further away from, uh, retail gigs and more and more into, uh, this kind
of thing.
Although today, today we went and bought some stuff for Ann's garden.
And in the, uh, complex where we went, no, we didn't, I know the complex where we went.
What do you know?
There's a brand new bricks and mini figs store opening up and I'm like, Oh shit.
So for those of you who aren't familiar, this is a chain, a franchise that actually deals
in used Legos and repurposed like, so, uh, huh.
So I think they're not going to open till summer next year.
It says, or, or spring at least.
So I'm going to work there.
I'm going to try.
I think I might as well, right?
If the, if the compensation is comparable, what the fuck?
I mean, I could spend all day fucking around with Legos and hosting kids Lego parties rather
than shoveling coal.
And this is going to be like Ellsroth at the weed place, you're just going to rise up there
without trying.
And you're just going to become a kingpin.
Yeah.
Oh man.
Did you hear about the weed stuff though?
That's, that was my first thought was Ellsroth today.
What happened?
Uh, no, they have, uh, our Congress has decided to outlaw weed again.
Nationally.
What?
Yes.
Couldn't possibly be a distraction from other things, but, uh, yeah, that's what they put
in that, uh, fucking, uh, open the government backup bill that, uh, weed's going to be illegal
nationally in 26 again.
I know.
Right?
Yeah.
Why?
Indeed.
It's almost as though they're trying to sabotage the country.
It's almost as though they're trying to just bring us to the brink of no, I mean, I mean,
like, okay, sure, because I can't, I've, uh, uh, it's, it's a weird time and Paul's more
right than wrong about this crazy shit, but, um, uh, like, like, okay, why isn't the government
bill is what I mean.
So in other words, why was it allowed to be part of the opening up of the government again?
Like is it helping prisons?
Is it helping?
Yes.
Do you know what I mean?
That's exactly it.
It's helping private prisons, getting private, getting more people back because private prisons
are complaining that they're not getting enough people.
So they need something else criminalized again and the liquor industry wants their, uh, liquor
money back from the people who are, have found out that weed doesn't make you want to kill
your family as much as alcohol does.
Uh, I feel like I still want to kill my family as much.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
But you're like, oh, the knife's all the way over there and my family's all the way over
there.
I'll do it tomorrow.
Are either of them next to chips?
Possibly.
Oh my God, Mike Nelson or my family is totally calling me out.
Uh, said I can't work at the bricks and mini figs place cause I kept saying Legos when
it's just Lego.
Oh, it is true.
They are.
They are pedantic about that, although bricks and mini figs.
So I don't have to say fucking Lego at all.
I just bring your bricks and mini figs about that figs is a weird, I've never heard that
term.
Yeah.
Bricks and mini figs is a, uh, like I said, it's a, it's a franchise.
So yeah, that's what they call the mini figs.
Um, any Lego figures, mini figures, figs is for figures.
Yeah.
Mini figs.
When you said bricks and mini figs at first, I was pursuing some like tawny, like upper
middle-class place for like bricks, like brick, brick, like masonry and trees and like beautiful
things like that.
Nope.
I'm talking about tiny little Lego men.
That's all it is.
Teensy little Lego men.
I'm looking at this stuff here.
I don't know if this is about weed as much as it's about hemp.
Well, it's saying THC products.
So it's no products that contain a certain amount of THC, uh, or, uh, or what's the other
active thing that's going on to the, the, any of it.
But anyway, last night, the Senate passed a continuous CBD, CBD.
That's it.
Oh, there you go.
Along with three appropriation bills, one of which an agricultural appropriation bill
effectively shut down the U S hemp industry.
Well, that's one way to put it, uh, growers use the plant cannabis sativa to produce both
hemp and marijuana, blah, blah, blah.
I don't know.
This is weird.
It's fucking weird.
Like I'm looking through it now.
I can't really read through the whole thing on the air right now, but like I'm looking
through it right now.
I guess I could, that's true.
I guess I got him, Paul, fucking shut up and read Jacob.
When you're right, you're right.
We are nothing.
If not a marijuana forward podcast forward, this is the thing.
Like I, I am the least smoky of all of us.
As in I have never, I have never imbibed and even a gummy, uh, you know, I'm just not a
drug dude, but I, I am very much an advocate of, of all of it because, you know, I've seen
the good effects it can have on people and it can make people feel good and mitigate
pain.
I, first of all, once lived in the Virgin islands, so we don't need to go over my partaking
of weed, but, um, what in the Virgin islands, you know, you don't, you don't live in a tree
house in the Caribbean and not smoke weed.
How much of your, how much of the residents you lived in was constructed of hemp?
How much of the building itself was just weed?
Just weed.
Yeah.
You just lived in weed.
Yes.
Uh, it, it like literally like in the movie, like washed up, we, one time had a giant
garbage bag of a wash up on shore.
Uh, it was that stereotypical, was it just like Christmas?
We may, Oh, that ended up leading cause it wasn't good weeds.
I ended up leading to my friend, Colin making what I called, uh, instead of weed cookies,
he made a weed briquettes is what I call them.
It came out green.
It was like, it was like your, it was like your gym sock, Paul, it was neon green, uh,
and they were so strong.
People accused him of lacing them with other illicit substances, which is hilarious because
he was Rosifarian and like really just believed in like just skunk weed.
And he's like, no, no.
But it is such a density cooked into the cookie as like sugar.
Yeah.
Uh, we were, it was more weed than sugar.
You're just feeling the power of jaw.
It was weeks of the craziest behavior.
It was just a really endemic, uh, uh, company.
But I bet nobody, nobody got hurt.
Nobody got enough brawl.
People got paranoid and stuck on, on, on like a little Island key, like a snorkeling Island,
like, uh, for like hours cause they were afraid to go back in the water, uh, they were worried
about their ability to swim to shore.
So there was an incident, there was an incident of survival.
Nobody was hurt.
It's, it's, you know, and like you said, I hate that I'm the diet of exposure on that
Island injured before dying.
I hate that I'm more right than wrong on this stuff, but I think, you know, weed is such
as such a good calming effect on a lot of people and just chills folks out and alcohol
just get some amped and people are going to turn to whatever substance they need to get
through the day.
I actually thought, like I thought, I thought, uh, legalizing weed in Nevada wouldn't be
that big of a deal.
Wouldn't change things.
And it was I wrong.
Like it changed things significantly.
You can't walk down the street without smelling it.
Exactly.
I don't enjoy the effect that weed has had on Vegas, but my answer to that is not jail.
My answer to that is not let's get involved, but also the capital punishment.
That's the fact that you can't walk down a Las Vegas street without smelling weed tells
you if you're not brain dead that, Oh, they are selling tons of this shit.
This is an industry, the stereotype of old cab drivers is they would take you to whatever
club, but they would, you know, not the one you asked for, but the one that paid the cabbies
the most, right, and that has now changed to weed dispensary.
Yeah.
Well, remember how we were talking even before, like we, there's before I moved, there was
still a real possibility that we could have been really fun dispensary, uh, entertainment.
Right.
Yeah.
There's going to be the easiest job in the world.
Exactly.
Motherfuckers will laugh to anything.
Oh, a couple of places here have tried the, uh, the cannabis lounges and nobody has figured
it out yet.
Yeah.
How to do the lounge.
What's the problem?
Just like hanging around and getting high somewhere else.
Isn't that appealing to people?
It's not, it's not, it's not working with standup lineups.
That's for sure.
Well, I suppose if, if one of the major side effects is paranoia, you don't want to be
in a strange place.
Well, this is it.
I have all these different strands now that one can, you know, the, the, the, the, this
is not going to get you paranoid, man.
This is just going to give you a real mellow trip.
Yeah.
And it tastes like ice cream.
So let's go.
I just saw a video of some cannabis celebration and somebody had rigged up an apparatus where
they had a giant stack of weed inside what amounted to a stove pipe.
And that stove pipe was directly built on top of, and Jerry rigged to, and taped up
to a leaf blower.
And so somebody lit all the weed with a blow torch in the top of the stove pipe.
They turned on the leaf blower and it just for like two minutes straight, just billowed
weed smoke.
Just look, it just looked like a haunted house.
It's just in the business we call that the dandy isn't that dandy.
It's the dandy.
Yeah.
It was crazy.
It was wild to see and just people just getting face full of weed smoke from a blower or from
a leaf blower.
The whole room was just coated.
Yeah.
So, but yeah, that really, that really bummed me out this morning.
And my first thought was Ellsroth cause he has found something he's exceptionally good
at.
He's enjoying the shit out of it.
He's trying to entrepreneurialize with it all.
He's trying.
He's become a true character, man.
Right.
And this is the thing.
This is exactly why I'm like, that's America.
That's fucking capitalism.
True.
That's, that's get it done.
And they're just putting a kibosh on it.
I guess we should.
What the fuck?
I'd be curious.
He's probably working, which is why he's not here, but I'd be curious what Ellsroth's
saying and what they're saying at his work.
I'd be curious about that.
Well, we've got a day here.
Maybe we can try and get him on tomorrow cause we're doing it again tomorrow.
Yeah.
Maybe we could get him into chiming.
Cause yeah, I would love to hear the initial cause and I'll give it a day to Stu cause
it just hit today.
So yeah, let's, let's hear it.
Let's hear it.
Speaking of hitting today.
So the, the new federal funding legislation moving through Congress is expected to impact
the sale, the sale of hemp driven THC products, but not state regulated sales of recreational
metal medical marijuana.
Okay.
Medical.
Yes.
It's CBD.
It looks like though, from this, from this other article that I'm looking at over here
from the cannabis business times.com, which sounds, they sound very CBT.
Let's not.
Let's not get confused.
Can a business is right there in a business.
Can a business times.
It should be Canada's times.
And it's definitely looking at it again, I was wrong though.
It's cannabis business times.
It's right there.
You gotta go.
I gotta make some calls.
Yeah.
Can a business letter, no, I only take my news from the times of cannabis, the times
of cannabis business weekly times of cannabis business weekly is out of the, that's out
of the realm.
You know, that's the cannabis.
I'm pretty leftist.
So I do this, the Sativa Tribune.
So I do this.
Sativa Tribune, you would you Pinko, how about, what about high times?
Oh, high times that old rag.
I'm all about cannabis business right now, people's front people's front, the people's
front.
Judea.
That's exactly what I was going for.
Jacob.
I knew you'd catch it.
Uh, yeah, this looks like it might be, uh, according to the, the, what should be the
cannabis in this times, uh, the bill if enacted would prevent the unregulated sale of intoxicating
hemp based or hemp derived products, including Delta eight from being sold online in gas
stations and corner stores while preserving non intoxicating CBT and industrial hemp products,
according to the summary.
Meanwhile, meanwhile, Kratom runs rampant.
Right.
Oh, it's stupid that they're involving themselves in it at all.
Absolutely.
That's the thing.
Is it just stupid?
Right.
We've gotten this point.
We've had nothing but wild success.
Let's fuck everything.
Yeah.
Let's, let's mess with it.
It doesn't make it.
I'll tell you who else wants to mess with stuff just for the sake of messing with it.
And that's the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by, where'd you go?
Where did you go?
I brought the jokers of magic and now we're screwed.
Did you go, um, I'm doing a commercial, um, today's show.
And the makers of permanently wet socks, permanently crunchy socks.
That's right.
Scuba Troopa in 2025, permanently crunchy socks.
Hey everybody.
It's me, Apple Jack from Apple Jacks, the mascot that never existed.
Hi, are you interested in shit in your socks?
You should try the Apple Jacks.
Apple Jacks is combining with Doritos to create a brand new sock full of Apple Jacks and Doritos.
That's right.
It's going to be crunchy, sticky, cheesy, and sharp.
Just like you like it.
It's the walking sensation that's sweeping the nation.
Crunchy cheesy, sticky sharp.
That's our guarantee.
C-H-I-T.
You can walk all over it.
Crunchy cheesy, not it, crunchy cheesy is two C's, crunchy is an S and a T. C-C-S-T.
Kissed.
You'll be kissed.
Your feet will be kissed with the delicious taste of Doritos, Apple Jacks, and the mixture
of the two with your sweat.
Nothing like foot sweat to get a Dorito to that perfect flavor taste place and combine
it with the sweet, sweet stickiness of Apple Jack cereal, which also have a certain crunch.
You can't beat it.
So go out and get yourself some Doritos and Apple Jacks filled socks from me, Apple Jack,
the mascot that never was.
Enter Hayscoops at checkout.
That's a cologne that I would wear.
Apple Jacks?
Apple Jacks and feet.
God damn it.
I mean, you wear any sweet enough cologne near your socks long enough and you've got
it.
Yeah.
By the way, Matt, it looks like Nextar Media Group already owns the CW.
Oh, okay.
We already owned, they, they own the biggest chunk of it.
And then like Paramount and a couple of other groups like that own like 12% stakes here
and there.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think I understood that they are.
Yeah.
I mean, I knew they had some organization behind them and Nextar I didn't know was Nextar,
but yeah, they're, they're already the big dog.
But doesn't, but it's weird that they're, they're still an independent streamer.
Independent.
Yeah.
They're still an independent streamers.
It's really important.
I'm pointing out.
Right.
I'm just, I'm confused now, now that I know that why they're still an independent streamer.
Yeah.
It seems like they would already have been looped into other things that their owners
own.
Right.
And they're not.
That's weird.
And they're not, which like the fact that they're not already part of the Paramount Plus or
Peacock or something like that makes it kind of weird.
Yeah.
And they.
All right.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Let's do a little Scoop Mail.
Let's do it.
Message for you, sir.
We got one here from Mrs. Cincy Scoop.
Dear Neapolitan, since this podcast is one of the reasons why I met the love of my life,
I wanted to share more happy news about our little family.
You're welcome.
And this is Manu.
Hi, Manu.
Manu, Mrs. Cincy Scoop.
A couple of weeks ago at the end of October, Mr. Cincy Scoop and I welcomed our Dippin'
Dot, a healthy little boy who was at 99, who was at the 99 percentile of size during most
of the pregnancy.
Oh, Jesus.
Which turns out to be great because he arrived three weeks early.
We were both fine and healthy after the birth.
I had my first hospital stay and do not recommend for anyone who needs to rest.
Baby is growing, getting nice and fat.
He likes to sleep so much that we need to pester him every few hours to feed him.
Then he feeds for about an hour straight until he falls asleep and the cycle repeats.
That's a baby after my own heart.
That's what I do on my days off right there.
That's exactly.
That is my life.
Zonk.
Most days are good, but the little one is getting the hang of being a human.
So other days are a little more challenging.
Overall, we are very happy.
The experience as a first time parent is interesting to say the least.
Honestly, the broken sleep is not the worst part for me.
Dealing with other people's bullshit comments and opinions are the real test on my nerves.
Since your advice is always impeccable, I come to you for solutions on how to deal with
the worst offenders.
I love these questions.
Oh boy.
Starting strong with questions about the baby's circumcision status.
I don't think it's appropriate to talk about my baby's genitalia at all, but I guess I'm
the weird one.
What do I even say to that?
Then how do I shut down the comments about the next baby?
There will be no next baby and it genuinely made me sad hearing those remarks only one
week postpartum.
That's insane.
People are asking you about the next baby while you're still healing from getting the first
one out of you.
Well, for the first question, you can tell them straight up and say, "No, Microsoft got
rid of Clippy."
So that's just done.
They phased Clippy right out.
Yeah.
Clippy is gone.
That's just not an option anymore.
Yeah.
I would say talk about their genitalia.
I was just going to say the short, quick answer is, "Why are you thinking about getting one?"
The bold one is to say, "Are you asking me about my child's penis?
Is that what we want to talk about right now?"
Right.
How about we just talk about other aspects of their genitalia instead of the tip of their
penis?
Let's talk about the shaft.
Oh, it doesn't have to be your child.
Turns out, you can just take any kid to the boil and they'll just nip the tip.
I remember one time having a guy, whatever, being like, "No, don't circumcise."
I didn't get circumcised.
I ended up having to get circumcised at 12 because of an issue or whatever.
I regret, "I wish we didn't get it done," or something like that.
I turned to the person.
I said, "You didn't stop fucking, did you?"
Then he laughed and I was like, "It just seems to me like ... " People try to compare it
to the oppressive circumcision of women that happens in different countries that's barbaric.
Right.
It's a little chore.
It's a lot different, actually.
It's a lot different than that.
It's a lot different.
For the most part, it is a sanitary thing but also, it's nobody's fucking business.
Yeah.
Mind your business.
This exactly goes right to this marijuana stuff.
Mind your business and let business mind its business.
It's outrageous.
The stuff, the talking out of both sides of their fucking heads with this, "We want business
to rock and roll and we're going to fuck with business," constant.
So stupid.
I mean, a nice response to it is, as much as I would love to talk about my baby's dick
with you, why don't we talk about anything else?
I've ... To say this, this is a life lesson from improv that I moved to real life, which
is don't get stuck having conversations you don't want to have.
Right?
If you're on stage in a scene and you and your scene partner don't feel like you're
enjoying the scene, either one of you, do anything to change the subject until you are
talking about something you want to talk about and the audience will be relieved, right?
And so, if you simply go like, "Oh, I don't want to get into this at all," if you just
say that and then just beat, silence, that person will not pester you about it.
They will change the subject.
Or if they do, get them out of there.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But simply saying like, "Oh, I don't want to get into this with you at all.
Not right now.
I don't feel like talking about it."
You know, anything along those lines, just shut the person up.
You know?
But you owe it to yourself to like, do not have conversations you don't want to have.
If you don't want to talk about your child's genitalia to somebody, you do not talk about
it.
And if you're confident and calm and almost quiet about it, that person will just freeze
up and one of you will move on.
Right.
Yeah.
Like, somebody will continue the conversation or the conversation will end and either way,
I feel like that's fine.
So also the people asking about the next baby, a week after this baby, they're asking about
the next baby.
I don't know.
You're going to pay for it?
If I have another baby, you're going to pay the bills for that baby?
I don't know.
I'm reading in chat.
Why are you worried about my kids?
I'm reading in chat saying, "My brother's wedding was just two weeks after I had my son and
everyone had a comment about not circumcising him.
And my aunt kept saying, "Well, my husband was, so I'm not going to talk about my kids
or husband's penis."
Yeah.
Like, it's really like they'll never be able to follow up on their hypothesis.
Right?
Right.
They have no medical background idea for this.
Whatever they're bringing up, they have no factual basis for it at all.
You know what could be really funny?
Tell them you're having it added on too.
I'm extending.
Yeah.
Tell them you're adding four inches.
My baby is going to have a five skin.
Exactly.
We're doing like a chip clip with like fishing weights on it and we're just going to stretch
this thing out.
It's going to be like the bungs of the rungs of the Notre Dame bell up there.
It's going to be like, "Bing-a-lay-lay-lay-lay-lay."
They're not going to be able to circumcise my kid because it would be a major surgery
based on how much they'll be removing.
The tip of his cock is going to look like the ladies' lips at Mar-a-Lago.
What I mean to say is like most people are concerned about it from the sake of like desensitizing
the children, the kids' penis, or that the person is going to be made fun of or ostracized
for not having it done.
Right?
Right.
And those people who have that opinion of a child that young are not going to remember
to check in 15 to 18 years from now to be like, "Hey, how's the fucking going with your
kids?"
Like they're not...
How's the head of your kid's dick doing?
You can't follow up.
You're never going to get an answer to your hypothesis.
You're only going off of your own personal shit.
So it's just as like, yeah.
It's madness that people think...
Because they go through this with like C-sections versus natural birth and stuff like that.
The amount of shaming that people do to each other's children and stuff like that.
And it just comes from...
What does it matter?
Well, it just comes from people not being confident in their own life decisions.
That's what it comes down to.
People do not have the confidence to just live in their own decisions and they need
validation and they need conformity from others to make them feel like, "Oh, I did the right
thing."
It's like, "Fuck you.
You did the right thing for you.
That doesn't mean it's the right thing, period."
And it's not necessarily the right thing, and you got to learn to live with decisions,
man.
Also, how much happier would everyone be if they just didn't know all this shit about
everybody else?
Oh, for God's sake, yeah.
I don't even know about anybody else's kid's genitals to live my life.
I don't know.
I think it's important that people realize I fired glowing jism out of my cock earlier
this week.
I think that's important.
No, no.
That is important.
That's important.
No, no.
We have carve-outs in these rules.
That's it.
You should go, "Hey, I don't know if I want to talk about my kid's peace with you right
now, but you know what?
I was thinking about most people have some form of herpes.
What form do you have, and how are you dealing with it?"
It's true.
It's universal, baby.
Before we get into this, what other aspects of my kid's genitals are you going to want
to talk about later so we can just knock all these conversations out right now?
You should be like, "Actually, the truth is I'm teaching a class on circumcision, and
I need you to give me $100 right now, or I cannot talk to you about it."
Yeah.
I didn't get him circumcised, but I got him a Prince Albert.
I'll let him make the choice a couple years later.
If he wants to keep it, he's got it.
If he wants to get rid of it, he's got a pull tab.
He can just click it away.
I got a pull tab.
He can just yerk.
He's got an injector seat.
Also, Mrs. Cincy Scoop is saying that people have been following up asking about the birth.
How do I convey that that's an incredibly personal moment, so I probably don't want
to talk about it?
You just say that we kept the foreskin, but we clipped his balls, so he's a eunuch.
He's going to have a lovely singing voice.
We were asked to choose.
We flipped a coin two-face style, like a Batman villain, and just thought, "Well, either we're
going to give him a circumcision or no nuts."
Let's see.
We were too busy debating how we're going to handle the fact that he was born with three
buttholes to figure out what we were going to do about his circumcision.
My son is essentially a bowling ball.
We were mainly worried about his tail.
My son is essentially a bowling ball with a tail.
You tell me where to prioritize, lady.
Well, the half-grown twin in his ass cheek would like a word or two.
He has a psychic conjoined twin named Quado.
He's got a Quado in his left butt saddle, so yeah, priorities.
We haven't gotten around to the circumcision talk yet.
Yeah, we're still exercising the ass Quado first.
Lastly, any tips on how to raise my baby gay?
I think you just start engaging in all of these conversations about their genitals.
I think you just engage with as many people and converse about their genitals as you can,
and that's how that works.
We've been doing our best.
We have a gay agenda.
We're trying to raise our kids gay, and believe it or not, they just figure it out on their
own.
It's the weirdest thing.
Yeah.
Life finds a way.
We have gay porn around the house, we have nothing like our Christmas decorations are
just like different dirty decks of cards with hot dudes, and we just hang the cards on the
Christmas tree.
It's not getting it now.
Man, they're really getting a full mouthful of it.
We only serve phallic fruits and vegetables for dinner.
I heard this really interesting thing, and I may have said this before on the podcast
show, but we're talking about how a lot of your hardcore religious types want to talk
about sexuality as a choice, right?
What this person said was, for them, it is a choice because they've had to choose to
repress their natural sexuality their whole life, and they don't realize that it's not
a choice.
It's just what you're born with.
They've had to make the conscientious choice to say no to their instincts, to their basic
human nature.
That's an interesting way to look at it.
They have had to make a choice their whole life, so they see it as everyone has to make
this choice, right?
I made this choice.
Everyone must have made this choice somewhere along the lines, like, "No, man.
It ain't a choice.
It's just the cards you're dealt with," but for those people, they're in that zone.
They don't understand that it's not a choice.
I'm not going down to the fucking bath house.
It's not a choice.
It's just your nature.
Because I'm choosing every day to not go down to the bath house.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's just your name.
But they don't understand that, and they can't see that, and especially if they've been indoctrinated
in a very small community that has the whole-
That's a good point.
I thought that was a really interesting look at it.
You would think it's a choice because you've had to choose to repress your own nature your
entire life.
Thank you for all the laughs and creating such an awesome community.
Murray is still a great name for a baby.
It sure as fuck is.
I'm going to pass on it because it doesn't work in Portuguese.
Okay.
Fucking you in the face with a boob full of milk.
That's Manu, Mrs. Cincy Scoop.
Thanks for the update, Manu.
Congratulations, Manu.
Yes, congratulations.
Yes.
Congratulations, Cincy Scoop.
Both of you.
Yes.
That's wonderful.
It's time for a little jock-a-versus-a-nerd.
It's on.
You want to do a little jock-a-versus-nerd action?
Oh, am I?
Fuck yeah.
I'm on the hunt for balls.
Oh, no.
Look at that.
There's a picture on the Zoom and the Twitch of the little baby Dippin' Dot Manu.
Baby.
Oh, that's two.
That's so cute.
Baby Cincy Scoop.
There's another reason why you should sub up and support the Patreon for as little as
three bucks a month.
You can see baby pictures.
You can come hang out with us.
Yeah.
Oh, we got a scooperty here today from...
Wait, wait.
Who's it from?
There's another note here I want to bring up.
Rebecca in chat.
Oh, yeah.
Go.
I had two kids, one in disposable diapers, formula-fed, hospital-born.
The second kid was born at home, breast-fed and diapered in cloth.
You wouldn't know.
They both turned out fine and I'm sorry, people said all this dumb stuff to you.
That's exactly what we're talking about is that we are the children you are worried about.
Look at all of us, which ones are formula-fed, which ones have circumcisions, which ones...
You can't tell.
Babies survive.
They find them in freaking dumpsters crap and they all live.
Babies are amazingly resilient.
I put those babies in those dumpsters absolutely with the intention of them dying and they
won't.
No.
And Jacob still walks free.
Why?
I'm just a prom night dumpster baby.
Well, it's because they didn't die.
Prom night dumpster baby and I'm taking a stroll.
Yeah.
From Scala Wall Scoop, hey you face fucking tit farming socialists.
I'm gearing up for a trip to New Zealand and thought I'd dive into some Kiwi culture beforehand
in hopes to hear this New Zealand themed scooperty while on my trip.
Apologies to the real New Zealand scoops for what is a tourist take on what I'm sure I'll
discover to be a lovely country.
Definitely less cunty than their neighboring land, mass hole of a continent, and a country
across the water.
Now that I've probably insulted two wonderful nations, does that give me honorary American
status?
See you at the churn.
Yes it does.
See you at the cone with that talk buddy.
Let's see, this scooperty is, the categories are Flight of the Concourse, New Zealand cities,
New Zealand actors, New Zealand director.
Oh great.
Let's see, I'll try New Zealand actors for 200.
This leading man probably wishes that Jurassic Park spared a little more expense.
Not sure why he went back to that island multiple times, can't be the money.
I don't know which one of those guys was in all the Jurassic Park movies.
Who's from New Zealand?
Yeah I don't know, is Jeff Goldblum from New Zealand?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I guess I'll pass.
Paul!
Ah shit, I'm just trying to rack my brain for his name.
He's in Event Horizon.
I just can't, I can't remember his name.
You remember his name Matt?
I have to pass.
I was thinking of Richard Attenborough, but I don't know if it's Richard Attenborough.
Oh it could be Richard Attenborough too.
Oh yeah, I guess it could be, I don't know.
I'll do Richard Attenborough.
Alright.
Sam Neal.
That's it.
That's the name I could think of.
That's the name you could remember Paul.
That's the name I could remember.
Oh Paul, you're up.
Oh I'm in the hole, I gotta start changing my tactics.
I will go New Zealand director.
Answer the questions correctly.
Or no, I'll go Fly the Concords.
Fly the Concords for 200.
The Boom King, the Rhymos, the Rhymosaurus.
Yeah the Rhymosaurus.
And Oscar winning member of the band.
That is Jermaine.
Ah, it was Brett.
Brett McKenzie also will accept, Brett.
Wait a minute.
I hung out with those guys every night at the Attenborough French Festival in 2004 and
it's so funny.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
They were awesome.
They were so funny and so funny.
Wait, wasn't, oh no, he's the Hippopotamus.
Jermaine's the Hippopotamus, not the Rhymosaurus.
Well there you go.
And go my face.
I'll try New Zealand cities for 200.
New Zealand's largest city known as the city of sails, it's home to the Sky Tower.
What's the capital of New Zealand?
It starts with an A.
A.
Isn't it Queensland?
Eighths?
I don't think so.
Oh Queensland.
That's Australia.
Yeah.
Oh what the fuck is that city called, I don't know, I can't think of it.
Oh wait, this was Matt's turn.
What?
How's this Matt's turn?
I don't know, it says Matt's turn on top.
Oh, in that case, pass.
I don't know.
I pass too.
Paul.
I'll pass.
Auckland.
It wasn't A, you were right.
You were on the right path.
Yup, that is the city I was trying to think of.
The Queensland of New Zealand, Auckland.
The Auckland.
Auckland.
Wait, that was my turn?
Okay.
Alright.
Oh, it was because of the passing.
It's my fault.
I got confused because of the passing.
So yeah, that was Matt's.
I'm playing under protest.
I quit.
I'm leaving.
Matt is continuing the game under protest.
I'll go to New Zealand cities for 400, although I didn't get Auckland, so I don't know why
I'm going to other New Zealand cities, because that's the one that I knew.
Located on the South Island, this city is nestled between Lake Wakipu, maybe, and the
snowy peaks of the Remarkables, with a name that hints to the country's British colonial
history.
Teatimesburg.
Oh, this is going to be like Queensland or something like that.
I don't know what it is though.
Pass.
Paul.
I'll go with London.
Alright.
Queenstown.
Ah, shit.
The London of New Zealand.
You take me to Queenstown.
I'll do New Zealand director for 800.
I got to get on the board.
Alright.
Daily Double.
Oh, man.
This is where I get redemption.
Well, this is your opportunity.
Sadly, we just lost this giant of directing talent to Parkinson's disease, known for his
great work on Once Were Warriors, The Edge, Along Came a Spider, and the James Bond film
Die Another Day.
Oh, Dolly the Sheep.
No.
Shoot.
I'd give you hints if I had any idea at all.
I have to pass.
I'm sorry.
You can't pass.
It's a Daily Double, dude.
Oh, I'll guess Richard Attenborough.
Richard Attenborough is correct.
It's not.
Lee Tomohori.
I knew it was going to be a native name from the Maori, but I didn't, I didn't know.
Matt, you're up.
God, we are killing this, huh?
Look at us with our New Zealand knowledge.
We know so much about New Zealand.
Currently, I am winning with zero.
I will do New Zealand actors for 400, please.
Okay.
This actress born in Winnipeg, but raised in New Zealand, shared her Oscar-winning debut
with fellow Kiwi Cliff Curtis in The Piano and went on to famously play women with powers,
a mutant and a telepath.
Okay, pass.
Okay, that passes to me.
I watch The Piano at least once a week.
I actually know this one, Jacob, if you want to pass it to me.
Well, that's good, because unfortunately, I've never paid attention to the actress from
New Zealand in The Piano.
I purposely don't pay attention to her at all while watching The Piano, so I will pass
as well.
You just watch Harvey Keitel's Weiner.
That's right.
Anna Paquin.
She won that when she was a baby.
That was a very young age to win an Oscar.
She was very, very young to get the Oscar then.
Yeah.
That changes the score completely now.
I am still in the lead with zero points.
Matt is still in second place with negative 200 points, but Paul is now still in third
place with negative 1,000 points.
It's anyone's game.
How am I still negative 1,000?
Good grief.
I don't know, because you lost points.
I guess.
I don't know how these games work.
You lost the Daily Double on the New Zealand.
Oh, that's right.
On the 800.
Yeah, that was 800.
But does it turn to 1,600?
What?
No, I guess it wasn't.
No, you had missed other ones too.
Oh, okay.
There you go.
I'll go to New Zealand Actors for 600.
Okay.
Known for her TV success, this actor has starred on iZombie, Once Upon a Time, and most recently,
Ghosts.
An actor by any other name would smell as sweet.
Okay.
Rose McGowan.
Good guess.
Rose MacGyver.
Oh, look at that.
You had three-fourths of it.
I did.
I had more of that name than I thought I was going to.
I'll do New Zealand Director.
What the hell?
For 800.
What?
That's not New Zealand Director?
Oh, you said Director.
I thought you said New Zealand Actor.
Sorry.
This is fine.
This young actor has made memorable turns.
Under protests.
More protests.
Yes.
So much protest.
This young actor has made memorable turns in Hunt for the Wilder People, Deadpool 2, and
How to Train Your Dragon.
He shares a name with the famous son of a beetle, not Dennis' son.
Uh, I don't know.
I'll have to pass.
Passes the map.
Probably Julie and somebody, but I can't tell you who.
Pass.
That passes to me.
Oh, I should have guessed.
Can I guess still?
Sure.
It's my turn, but you can guess.
I'm going to guess it's Julius Rodman.
Just on context clues.
Great.
I'll guess Julius Rodman.
Motherfucker!
It's Julian Dennison.
Oh, there you go.
Eat shit.
Matt, you're up.
I'll take Dennis Rodman's relatives for 600, please.
Give me a flight of the concords for 400.
This fanatic co-star on the series went on to animated series fame as Mabel in Gravity
Falls.
Yeah.
Is this Kristen Schaal?
This is Kristen Schaal.
Oh, okay.
It sure is.
It is.
Nice job.
Just a legit correct answer for one of these questions.
It's so refreshing.
It's a new day.
It's me.
I'll try New Zealand director 200.
The most famous director to come out of New Zealand, he doesn't know when to quit when
it comes to hobbits and beetles.
What the fuck is that guy's name?
Who did he pass to?
I pass it to Paul.
Dennis.
Peter.
Pumpkin eater?
Jackson?
Is it Jackson?
Peter Jackson?
That sounds right.
Peter Jackson.
That's right.
Hey, Peter Jackson.
Peter Pumpkin.
Two direct answers in a row.
Those two questions were the only ones I was hunting for.
They're the only ones I know I'd do in this category, is looking for Kristen Schaal and
Peter Jackson.
You got it.
Paul.
I will do flight of the concords for eight.
I got to get on the board.
This musician is depicted by Jamin Clement, who comes to Brett in several dream sequences
representing different personas and eras of the artist, even seeing a song named after
the musician.
It's me, Brett, David Bowie from the music video of Ashes to Ashes.
It's David Bowie.
David Bowie is correct.
Three right answers in a row.
Such a great.
What are we coming to?
I'm the runner for that episode.
So all right, Matt, let's see if we can make it four right answers in a row.
You're up for the Concord 600.
He is the band's manager who later went on to play a gentleman turned pirate on our flag
means death.
Oh, shoot.
I know the guy, but I don't know his name.
He's great.
Yep.
Yes, he is.
He's really funny.
You know, really good.
I don't pass, pass to me.
I pass as well.
Reese Davis.
Oh, fuck.
Reese Darby.
Fuck my ass.
He was so sure of himself.
That was some last name revenge there.
I was fucking sure I'll go to New Zealand cities for 600 Darby.
Shit, it's the other daily double.
And the game is mine.
Now I just pass, pass, pass with my 200 point victory.
The capital of New Zealand.
This city is nicknamed Windy on account of the strong winds of the Cook Strait.
Not sure if it's famous for its beef, too.
I thought Auckland was the capital of New Zealand.
Huh.
Auckland doesn't lend itself to any beef related anything, though.
The answer is, it sounds like it's trying to say the name is Chicago, but I don't think
that the capital city of New Zealand is Chicago.
Right?
Capital.
It'd be really funny if it was, though, and we just didn't know it.
I have beef experience.
Yeah.
If only I had a little more beef experience.
I have no idea Auckland, I don't know Wellington beef, Wellington Wellington.
I don't know how the windy is part of that, but OK, well, I guess it's just windy and
Wellington.
Oh, I guess it's windy.
Well, it's Nick.
OK.
Windy Wellington.
I don't know.
I dated it.
Windy Wellington.
Uh, she was lovely.
Director for why didn't you marry her 600 because she was disgusted by my uncircumcised penis
as she ran away was the chip clips on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This two time Oscar winning director has directed the following women in leading roles.
Kate Winslet, Meg Ryan, Nicole Kidman, Holly Hunter and Kirsten Dunst.
Oh, I watched an outtake of the first Spider-Man movie with Kirsten Dunst in it the other day.
And it was just over and over again.
This one crowd scene where she's in front of the crowd and the director is just trying
to get this one extra to stop doing something.
Yeah.
Oh, that's every time they'll cut the director over the speaker will be like, great, great,
great.
You were doing this.
Don't do that.
Kirsten is doing that.
So don't do that thing that you're doing.
Oh man.
Let's go again.
And then they'd go again.
And the extra would just do it again.
It was great.
It says Sam Raimi, right?
That was Sam Raimi.
Oh yeah.
I guess it would be.
So I know that director exactly.
I'm the same here with like the original Spider-Man movie isn't on the, on the category.
Don't think Sam, Nicole Kidman, uh, Holly Hunter, goodness sakes, um, not to pass passes
the mat.
Uh, it's New Zealand's own Steven Spielberg, sheep fucker.
Oh, you're using his full name, Steven, New Zealand Berg did Stanley Kubrick direct all
of these people.
And does he New Zealand?
I don't think Kubrick directed Meg Ryan, maybe I'm wrong or, or Kate Winslet.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Uh, pass.
I was just about to say it's a lady.
There you go.
Jane, that's the, uh, you've got mail lady, I think maybe, uh, Matt, you got New Zealand
cities or New Zealand director.
Gosh, I won't know either.
Um, let's do, uh, luckily you are submitted in first place.
Yeah.
I'll do director for 400.
This actor slash director has lent his talents to both TV and films, notably reservation
dogs, the Mandalorian.
Our flag means death and Marvel movies, not to mention his turn as Adolf Hitler.
Oh, isn't this, uh, take, take Kiwa Titi.
That's it.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
Take away Titi.
Yes.
I got a last name.
Right.
It's a different, it's a different day.
Tight.
Titi walkies.
Titi walkie.
Walkie talkie bikini walkie talkie that's who it was.
Yeah.
And I'm closing out the category and the game New Zealand cities for 800.
This is the oldest city in New Zealand and was sadly devastated by earthquakes in 2010
and 2011.
Not sure if locals shouted out the town's name in frustration while it happened.
Still water.
Fucker.
Yeah.
Still water.
This is bad.
I come from Aaron air, air, air, air, air towns full edited.
I guess I'll pass a Paul.
You seem to know this one.
Uh, uh, shite shite.
Let's try shite a Christ church.
Christ church.
Damn it.
That's the other city in New Zealand that I knew the name of Christ church on a cracker
and there that is the game with 600 Paul is in second with negative 1600 and I'm in third
with the negative 1800 and that's from Scholar walls scoop.
Thank you.
Scholar walls.
Scoop.
If you want to send us a scoopity or a price of Skype jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock
versus nerd.
Oh, hold on.
Somebody just unmuted themselves.
Got it.
Oh, there we go.
Uh, anyway, if you want to send us any of those jock versus nerds up, you can hear us
though.
Can't you?
Oh, I think I muted 10 scoop and then he tried to unmute himself again or he tried to mute
himself and unmute himself.
I don't know.
I got it.
What a mess.
Price is right.
Obelisk, scooperty, uh, scoop mail.
Do all those things right over there at haste scoops.com.
Go to haste scoops.com.
You can do all those things.
We are still running low on those jock versus nerd.
So head over there, make us some jock versus nerds and send them on in.
You can see how much we crushed the New Zealand one.
So, you know, just pick a topic and knock it out.
Yeah.
We basically know everything about New Zealand.
Let's get another, let's get another New Zealand quiz in here.
Keep them coming guys.
All New Zealand all the time.
Line them up.
Knock them down.
Bam.
Now we can get into the deep cuts where we can really shine.
Yeah.
If we did that same scooperty again, I feel like we'd get as many questions right.
I think you'd be pretty close to the same.
Yes.
Yeah.
Pretty close.
But we do sincerely appreciate everyone right again with all their stuff.
Of course.
Thank you all so much for, uh, signing up for our Patreon.
Those of you have, I did a test Patreon hangout trying to learn the ropes on, uh, how to get
the zoom thing going.
And I think I did it.
I'll have to double check with Jacob to talk it out, but I think I got it right.
Uh, joined my own meeting, but it worked out.
So I guess that's how it goes.
I don't know.
Is that how it works?
Yeah.
Okay.
Join your own meeting and it pops in.
Great.
Yeah.
So yeah, I did it.
I figured it out.
I got the list from the, from the thing.
And yeah.
So anyway, yeah, we got some more fun stuff coming up.
And uh, please join in, support us if you can.
If you can't support us financially currently understood, but please don't forget about
the obelisk scheme.
Just tell one person and one person only about the podcast.
Someone you think would actually enjoy hearing about my glow in the dark jizz and then see
if they would like to listen to this podcast ever again, ever, uh, chances are they won't,
but you know, Hey, but if the answer is maybe, if the answer is maybe, give it a shot, man.
That's exactly.
That's how we get our scoops for life.
But anyway, we really appreciate all of your help, uh, both financial and emotional.
It's wonderful to, to, to have all of you listening out there and uh, yeah, we're pleased
that you're listening.
Oh, lemur, screamer, creamer in the chat, uh, Lord, there were no Lord questions and
lemur, screamer, creamer is sad that there were no Lord questions.
I am too.
I knew Lord was from New Zealand guys.
I might've gotten a Lord question time for another New Zealand quiz.
Let's go.
Get on it.
New Zealand, all Lord Lord, just make Lord the answer to every one.
I want to thank everyone who supports us over on our Patreon page, uh, right now.
Some folks have just simply gone from the JLR level to the $3 level, just to, just to
go with the rising costs.
We appreciate that.
Other people who signed up for the first time, uh, we even got a new ice cream truck driver.
Oh man, that's immense.
Yes.
Um, so, uh, thank you all for, for doing that so much.
We really appreciate it.
Um, if you want to support our podcast and you have it within your budget to do so, pick
out a tier that fits your budget over at preachingfun.com.
, or if we didn't talk about Paul's jizz as much as you expected us to today, head on over to fartsinabag.biz.
Let's give them something to talk about.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com.
It takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little as $3 a month, you can help
keep this show on the air.
That's right.
If you think the show is worth more than $3 a month, uh, don't go there, or no wait, do
go there.
Do go there.
If you think the show is worth more than $3 a month.
Yes.
If you think the show is worth less than $3 a month, don't even bother.
And also we get it.
Yes.
Uh, thanks for listening everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you at the cone.
At the cone we don't talk about us, the people's kids and their dips.
See ya!