You want to go for it? Want to go for it? Twerk off right now?
She goes, "Oh, I see a twerk off, all right."
Oh, hello there! I am so glad you're here! It's time to thank you, the ice cream truck drivers!
Thank you so much, ice cream truck drivers! Right now, I'd like to thank Dr. Scoop Little, Elkin Magic Scoop,
Fifi, Frankie's Tiki Scoop, Galactic President Scooper Star McScoopsalot, Ice Blue Scoop,
I Wanna Scoop Baby, Jacob Dick Laker, Jake Schneider, Jason Klepper, and Jeff Harris!
If you want to be an ice cream truck driver just like these fine folks and help deliver that fucking ice cream
straight into people's fucking ear holes, head over to PreachingFun.com!
PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign up, and who knows? The life you save may be your own!
Here's a show!
Hey, Johnny! Do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great, let's go!
Broom, broom, broom!
Big sewer plate strikes again!
No way! Did it happen again?
Manhole cover messes up F1, uh, again.
Stop it!
Stupid ass.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's ice cream social in Las Vegas!
That's Matt Donnelly! In Pittsburgh, that's Paul Mattingly!
In Las Vegas, it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy! We're Preaching Fun!
We are Preaching Fun.
Yes.
Let's get silly. Oh my god, Manhole versus car 2-0, huh?
It was again, there was two different rounds of practice laps yesterday, and the second
round of practice laps was called off because of a loose Manhole cover for the second time
in three years.
Two out of three years!
Newman didn't pay this time to come to it, so at least that part didn't happen.
That's crazy, though.
That's good, at least.
The money they spend on that thing, and then to just have that happen again, that's got
to be.
According to Newman, he got a hundred dollar F1 credit, which he spent at the store and
got five-eighths of a hoodie.
He got nearly all of a hoodie.
I was, you know, like, I get these, uh, I'm doing a gig for F1, uh, this year, and we'll
talk about it more in a sec, but on the break, I walked around and saw the store, and sure
enough, you just see this beautiful merch, you know, booth, and you're like, "Oh, maybe
I'll get myself a nice, like, F1 sweatshirt."
And they're so expensive, and then you're like, "Wait, where am I, where am I going
to wear this?"
Right.
Not only where am I going to wear this, but who's going to respect me in Las Vegas for
wearing this?
Oh, no.
It is so strange, okay?
So, like, there's so much local anger and hatred towards F1.
Oh, yeah.
Just a ton.
Uh, was the Rio put up a billboard?
We got 99 problems, but F1 traffic ain't one.
Nice.
Uh, you know, our pal, Jonas Robertson said a happy F1 to everyone.
It's a picture of him giving two fingers to the camera.
Um, and, uh, and I, and Jacob, you know, uh, your, your commute has been, you know,
fucked up for weeks, right?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm just, I'm just losing hours out of my day every day.
And so I am feeling guilt, Paul.
I'm feeling guilt about, like, how fun and cool it is to be in the middle of F1 for the
race.
Hey, I understand, but this is the life of the performer, right?
This is how it goes.
Yeah.
We have lots of our friends who are doing the stuff with the Sphere.
The Sphere is sucking the very life marrow out of entertainment in Las Vegas.
What can you do?
You gotta ride the devil, the devil, the devil for a while.
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know either.
Paul Mattingly, gotta ride the devil.
We gotta ride the devil.
Uh, and that's what I tell everyone when I ride it, when I go.
All right, guys, time to ride the devil.
When the cab driver says, I can't drop you off at the West and the road is closed, I
say, ride the devil, ride the devil.
If we can get a Paul Mattingly ride the devil shirt in time, that'll be our Black Friday
sale.
Great.
That'd be a good one.
Yeah.
Black Friday.
So, uh, Spiegelworld is a hired partner of Mercedes, uh, and for many years, uh, not
many years, for now three years, um, they've been doing events here and also sometimes
at the Miami location as well.
And this is where, this is, this is, Jacob, you've been in the employee of Spiegelworld
for quite some time.
We've all been in the, in the employee of Spiegelworld for here and there.
Um, this is my first time since the pandemic officially in their, in their employee.
It is both amazing how much talent they attract in front of and behind the stage and how much
there's attention of, of always of like, what are, what are we, what are we doing and why
are we doing it?
That's the whole thing.
And yet, right.
So what I'm a part of in Mercedes is like why you do hire a Spiegelworld is because
they make strange decisions, right?
So it's Spiegelworld, but they're like, Hey, you know, the circus act thing is pretty cool,
but can you do something totally different for us?
We want our Mercedes people to feel special.
Their answer was let's build a ski lodge.
Let's build a giant ski launch.
Let's have a Yeti.
Let's have fake snow going.
Let's just totally transport people to something inappropriate to both Miami and Las Vegas.
Right.
And people fucking love it.
People.
It is such a treat to the eye.
They eat it up.
It's, it's incredible.
Ski Lodge.
We are so jaded.
Yeah.
Ski Lodge was one of the best things about super frico.
Right.
Oh, and it's still there and it's still, it's still rocking.
It's still great.
Yeah.
Ski Lodge is super frico.
I think there's just a market to expand on this and just grow it out.
He just needs to open up ski lodge diners.
No, Ross just needs to make some standout, some ski lodge diners.
It's the diner part that he needs a little work on, but, um, why, because they don't
know how to make food.
The one diner they opened, they turn it into a steakhouse.
So they're not there.
They're diners.
Oh, no, no, no.
It needs to be pizza only, it needs to go the Chuck E Cheese route.
You got already, you already got the animatronic abominable snowman.
You add some other, you add some other animatronics.
If you add a bunch of animatronics, but half the animatronics are live performers that
pop out every now and then and freak people out.
Holy crap.
I was, I was, I need a meeting with Ross.
Let me get a meeting with Ross.
I need to sit down and we need to talk about this whole revitalization.
You are accelerating like an F1 race car right now and I'm telling you to pump your brakes.
You know what I'm doing?
What's that?
I'm riding the devil.
Riding the devil!
That's what I'm doing.
I was just to say, I was worried they might be listening to this, but as soon as you said
Chuck E Cheese pizza, I'm positive they turned it off.
Bullshit.
It needs to happen.
That guy who did Evil Pie said he was going to do it and he never did it because he dropped
the fucking ball on a billion dollar idea.
It needs to happen and it needs to be one of those things where you don't know, is that
an animatronic or is that a real person, and that's going to be the best thing when that
thing walks off the stage and freaks children out and scares everybody in the restaurant.
Where are the children coming from?
It's going to be a family friendly restaurant.
I've lost track as to where you think this is happening.
Where is this going?
This is worldwide, son.
Okay, okay, okay.
Franchised.
Not for the F1 track.
I got it.
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Was that what you thought I was talking about?
Yep.
Oh, I've, no, I've taken this story all the way.
He's left that behind.
No, this is my whole thing.
No, no.
Once you ride the devil, you go to different places.
Very different places.
Oh man.
All right, all right.
Ride the devil.
Let's bring it back to the enchantment of this current iteration of the Ski Lodge, which
has yet to reach its full animatronic potential.
Go ahead.
Well, there's no animatronic, so by potential, I mean-
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, yeah.
It has not reached its full animatronic potential.
All those billionaires hang out and chat together anyway.
Isn't he talking with Elon?
You know, China's replacing their entire workforce with robots.
Get on it, son.
I don't think that's happening.
I'll just-
I'm-
Doesn't seem like it is.
Very hopeful and happy that it's not.
No, I don't.
I know, I know.
For all the comparisons of our crazy, wily CEOs, there's a gigantic divide when it comes
to-
A gulf.
A gulf of humanity.
Yes.
A chasm.
A chasm of humanity.
Respect for artists and all that kind of stuff.
Did you see-
Yes.
He's such a chode.
Did you see Elon got completely ratioed on Twitter recently, someone, and I was terrible,
I can't remember the name of the lady, but she called him out and she was like, "This
guy has everything.
He's got the whole," you know, oh God, there he is, smoking a cigar with all the billionaires.
He-
Quit distracting Paul.
No, it's fine.
But he's got all the money in the world and yet he has no passions.
He's not interested in literature or film or art.
He's never even complimented a movie.
He's never even talked about a movie he likes.
And he got so butt hurt, he started listing movies and like, "This is a good movie.
This movie's good."
Oh no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's terrible.
He is such a loser, such a loser.
Hold on here.
We can fix this.
Let's see here.
Yeah, let's do this.
Elon, buddy, don't list movies that you like when people say you don't like movies.
That's a bad move.
That's like listing your black friends.
It works just as well.
What are you doing?
It's exactly the kind of move-
If only you had black friends.
It's exactly the kind of move.
It's exactly how it read too.
It came off so hollow and so ridiculous.
He started talking about movies from like 2003.
Titanic was a good movie.
Yeah, that's exactly like the stuff he was like, "What?"
News broke.
Obviously there was going to become a trillionaire, right?
Right.
He wrote, "I will carry the light of consciousness to other planets and to Mars and beyond."
Bullshit.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Bullshit.
Someone just wrote, "Can you just pay taxes on it?
Can you just pay your fair amount of taxes on it?"
Yeah.
It was weird.
It's like, if you think you take your trillions, which no one singular human should ever have,
it is a sickness.
Having a billion dollars seems like the weirdest, craziest thing in history.
Having a trillion dollars, I don't even know what that means.
That's just it.
It is the biggest flaw of Americans to not properly fathom the wealth gap and what obscene
wealth means.
Oh, yeah.
It is the biggest problem.
We should be ... I don't understand why we're not in the streets right now.
We have a podcast where it's fall.
Yeah.
It's raining out.
It's raining here too.
Wow.
Give me an hour.
When it stops raining in an hour, I'll go to the streets.
No problem.
Yeah.
Okay, great.
Great, great, great.
Yeah.
A trillion dollars is meaningless, coffee bean scoop.
It does lose objective reality for most human beings.
We can't fathom it.
I think we're all human beings.
I don't think anybody can.
Yeah.
It is anti-capitalist because capitalism is money reentering the flow of commerce.
These are weird dragons hoarding wealth that never gets recycled into the environment.
It never gets back.
It'll never trickle down.
I don't want to get into it, but at any rate, he's a douche.
Oh, that reminds me.
And also speaking of hoarding wealth, we owe an apology as a podcast and as a group
to Jake Paul.
Last week we called Jake Paul a douche bag.
He announced that he has just purchased a 364 carat diamond necklace ahead of his upcoming
fight and it looks like diamond bullets hanging off of his neck.
So sorry, Jake Paul, that we called you a douche.
I think I said it about Logan Paul.
Our bad.
They're both awful.
They're both monsters.
No.
Paul, did you not hear what I just said?
Let me tell you about his necklace again.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
I miss heard you.
Think of the children.
I misheard you.
Gold plated bullets.
Okay.
Great.
Oh, sorry.
I got so wound up in my anger.
Use that money to save this planet instead of worrying about putting it on other planets.
Like that actually is enough money to probably do a lot for this planet.
When I was a younger man, everybody could just have food.
When I was a younger man and fully locked in with Star Trek and sci-fi and all that,
I really was a proponent of space travel, and I still am to a degree.
There have been great discoveries that we as a species have made through the advancement
of space traveling technology.
Velcro is just one.
However, having said that, when I became a somewhat older, wiser man, have you guys ever
heard Gil Scott Heron's, "YD's on the Moon?"
Yes.
It's perfect.
That always keeps resonating in my head whenever I hear these motherfuckers talking about going
to space.
It's like, man, we've got way more shit to handle here.
It's literally because they don't know what to do with their money.
It is too much money because when you have hundreds of millions of dollars, you can afford
every single house that you want on the planet.
You can travel privately to every single place on the planet.
You can afford every single meal that anyone could possibly prepare on the planet.
You can afford everything, every watch, every piece of clothing, every car.
I always say you don't have to consider money.
Money becomes not a consideration in life.
It's crazy.
The only reason to go higher is strictly insane ego bullshit.
To want that insane ego bullshit and still want to do nothing or barely anything for
humans on the planet is just ridiculous.
Yeah, it's grotesque.
All right.
But you can't accumulate.
There's no great fortune without some great crime.
That's what it comes down to.
Also, just bitching about these things and not acting on them, that's just a waste of
our time and your time.
We here at Matt and Madeline's Ice Cream Social, we want to act on this.
Here's what I propose.
I propose that our Patreons give each of us $1 billion and we're each going to use that
billion dollars as we think a billionaire should.
Do you know how hard pressed I would be to even do this podcast if I had even a million
dollars in my bank account?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing will stop me from wanting to hear the sound of my own voice, Paul.
There isn't a bad amount of money on the planet.
That would be really fun.
If I had like crazy money, I would be setting up random live events with us all the time.
That's what we would do, actually.
That's true.
That actually is.
We would just just do events all over the place.
That's why a lot of these celebrity podcasts are making that loot and catching on because
they have the money to go set up live events all over the world and get more interest.
Amy Poehler did her first live podcast.
It's pretty great.
Go check it out.
I listened to it.
Man of Scalco.
Is that?
Did I say that right?
They said no, but I don't have a I don't have a better way to say it.
Man of Scalco.
Meta Scalco.
I don't know.
Medicine.
Calico.
So anyway, Preachingfun.com, we need three billion dollars after Patreon fees.
Sebastian Meta Scalco, especially nailed the last name and blew the first name with the
hard part versus the easy part there.
Sebastian Meta Scalco.
That's so funny.
I only listen to the last name because that's the part that I just have no idea.
Yeah.
Or go to will show them.org.
Oh my God.
And and we can show how it's done.
Org.
It lemur creamers with more animatronics, it would be more animatronics as soon as I
had like crate.
If I had crazy, I would have me a showbiz pizza slash Chuck E. Cheese.
I'd have you would have a basically an animatronic music.
It would be.
I've got that showbiz pizza.
I've got that Chuck E. Cheese.
I've got that combination showbiz pizza and Chuck E. Cheese.
It would be both for sure.
I would have all of them.
I'd have Chuck E. and the and the pizza time theater band with Pasquale and all the other
dips and I'd have everybody with the rocket fire explosion.
Forget about it.
Oh, man.
Guys.
Amazing.
Some sense really come up in the chat.
I mean, if you take a billion, we usually get at least, you know, 200 people to come
out to Scoop Fest.
We just charge five million a ticket.
It's done.
But billion.
Done deal.
All right.
I'm going to tell you what, for the five million dollar VIP ticket, yes, you're going to get
a lot of attention from us.
You would get away with a lot of personal attention.
You would get away with a lot.
Speaking of which seems to be the case with our entire governmental system.
Speaking of five million dollar Scoop Fest.
Yes.
We have a guest here.
We're going to have have him pop on here.
JD, would you unmute yourself, please?
I said, JD, would you meet yourself, please?
Good to see you, JD.
How are you?
I'm going to leave that entire pause in everyone's going to assume like some episode error happened.
I'm good.
Very good.
We're we're working on the documentary and we're going to launch a go fund me to kind
of help raise some finishing funds.
So remind everyone about the documentary in general.
What is the documentary?
The documentary is about the Scoops.
So we were at Scoop Fest.
A lot of you there did interviews with us and we got some great footage and we're probably
about seventy five percent to eighty percent there as far as what we need.
Right now, we have like a four and a half hour rough cut that we still need to fill
in those spots.
So we need to interview Jacob, S.J., Matt, Sarah and Penn.
We couldn't get Penn at Scoop Fest because he was sick.
Oh, you get that crew back to Vegas.
They were a volunteer crew, friends of friends, and they're all in L.A. So to get them back
at some point when everybody's schedule lines up and get all these interviews again, we
also need a little bit cash for our art musicians.
So Spadoni is doing the music.
We got Brogan and Ryar doing some logos for us and we want to make sure that people get
a little cash in their pocket.
And then at the end, we're going to submit the film to festivals, actual festivals.
So we want to take it old school like we used to do about twenty five years ago and hopefully
we can travel around and show it or maybe we'll end up selling it.
We'll see.
Oh, it's so exciting.
Yeah, it's super fun.
So I'll post the GoFundMe link.
We're going to post the GoFundMe link in the chat here so the people on Zoom can see it.
And we will post that along with the episode description for this very episode that everybody
is listening to and of course, all over the social medias and everything.
So yeah, go check that out.
This is the part of the show where we listen to JD figure out how to copy and paste.
It's pretty great.
It's solid.
It's solid material.
He turned his camera off for a second.
It's pretty exciting.
The coolest thing, the coolest thing is that, you know, with any luck, this gets a little
traction somewhere and generates a little buzz.
And then who knows what could happen with the podcast?
Maybe we could start doing some live shows around the country tour with the with the
movie maybe even the goal is for two thousand six hundred dollars.
That's the start.
The way that GoFundMe tears it up.
So the full goal is ten thousand, but you need to pay it out before that.
Got it.
OK, OK, OK.
It's actually it's way better than like Kickstarter or anything, especially for this.
We don't have to get randos to find it and be interested that we can kind of community,
hopefully community raise some money for that.
It's a reasonable.
It's a reasonable amount of money to fundraise.
It's not it's not it's not astronomical.
Yeah.
And, you know, I kind of maxed out my friend JD for the production.
Right.
Yeah.
If you promise to take the light of consciousness to Mars and beyond, you can ask for a trillion
dollars.
Do you know that?
What would you do with the other $999 billion?
Don't worry about that.
We got that covered.
We have a very interesting experiment we're going to do.
I think a lot of people are going to be very interested.
I have some plans.
I have like, you know how you can like eat sushi off of people at fancy restaurants,
JD?
Yeah.
Just like a lot of people, like a lot of people like a train track, so many people sushi on
them.
It's called I'm going to launch my dream, which is spicy tuna train to Chicago, where
we just eat our way.
I'm on, hey, hey, we're on a spicy to the train to Chicago and the musical rights itself
and those rights are just hours afterward, like we can't stop making money once we do
it.
Can't stop, won't stop, but it all starts with this GoFundMe.
Yeah.
And we're going to get it in front of Netflix because we have connections there and, um,
we have, we know people from, uh, the, uh, the nearest film festival in, uh, Tribeca
in New York.
Wow.
Can we ask you, JD, when you go in front of your friends, because I know you brought,
you brought investors to see me at the Magic Castle, um, what do you tell them when you
tell them you want to make a movie about us?
What do you say to these people?
That's, that's very funny that you bring up.
So, uh, those were our producers that you met and they were at Scoop Let's with us.
And, uh, I told him I wanted to do this and he just said, yeah, I'll help you.
Whatever you need.
Let's do it.
And I said, okay, Matt's going to be in LA.
Let's go take a look.
And he was the Hemen and Han about it.
He wasn't very interested.
I said, you know, send them the podcast.
They didn't listen to it.
And then when they saw you, when they saw you perform, I saw him get excited.
They're already smart people.
Yeah.
And he went, oh, now I kind of get what you're doing.
And that was just, yeah, yeah.
He got excited and, and, you know, he's one of my oldest friends in the world.
And once I saw him, he got up on stage with you doing something and you saw the eyes light
up.
And then I had them.
So good.
And then I pulled out the fish and the light bulb turned up.
The clown was in that show.
Matt busted out the clown jump scared clown.
I think I had a fish and a clown in that one.
Yeah.
You know, me production, production, baby, production, production, production.
But my, my pitch to people about it is like, this is a very unique community that I'm just
starting to find out about.
And now I've just found out about a doctor scoop and all the stuff they do there in holidays.
It's fucking amazing.
And the, the amount of love and acceptance and joyfulness is that in this community just
blew me away.
And that's why I asked to do it.
If this doc can get made and really get out there and a lot of people can see it, it will
be doing Matt and Paul and I, a personal favor on a different level that I think anybody
has really thought about.
And that is when we have to explain to people who aren't in this community, what this community
is like, we can now just point at a documentary and say, watch this because I don't know how
to explain it.
Yeah.
That was the hardest thing.
People are like, what are you doing?
And even the scoops when I, when we were at script fest and get everybody to, uh, sign
the releases, several people are like, I don't know what you're doing.
What is this?
What is this about?
And then I have to try to explain it that this is about exploring this, this amazing
community.
That's grown organically over the past 10, 12 years and they're like, Oh, okay, that
makes sense.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Myra makes a good point in the chat, which is like a scoop speeding up outside of scoop
fest.
Like without us, they just all get up together and meet with each other.
We love seeing that and people let us know that they got together.
It's like the coolest feeling.
Yeah.
We got a couple of those stories in their interviews and I was just, like I said, it's
the whole community.
Like Carl, Carl Jabelbis, Carl is welcome to this community and he's not welcome in
any other community.
He's not welcome to hang out with anyone and there's a tolerance level in this community
that's higher than anyone he's ever worked with any group, any bowling team he's joined.
I mean, any poker club, like they've all gotten rid of him and his family, he's still just
thriving here.
We should say that a JD's plug for the go fund me is also sponsored and it's brought
to you by the following, the following.
That's right.
It's brought to you by the following sponsor.
No heavens.
Today's show.
Nope.
I'm sorry.
The documentary go fund me is brought to you by Billy from Boston's baked bean ice cream.
That's right.
That's from Florida man in 2024.
That's Billy from Boston's baked bean ice cream.
Hey there.
How you doing?
I'm Billy from Boston.
I got baked beans, ice creams.
You want some?
Yeah.
You would chuckle head.
All right, go ahead and sample a little taste, how's your sister?
Won't you let her know I'm looking for, huh?
Yeah.
Trying to talk to her.
I'm trying to talk to your sister.
What's going on?
Yeah.
I just came in for ice cream.
How did you know I had a sister?
Oh, I can tell by the rings on your neck, you brony.
All right.
Well, yeah, if I don't have to pay, if I can just get ice cream.
Oh, you're going to pay.
Oh, you're going to pay pal.
Yeah.
Oh, you're going to pay big time.
How about them apples?
Whoa.
Hey bro, did you get me my ice cream yet?
You know what?
Get back in the car.
Bring her over here.
Hurry up.
Oh no.
That's your sister I'm trying to talk at.
Hey, come here.
Come here, cute sister.
Come here.
Oh, who are you?
Don't worry about it.
I'm the guy.
Come on over here and have some of my baked pilliaries.
How mysterious.
I got some mystery baked bean ice cream in the back.
I can't wait.
Oh, you got to wait.
That's my favorite kind of ice cream.
Yeah.
All right, pal.
It's on the house.
Cause I got a date with your sister now.
All right.
Thank you.
Billy from the baked bean ice cream company.
You're welcome.
How about them apples.
I'll get my own ride home, Matt.
I'll see you later.
That's right.
I'm going to crack her like the Liberty bow.
What do you think?
Yeah, uh, what?
Philly.
I was just going to say the Liberty bell is not a Boston reference.
No, it's Boston.
It's totally Boston.
It's totally.
I'm going to, I'm going to get her wedded in a T the T Harbor.
There we go.
How about that?
Yeah.
Boston teapot.
I'm already halfway there.
Yeah.
I'm going to turn her into a fricking tea party.
Oh, it's the same color too.
That's right.
Get ready.
I'm going to hear about my sister's tea Harbor.
Oh, you don't know.
I can tell you already have a bunch since last Christmas.
Well, we all, of course, every Christmas we update the family on our D harbors.
That's a given.
Nobody's talking to you anymore.
Stack of dimes.
You need to hit the arches.
That was more drifting than the Tokyo drift on that accent there.
I mean, it was like, ah, we're going out to the, to the barber shop.
We're going to go get a bar.
We're going to go to the barbershop.
You think you're better than me.
You think you're better than me, eh, eh, Boston tea party, fasten pack your car.
That's it.
There you go.
Car in the habit.
Bring your sister over here.
Pencil neck.
Come over here.
Dimes.
Let's go back pack your car.
That last sponsor ran so long.
It's time for the next sponsor.
Oh jeez.
Wow.
Boston represent, really brought it home.
Okay.
I have, I have a serious, your mayor Quimby, you need a mayor Quimby to get through.
Is that, is that, but they're not, he's Boston, he's Kennedy's Massachusetts.
He's Kelly.
Does that work?
Yeah.
Better than what you did.
Oh my God.
Well, if I had known that I would have done that.
All right.
Take two.
Hey there.
I got a Boston baked bean, a delicious ice cream.
Go ahead and sample some.
How about them apples?
Would you like some?
Hey, I'd like to date your sister.
Bring her over here.
Nobody's talking to you anymore.
Stack of dimes.
Come over here.
I'm going to crack you like the Liberty bell still out, Liberty.
Come on over here.
I'm going to go under and through you like the great arch, like the great arch.
No, that's St. Louis.
No, come on.
I'm sure that was there.
I'm pretty sure I could be wrong.
Park your car, park your car, spot on.
Get me some ice cream with baked beans in it.
Your accent is so authentic.
I'm so desperate to crack you like the Liberty bell.
You freak.
You little freaky thing.
You, you weird little sister girl.
Come explore my Grand Canyon.
Yes.
Just like our majestic Grand Canyon, one of the wonders of Boston, the Grand Canyon, one
of the wonders of the, of the world, Boston's Grand Canyon.
Oh look, it's the Mississippi, here in Boston.
Turns out it's your mom.
Your mom is the Grand Canyon of Boston, you stack of dimes.
Planes can see you when they're flying overhead.
They go, hey, check it to your left.
Look out the window and you might just see the most cavernous VJ that ever walked.
You've actually got grad students still stuck in your vaginal cavity.
I know you do.
Don't lie about it.
I'm going to crack you like the Liberty bell.
Oh, good news.
Twitch just gave us a big upgrade on our, no, nevermind.
They took it away.
Oh, no.
Oh no.
We're going to crack them like a stack of dimes.
I love stack of dimes.
I think that's my favorite insult.
I think I'm going to just keep using it.
Production meeting.
Good.
Okay.
No, I have a serious question for JD.
Ah, okay.
JD, come on back.
This is good because we were supposed to put it in the last episode, so now we're putting
them twice in this episode.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unless he left.
Did he leave?
No, he's there.
He's there.
He's on mute.
Oh, there he is.
So JD, I am a physical media snob.
Is there a chance that there is a tier for production of a DVD or a Blu-ray?
There's no tiers on a GoFundMe.
Huh?
There are tiers on a GoFundMe's.
Aren't there?
Oh, no.
I'm thinking Kickstarter.
Yes, you are.
Sorry.
I got confused.
Paul, I'm in the same boat with you.
I love physical media.
I like buying music on vinyl.
So I have two goals with this, and one of them definitely is to put it to Blu-ray.
And the other one is to get your album printed to vinyl.
Well, that's good because we owe like 25 people that.
We owe people some vinyl copies.
We really do.
That could kill two birds with one stone.
I still feel bad about that.
That's like one of the only things we've ever kind of really fucked up.
I think it's the only thing that we ever missed.
Yeah.
Like never fully missed.
And people are very kind about it.
The company that we were going to use to make the vinyl no longer is a company.
Yeah, that's a strike against this.
Yeah.
It's actually pretty easy to do nowadays.
There's lots of companies that will do it for you.
It really has changed even since we recorded the album.
Like it's a lot more prevalent even in just a couple of years here.
Yeah.
We recorded the album 18 years ago.
So yeah.
I did.
Oh, that'd be awesome, JD.
But don't need doing the music for the documentary as well.
Tag that on, make it a soundtrack, collaboration album, whole big thing.
Yeah.
We'll figure it out.
Deluxe haste book thing.
Yeah.
I would love to do that kind of stuff.
I do love comic books and stuff like that.
Yeah.
And well, with you mentioning there's a four hour rough cut already, are we going to be
able to get like behind the scenes deleted footage and all that too?
That's what I'd love.
JD, I think what Paul's asking for is final cut.
Can he have...
Yeah.
Final cut.
I do not.
No.
Okay.
Last question.
What's the working title?
Is there a working title?
Working title right now is just Hey Scoots the Movie.
I haven't come up with anything better, but I like it and it kind of, it is what it is.
Yeah.
It says everything and it directs people to our website.
So...
JD.
Paul, always thinking about shuffling people to their own website.
I don't know what the fuck they even...
JD, how far can Paul put this cart ahead of the horse before you can't see the cart anymore?
How much is a booth at Comic-Con and what are we giving out?
Hey, that's a great idea, man.
I'm here for it all.
If we did a booth at Comic-Con, you know what we could do, seriously?
We could doctor it up like a stage and we could put on 15 minute improv shows every
hour and it would be one of the most popular booths in all of Comic-Condom.
There we go.
Actually, a while back, remember we really were trying to figure out a way to do improv
shows, bucket shows at Comic-Con.
We did look at that.
I know.
It would've been a good idea.
There's a rumor that Comic-Con's moving to Vegas, too.
Yeah, that's a rumor.
And maybe...
That'll make it easier to do the show, for sure.
It will make it easier.
I think maybe we'd even need to look into PAX or some other smaller video game cons might
be fun.
Smaller cons would be the way to go and it would be interesting that we're supplying
entertainment at a con that doesn't really have evening entertainment.
Yes.
That would be a smart way to go.
That's the way to go.
All right.
One other person I wanted to shout out real quick on is Wayne Gio, who is doing our animation.
Joe Bonazzi.
And he's...
That's my Boston accent.
He's done how many movies?
He's done an intro to our movie.
Oh, wow.
Oh, so cool.
He's done an intro.
Yeah, and it's fucking hilarious.
Oh, no.
He's great.
I love his style.
He's so good.
That's so cool.
That really, that makes me kind of jump a little bit.
That makes my heart really happy because one of my all-time favorite films is Christmas
Vacation, and that whole intro is animated.
Yeah.
And a lot of great films started with animated stuff.
So that's awesome.
One of the greatest artistic casualties in my life, I think, is just being able to do
this.
Artistic casualties in my life is that when I stopped wearing overalls and started wearing
a performance tuxedo, I stopped being amused to Joe Bonazzi.
I stopped appearing in his cartoons.
It's good to know that at least we can pay him to get back on the wagon, so that's good.
Yeah.
It's pretty epic.
I can't wait to show people.
It's spectacular.
Great.
Well, that alone makes me thrilled, too, that you're already pleased with the product and
excited about how it's going to go with the final edit and everything, so yeah.
Yeah.
That's really fun, crowdsourcing this within the Scoop community and making sure that they
have input on this and are along for the whole ride.
Yeah.
It's been an awesome experience, but I can't wait to finish it and show everybody.
Well, there you go, guys.
We're almost across the finish line with the movie, so please help out if you can.
Even a dollar will probably help us get to that goal quicker.
But not that much.
I mean, it won't help that much.
Nah, yeah.
I mean, it'll help.
It'll help.
It won't be nothing.
Yeah.
It won't help that much.
Every little bit.
Kick it up to two dollars.
But you're going to take all the time to fill out the form for a dollar, and then they're
going to take their piece.
I will.
I will fill it out for a dollar.
Do ten bucks.
Yeah.
Ten bucks.
It's on GoFundMe.
Go check it out.
It's HeyScoops the Movie.
The campaign is called Help Finish HeyScoops the Movie, so if you're searching for it,
do that.
Also, the link for it is up on our social media.
It's up on the episode description for this show.
Go over there.
Help it out.
It's going to be a really interesting project, and I think everybody's going to be super
interested and fascinated in how it turns out.
I know I'm going to be.
It's like, however you acquire that dollar, just do that five more times before you fill
out the form, is what I'm saying.
There you go.
Just find a way to make that dollar $5, I think.
Maybe like a couple of you go in, like a couple of you people who are doing the dollars go
in together, like find four friends, and all of you go in together on a fiver.
This is starting to sound like a pyramid scheme, Jacob.
No, no, no, no, no, this is a GoFundMe.
It's a whole different thing.
Jacob, if those five people just find five more people each, then that'll make it much
easier.
And they find five people.
When it comes out of your mouth, Paul, I hear it.
I hear it.
Yeah.
Especially when he does that tone of voice.
Boy, that's not the first time I've heard that.
It was usually about the pet bird that we had as kids.
What the hell are you talking about?
When it comes out of your mouth, Paul, I hear it.
That was otherwise.
Otherwise, you couldn't hear the bird.
Yeah.
Uh, we, we had no bird for long.
No, we had no bird.
What?
You're being Sylvester.
Good God.
I would not know.
I mean, they told me it was a swallow, so no, we had no bird.
We had no bird.
Why are you yelling at us?
Because I don't want people thinking I put a bird in my mouth for prolonged periods of
time as a child.
I didn't.
It was just for a joke.
He did, but he doesn't want you to think that.
Look, it was for a joke.
The more you say it, the more we think you actually probably had a bird in your mouth
as a kid.
I know.
No one else brought this up.
Which is now an even better bit.
Now it's weird, which I love it because now it's like, did he put a bird in his mouth
for a long time?
Probably.
I mean, also it was Kentucky, right?
Who can say?
Yeah.
It'd be like, I'd be the Roger Whitaker sing, sing, sing, Kentucky songbird wing, wing,
wing.
Your love to me.
I spent too much time traveling on my own Kentucky songbird.
I'm coming home.
Now I put it in my mouth.
He can't hear it anymore.
You know who else is very excited about that Kentucky songbird as well as JD's second appearance
on this episode.
And that is the following sponsor, Paul Mattingly's illustrated guide to feeding a fed horse.
That's PETA approved idiom edition slash Boston edition.
If you're interested in feeding this horse, I'm about to crack it like the Liberty bell.
Go ahead and get yourself some birds and stick it in the horse's mouth.
Two birds in the horse is worth one in the bush, which I just cracked like the Liberty
bell.
Horse bush cracking, horse bush cracking.
You can lead a horse to a bird's nest, but you can't make him put a bird in his mouth.
So hey scoops, a check out nest.
That was the PETA approved version of that horse nest.
This is a horse house.
That was from frozen cusser by the way.
Frozen.
Thanks.
Frozen cusser.
Good stuff.
I did not ever put a bird in my mouth for prolonged periods of time.
No one believes you.
Great.
This is what I'm saying.
This is my new bit.
This is my new thing about me.
Maybe or maybe not putting a bird in my mouth.
He definitely did.
I'm not saying one way or the other now, like we were backstage for the first hillbill shows.
Those baby chicks, they would come out kind of wet.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I think Paul put them in his mouth from my mouth juices.
I think we had an episode.
I thought we already had the episode title, but Paul's mouth juices.
The thing is, the birds don't realize it because they're in there and it's warm and it's nice
and it's dark, but the digestion process has begun.
That's wave one of the digestion process.
Right.
The mouth juices.
Yeah.
Our stone faces aren't because we don't understand what you're saying.
Okay.
Remember when that one bird came out and looked all like it was plucked.
Listen, as someone who owns the owner of Shmeeky and Shmooky, all this bird talk is really
kind of just brings back memories.
Oh my God.
How many more birds has escape artist Shmeeky gotten away with now because they're getting
out and killing birds at night now, right?
Well, she was at it again last night.
I had to literally put like a bunch of things in front of the door.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I want to hear this.
But Nick Newman has just shared an astounding fact.
He claims horse saliva does not have digestive properties.
What?
Again, that's why I had to breaking news this.
So like, how do they wait?
So they chew, chew, chew.
So they're just totally chewing.
No additional help from inside their gut.
And it unlike with humans, where with humans, the digestive process begins with the mouth
juices.
All right.
Where is, where is Newman?
See here?
It'd be weird if he wasn't because he's typed in the chat.
Right.
It'd be really weird if he's just typing random stuff and just guessed on that.
He wouldn't have guessed on that.
Not in a million years could you guess about mouth juices.
He might be at work and not able to talk though.
Where did he go?
Hey, what's going on?
There he is.
Okay.
Well, how the hell does a horse digestive work if there's saliva doesn't have any
digestive properties?
Yeah.
Their saliva has had no enzymes.
It is, it is just a lubricant and the digestion doesn't start until their guts.
Yeah.
It's just a lubricant.
Please don't be so dismissive of a lubricant.
That is just a lubricant.
That's why they're big old mushy snout.
It's more cushion for the pushing.
Okay.
We give medicine.
We have to be aware of that, that the medicine will not start.
You can't give sublingual medication to a horse.
It has to get to their gut before it can.
Wow.
Podcast.
Okay.
Now, now that we have you here and with your horse facts, okay, we discussed that a wolf
used someone else's crab trap, right?
My cats have learned to escape from their own cat.
Now in Sweden, birds have figured out how to convert litter into food.
Have you seen this?
No.
Litter?
In Sweden.
Like cat litter?
No.
Like refuse.
Like regular trash?
Yes.
So they have, so they've set up machines where if you bring basically garbage to this machine,
the machine will take it in and then give out bird seed as a thank you.
And so birds are sort of cleaning up around parks in Sweden.
Oh my, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So they're not actually converting.
They're not like, it's not Mr. Fusion type science.
They're not converting.
I thought you were, I thought you were saying like they're learning how to eat cigarette
butts.
No, no, no.
That's what I thought.
And then I thought, man, I'm never going to put one of those nicotine, nicotine addicted
birds in my mouth again, but the birds collect trash, put it in a receptacle.
The receptacle once having obtained the trash gives out some bird seed as a reward for the
bird doing it.
Crows are going to love this.
It's a startup project in Sweden by a company called Corvid Cleaning.
And yet in the wild crows to pick up litter, what did I just say?
And I certainly have not put a crow in my mouth all the way, all the way, all the way.
So some of the way you have, I didn't say that.
Okay.
It seems that the qualifier implies that you can't ever know.
You'll never know.
It's like a weird thing to bring up.
That's between me and author James Obar.
Yeah.
Newman, what is the smartest thing you've ever seen a horse do?
I had a horse, he's a race horse named King Sonic, and if we didn't fill his water bucket,
like if his water bucket in the stall got too low, he would shit in it.
Whoa.
And I believe he would recognize that I was irritated with the shit I cleaned out of this
bucket.
And he'd be like, he was talking that like, if you don't, you're going to clean and he
had full bucket at all times.
Matt, did you ever have any patrons like that when you were a bartender?
Yes.
If there's like holding their empty beer glass, if I took too long, they just shat their beer
glass and put it up on the thing and be like, Oh, you want to get me a beer?
That's why Matt stopped allowing patrons with kilts into the restaurant.
I really got to keep my, keep up my laps around this Tierney's bar or else it would be glasses
of poop.
I did not get me beer for like three minutes.
So here you go, sonny, you got a pint of Guinness crap.
You got a pint of poop, a pint of poo, a pint of the old hot brown.
Enjoy it.
You'd have a woman who would come into the bar, typically on Sunday afternoons and she
loved the tastes of a bass beer, bass, yeah, best sale.
And but if she had too much beer, she would blow up the restroom, like blood, like just
destroy it.
Yeah.
Like hover and destroy, turn the women's bathroom into a super fun site.
Oh, somebody gave her her fifth get by sale.
I didn't realize she's about to crack that bathroom, like the Liberty bill.
And because she was, because she was a tiny, she cracked it like the Liberty bill.
How about them apples?
That is a spot on Boston accent ball.
That's right.
Whoa.
Look out for the grand Canyon known as your mama's twat.
What?
That's right.
That's a grand Canyon Scottish.
Yeah.
Are you Scottish?
I didn't know.
I don't know.
Scooping over girls, piffier.
So because she was a petite woman, it took us a very long time to tune two together.
This was happening because the Sunday day crowd didn't attract a lot of women.
So therefore we weren't going to the women's bathroom very often in the shift to check
things out.
Right.
And it took us.
It was a Pat, my buddy, Pat, who finally was figuring out this woman, if she had a second
beer with like shit herself, my question to you, man.
Here's my question to you.
So we all like feverish flashbacks, right?
Cause you know, someone finishes a beer, you go, you want another one or whatever.
And I always make fun of the fact that she would giggle back.
Oh really?
Oh, oh shoot.
Like always.
Like, uh, yes, I suppose.
Like she got really excited about getting that second beer like because she was playing
Russia roulette with her asshole.
Yes.
Look, as I was like, Oh my God, that explains why she was so fucking weird.
Every time I offered her a second beer.
That's really funny.
This is my question to you in your, in your theorizing, well, this is what I'm wondering.
Jacob is, what do you guys envision?
Are we thinking like a whoopee cushion type flapping action or are we talking like a hole
so tight it's like putting your thumb over the end of a garden hose, thus causing all
the crazy is that was she just really clenched back there and that was what caused everything
going crazy or was it all flippity flappity?
No, I think she's too loose.
I think you're, I think you're flippity flappity is flippity flappity.
All right.
She's flippity flappity.
There's no way she's going to make it home.
Right.
Well, I tell you what I'm going to start peeping on the girls drinking the bass ale at the
bars because I got the flippity flappity going on because you like that hot brown flippity
flappity.
Nobody tell Anne, she, she's like, yeah, Paul Mattingly will go to a bar any minute now.
That's really funny, man.
Yeah.
And then, and then that really explained her odd behavior.
Yes.
Did she ever cop to blowing up the bathroom?
How was she subtle enough?
Could you smell it on her when she got out?
You say it was, it went everywhere.
She was still pretty clean.
Did she, she did not come out looking like a girl.
I think she didn't come out like a poop scarecrow.
Yeah.
Can you imagine, she came out covered in shit and hay and she's just like, I don't know
what happened.
What happened in there?
I don't know what happened.
I got attacked.
Second bass ale.
I got attacked by someone dressed up like the wizard of Oz.
I believe she would leave after she fucked the bathroom up.
So, so you couldn't get a real good look.
It was, did anybody see any, did she ever like trail anything out of the restaurant?
Was there ever like a, it's not that I don't appreciate your questions, Paul.
He signed an NDA.
The answer to all these questions means we would have figured it out was her sooner than
we did.
It took us a while to decipher.
It doesn't necessarily, you wouldn't necessarily have been able to follow the trail.
I don't know.
I mean, if you look at the floor of Tierney's tavern, it's from the same floor, 1938.
She might have walked backwards to throw you off.
She might've done some weird tricky.
Gestured to things on the, on like the shelves and stuff, just pointing.
And then suddenly you look down and there's just, she was doing card tricks.
On her way out.
You couldn't look at her feet.
There's this thin stream going all the way from the bathroom and like, what the hell?
No.
I've heard of a snail trail, but this is ridiculous.
So we eventually kept the one beer rule that she would come in, we'd have a beer and then
we would just ignore her until she left.
I bet she was relieved in a lot of ways and then not relieved in some other ways.
She was more relieved after a second bass.
Oh, yeah.
We're like ass ale.
Am I right?
Exactly.
Ass ale.
Ass bail.
Move the be over.
I've been, uh, I've been doing searches while we've been talking because my Google search
history is not weird enough and apparently a lot of people complain about bass, uh, making
them shit themselves.
Apparently is not an uncommon, uh, critique of what has sale.
What is the diuretic in pass sale?
Well, all liquor is, is a bit of a diuretic.
Oh, really?
Professor Jacob do tell I just, that's, that's where, that's where you're suspicious of Jacob
science and say I just want to know more because apparently someone, I mean, I didn't have
to ask him anything.
He's just like right off the cuff.
He's like, Oh yes.
Well, it turns out that all liquor has certain medicinal properties that I did not use my
Boston accent cause the, they cause the flappity flappity to go very short and Brown yeast
and alcohol, alcohol increases your gut modally, uh, things move through you faster.
I don't know.
M O T I L I T Y modality, what's how that's M O T I L I T Y motility, motility.
Yeah.
Motility.
I guess.
Sure.
Motility.
Things move through you faster.
Motility to absorb water and that makes a looser, quicker bowel movements.
All right.
Well, if you're bound up like a cat in a cage, maybe have a bass.
They should start branding it that way.
Why don't they start branding it?
Why?
Big mouth, Billy bass.
Why is there not bass sale next to the prune juice in the old person's section at the store?
Why isn't there?
Yeah.
Probably because of liquor laws, but it's stupid.
Ah, okay.
Maybe they could put prune juice next to the bath sale in the liquor cabinet so people would
get the idea.
I'm also curious, like black.
It was black and tans, right?
That's where that's where like people do have no way to speak of her.
Half get us half bath sales, call the black and tan.
Oh, is that right?
Okay.
Yeah.
I thought for a second you were turning into an ice agent.
Go ahead.
Uh, oh my God.
Have you heard that song?
Oh yeah.
Uh, Jesse Elms.
Is that his name?
Yeah.
That's fucking great.
I've been following him on Tik Tok for a minute.
Really well-written.
On a lot of different social.
He has some really cutting song.
I guess his first album just came out.
He's blowing up.
Jesse Wells.
Oh, good for him.
He's so good.
Have you heard any of his stuff?
Jacob?
Yeah, I have.
I, I, I know him from social media.
Uh, yeah.
Folk singer.
Really, really strong.
Uh, poignant.
No, I didn't know he had an album.
That's really cool.
His joint.
His joint ice song is South park level scathing and well-written.
Yeah.
I did hear, I heard clips of this.
This was, it was amazing.
Yeah.
I'm, that's interesting.
That's an interesting thing to note, uh, Matt.
I would be surprised if he doesn't get, uh, tapped to put together some sort of musical.
Yeah.
I mean, uh, yeah.
He's really good.
You say right for South park, it's like, which is not the gift that you think.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
Put together his own musical.
I've talked to anyone who's ever.
Yeah.
I just think it's a fun fact for people to know is if you ever listen to anyone who's
ever been tapped by South park to be a writer, it is a brutal, uh, crazy ass process to be
unless you're, unless you're a hater, right?
He had, he's the only one that had fun with it.
Yeah.
But he'd already made his bones so he didn't have to sweat it.
He was already bill hater.
Yeah.
Um, uh, but yeah, anyhow, sorry, I got distracted cause I heard it this morning and I was just
was like, my jaw was on the floor.
I was like, good Lord, this song.
So a black and tan.
Yes.
You think that would be a proper diuretic remedy?
Um, it would, it would, it would slow things down, right?
Cause the poor, uh, I don't think stout has the same effect.
Oh, oh, so it's like, no, I'm saying, no, I don't even know what mortality means.
So maybe I shouldn't be saying what it's like going to Chili's.
I down a fifth of Pepto Bismol before I eat my triple dipper.
So it all kind of works out in the wash.
I got you.
That's why he is a motherfucking professional.
I mean, yeah.
Pre Pepto.
I call it my Pepto talk.
I've given my system the Pepto talk.
I guess, Oh, what I was going to get at is that like, I don't go to bars nearly as often,
but I don't even think that I don't, I don't think bass is still on tap at Tierney's.
I haven't, what was the last time I've seen bass on tap anywhere is what I was trying
to think of his bass.
He'll still like a bass around very, very often.
I think, I think it's, I think it's a, I think it's an old,
I think it's gone the way of the, does it have, does it have fish in it?
Fish.
Yeah.
Fish oil.
That's what really gets it going.
It's the fish oil.
Yeah.
What do they call it?
Omega three and Omega six fats and the, and the bass omega three fatties.
That was your nickname for that, that crazy shitter lady.
That's the name of this mega three fatty.
If Jacob would put on a few LBs, we could be an omega three fatty.
I'm sorry.
God damn it.
I'm trying.
Omega three fatty?
I had dinner.
We're the alpha three fatty.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
Who are we kidding?
We're the beta three fatties.
We're the beta three family.
Speaking of betas, let's do a little jock versus nerd.
And the beta three fatties, ladies and gentlemen, it is time, beta three fatties, time for jock
versus nerd.
Explosion.
A very slippery poop.
We got a scooperty coming to us today from Keister Sunday.
Ah, Keister Sunday.
Thank you.
Been a minute.
Yeah, this is a, uh, uh, uh, what's the, what's the thing?
The, uh, the, uh, the second movie sequel.
That's the movie where I can't think of.
This is the sequel to Keister Sunday's last scooperty.
Keister Sunday says, like most sequels, uh, less work was put into it.
The categories are more eighties comedy, more eighties horror, more eighties action and more
eighties sci-fi.
Matt, you're up first.
What you want?
Um, I will do action please for 200 about that action.
I'm too old for this shit.
Name that film.
Uh, it's not, I'm getting too old for this shit.
I saw I'm too old for this.
Right.
I thought it was, I'm getting too old for this shit, but it might be, I'm too old for
this shit.
Uh, it's a, a, a lethal weapon.
Yeah.
Lethal weapon is correct.
I will take sci-fi for 800.
Let's go.
Ooh.
Yeah.
It may be a case of being too ambitious for a single movie, which is why the recent adaptation
is multiple films.
But this 1984 sci-fi epic is the only movie David Lynch regretted making for he is the
quits.
It is back, it is Dune Arrakis, my Dune, man.
I tell you, those are becoming my favorite bedtime flicks.
I throw them on.
Yeah.
That'll put your right to bed.
I mean it.
No, it's great.
I love playing them in the background, but they're really, I love those movies though.
I got them on the blue ray.
I love the new ones are the old ones, the new ones.
Are you watching, uh, alien earth?
I watched the first like four episodes.
It kind of, it kind of faded for me.
It started really strong.
I still like it.
Are you, did you, are you in?
Yeah.
It took me a while to get through the first episode that I really like the second and
third episode.
And that's where I am app up to is I still enjoy a lot of the concepts that are going
on with it.
I wasn't a watch it, except I found out the guy behind it's the guy behind all the Fargo
uh, uh, series shows.
Okay.
I haven't watched any of the Fargo shows.
So,
Oh, those are great.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, let's see.
I'll try.
Um, uh, 80s comedy, 200 Lloyd bridges picked the wrong week to quit drinking, doing amphetamines
and sniffing glue.
He sure did.
He did that on airplane.
Yep.
Yeah.
Nice.
Matt.
Uh, I'll go back to action, please.
Back to action.
Donnelly for 400 daily doubles, all of it, Jacob.
I want to bet all of it.
I feel the need, the need for speed tally day and night.
My Coke head Vegas bachelor party.
Yeah.
Um, uh, that is top top gun.
That is top top gun is correct.
I would have messed that up.
What did you think it was?
I really thought it was, uh, days of thunder.
Oh, there you go.
There you go.
Paul, you're up.
Uh, sci fi, please.
For six.
For 600.
Yeah.
This 1982 Disney date load classic starring the dude is way more boring than you remember.
Boo.
Tron.
Tron is correct.
I love Tron.
That's a nice one to go to sleep to too.
That is another good one.
It's a good, but it's such a good movie.
It's so beautiful.
I feel like it's not the phrase you think it is.
The filmmakers don't want to hear that.
That's for sure.
I love Tron.
I know.
I hear that.
I hear people say, but I, but to me there's, that's a high level of praise that I fall
asleep to your movie because it means it's my, it's a comfort movie for me and I've watched
it a lot.
So anyway.
All right.
I'm telling you, it doesn't sound good.
I realize you're right.
I know that you're right.
I could have killed them all.
I could have killed you in town.
You're the law out here.
It's me.
Don't push it.
Or I'll give you a war.
You won't believe this.
Was that a, was that a truth social tweet?
What?
I believe this is, uh, first blood.
First blood is my answer.
Oh, good.
Good job, Jacob.
Yeah, don't ask me Rambo questions.
I will answer them.
Matt.
Johnny Rambo.
I do declare, uh, eighties action 800 please.
You cold blooded bastard.
I'll tell you what I think of it.
I live to see you eat that contract, but I hope you leave enough room for my fist because
I'm going to ram it into your stomach and break your goddamn spine.
It's mommy dearest.
Isn't it?
This is, uh, this is just from succession.
I actually, I actually know this one.
Am I right that Arnold Schwarzenegger is saying this?
You got it.
That was, I was going to, I was going to read it in that voice because that's how it goes.
That's how it gets.
I hope you leave enough room for my fist because I'm going to ram it in your stomach and break
your goddamn spine.
I said, break your goddamn spine.
I remember being such an awkward for them spine.
Yeah.
Now the thing is, I'd still don't know what movie this is, but the contract makes me think
it's running man scooper Nova girl is saying twins.
I think that's a good guess.
No, I think, I think you're dead on a running man is my guest, Jacob running man is I'm
sorry, Matt.
It's the running man.
Damn it.
Running man.
I'm sorry.
They're remaking the running man.
It's already out and flopped, dude.
It's already, it already came out and made no money.
No, no, Paul.
I hear they're remaking it.
Man.
You say so.
Maybe the third time's a charm.
They're already making, remaking the Glenn Powell version of running man.
I'll keep at the, the sci-fi please for 400.
All right.
Daily double.
Now comes the big windfall daddy.
My name is Jacob in this fun eighties romp Cardinal Blick from dogma guides Neo and one
of the lost boys to passing their history exam and creating world peace through the
power of rock music.
Bill and Ted's excellent adventure.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's bogus journey.
I'm sorry.
It's bogus journey is what it's the first one bogus journey involves death adventure.
That's true.
Yeah.
And even a raps, um, I'll do, um, eighties comedy 400 a year before killing those people
in Ireland.
Abe Froman sausage King of Chicago is guilty of truancy, but don't worry.
All around swell human being, uh, Jeffrey Jones is on the case.
Oh my God.
That question.
I am so confused by that question.
Oh, I think I, I think I even get the, no, I get the references.
I don't even know what it's talking about here before killing those people in Ireland.
Abe Froman sausage King of Chicago is guilty of truancy, but don't worry.
All around swell human being.
Jeffrey Jones is on the case.
So do you know who Jeffrey Jones is?
That's the, that's the part that I'm missing.
I think I got to pass Matt.
Oh, uh, so this is all Matthew Broderick, uh, the movie is Ferris Bueller's day off
and a year before King all those people in Ireland is Matthew Broderick when he was an
actor, uh, killed a bunch of people in Ireland and they basically paid off and covered up
the case.
Uh, he plays, he said he lies and says he's a Roman sausage of Chicago.
That's his alias in that.
That's right.
And Jeffrey Jones, I think, uh, Cameron is the one that provides the voice for Abe Froman.
Oh, I think you're right.
And then who is Jeffrey Jones is the guy that kicked out of the, he's plays the principal.
He's the one who kicked out the Beatles movie because he, he's a child.
Yeah.
There you go.
Ferris Bueller's day off.
That's correct.
Matt and, uh, Matt, it's your turn.
Uh, eighties comedy 600 please.
The director of the smash hit dark shadows also made this little known film in the eighties
starring Batman, Thelma and Stephen Baldwin's less talented brother.
Uh, so that's Michael Keaton, uh, uh, Michael Keaton, Alec Baldwin and, uh, who plays Ferris
Bueller.
But I got this one.
Well, I mean, you just talked about it, man.
The movie.
Yeah.
Essentially.
Well, there's an, you talked about.
Yeah.
You talked about it.
Okay.
Uh, Oh, this is Beetlejuice.
There you go.
It's Beetlejuice.
Now I get it.
Paul, I'll do horror for 800 and the sequels to this entirely unproblematic 80 slasher
movie.
The boss's sister plays a mentally deranged slash abused camp counselor obsessed with spreading
summer camp spirit with murder.
For some reason, James Earl Jones's dad was in the first one.
Oh, uh, huh.
Uh, the sequels.
Oh, uh, I think this is a sleepaway camp.
All right.
It's sleepaway camp.
Wow.
Got there.
Oh, it's me.
I'll try.
I'll close out comedy 800 Woody, Princess Leia and rock and roll megastar Corey Feldman
suspect their new neighbors, brother Theodore and his family of killing Mr. Moody.
That's the fucking burbs y'all.
Yeah, it is.
That was a weird one.
The weird one.
How dare you?
I never liked the burbs.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I like the burbs.
Tom Hanks.
Fine.
Enjoy the burbs.
Thank you, Paul.
Also, I never put the burbs in my mouth.
Not all the way.
I would.
You would bring it up.
I would need to get all of the leftover questions to beat Paul.
Oh yeah.
Paul has 3600, Matt has 2400, I have 1600 and there are no more daily doubles left.
There are four questions left.
Just try it.
That's a grand total of 1400 points total.
Yeah.
And I'm down by 1200 to Paul.
So I will do I will do 600 or Rodney Dangerfield son and back to school plays a bullied teen
who falls in actual love with his 58 Plymouth Fury in this carpenter classic is a good flick.
God, Christine, Christine.
That's it.
I'm sitting over here in my head going like Nadine, Charlene, Christine, Christine, Christine,
Christine.
Please don't put unleaded in my tank.
What's the what's the what's the I could be like, Carrie is not Carrie.
Carrie is not Carrie.
That's what my brain was doing.
That's that's a good loop.
It's still not Carrie.
It's definitely not Carrie.
I'm on it.
There's a lady with a C name.
That's right.
What'd you say about my mom?
I said she's like the Grand Canyon.
I crack.
I like the Liberty Belle 80s or for 400.
All right.
In this film directed by the author of the novella, it's adapting a fun melanin challenged
fella just wants to share the joy of playing with his Rubik's Cube.
I kind of want.
Wait, this is horror.
Yes, that is the question that you.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
This would be, uh, I think it's a good one.
I think it's a good one.
It wasn't a nightmare.
It's all happening for real.
For real.
I am for real.
On this road that I live on.
Never meant to kill you in your dreams.
I am sorry for your terrible screams.
Ah, Matt, that's your question.
Oh, it's me.
Oh, Nightmare on Elm Street.
Sorry.
There you go.
Nightmare on Elm Street.
It is a Nightmare on Elm Street.
I thought it was yours.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no worries.
No, it was the last one.
That is the game.
Paul wins with 4,000.
Matt is in second with 3,200.
I'm in third with 1,800.
And that's from Keester Sunday.
Thank you, Keester Sunday.
Keester Sunday.
Thank you.
If you want to send us in a Scoopery or a Price of Skryte Jock vs. Nerd or an Obelisk
Jock vs. Nerd or some Scoop Mail, you can do all those things right over there at heyscoops.com.
Go over there.
It's on the home page.
It's Jock vs. Nerd, send us some Scoop Mail.
We love to hear from you.
We need to hear from you.
It's part of the whole show.
I was basically lost in trying to find how to say the Kevin Spacey thing and not leave
a curiosity and worse things happening going to a future episode.
On the one hand, he was acquitted of everything.
He was never convicted.
He had one conviction in a foreign court that was overturned.
And on the other hand, you're not entitled to be a movie star.
Being a working actor is one thing.
Being a star involves affection and you can lose affection, right?
And there are many people who have had their career take a downturn for less controversial
reasons who simply can't be actors anymore, right?
So the idea that Kevin Smith, Kevin Spacey, let's not mix those two up.
The idea that Kevin Spacey is homeless to me just simply says he's not willing to work
at any other job.
You can do other things besides act and make money.
Do something else.
Yeah, he's getting what he deserves.
What a joke.
I don't believe that he is destitute or anything like that, so I just don't care about the
story at all.
It also means like, did you do nothing with your money while you were making all that
money?
Including just putting it in a mattress or something, nothing?
Like Shaq owns like 400 Annie Anne pretzels.
Like get yourself a franchise, buddy.
He has a pizza named after him.
Get some Buffalo Wild Wings going.
Yeah.
Shaq Arone.
We could be eating Space Arone pizza right now.
We're wondering what it's named for.
We don't remember.
Why aren't we taking the streets yet?
There's a trillionaire.
Oh, no, no, it's still raining.
It is still raining.
That is a fine point.
Scoop Jesus with a very slick investment opportunity.
He could have invested in storage units, called it Kevin Spacey's.
You're right.
He did miss that one.
I want to thank JD for coming on the podcast.
Go check it out.
Go fund me.
And for putting together the documentary.
Yeah.
The link is in the episode notes, and I want to thank all the people who support us over
on Patreon.
In fact, I have a list of them right now, and all these people could do something else
besides try to revive House of Cards on Netflix.
That's gross.
Is he even trying that really gross?
Dole Whip Scoop, Dippin' Dots Jack, Dirty Old Scoop, Distiller Scoop, Doc Scoop, Don
Dottie, Don't Say Scoop Name, Doug Lay, Dr. Science Scoop, Dr. Scoop Little, Dr. Tobias
Scoopay, Duck Flambe, Duck Scoop, Duane Webb, Ed Short Arms, Marcus, Ed Ondrick, Ed Wagner,
and Ed Les Scoop.
The following people go off like those dog fireworks that you lighten their ass poops
out a thing as soon as you get them that fourth baths ale.
Gene Zink, Genetic Scoop, George Guskov, Gerardo Garcia, Gizmo Scoop, Greater Sunday Scoop,
Gravel Scoop, Green Wolf Scoop, Grill Sergeant Scoops, Guy Wade, Gwarthok, Hatchet Scoop,
Heather Divine Hanson, Holly Marshmello Lightly, House Dad Scoop, Hillean Scoop, I Don't Have
a Scoop Name, Ian A. Chapman, Ian Soto, Ice Cream Manwich, Ice Blue Scoop, I Want a Scoop
Baby, Jacob Dinklaker, and Jake Schneider.
The following people all can't wait to go to the Lincoln Memorial in Boston.
Edward Bender, Eliza Walczak, Elkton Magic Scoop, Eric Nielsen, Erotic Scrape Scoop,
Evil Monkey, Fade Out Scoop, Fifi, Finn Steffensen, Flat Kiddy, Frankie's Tiki Scoop, Freehold
Scoop, Freeze Dried Scoop, Frozen 49th Scoop, Frozen Cusser, Fudgie the Whale, Galoosha
Scoop, Galactic Presence Starman Scoopsalot, Galen Diggs, Garrett Godfrey, Gas Man Scoop,
Caspacho Scoop, Gelato Problems, Gelato Steve, and of course, Bossy the Portuguese Scoop,
because he's here in the chat and probably didn't get thanked another time.
There you go.
Well done.
Well, good catch on that one.
These individuals are about to get cracked like the Liberty Bell.
James Dawson, James Fox, James Hubbell, Jameson Fisher, Janine Lankard, Jason Klepper, Jason
Acostas, Jason Speckland, Jason Street, Jason Vazquez, Jason Victor, Jason Janowitz, Jay
Shapiro, Jed Taxon, Jeff Bezare, Jeff Faust, Jeff Harris, and Jeff Libby.
And the following scoops looked a little too closely into my sister's tea harbor.
That's Jeff Loomis, Ginny Ebarb, Jeremy Hudson, Jesse Rain, Jill Short, Jimmy Sloanina, John
Carter, John Lohr, John Hulshan, John Jacob, Scoopenheimer Schmidt, Johnny Parker, Jonathan,
Jordan Campbell, Joseph Foster, Joseph Pilaro, Josh Katona, Josh Roberts, Joshua Tarr, Joshua
Wilson, J Rock Scoop, Juan Galvez, Judy Schneider, Justin Robert Young, Kay Mathis, Keester Sunday,
Keith Robert Corning Scoop, Kelsey Conderry, Ken Fargey, Ken Soto, Kevin Chamberlain, Kevin
Dory, Kimchey Douche Scoop, King Scoop, Kiwi Fruit Scoop, Colin Townie, Kristen Claddock,
Kurt Egner, Kurt Henderson, L.A.J., Lance Amon, Larry Goodale, and Latter-day Scoop.
Thank you all so much.
We sure do appreciate you.
Thank you.
Thank you all so much.
If you want to hear your name read on air or receive a bunch of other kinds of prizes
and rewards, head on over to preachingfun.com and select a tier that works for you.
Or if you too are looking forward to a Hey Scoops documentary just to help you explain
what all this is to other people, head over to fartsinabag.biz.
That along with preachingfun.com takes you over to our Patreon page where for as little
as $3 you can help keep this show on the air.
This show is dependent on our Patreon supporters.
So if you think this show is worth more than $0, preachingfun.com, fartsinabag.biz, those
are the places to go.
Also, of course, you can always help us out by going to our shop.
That's over there at heyscoops.com/shop.
How do you get there?
And that's part of our billionaire plan because the percentage we get from our shop, we just
need to sell a billion t-shirts and we'll become a billionaire.
Hey, you know, I've been getting inundated with T-Fury discount stuff.
They're having sales.
They're having sales constantly.
So now is the time during this holiday.
Come on there, get go through, please go through our shop storefront.
And even if you don't buy any of our merch, we get to wet our beak a little bit.
And we really appreciate that.
Heyscoops.com/shop or storejingle.com.
Also the Patreon has now made it easier to give subscriptions as gifts.
So if you don't know what to ask for, for Christmas, people are like, what do you want
for Christmas?
And you're like, I don't know.
You can give a Patreon subscription to our show as an idea for one of your gifts that
you'd like.
There you go.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
And if you're at the $10 a month level or more, you get to come and hang out with us
on an unrecorded zoom hang.
The next one, this month's one is happening next Wednesday, the day before Thanksgiving,
believe it or don't it happening.
My time.
7pm.
Yes.
The, the time when the, the line between the worlds is at its thinnest.
So because, because on Thanksgiving you get fat, thin goes out the window.
You know, we can join you in that chat now, Sarah Fowler-Wolf, who just upped her Patreon
pledge to the $10 tier.
Fantastic.
Shout out to that person.
So the invite has already gone out for those of you who subscribe to the Patreon.
Look, check your emails, check your papers for openings, check your openings for papers.
It is in there.
You can grab onto that link and jump in on Wednesday at 7pm my time, 4pm Vegas time and
come on by.
It's going to be a hootenanny.
We're going to just chill and talk.
Hootenanny.
Well, I'll probably, I'll probably bust out some toys.
We'll see what's going on.
I think that's my plan is maybe just build some, some Lego or something.
I don't know.
Nothing too.
Nothing too heavy.
We're just going to talk.
We're just going to hang out and chat and you know, no big whoop.
No big whoop.
Just very heavy.
It'll be very heavy, but it's going to be a lot of fun.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fun, not guaranteed.
All right.
Well, thanks for everybody.
Stay safe out there.
We love you and we'll see you soon.
Hey, Scoot, the movie.
Don't fund me.
Let's make some magic, y'all.
Rachel Mutt.
Thanks for watching.
We love you.
See ya! Bye!