Oh, hello there. I am so glad you are here, because I want to thank you, the Ice Cream
Truck Drivers. Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers. Right now, I'd like to thank
Bearded Scoop 3, Blue Line Scoop, Chasing the Dragon Scoop, Christine Elsesser, Christy
Salinas, Darren Cunningham, Darth Scooper, David Walker, Dead Lazlo, Dirty Old Scoop,
and Dr. Scoop Little. If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, just like these five
fine folks, head over to PreachingFun.com. PreachingFun.com is where you can go to sign
up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows, maybe the life you save, wait, the life
you save may be your own. Nailed it. Here's the show.
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to. Great. Let's go.
A man was arrested in New Jersey recently. Here come the Hawks. Get your tickets today,
and get in on the excitement that is filling the United Center.
Hawks win. Visit BlackHawks.com/tickets before it's too late.
For a road rage where he shot a woman in the face. She's fine, but he shot her in the face.
He's fine. Yep. It's time for Matt Maddly's Ice Cream
Social. Sitting over there with a confused look on his face. That's Paul Maddly. Sitting
over there with an understanding look on his face. That's Matt Maddly. We're PreachingFun.
I just saw this. Apparently, he's a Sopranos guy, a couple of others.
He's a bit actor. His role on The Sopranos, his character name on The Sopranos was Thief.
Oh. Yeah, yeah. He's a Sopranos actor the same way that the guy who walked in the back
of the scene is a Sopranos actor. Right, but to say she got shot in the face
and is okay, that's not right either. It apparently grazed her nose. It hit her in the nose, but
it went across her nose. So she went to the hospital and everything, but she was not in
any full recovery. I believe so. I don't believe there was any life threatening injury.
It was a flesh wound, as they say. Yeah, but he is facing 31 counts in connection
with the violent rampage, including first degree attempted murder and aggravated assault
with a deadly weapon. Apparently, they were both trying to get into the same lane at the
same time. She absolutely had the right of way. Yeah, right.
She got just enraged and shot a gun out of the window of his car, which just goes to
show you how advanced Matt Donnelly is for a New Jersey driver. Man, just calm, mellow.
The amount of people that'd be surprised if my death or someone else's death involved
my road rage would be zero people, zero. It would be sad, just not surprised.
Not surprised. I'd say it's the one benefit probably, I don't know if it's even a benefit
of the surveillance state that we live in, is that they're going to have plenty of footage
of this from the cameras everywhere. I got into an Uber the other day and the Uber driver
pointed out the inside and outside cameras to me as I got in and he definitely was doing
it in a way to be like, "I've had trouble in here before. Here are the cameras. Please
don't be an asshole." I'm a Las Vegas local. I'm just going to my house. He was like, "Oh,
thank God." Please ignore the hair. Oh boy, what a hassle.
Well, I'll pile on the bad, sad. I don't know if you guys heard about this. Noted YouTube
vlogger Adam the Woo passed away. Oh goodness. I did not. What was he known for?
He was known for Disney parks reviews and haunted attraction reviews. He did a daily
blog, daily vlog. He was good friends with a lot of other creators that I'm interested
in like Jacob the Carpet Bagger and a couple other people. He went to all kinds of theme
parks and stuff. He even did Paris Disney recently. He was very prolific with his work
and just apparently natural causes, almost exact same age as me, bit the dust. Really
a heartbreaker. Yeah, everybody's really sad about it. It's one of those deaths that makes
me look at it. You look at the breadth of his creative output and you look at the reactions
from the creator community as well as the fans and you see a person who lived their
life well. You see nice results from their life.
Negative thing to be said. Yeah. If anything, lots of positive things. Fan interactions,
people. He treated everyone very kindly, remembered people. He would go to many of these fan events
over and over again, these horror nights and horror conventions. He would see people who
go to the horror convention regularly and he could recognize them in costume and stuff
like that. Seems to have been a general all around good guy.
Good news though, Paul. I've looked him up here. He's actually going to be now haunting
the Disney parks so people will be able to do his style of show now about him. It's the
circle of life. There you go. Well, they are suggesting that
he be buried or at least have the funeral ceremony somewhere near the Disney parks.
That was his favoritest thing. Who knows? Disney don't get into that shit. Disney is
like, if you want to do that somewhere on private property and say that it's close to
our place, that's fine. If you want to do that shit on our property, you can go fuck
yourself. You know how many times they've had to clean
up human remains out of the haunted mansion. Oh yeah. I think that's the entire reason
that they don't want to fuck with any of it. Bring their cremated loved ones and dump
them in the dune buggies. Please don't do that. It's the public service announcement
for the 19 year old that has to clean up your loved one's remains. Please don't dump their
ashes on the haunted mansion ride. It's a ride.
We are advocates of the Throshen option. Throshen is the best.
Throshen is out there. It's the most environmentally clean option
if you're not a fish. People keep suggesting that Throshen be the best option for the current
resident of the White House as otherwise talk about clean up services being required.
No, I'm sure it's all fine. Well, regardless, yeah, just tragic. You know,
the other side too, when I would go to Kings Island as a kid, this was still rural Ohio
back in the day. It's been somewhat more developed as it goes along, but it was still country-ish.
Yeah. And there was a tiny graveyard just outside
of Kings Island. As you were walking towards the front gates and even in the parking area,
you could see a small graveyard. These were the people that died on the beast.
I don't know who exactly, I should look it up. It's a known thing. It's a bunch of gravestones
and grave markers right outside of Kings Island. Okay.
And I always thought what a great place to be buried because I loved Kings Island so
much as a kid. And even as we know, Annie is a listener of the podcast. So take some
notes here. Maybe it's a little arrogant to assume that
Annie will outlive you, but I don't know if it's very arrogant to assume Annie will outlive
you. I would just have to, oh no, Anne's already
got us grave plots secured. Did she have one for both of you or just
you? No, two of us.
She's not going to bury you at Kings Island then?
She's not going to bury me at Kings Island, but I've told her I don't want to burial.
I'm going to get cremated and then whatever. I don't know why I was calling her Annie.
I was calling her Annie because we're reading on an email from our Annie.
We're thinking about Annie. Yeah.
Anne, I think Anne should take note that you want to be buried at Kings Island.
She knows. The cemetery outside of Kings Island, known
as the Dog Street Cemetery, is a historic but forgotten burial ground.
Not forgotten. We're talking about it right now.
Well, the people who are in it. No, people don't know I guess the people who are in it.
I think it's the dead people who have been forgotten about that.
Oh, got it. Got it. Got it.
So are the graves unmarked in that way, at least?
They're marked, but they're marked with things like Missouri Jane.
Ah, okay. Yeah. And it still sits quietly within the
park's property near the main entrance. Yep.
Yeah. No, you'd walk by it every time. Oh, and apparently it was, the cemetery itself
was forgotten about and was rediscovered in the 1890s.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah, you can't miss it.
They found an overgrown cemetery that had been reclaimed by the woods and everything
in the 1890s. Yeah, you can't miss it when you're going
into Kings Island. It's kind of a nice little memento mori, you know, it's like, because
not everybody survives the bat. Not everybody makes it off Top Gun.
Yeah. Lindsay and Chad says, go ahead and dump me in the Haunted Mansion. Don't cremate
me. Just weekend at Bernie's meet through the park.
Just remains, not cremated remains, just remains.
What would be the legality and what would be? It's not. It's not legal.
No, but hear me out now. Hear me out. I believe it falls under an illegal dumping
statute. No, okay. Yeah. I'm not talking Disney anymore.
Let's get away from the Disney affiliation. How much would it take? What kind of legal
red tape, given that we are in the Wild West again, as far as if you've got the money,
you can do the thing. This has probably been done. Now that I'm saying it, this has probably
been done, but you could have people who are horror fans volunteer to have their corpse
is utilized in a haunted attraction and you just go through on a little scooter and see
rotting dead people, maybe put some animatronics in them, maybe make them jiggle around a little
bit. This next body is actually Zach Baggins. He
founded this museum back in the 2000s. Right. I mean, if Scoop Jesus is talking about how
bad it would stink. Yes, Scoop Jesus. Yes, it would stink.
If Epstein was as enthusiastic about haunted houses as he was about child rape, then it
would have already happened. It would have already been happening. It would have been
already a feature of his island. To be fair, we don't know for sure that it's
not unless... Oh, Matt, have you been to the island, Matt? Are you at the island right
now? I'm glad we're recording on a Tuesday because
you do not want to record with me on Thursday. I'll tell you that much right now. And those
files come out. Just one very small haunted hole on Jeffrey Island.
Just a small haunted hole. He calls it his boo cave. He does. Don't go to the boo cave.
That's worse than the tickle house, y'all. Stay the fuck out of the boo cave on Epstein
Island. The haunted hole.
I figured out how to get Trump's name off of the Kennedy Center. Have I told you about
this? Oh, no. How you do it? All you have to do is show up with an even larger Donald
J. Trump sign. And so when you go to take the one off, they'll go, "Hey, you're not
supposed to take that off." You go, "No, no, no. The president said his name wasn't big
enough." And then that'll allow you to get it off because everyone will believe you that
he wants a bigger name. Oh, that is true.
Yeah. Yeah. That's true.
So just do it that way. If Vandals showed up with a giant Donald J. Trump sign, I mean,
no, no, we're going to put this one on after we take this one off.
That's it. And then you're going to clear. Everybody would leave you alone. Yeah. This
is the ultimate wearing blacks and carrying a ladder.
See you tomorrow. Yeah. Right. And then boom. I look forward to seeing this new, enormous
Donald Trump sign tomorrow when I do my rounds. Oh, that security guard is going to be embarrassed.
But he'll say, "They said they're going to put a bigger sign up." And everybody's like,
"Oh, makes sense, Terry. So sorry, buddy." Oh, I would have fallen for it too, Terry.
That would have gotten me. That really sucks. And they were in like coveralls. Oh, yeah,
yeah. No, they were wearing coveralls. In hindsight, they definitely got those at Walmart.
But they were, they looked really official. They had a wagon, a big wagon, a ladder.
He said he was a big fan of that Kirk guy. I figured that he was okay. What was it? Our
friend, Miss Zula pointed out that the Arizona Cardinals haven't won a game there since they
did the Charlie Kirk Memorial. Yeah. That's, I mean, they've won away games, but not games.
It's a unique way to look at it. The Cardinals aren't very good at football. So it's not
the hardest thing to, you know, stretch the truth on. That's it. Yeah. Jacob. Yes, Paul.
I saw that you had an actual vacation. I mean, in the sense that we went places out of town,
it was a vacation. Oh, heavens, what happened? In the sense that it was relaxing in any way
at all. It was not. Oh no. It wasn't bad. It was just so fast paced. We went down south.
We went all over the place. We flew into Austin, Texas. There was your first mistake. Yeah,
exactly. Saw some of SJ's family outside of Austin, went further east in Texas and saw
some more of her family and then drove to Louisiana and saw some of my family. And then
we flew out of Jackson, Mississippi. So we did Texas, Louisiana and Mississippi. Oh,
goodness sakes. That's a lot. And I think we did it in four nights, five days. No, no,
no. That's okay. So, but we saw the whole family. We had Christmas every day in a new
location with the kids and the family members in that location. So it was really nice. It
was a really nice trip. We were just fucking exhausted. Yeah. And one of the more embarrassing
things that I've had to do happened on the flight back as well. Oh no. And that was situational
awareness territory. No, no, no, no. Thank goodness. That is not where I'm going. All
of my pants are fine. All of my clothing is not in the garbage. So we had a layover in
Nashville and the Nashville airport. If you've never been through that Nashville airport,
it's really cool. They have a bunch of live music stations set up all over the place.
Like in the gates and everything, they'll just have little stages ready for somebody
with a guitar to sit there and sing some stuff into the microphone there. It's really nice.
And so we were hanging out. They have an Ole Red, an Ole Red in the Nashville airport there.
So we said, Oh, we'll go get some dinner in Ole Red. We'll sit there and we'll listen
to some music before we get on the flight back to old hometown Vegas. And so we're sitting
there at the bar in the restaurant and we're listening to the live music. It's really good.
We're talking to the bartender. Everybody's really nice. And this fella comes and sits
down at the bar stool next to me. He asks if anybody's sitting there. I say, nope. And
that is the extent of our interaction. I said, no, no, it's all you. I had a bag that was
kind of in the way, so I moved from a bag. I said, no problem. You enjoy it. And then
we sat there and we did not interact anymore for about an hour. And then he turned to me
and goes, so you're a podcaster, huh? Yeah, I am. Yeah, that's right. And now I'm sitting
there racking my brain. Did SJ and I say anything? Like have we been talking about the podcast?
I don't think we have. I don't think we've mentioned anything about any of it. Turns
out he thought I was a different podcaster and just asked me if I was a podcaster and
I said, yes. And then he realized that he was talking about a different person entirely
that he thought that I was. There's a couple of us now. He thought that I was a Theo Vaughn.
Get the fuck out of here. I mean, I can see it. This man believed that I was a podcaster,
Theo Vaughn. Hilarious. At which point I had to explain to him that I was not Theo Vaughn,
just a different middle-aged white guy with a podcast. Right. Yeah. Did you give him a
chip? Because that solves it all, Jacob. I didn't have a chip. I didn't have any bags
with me, so I did not have a chip. But I believe that he is a new scoop now. We did chat. We
had a real nice chat. I hope so. Well, I think he said his name was Dave. So shout out Dave
from Old Red at the Nashville airport. I keep two chips in my wallet at all times as last
minute. I don't carry a wallet. What the fuck is going on? I have like the little card holder
that I keep in my front pocket, and that's it. I keep a little cash rolled up in it.
Well, you wear jeans, right, with the little front lippity upper pocket? I do. I suppose
I wear pants with a little lippity upper pocket. A chip fits perfectly in the lippity upper
pocket. Two is great, too. So I would just suggest tuck one in between cheek and gum
for emergency situations. Well, good. I hope we did get an obelisk off of that. I think
I'm over the course of an hour. Obelished one person. Great. It's not an efficient system
that we're not. We're not an efficient system. I'll tell you who else does not have a very
efficient system that they run on. And somehow they also base their entire business model
off of it as well. And that is the following sponsor. Today's show, man. Manley's ice cream
social is brought to you by the wearable blanket, a blanket with sleeves so you can nap better
on your couch. That's from Smitty Scoop in twenty twenty five. Hey, everybody, it's me,
Captain Crunch. I'm here to advertise a wearable blanket. I don't know what I like. I like
a blanket with sleeves. It lets me eat my cereal and warmth and contentment and keeps
me away from the soggies. Those motherfuckers are always ruining my fucking cereal. God
damn it. Eat my own asshole all the way, you soggy fucks. Now you can't get to me because
I've got a wearable blanket on. And if I drop my milk on me, it doesn't matter. The soggies
can't get me. You know, the horrible thing about my existence is I can't live without
the soggies. I need my milk on my cereal, but I hate them and they try to destroy me
and my product at every turn. But they're a necessary evil if I want to have my cereal
eaten. Oh, boy. Look, catch twenty two. Fuck these bastards. I hate them all. I catch them
on the open seas. It's on international waters. I got love to see on my side, bitches. And
that was how Captain Crunch became a pirate. Look at me, soggies. I'm a captain now. That's
Captain with an apostrophe in. SJ had a show at the Silverton the other day. We had a fun
Taylor Swift show the other night. Oh, nice. And a big free show. They did it as part of
the rodeo. And boy, was it fun watching all these little kids up there dancing around.
It was so good. I was exhausted by the end of it. Just run around talking to people,
just kind of socially exhausted by the end of it. Sure. Walk through Silverton. There
was a Johnny Rockets. Oh, yeah. Motherfucker. Did you want a chocolate shake? That's exactly
like Johnny Rockets. A Johnny Rockets shake. I'm gonna go get me a Johnny Rockets shake.
I'll go up to the Johnny Rockets counter and say I would like one chocolate shake to go
please because everybody else was going over to a restaurant to go meet up after. I said
I'm gonna go. I'm gonna show up with a chocolate shake. I'm not eating anything. I'll have
some beverages in my chocolate shake. This is gonna be great. And the guy at the counter
told me how much the shake was. And he said it was $13.22. What? $13.22. Where was this?
The Johnny Rockets. Yes. In the Silverton casino. Oh, my god damn. I mean, McDonald's
shakes are $5 now, so. I exclaimed for a moment and said, you know, that is a very expensive
chocolate shake. And then he handed it to me and I took a sip of it. I know that is
very good. I don't know if it's $13 good though. He said, well, he goes, it doesn't matter.
You already paid for it. Oh, Jesus. And I said what? He goes, you instantly tapped your
phone on the thing because I was standing there thinking that I hadn't paid for it yet.
And I had just completely spaced and without meaning to had just like tapped my phone on
the little card reader and be like, yep, there we go. You had a very, I was still complaining
about the price having already paid for it. A very pulp fiction moment there. Yeah. Yeah.
And that was the $5 milkshake where everybody's like, what the fuck? $5. It was five at Jack
Rabbit slims. Holy shit. $5. That's outrageous. Yeah. Well, you know, the, you know, being
able to like bring the dairy cows in Montana down because of drought now and stuff like
that, you know, milkshakes have gotten very expensive. Well, that's the fucked up thing
within our lifetime. It ain't getting cheaper for a milkshake. So drink them up now boys.
Enjoy them. Enjoy them now. And chocolate cows are harder to move too. To move. I did
a corporate show in Sexton, Missouri. Oh, this is, this is the, this is the one, right?
Two hours outside of St. Louis. This was the, you had to jump away from your regular gig.
Yeah. Got it all cleared. I loaded into Chicago, do my first show in Chicago, pack up, go to
the airport, fly to Missouri to show Missouri pack up, fly back to Chicago, load in again
and finish up my run in Chicago. This was pound to flesh. This was not, uh, not going
to be easy as per your management. Yes. Possibly. This was for drunken businessman was the pitch.
It was, and it was not that I, that it was, it was mispitched that way. Okay. Cause the,
the guy that booked you told you this was going to be blood money. Yes. Is this going
to be a real pain in the ass? Yes. Um, it was, it was, it was a Christmas party for
a company that specializes in like, um, uh, basically like a gas tank, uh, compatibility.
So whether you have like ethanol or butane or whatever, like, uh, it basically is like
a, a tank company, like different types of gas tank company. It was a family party. So
it was all the workers and their husbands and wives. Uh, and it was held inside that
paintball, uh, place, uh, like kind of like amusement park area. This town, this town
was small. Like it drove through town. No, no lights, no traffic lights, you know, no
sidewalks, you know, uh, literally had one gas pump. What, like the gas station had one
pump. Oh shit. Uh, it was, uh, you know, like that's a small town. The firehouse had like
a little Christmas tree outside of a decorated, you know, that's, that's the little activity
scene. That's the, that's it's Christmas time. And, uh, inside it did, it had, it had, you
know, uh, you know, everything's for a dollar else. The freshmen stand at the, at the, at
the, uh, it wasn't open. I was there for a closed event, but you know, like I was like,
oh, they still sell sodas and water for a dollar and snacks for a dollar in places.
That's cute. It was very nice. Yeah. Um, but no, uh, they, uh, they just don't go to shows
often, right? So the idea of like putting on a show was just something that was kind
of like, okay, now the funny thing that happened was the woman who was supposed to Duke you
my intro, like she went over all the intro with me and I was like, yep, that's the intro.
And then, uh, they had to show a video and then break down the screen and take everything
off stage to make room for me. Uh, and after the intro, well, this is it. So I thought
my intro would be after the breakdown of the screen. Oh no. The video finishes and she
just calls from, from the audience, not from stage, from the audience, just turn to the
microphone. He goes, uh, the man of the hour, Matt Donnelly, just like that. Yeah. Man of
the hour, the man of the, the event was there to honor you. That's what I mean. Like man
of the honor, as you're like, Oh, I don't know. A man of the honor, like man of the
hour. I mean, like what, like we're not there for me retirement from magic. This is his
last show. Everyone, Mr. Matt Donnelly, the mine noodler. That's the, that's the comedian
coming up and go, you guys ready to laugh? Yeah, exactly. Exactly. Oh my, what a great
prank. How about some fantastic jokes? Everybody it's giggle time. If we gathered everyone,
Matt, take your ear, take your earphones out. Okay. All right. So here's what we're going
to do. We're going to, we're going to gather everyone that has been important in Matt's
life and in his professional career. And we're just going to put together a last retirement
show for Matt, but he's not going to know about it. We're just going to hire him. He's
going to come in. It's going to be billed as Matt Donnelly, the mine noodlers last show.
That's the way to go. Speeches. It's going to be great. Lonnie Hamilton out in Vegas,
the brain surgeon. Oh yeah. He had a crazy house that you could tour for a while. I got
to go one time. Just, you know, no, nothing even remotely close to an HOA. He had crazy
shit in there and he planned and held his own funeral. And yes, cause you want to hear
what people said about it. Yeah. And I think he's still kicking. He did this several years
ago and he's still alive. So I believe so. Yeah. So good for him. Yeah. Uh, I guess that's
what Matt's going to do, but it's good, but he's not going to know about it. It'd be great
if Richard was a, ladies and gentlemen, the man who will do a bat an hour, Matt Donnelly.
Yeah, that would, yeah, that's what you needed. The man who promised to do an hour comfortable
for an hour ish. It's Matt. After that uncomfortable intro, how did things pick up during the show?
Well, I had to wait for them to break down the stage. Oh, they weren't done. No. So the
video finishes, she introduces me. This is great. This is great. Three or four minutes
of total silence as they break down the screen and move everything off of the stage. Start
your final show while they're still breaking down. Right? This is the way you do it, man.
Yeah. Ice them. Yeah. Ice them cold. And I literally just went over to the side of the
stage where she had moved to and said, uh, are you, are you, is that, are you going to
introduce me now again? Or yeah. She goes, Oh, uh, no, just, just, no, just go, just
do it. And I go, but that's it. So I go, so then I go out on stage right now and just
start. She goes, you just want me to do it. Yeah. Uh, yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Perfect. One
gas tank, everybody. I started, uh, I started the show and it wasn't, honestly, people weren't
heckling me. A lot of people were like, no, I don't want to go on stage, which is annoying.
Sure. Okay. And it wasn't like a lot of people were clapping. A lot of people were laughing.
I was getting to my stuff. It just felt like I was doing one magic trick after another.
It didn't feel like a show. Do you know what I mean? I got you. I was like, I'm just going
to keep going. And I got another one. And here's another Diddy. Uh, how many were in
the room? Your last show was, uh, was that bad? About 150, about 150. Okay. Yeah. Uh,
but I went out doing what I loved, you know, and I had to call magic lounge and say, sorry,
this was it. This is it. How did the, uh, the trip out to the, to the random gig went
well and everything. There were no hiccups in the, in the travel. Uh, funny. I get there
and, uh, I take my little shuttle to, okay. So do you have any, what is your tactics for
renting a car when you travel? Jacob? I usually pre pre book before we get there. Uh, if I
can check in before getting to the rental car place, if I'm able to check in before
getting to the desk, then I will. And hopefully there is just a, a key pickup spot somewhere
or the keys are in the car and we, we load up, get in the car and, and head right out.
This is, this is where I need to get more savvy. I'm not, okay. I'm not good at figuring
out like how to be one of the guys that walks past the counter to the directly to where
the cars are. Right. The only tactics I have been using, and this used to be very successful
and now it's not. And I'll tell you why I used to book the third or fourth cheapest
option because it's usually a difference of like $5. Uh, uh, and so I would, I would choose
that because basically sometimes there's a rush at one rental car counter when you get
there and the lines like out the door. Yes. And so I've been, I was always, I always book
like the third or fourth cheapest rental car because usually that means like, I won't,
I won't be on that same line. Okay. And this used to be a successful tactic until now this
happened when Paul and I, when we went to Jersey, uh, and this happened, uh, and now
when I came here, all these rental car companies are now just run by the same, by, by the same
people.
Like when you get, when you get to the counter, everybody works for all three rental car places
at that counter. Like nobody like budget thrifty and Avis are all the same company. They're
all just, no, there's no merger. They're just running the, yeah, it's just like the guy
at the desk at thrifty. Yeah. If there's nobody at the desk at budget and he doesn't have
anybody in line at thrifty, he just stands up and moves over to the desk at budget. It's
budget cuts like, oh, so he's only getting paid one salary and working three jobs. That's
right. Fuck man. I don't know. I don't know how that guy is being paid, but yes, he's
definitely working three jobs. He might be making $700,000 a year. I don't know. I'm,
I'm guessing not probably not. If I made $700,000 in one year working for a rental car company,
you would never see me at the rental car company again. Yeah, that would be it. I'd be there
until they figured it out. Are you kidding? This guy, this guy's been working here for
28 years, rivaling Elon Musk, a higher threshold for pain than I ever will. If I saw 700 K
in my bank account today, I would disappear. Disappear, poof, gone without a trace. I'd
keep doing this show. This is where we find out that Paul and I are different people.
Fair enough. So I get there and the line is like out the door. I am like the 40th person
in line and there's two people working there and like one guy's wearing like a Santa Claus
hat to be like festive because it's a Christmas weekend. And I was like, yeah, it's a freaking
Christmas weekend. Maybe I have more than two people at the rental car counter. For
sure. No, he's like, absolutely not. So I am nervous because I'm supposed to be there
at like four. Okay. And, and I didn't, I didn't account for an hour of waiting for the car.
No, I sarcastically brought up Netflix on my phone and started watching the new knives
out movie being like, I'll never get through this. Cause it's two 40. That's a long and
I was like, I was like, so it's like timing each person. I was really getting myself really
angry and anxious and I was like, Oh yeah. I was like, I need to like check out. Like
I need to like be gone and podcasts are not doing it because I'm still looking around.
So I started watching. I started watching knives out. Took me an hour and 15 minutes to get
my car. That's a bit of a holy shit. It took me an hour and 15 minutes to get my car. That's
a wait baby. That's crazy. Yeah. It was maddening. It was really bad. And what airport was this?
St. Louis. It's a major airport. Uh, it's a major airport. Not the smallest little
podunk airport that you've ever seen in your life. Yeah. No. And like cause it's run by
those St. Lunatics. That's right. And you know, they had enough desks for eight people
to work. Um, well that's it, Matt. They spent all their money on desks. They can't get desks
and employees. I, uh, I got through an hour. Somebody asked me if I finished the film.
I haven't finished it yet. Uh, it seems, it seems to be the better one of the knives out
movies. It seems to be like the best one. Really? Oh, we should watch it at scoop fest.
Oh shit. For people who don't remember, we tried that at the scoop fest one time. Didn't
work well. We did a different, we have murder on the orient express. It was my call and
it was the wrong call. Um, it was your call, but we were all excited about it. You had
the idea, but all three of us were very excited about it. And it was a bad idea. Yeah. Uh,
so, uh, yeah. So anyways, I ended up getting like late to the gig, which is not great,
but they were, it ended up being fine. They had rental car trouble in Austin as well,
but different type of rental car trouble. We, we breezed through the line that that
wasn't an issue. We got in the car and went to drive away and SJ was driving and, uh,
she goes, Oh, there's a, uh, a tire pressure warning light on and sure enough, the, uh,
the passenger front tire, uh, according to the car was supposed to be 38 pounds per square
inch, 38 PSI. And it was at, uh, like 16 or 17. It was, it was quite low. It was quite
low. Whoa. So we went back into the office and we're like, Hey, the, uh, the, the car
has a low tire light on it. Um, y'all, y'all want to do something about that. And she said,
I shit you not. She goes, Oh, well you can feel free to fill that up like a gas station
or something when you're, when you're, after you get the car out. But if, if the tire has
a leak in it, then I'm in more trouble than I am now. She was like, Oh, it's just the
cold weather. I was like, no, no, no. The cold weather knocks it down like five or six
or seven PSI. This is like 20. Yeah. Like it might just be going flat. Like if you're
telling me it's fine and just need some air in it, then put some air in it and I'll take
it out and I guess we'll deal with it. But like we were going out into the country to
visit my in-laws. Like, well, I'm not, I'm not trying to have a flat tire out in the
fucking woods somewhere. No. And so finally they go, well you can do a, cause we had paid
for it with, with points. And so, so we had gotten like the, the premium, the premium
level car or whatever. Yeah. It shows, she goes, Oh, well you can take this other, you
know, basically just like the low level, you know, the, the budget, the budget car. Yeah.
We were like, Oh, well, okay. That's fine. But do we get a refund on? No, no, there's,
there's no refunds. Yeah. And so that just went back and forth for a while. And finally
I was like, just cause she goes, Oh, well you can cancel the reservation as well. Oh
boy. So what, what do you mean? We were here. We, we have to have a car. I'm waiting here
after to see where you can get me a car with, with all four tires. That's all. That's the
only you guys don't have an air compressor. You don't have just somebody that could come
out and put air in the tire and someone does a check, right? Don't they do a check on the
cars as they're cleaning them up and whatnot? Yes. And then she goes, Oh, well, you know,
we can, we can get you some, we can get you a different car, but it's going to be a big
car. So they finally, they finally give us like a nice car, like a Tahoe, like something,
something that if the three of us were going somewhere and I had rented a car and I rented
this, at least one of the two of you would be like, Jacob, why'd you rent such a big
fucking car? Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. This was like eight people could fit in this thing
plus luggage and yeah, it was stupid. It was very nice though. Or you can have whatever's
in this box and just put this box, this three box up on there, gave it a tap or you're going
to ride on this goat, ride this goat all the way through the country. And when you open
the box, there's just a dildo inside that said, go fuck yourself. Oh boy. It was such
a pain. It was so weird. And we were both on like no sleep at all. I think I had slept
for maybe an hour and a half the night before and literally no sleep. What a load. I'm just
standing there in this car rental office with that like sleep deprived confusion. Yeah.
Yes. I'm like, I don't understand why we don't have a car and why we aren't leaving already.
You have so many cars here and that the one you gave us has a flat tire. So what is what?
So dumb. And then like she goes, Oh, well you can, you can take this Tahoe, you can
take this Tahoe. And I go great. And then they tell us the parking spot and we go out
to it and there was a large Tahoe type SUV in the, in the parking spot, but it says Denali
on it. And so I was like, well, that's not a, is that a Tahoe? I don't know if Denali
is a Tahoe. And so I go back in and I was like, Hey, the, the thing in the spot there,
it looks like a Tahoe, but it says Denali on it. She goes, yeah, that's the type of
Tahoe it is. It's a Denali. It's a nice one. Oh, okay. Okay. I was just asking. I was making
sure we were taking the right fucking car. Don't yell at me. She went back to blowing
up your other tire by, by my mouth. Like, like, like, like a clown with a balloon animal.
Just like, I will tell you, I will tell you one of the things that I do really love about
living out here in old Western PA. I can drive to the sheets, gas station. I can pull up
next to an air compressor machine. I can push that baby to where I want it to go. Pressure
wise. I can stick that tube on my tire and go and then be done all for fucking free.
Done. None of this charging bullshit. My God. I had, then Paul pulls out his dick and pisses
all over it so that no one else will be able to enjoy it. I had to have like three different
locations in Vegas because either someone would rip the fucking nozzle off and steal
the copper gas users are a disaster here. They really would. Yeah. Or they would tear
up the e-reader so you couldn't use the machine or as only quarters and you, the only place
you ever still had to use quarters was that fucking air compressing machine. There is,
as I always said, when you did live here, I said, Paul, when you're at my house, just
tell me I own an air compressor and we can put air in your tires. Never did that though.
We never did. On quarters. I just kept carrying around quarters because it doesn't happen.
Yeah. When he goes to the sheets, he finishes off with a happy ending. He, he, he, he suitcases
it at the very end and gives a little rate up the keyster. Just, just wake it up. I just
wake it up a little bit. I offered that I offered that he didn't take me up on my happy
end to get the sheets as a fountain drink for Ann. That's what that is. She loves a
sheet fountain drink and I can't blame her. They're quite good. I got to take a sheet
fountain drink to Ann McPheeters. You better have a poncho on. I got some diet. I got a
diet Pepsi fountain drink for her the other day. It was primo top notch. I, yeah, I, I
sheets is pretty good. So, uh, I've got to give a shout out to Ann. Poor thing. She's
trying to get home. She's supposed to be off today. She worked a 14 hour day yesterday.
She's supposed to be off today. She's been at work since six o'clock. It's a nightmare.
People just keep calling off and she's too good to not just let the place burn in hell.
So it's not something terrible happening. It's just people calling out. Well, it's just
holiday schedule type stuff. Yeah. It's bullshit. Yeah. But she's supposed to be off. But anyway,
it's like the milk frothing machine is raging out of control or anything like that. Nothing
like that. But she's been dealing, she's been putting out fires for weeks now and it's just
a bunch of bullshit and I hope things clear up soon. So yeah, I'm going to give a shout
out to the people of Chicago. Oh, I had a blast at Chicago Magic Lounge this weekend.
I really fun shows. It was really great. I love Chicago audiences. I always have ever
before magic. It just took improv in Chicago. I just have always loved doing shows in Chicago.
Good theater town. And good entertainment town. They know how to behave in a show. Yeah.
I want to show where a guy was just messing up and I was like starting to get frustrated
in a way that everyone thought was funny, right? I said he was being, it was on a really
hard time giving me straight answers. And then finally I did the whole like think of
any animal. And he, and he said, I go, yeah, I want to go see that. He goes, what is it?
He goes, seven. What was it? Was he on something? Was he, was he just pulling your leg? He was
not sober. He was not sober. Okay. But this is what I love Chicago audiences where I go
like, what is happening? What world are we living in? Did I enter a vortex? You know,
whatever. And I just turned and I turned, I was like, I gotta find somebody else. And
I was like, you, what's your name? And he's like, Dan, I was like, Dan, are you an asshole?
And everyone laughs, including the guy. Yeah. The guy goes, I don't think so. And I go good.
Name any animal. And he's like, good, good, good. I did boom, pulled out a fish as squirrel.
And I said, just see how hard that is. It's so good though. When the, when the drunk guy
laughs along, he goes like, I'm sorry. And I was trying to explain this. I got through
the whole weekend with Mike Mills and Mike Mills. I'm about to go out with jokers and
magic. And as I explained to him, I was like, you know, my clips that do best on my Instagram
feed and stuff like that and tick tock and all that stuff are ones where I am frustrated.
And the problem is the comments in the thing are some of them are like, boy, this guy's
an asshole, right? Right. And it's hard to explain. It's like, no, no, no. Like from
your family. And I was like, you know, the firehouse could still use volunteers and um,
like everybody was laughing. I was frustrated, but jokingly frustrated. Like I was playing
it up. Right. And the whole audience was laughing, including the guy who I was messing with the
whole time. You know, right. Oh, it's the best. And I was like, but, but if that clip
runs social media, like they'd just be like this magician's being a dickhead. And so it's
really hard. Even the one that's the most famous for the more is really busting the
guy's ball and threatened him to leave and that kind of stuff. Yeah. Uh, we hung out
after that show and talked for 20 minutes. We, we, we, we, he was happy. He was happy.
You know, he was happy with his show experience. Yeah. And so it's just hard. It's just hard.
But I had a blast in Chicago. It is always weird. I see, I see people doing this, not
just on your social media, but on many of my friends, many of my performer friends, social
media, people will critique the, you know, eight seconds of performance that they saw
on this slip. I'm like, guys, this is not, I know it's hard. This is not what this is.
And on the other hand, I'm going to put it out, right? Like it's really, it's really
hard. It's, it's difficult. I can't pitch too much scoop is making the announcement.
That guy is Matt's apprentice now. Uh, I do the bit, uh, scoop it over glass. If I do
a six, seven joke, I had it in my show briefly because I always say, what's our connection
scale of one to 10? I pull a number out of my pocket. Uh, and I can pull it out and it's
six, seven. It's a really, uh, polarizing, polarizing joke. It's a polarizing joke. Some
people really love it and some people go like, Oh God. And then I hate that. It's the devil
makes my children say that. And the risk is, uh, that I look like an old guy trying to
look hip. That's why I don't do it. I was about to ask if you like that joke, I could
give a shit. Yeah, exactly. I mean, you don't care about that joke. No, look, I got soccer
jerseys made for my kid and for this Christmas tournament. And, uh, uh, boy, we didn't talk
about that. Did we end down? No, we didn't talk about your kids, Christmas soccer tournament,
the three on three. Oh, I feel bad because I'm one, I don't know if everyone listens
here. This is a Penn Sunday school, but I have this conversation at Penn Sunday school,
but you guys reactively, then Penn does everything. So it's, it's fine by me. Uh, but I got shirts
made up for it. You know, my brother designed a logo for the jingle ballers. I had everyone's
jersey number six, seven, uh, and, uh, every kid was loving as we walked by in our shirts
with a six, seven, because I was amongst children and that's what the joke is for. Yes. Um,
but uh, uh, yeah. So the show, I don't do it because it just looks like, I could look
like an old guy trying to look hip and that that's dumb. And it also slows things down.
It's a, it eats the, cause it's right. The number joke is a quick bit that leads to the
fish reveal. So it kind of really clunks it up. Rhythm wise, if it takes up too much,
I was going to say, cause then you have to get back and do the actual joke. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So it, it reads as a recovery and that's not funny. Right. But, uh, yeah, guys, hey,
uh, you are talking to a now retired soccer coach. Yeah. Just in and out. I, uh, you know,
I, I gotta, I gotta go out on top, you know, you're going out on top, huh? Uh, look, let's
just say mistakes were made, uh, for the three on three. Yes. Did, did the, uh, did the athletes
on the field not follow your instructions to the point that they should have thus losing
the game, uh, via no fault of yours coach. No, it's not even, we're not even like, we're
not even, it's not even, I wish, I wish that was a problem. Oh no. The mistake I made was
you could check a box. You either be recreational team or competitive team. Oh, okay. You check
competitive. Correct. Cause my kids have been playing together for seven years and that's
right. They had a really good coach and they're going on. And so we go off our first game
and we crushed the other team. Five, nothing like really, really great. Like great. We're
riding high. We're feeling good. Sounds like Donnelly's on the sideline. You're like guys,
I checked the competitive box. How come you're not bringing me competitive teams. And even
the old coach whose kid is on our teams showed up and he was like, Hey, maybe we'll do a
barbecue at my house when this is all over. Like we're feeling good. All right. It's an
all day event. So we've got to wait like an hour and change between each game. Okay. And
the next game we go up against the games are really quick games are like 12, 12 minute
halves. The whole thing's over an hour. Oh, that's fun. Oh, okay. Yeah. And so you do
first thing first batch around Robbins and then you do a semifinal and final of the best
teams from the round Robin. Okay. So then we go up against a team that is the, yeah,
it's the split team of the traveling team in town. Like the main traveling team in town
split into different teams and we're playing one of the, one of the very Brazilian national
team. They beat us eight, nothing. And, uh, and it was hard. They scored fast. They're
up for nothing. Like very fast. Yeah. And same age as, as your team, right? Yeah, same
ages, same ages, but just, you know, these are guys are practicing year round three times
a week. They're going at it. They're going at it. Yeah. Yeah. Playing well or playing
dirty. Uh, Oh, so good point, Paul. So it turns out we play in a rec league when you
play club team, it turns out a physical contact is not a refereed as closely as recreation
rec, a lot of shoving. Right, right, right, right, right. And the competitive, uh, travel
teams, they allows, they allow a lot more contact. So yes, indeed my kids are actually
getting pushed around and then it's hard to watch. That's what I figured. And they want
to complain. And I'm saying like, you got to just play through it. Right. Now here's
the problem. This whole thing, you can't do that in, you can't do that mid game. You can't,
you can't shift that, that thought process. There's no adult to be. No, no, no. And that's
why I know this. Like my only thing is I just try to like not raise my voice and just like,
we got to keep playing. We got to keep going. All you can do is be the calm example at that
point. This whole thing was because my youngest kid had a nightmare soccer season because
what happens when you play rec is that the, the, whatever core group you have will stay
together, but you always don't have, you know, it's rare to have like 12 core group people.
And so you get five or six new kids each season. And this particular season, my kid got a bunch
of kids who didn't show up. Uh, one kid like broke his arm and like, uh, and we just lost.
So we were playing luckily at soccer. So you don't need your arm. We were playing shorthanded
the entire season. My son had to play the entire game of every game. That's right. Yeah.
Yeah. He was just out there all the time. Yeah. And sometimes one kid short. So they're
getting their butts kicked through it by, by playing, you know, seven on six or whatever.
Right. And so I just want to one last fun event for these kids to like not have it so
hard and then I've marched them into a buzzsaw. Yeah. You should have gone home after the
first game. Exactly. We should just, well, we won. We should have been like barbecue.
Let's go. Yeah. Barbecue sounds great. That's the plan. So because we beat that other shitty
team five, nothing, we got extra points higher. Yes. Extra points for a shutout. So you're
going against the gods. Yep. So we qualify for the finals and it's three of the travel
team teams and our team. So you played a third game. Yes. Because we're the number four round
Robin. So it goes into a quarterfinal. It's one versus four. So we have to play an even
better team than the team that just kicked our ass, ate nothing. You had to keep playing
with this Paul again. You think you're just bringing up a philosophical point and you're
reading the story. So, uh, this next team just destroys us. I mean, just like it is
16, nothing in the first 12 minutes and literally like a minute into the second half, like this,
you know, 14 year old kid walks over to me. He's the ref, you know, no, it's going to
hurt down. We'll just be the user. He's like, here he's like, there's a mercy rule. You
can just call it, you know? Yeah. And I was like, and no, I'm not calling. I'm not calling.
Oh no, Matt, you got to call it. You got to call it. Did you ask the kids? Did you, did
you propose it to the kids at all or no? No. Cause they were, they would just confirm it.
Like, like that's, that to me is more demoralizing. You think, okay, all right. I mean, you're
having the option for the mercy rule is demoralizing moment. It is a demoralizing moment, but if
the ref is telling you, Hey, we can, we can put a gun to this horse's head. Yes. I take
that option, but I mean, that's me, but you're not out there playing a rec league soccer
game in the first place. I just wanted my kids to score. I want to see it. I want to
see if my kids could score another goal or something. I just want to see if they could
just find something, some fun moment or whatever. And they weren't getting shut out in the,
in the no, no, we scored a couple of times. We scored, scored on them. We actually scored
first, which got things way too exciting. We were, we were, we were briefly up one nothing
and then down a lot to one, uh, which is a terrible, uh, cause it even gave a moment
of false hope. Sure. Right. Like, Oh, maybe we are good enough. We're not. It's more
self-examination that you don't want. Now, as you know, this, this, uh, this, this, this
show is familiar with the term Italian air show. Sure. Yeah. So worst to worst. So the
Italian national team showed up. This is where, this is where we, this is where, this is where
we take my Italian soccer team to Romstein. And, um, so I, I look on my app, like there's
a giant thing that's taking place all over the field with all these different age groups
and everything else. And so every time you go to the desk for help, they're like, look
at the app, look at the app, look at the app and the refs just record the scores and the,
and the app naturally populates your next matchup. And I see on the tournament thing
that underneath the finals, it says consolation game. So I assume that that means that the
loser of the two finals teams play a consolation game. That's the way it looks like on the
app. Okay. Like a third place game or something. So after we lost, I don't know, a million
to two, I'd be like, Hey, this is where I do offer the mercy role. I'm like, Hey, I'm
according to the app. We can play one more game, but it's against the team that we, you
know, we two games, we lost two, two games ago or whoever lost to them, but it's another
club team.
My son is out. He's like, no, yeah. He's like, no, I'm done. And I was like, yeah. And I
had my hand like, I hear you. Cool. I hear you. And the other four kids say, yes. No.
And then I'm looking at the thing and it says, did you give your son an opportunity to talk
the other kids out of it? Did you squeeze into the tightest Jersey fit you've ever done?
Yeah. I'm a jingle baller. If that were the end of this story, it'd be if you, if you
shaved and put on like a beanie and did a dwarf, did a dwarf on your knees out to the
field thing. I've been fucking hilarious. No, my kid and I have a very emotional conversation.
He's mad because he doesn't want to play, but he can't quit. He won't quit. And so if
his kids are in, he's in, but he has to play. And I'm saying, you can go home if you want.
Don't worry about it. And he's interpreting that as like me, like admonishing him. And
I'm like, no, no, this is not like a sarcastic or teach dad moment. For real. If you want
to go home, it's fine. Dad agrees. This sucks. If you want to go, go. I'm only finishing
my obligation as coach to these other kids. And we don't have this obligation. I do. You
can leave, but he doesn't have much of a choice there. He can't leave. No, it sucks. It sucks.
It just sucks. And in my head, I'm like, I want to be like, buddy, I already failed.
Like no matter what this day is a fucking failure for what I wanted to have happen today.
It's already gone. I don't even have a silver lining for what today is. Not a single part
of this went according to my, I was trying to put an extra little pep in your step or
your five core players that, that you committed with for seven seasons. And all I did was
make you just put an exclamation point on the shit that was this season. That's all
I did was facilitate an extra a hundred kicks to the balls, right? Like, what the hell I'm,
I'm just feeling like a terrible person. I would also like my day to end. I sure would
like to go home to these other kids want to keep playing those. So I have to stick around.
I misread the app. The constellation game is for the winners of the losers. So all the
losers that didn't make the, the final tournament went to their own bracket, a bracket I'm sure
we would have loved to have been in. Sure. And so the, what they called the fun bracket,
the two winners of the losers got one last game on another field. And I had to then turn
around after all that fighting, I just did with my son and all of the, all the pep talks,
all the parishes gave to their other kids and go, just kidding. I misread the app game.
Go home. Oh, what a headache on the text thread. Like, are we still doing a picnic? Right.
Barbecue. Where's the barbecue motherfucker? Let's rain check on this one and we'll do
it some other day. Yeah. It's been a day. It's let's try. Trying is the first step to
failure. Oh, that's awful, dude. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Kids into the holiday spirit though.
Maybe a good lesson in sports bullshitness. Well, I found myself like going through all
these things in my head. Right. And then I was reminded of America's got talent where
like when I crashed up on America's got talent, I kept it like, Oh, if I ever do this next
time. And then my brain kept going like, there is no next time. And then I would still swim
and swirl and beat myself up and stuff. And my brain would go like, you're never going
back. And so that's what's happening here. I keep it like, Oh, if I next time we'll do
the recreation league, there's no next time. We're not rallying this back together again.
We're not, no, no, no. We're not getting the old gang back together next year. We're not,
I'm not going to call these parents again. Hey guys, remember that tournament we played
last year? You want to do that again? Remember when you put your trust in me to march your
kids to an awesome afternoon of soccer and I just got there. It was more of a death march.
I was like, I saw like, yeah, all these adjustments in my head. You gave me your kids and I got
up these really cute jerseys. They said six, seven, the jingle ballers was a whole thing.
And then the other team made them dig their own graves. Execution style. Yeah. That's
also, I will call them all next year in December and be like, are your kids feeling a little
too arrogant or cocky? Could they use another lesson in humility? How are your kids doing
to get knocked down a peg? Send the link for the three on three. Boom. Let's go.
It's humility train. Get on board. Everybody on board the humility train. It's the opposite
of like a ropes course where they build kids' confidence up over, you know, whatever. It's
like, you call me like your kids are arrogant. Don't worry. I will sign them up for a three
on three soccer team. No, no, no. You're not so great. 12 year old. Oh man. Like, you know,
we're sitting around before the games. So this kids are just playing soccer with other
random kids and just, you know, plan on random, you know, just, just fucking around right
and playing. Yeah. And so I guess other kids that were on that team that, that beat us
eight, nothing. We're like playing around with them and literally like was like, Oh,
we're playing you guys next. And then one kid was like, Oh, we're going to beat them.
Like, and so like, you want to be like, Oh, we'll show them. And then they did. And then
just as like, Oh, it's like everything from a terrible movie and there's no, there's no
second act. It's just, it's just the first act of the terrible movie.
It's a more realistic movie where the, where the rich, tough team comes in and just beats
the shit out of the upstart team. But you're done coaching now. That's cool. That's great.
That's what I said. I said, if you want to, I said, if you guys want to start an improv
group or play basketball, you let me know. There you go. You're done until then leave
me alone. Are you done walking yet? What you like in general, the milers shit, an intervention
from Paul, any kind of physical activity bail on everything. It doesn't lead to anything
positive. It just doesn't give him one hip replacement. He's like, quit walking, not
take it off. This is my strutting around cock of the block. Here I am. Ambulatory as fuck.
Look at me. Do to do to do king in the castle. Are you guys talking about Matt Donnelly?
You talk about the guy who walks. Yeah. Fucking walking guy. The ambulatory flex is annoying.
He can't even get to a thousand miles dip shit. He can't count. He can, he can walk.
They can't fucking count. Yes. Kids can count. They don't play soccer well, but that one,
that one, it was my failure. Not theirs. They achieved their goals. Right. And so it was
like a joke of the family for my kids to make fun of me failing. So I got to really lean
into that and own that. And that was this one. You just kind of had to eat shit. You
don't feel like you're going to lean into this one in the future. It's going to come
up on new years. It's a big funny joke. That's what I mean. Jacob is like everywhere I look
at them. Like, no, it's just an L it's just a total fucking loss. It's just a total sucks.
I just failed and it's over. Like there's nothing, there's no way to point at it. There's
a silver lining. Here's the silver lining. Oh, okay. Those jerseys. You got them. Yeah.
With the six, seven gang. Yeah. Every time they hear the six, seven shit now it's going
to be like, Oh, fuck that. So you may have started a kind of underground rid of the six,
seven, six, seven, at least for them, at least for your kids are not going to enjoy it. We
have neighbors who are more religious. They really do think it's some kind of devil practice
and they did. They said this. Oh, I wasn't joking when I said it's a devil ritual. That's
what these fucking people think. They're crazy as fuck. We know this. Their kids have said
to our kids, like, can you not make six, seven jokes around us? My parents say it's satanic.
So fucking stupid. This country is getting what it deserves. And I had, I am like, do
they believe that or do they just hate that joke so much? They want it to stop. They believe
it. If it's the second, then I'm with them. This is one of those things I am all for.
I'm all for lying to children. No, no. If it accomplishes getting rid of a joke, that's
really annoying. No, this is, this is the dumbest thing. It is, it is the same as rock
and roll. It is the same as underground comedy. It is the same as anything that the younger
generation has ownership of and understanding of that the older generation can't comprehend
fully. And nothing makes the older generation go crazier than when their kids are doing
something that they don't understand. And it makes them fucking nuts. K-pop in general
makes me feel old and out of touch. See? And I love it. Anytime I see, no, I love it. It's
great. But like every time I see or hear anything related to K-pop, I just feel old. Well, I
feel old and out of touch. And you should. We are. Yeah. I think it's just correct. I
think it's the correct feeling. But it doesn't mean the devil made it to poison and kill
your children. It's the dumbest shit. It's all, it's all just, and it's all just control.
I don't think K-pop is of the devil. It's all control. I do believe that 6/7 is. It's
all control. It's all misogyny. It's all racism. It's all tied together in this bullshit that
this country is doing constantly. No, it's probably fine. This country's had it fine.
It's good. Sure. It's nailed it. I'll tell you what else is brought to you by racism
and misogyny. No, no. And that the United States of America. Today's show is brought
to you by, um, yeti brand ice creams, sitting cones, yeti brand, yeti brand ice cream, sitting
cones. This is a, this is a real thing. Who's this from? This is from the microscope in
24. Microscope. So this is from an, a classic episode of the electric company. Oh, you ever
seen this? So it's a spider-man episode where there's this yeti running loose in New York
and Spidey has to trap him. So what he does is he buys ice cream cones. Cause of course
the yeti is attracted to cold and he makes this trail of ice cream cones and the yeti
incredibly suggestively sits on every ice cream cone as he follows the trail of ice
cream cones to the trap that spider-man has set for the yeti. So I don't even know microscope
what commercial I can do here that comes close to just telling people to go on YouTube and
look up the yeti episode of spider-man from the electric company and watch the yeti suggestively
keister a ton of ice cream cones up its ass. It's, it's beyond disturbing. And when it
does it, it makes like a, a hiss sound, you know, like when you, when you throw a hot,
hot, like a, a little bit of water on a hot griddle and it's all that's the yeti hot griddles,
all these fucking ice cream cones and just, and like really loves it. Like the yeti, the
yeti really loves it. Yeah. So go watch the yeti get off on sitting on a bunch of ice
cubes. Oh God, there it is. Speaking of getting off, you're about to be getting off with some
jock versus nerds. Oh no. Ladies and gentlemen, it is time. Time for jock versus nerds. Explosion
of sexually gratified yetis. It's, it's live action. Scoop and overgrowth. I was animated.
No, it's live action. And the live, the guy who played the live action, spider-man just
passed away, uh, like a week ago, Toby McGuire. No, this was technically the, he was a Henson
guy. I think I don't remember, but he, uh, he was the technically the first live action
spider-man. And it's really, yeah, kind of sad. I wanted one more quick little announcement
of what I did last week. Uh, Matt and Malia are, are my dear Pennsylvania scoop friends
were kind enough to invite me out to Christmas vacations put on by the bricolage, uh, production
company. They did a midnight radio kind of thing. They do a radio play version of national
Lampoon's Christmas vacation with tons of Pittsburgh references in it. Oh, that's fun.
It was kind of cute. So lots of Foley work going on through the whole thing and them
just, and so you just sit and you watch performers standing and reading through the script, but
doing all kinds of Foley work at the same time. It was really funny. Uh, a couple of
things went over my head cause I haven't been out here long enough to know all the, uh,
the ins and outs. Oh boy, I got it. But, um, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, we've got a scooper to come and ask today from rune scoop, uh, who sent a nice
email to about, uh, seeing Matt at the Chicago magic lounge. So, uh, the room scoop really
enjoyed Matt's performance at the Chicago magic lounge. Uh, so you got that going for
you, which is nice. Hey, my last shows the retirement shows. It was great. Yeah. The
categories are every breath you take un-camouflaged animals, 50 50 and run it back. Oh, and let's
see, uh, team sling here. I hear your fresh stats. Matt has 2,800 all time. Jacob has
2000 all time. Paul is in the rear with negative 2000. I'm always in the rear. So that's, that's
on the rune scoop games here. Every breath you take is a category all about the polices.
Every breath you take. Uh, I love the concept from Eric Dittleman's, uh, of, uh, camouflage
animals. So I present that to you with my own twist un-camouflaged animals, uh, find
the animal 50 50 where the odds are forever in your favor and run it back questions from
my last scooper D. Uh, Paul, you're up first. What do you want? Okay. Uh, I'll try un-camouflaged
animals for 200, three, two, elephant blast off. Un-camouflaged animals, right? Uh huh.
Three to elephant. There's a number three, a number two, the word elephant and blast
off three, two, one. I mean, goodness, my dog is over here just going crazy about something.
I'll be right back. Talk amongst yourselves. The dog is like, it's obvious. The answer
is obvious. Right? Well, what one as like the answer as a, I don't know. What do you
think, Matt? Three, two, elephant blast off. What's the category? Un-camouflaged animals.
Uh, I wonder if it's just elephant trunk. Oh, you might be right. There you go. It's
a give me, it's a give me, uh, I think he's making fun of the Dittleman category instead
of, you know what I mean? We're like all the now I get it. Now I get it. You're right.
That's exactly what it is. Elephant is the answer. It'd be weird if this was the time
where Jacob's dogs decided to take over and eat him. I don't know if anybody saw the follow
up that Dittleman posted on our Insta, but he would have given me credit for Roo and
then it would have not given me credit for Holy cross. So I should, you should have won
and I should have lost. I should have won, but Hey, yeah, water under the bridge. All
right. Jacob's back with a pupper. Now our views are going to go up. Views are going
to go through the moon. So it's elephant, Jacob. It's elephant. That's, we figured
it out. It's a, it's a play on, on Dittleman's game of hiding the names. There's no hiding.
So it's elephant. Do you think the answer is elephant? They think so. Yeah, there we
go. It is elephant. Matt, I'll do un-camouflaged animals for 800, please. Let's try it. Your
left shoe is plotting a coup against reality. Oh, he did it. It wasn't, it wasn't going
to be that fun. Okay. You got diddled. I got, I got diddled. Let's see here. Your left
shoe is plotting a coup against reality. Damn it. I don't see it. I'll pass. That passes
to me. I don't, I don't understand what's happening in this category. What's the category?
This is the Dittleman one, the un-camouflaged animals. I had a delivery come to my house
and my dog is furious about it. I get it. Huh. What do you think? I feel like pigeon,
but I'm going to pass. Cause I don't know. All right. There is no animal. It's just a
sentence. Wow, sneaky, sneaky. He promised me it would be unhinged and he is delivering.
All right. There you go. I'll do un-camouflaged animals for 600. The chef told us if we wanted
to be average to work elsewhere, it's be average. The answer is beaver. Be average together.
It's beaver guys. Beaver is what I'm going with. Beaver. Beaver. Boy, I'm glad I got
that one right. Paul. Every breath you take for 800. I'm going to shoot them. Ooh. Paul
knows all about the police. This is where I next saw you, a venue. Oh my goodness. This
is where I next saw you. See, now this is clearly one that I needed to do in order.
Paul, pass. Clearly. Matt, pass. Pass. The Turner hall ballroom jokers tour. Okay. That's
who's going to see me next. See if I'm playing near you. Go to jokersofmagic.com. Un-camouflaged
animals, 400. Daily double. I bet it all. I have zero points. I bet it all. Hey kids,
quit monkeying around. Monkey. Ooh. It is monkey. It's in monkeying. You probably couldn't
see it earlier. The word monkey is hidden cleverly inside of the word monkeying. Pretty
fucking sneaky. It's me. I'll try 50/50 for 200. The odds you get this question right
are 50/50. True. True. Hey, look at that. So now wait. I'd say the odds are 100%. Yeah.
I guess if I picked false, they wouldn't have been. Paul. This is that riddle of the twins
at the window like that. Yeah, exactly. Everything I say is a lie and you can't believe anything
I say or something. I don't know. Yeah, yeah. I only tell the truth. I only tell lies. Something
else. Run it back for 200. What is my favorite word? Hint. It's six letters, three of which
are Y. Definition, a conjunction or opposition, especially of the moon with the sun. What
is my favorite word? Six letters, three Y's. Wow. Y Y Y. Yeah. Conjunction or opposition
of the moon. Yak moon. No, what's that called? It's not an eclipse, not an eclipse, not a
ellipse. I'll pass. I don't know. Matt. Pass. Pass. Z Y G Y. Sijiji. Sijiji. Sijiji. Sijiji.
That's a hell of a word. I'll do 50/50, 400. The odds you get this question right are one
in 25. False. It is false. Well done. Knock that math out of the park. I'm going 50/50
for 800. I'll take the burn this time. Whoa. The odds you get this question right are one
in 100. All right, let's see. I'm going to say false. Oh, it's true. It's either right
or it's wrong. Oh man. Wait, the odds you get this question right are one in 100. True.
It's right or it's wrong. I don't get that at all. I don't get that at all. Somebody
explained that to me. I got it wrong, but somebody explain it to me. Yeah. Paul. Run
it back for 400. Free square. Yay. Reaction or response must feature a reference to bingo
to get points. Oh no. I said yay. You only said yay. I thought yay might be enough.
It wasn't. I'm sorry, Paul. You got that wrong. That's fair enough. Matt. Oh man. Now I'm
trying not to step in a landmine. This is a sneaky fucking scooperty. Every breath you
take for 200. All right. This is where I first saw you on platform. Also, this is just a
police style. Every breath you take category just to Matt. Stalking you. Yeah. It's gotta
be fool us, right? Matt. No, no, no. He came and saw me live and he told me when I saw
him and I'm trying to remember, I think it was when I was opening for PIF in Chicago.
I think it was in Chicago when I opened for PIF. Do I know the name of the club? I thought
this was going to be like, I thought the platform meant like Twitch. Oh, I'm just wrong on all
of this. I think I don't know. Okay. Uh, pass. There you go. That's the solve. That's where
did runes scoop first see Matt Donnelly? Um, fuck it. Twitch. You too. Good job. Good
job. Jacob. You got it right. Good. It's me. I'll try, um, uh, run it back 600 to protect
his new wealth. A young, uh, the Greek freak Janice, uh, I'm not going to try and say his
last name. That's it. Kept in, kept in the NBA, kept in the NBA, kept his money at the
FDIC limit in this many banks hint plus or minus, uh, plus or minus two. It's the first
year of his rookie contract. Oh, wow. So he just so money insured up to the FDIC amount
in every many banks. Wow. Oh, I see. God, how many, how many, I mean, well first time,
how much is FDIC insured? Well, I believe that is the, uh, half of this entire question.
Okay. And I don't know his rookie contract. I'm telling you that there are two halves
of this question. I don't know either. Well, educated guesses. How much do you think banks
insured 25 K? I think it goes higher than that. I think, no, it's going to be, I would
think it was million. No, it's at least a million. Who's your pastor, Jacob? That passes
to Paul. Okay. I'll guess, uh, I'll guess four. No, I'll guess 25 banks, 25 banks. Let's
see seven. Seven is the answer. And does it make more sense this time? Paul, did it make
more sense this time? Nope. Not right then. Not to me. Paul, you're wrong. Run it back.
For 800. Expand the window as you read from the category. Let me see here. Hold on. Can
I do this? What do I have to do here? Uh, from the category, I don't know if I can expand
this window because I have the thing. This is truly outside the box. The category spaces
category spaceless potpourri. Oh, it keeps going. Oh, here we go. Although owned by the
Mars corporation, M&Ms were co-invented by the son of the president of this chocolate
company and filled with their chocolate owned by the Mars corporation. M&Ms were co-invented
by the son of the president of this chocolate company and filled with their chocolate. Gotta
be Hershey. Let's try Hershey. Oh man, this is off the rails. I love it. It is Hershey.
Hey, I'm back to zero. Fuck yeah. Matt, you're up. Back on the board. I can't see it anymore.
I can't see the board. No, uh, I would take every breath you take for 600. Daily double.
Now it's for 800. This is where I third saw you. Chicago magic lounge. It's the Chicago
magic lounge. Nice one. Was that this time? This was the third? That's correct. All right.
Score check with two questions left. Matt now has the lead with 1600. I'm in second with
200. Paul's in third with zero. There's no more daily doubles left. There's an every
breath you take for 400 and a 50-50 for 600. I'm going to do that 50-50 instead of trying
to figure out where Rune Scoop saw Matt Donnelly at different times. Anybody's game. Paul,
is that squirrel in your background? Is that the squirrel in your background? No. Paul,
is that the squirrel in your background? No, thank God. I'm going to say yes. Okay. Points
if Paul looked, did you look Paul? Nope. Did you see me? I didn't see you look. That's
why I asked. No, Jacob got that one wrong. Paul closing out the category. Every breath
you take for 400. This is the game. Uh, this is where I second saw you. What venue did
Rune Scoop see Matt at the second time he saw Matt? I will pass. I don't know. Oh, interesting
hat. That passes to you. I am trying to remember. He told me when I say opening for PIF, I don't
think that's right. Okay. I think maybe came and saw a foolers tour show. Um, I forget
though pass. Oh, that passes to me. Uh, that would be Matt's house through the second story
window at Matt's house that Rune Scoop was looking through. Oh no, it's the paps. Yeah.
The fuller store. There you go. I got that one wrong and that is the game. Matt wins
with 1600. Paul is in second with zero and I am in third with negative 800. That's from
Rune Scoop. Thank you so much. Rune Scoop. If you want to send us a scooper to your price,
a Scryte jock versus nerd or an obelisk jock versus nerd, head over to preaching fun.com.
Nope. That's wrong. Head over to HeyScoops.com. HeyScoops.com right there on the home page.
You can make us any of those jock versus nerds. You can send us some email that'll get read on
the show. All those things happen right over there at HeyScoops.com. Go there now. Well,
not right now. Finish the show first and then go. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, I want to thank the fun
people who support us over on Patreon. Absolutely. These people all scored a goal against my son's
team in the three on three. Angela Chan, Peter McDougal, Gelato Steve, Rodimus Scoop, Nikki
Benoit, Scoop Chang the Beijing Bugle, Scoop of Root Canal, All-Star Scoop, Coach Rat Bastard,
Coconut Time Travel, Cream City Scoop, Doc Scoop, Edla Scoop, Erotic Scrape Scoop, Freeze Dried
Scoop, Gelato Problems, Genetics Scoop, Greater Sunday Scoop, House Dad Scoop, Mississippi
Churning Scoop, One Fell Scoop, P.E. Scoop, Petty Officer Scoop, Quiet Quiet Scoop, Salt Lake Scoop,
Scoop Bucky, Scoop Emily, Scoop Skywalker, Scoop Mids, Scoop Nick, and Scoopy Bartfast.
The following people think a flat tire on a rental car is not that big of a deal. Evil Monkey,
Gerardo Garcia, Jacob Dinklelaker, Jason Horcastis, Jason Speckland, Jeff Bizarre,
John Carter, Johnny Parker, Judy Schneider, Kurt Hendrickson, Larry Goodale, Leon Cox,
Logan C., Mario Rosa, Matt Glowacki, Michael Calder, Mike Wenz, Paula, Roger Edge, Sanja Petrovic,
Scoop La Quise, Scoop La Quise rather, uh, Jonathan P., Stab and Dash Scoop, Stephanie Young,
Steven Biggs, Thomas Beach, Tom Krieger, Tom Stott, Tony Cowley, Frozen Cusser, Pete Romano,
Sugar Rush Socio, The Famous Ball, Jenny Ebarb, Macho Scoop, Randy Sprinkles.
The following people, um, uh, all got all the Pittsburgh jokes at the holiday show.
Ian's knows what I'm talking about. Scoopy Scoopy, Jess Jess, Six Foot Scoop, Slightly
Slightly Scoop, Smitty Scoop, Solar Powered Scoop, Sweetest Scoop, Take It Easy Podcast Scoop,
The Last Thing in the Attic, That Thing in the Attic, The Lost Ice Cream Truck Driver,
Water Ice Scoop, Adam Stickney, Adam Jernberg, Brian Richard, Brooks Lyle, Cali Ghost,
Carolyn Albert, Court Myers, David Sorensen, and Derek Dozier.
The following individuals, all Ian's went down the house and moved my parking chair.
The Micro Scoop, Unbanned Scoop, A Ranch Slunk, Ameriscot Scoop, Apple Scoop, AWOL Scoop,
Bad Pirate Scoop, Bear Scoop, Belgian Triple Scoop, Venture Man Scoop, Big Loda Scoop,
Big Sexy, The Digital Nomad, Bike Scoop, uh, Bosun Scoop, Canadian Scoop, Crystal,
and Captain James T. Scoop. And of course, the following
scoops were all accidentally shot in the face while executing the New Jersey Merge.
That's Kargo Van Killa, Coffee Bean Scoop, Cone, Photo Scoop, uh, Photo Rescoopter,
Counselor Matt, Country Scoop, Dave Serial, Dole Whip Scoop, Dippin' Dot Jack, Distiller
Scoop, Don't Say Scoop Name, Fade Out Scoop, Freehold Scoop, Frozen 49th Scoop, Fudgy the Whale,
Galoosha Scoop, Gas Man Scoop, uh, Gaspacho Scoop, Gravel Scoop, Green Wolf Scoop,
Grill Sergeant Scoops, Hatchet Scoops, Hylian Scoop, J Rock Scoop, Keith Robert Corning Scoop,
Kiwi Fruit Scoop, L.A.J. Latter-day Scoop, Lemur Cream, Lemur Screamer Creamer, excuse me,
Lil Red, Mama Ninja Scoop, Matcha Ice Cream Sundae, Matt Scoop-a-Fail, Max the Ginger Scoop,
McTits, Milkleg Scoop, Mitzula, Motor City Smitty, Mr. Head Scoop, Neapolitan, Nice Private Parts,
I'll get back to the list now, Oakey Scoop, Polygon, Pebex Scoop, Phil Tomlinson, Radioactive
Scoop, Refrigerator Perry Scoop, Remember the Ala Mode, Reverend Nick Dingman of the Church of
the Flying Spaghetti Monster, I think is what the rest of that says. Um, maybe Scoop Eddie Monster?
I don't know. Richard Graffiti, Robots Ahoy, and Scabby the Rat Scoop. Thank you all so much. We
sure do love you. Thank you so much. If you want your name read on air, if you want a myriad of
other rewards, then get yourself over to PreachingFun.com and find a tier that you can afford today.
Or if you're listening to this while you're on the field at your three-on-three soccer tournament,
get back to work. You're losing. It's fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our
Patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
This show is dependent on our Patreon supporters. So if you have it in your hearts and you think
this show is worth more than zero dollars, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz. Those are
the places you can go. And then there's all kinds of cool things that happen after you do that. Do
you hang out with us on Zoom? There's all kinds. You get to see like Paul's basement. He gives full
tours of his basement. He introduces you to all of the rodents that are down there. It's a very
sweet thing. It's a super nice, super sweet thing. Head on over there, fartsinabag.biz,
PreachingFun.com. Do it now. It's great. All right. Thanks, everybody. Stay safe out there.
Happy holidays and Merry Christmas. And we'll see you soon. We'll see you soon.
[Music]