Oh hello there I didn't see you but I'm so happy you're here because I'd like
to thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck
drivers it's a new month we don't have a new list yet happy Labor Day by the
well belated I know but we will get to every single person on that ice cream
truck driver list and thank them at this part of the episode before this month is
over so if you want to be an ice cream truck driver help deliver that frickin
ice cream straight to people's frickin ear holes head over to hey scoops dot
com that's wrong head over to preaching fun dot com preaching fun dot com is
where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the
life you save may be your own a program hey Johnny do you want to go to an ice
cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
hey
well well well it's time for Matt and Natalie's ice cream social sitting in
Texas that's Matt Donnelly sitting in Pennsylvania that's Paul Mattingly seeing
the bad guys how's the weather in Texas Matt Donnelly it is a humid it's humid
and kind of rainy oh perfect and I'm back at the magic saloon here in San
Antonio and last time I was here scoops gave us Bucky's shot glasses and there's
one for each of you that forgot to bring home oh wow bring you some Bucky's
adorable glasses thank you yeah I what do you think of Bucky's do you do you go
to Bucky's while you're in Texas um I've been I haven't been I know it's like a
statewide treasure I know people yeah been to Bucky's love of Bucky's and it's
it's I think it's expanding or has expanded to Louisiana as well all I know
is that when I was performing as hillbill I put my baseball cards into a
Bucky's bag and put that out with a fishing pole and people really laughed at
the Bucky's people love the Bucky's bag yeah that makes sense that makes sense
Bucky's for people who don't know is the biggest truck stop you've ever seen in
your life but it's not for truckers it's just for you know regular Joe's driving
their little Toyota Corollas up and down the street yeah so it's ridiculous yeah
they've got smokers they've got smoke shops you can go in there yeah it's all
crazy I think there's one supposed to open up near Las Vegas or like on the
way to Las Vegas or something like that it was a latter-day scoop in the chat
right now is saying supposed to be getting a Bucky's in Utah yeah maybe
maybe that's it yeah can't believe Utah's ahead of Nevada on the Bucky's
list man but that hurts that hurts my feelings I feel like you know we don't
we don't have the the lottery we don't have Bucky's I feel like 20 years from
now we're gonna be dealing with Bucky's like the Walmart situation like how
there are no more gas stations there's just Bucky's it's just Bucky's yeah yeah
oh yeah no yeah for sure oh and Leon Kasab is pointing out in the chat too
that they're they're big Christian no big Christian activists as well and yeah
it's it's tough it's tough no I guess we'll just go to In-N-Out or Domino's
instead yeah you'll be fine we got we got a Sheetz slash Wawa locked down out
here in PA so ain't nobody coming for Sheetz and Wawa I don't think holy
Sheetz oh why the why the Sheetz not that's their current catchphrase stop it
no why why the Sheetz not that's hey hey you want to get ten tacos for $6.99 why
the Sheetz not that's terrible that's what they say oh and they're in their
chicken nuggets are called nuggets chicken nuggets are called schnuggets
cuz that's fine but yeah everything's why the schnuggets makes more sense than
why the Sheetz not schnuggets approved it's approved no problem I'm fine with
schnuggets you got to explain why the Sheetz not because they didn't want to
go with eat my sheets I sheets you not I sheets you not guaranteed to give you
the sheets no bullshit yeah that'd be good Laszlo I could give two sheets these
are all better than why the Sheetz not why does he's not because she's isn't
substitute for the word fuck now it's yeah why is it why the shit not it is
not us is not a phrase oh well I don't know maybe you don't know look if you
talk to my bundled up GI that's every day it's a sheets not it's like it's
like a Rubik's Cube no I'm never I've never wanted to talk to your bowels I
will tell you this one thing I do not suffer from is constipation that has
never been an issue in my life ever ever Paul's Native American name is flowing
river it's absolutely it is mud creek unstoppable maybe it's cuz you're
getting too many schnuggets I haven't eaten a long time haven't eaten it
sheets in a long time but I will tell you this I was betrayed by value
gentlemen oh yes so we went we went last week to to Aldi do you guys have Aldi now
in Vegas we just got it yeah right I haven't been yet but we and I grew up I
grew up with an Aldi around me in Jersey okay so I really like Aldi our Aldi is
good it's got some really great stuff and brother the value just stacks so we're
going long and I'm grabbing some grub here and there picking out a few things
and all these one of these places where you can put in a quarter into the bass
cart and get a bass cart and rent the bass cart what it you just said bass
cart three times what the fuck is a bass cart so I grew up calling them carts yeah
Buggies I see I never call them Buggies they're called no I called them Buggies
they call them Buggies out here okay I always called them carts or baskets yeah
that's fine no they people out here don't know what the hell you're saying
when you say when you say bass cart no one people like I think I only have that
with the sheets that was a snuggies independent film that came out in the
90s about that artist who drew with like maple syrup on his placemat you know
what he was great my dad was a my dad was a grocery man I'm gonna say bass cart
is probably insider terminology that I inherited oh I bet you it is yeah gotta
be I bet you anything because he would you know I just I always called it a
bass cart anyway so I actually when I go shopping I don't deal with any of that
okay I get on like a mechanic sled and I lie on my back and I walk around with
like an Easter basket on my belly and I just shopped that way I just reach I
back around I move around the store that's like that old Richard Simmons
thing right of like only search shop in certain spots in the grocery store and
this is the way to do it you get on your belly on the bound oh yeah only stuff
you can reach from your from laying down that's the only stuff that's safe to eat
anymore yeah so anyway I don't think I've ever heard the term bass cart
before well but yet regional term particularly used in the Pacific
Northwest and other areas for shopping cart or grocery cart I but you for the
smaller one right you're talking about no this is just saying the the big one
the regular size was bass cart because I was accepting the notion that it was an
insider for a different kind of cart right so you get the regular shopping
carts and you get together get the bass carts - I know it's talking about say in
my brain I always just conflated it to being it's a cart that has a wire basket
on it mm-hmm right that was what that was why it was a bass cart that's that's
what it looks like here on the of the old Google yeah so anyway nobody out here
stealing carts or but what about what about what about tiscots or tascots is
anyone stealing those out there yes the blue and yellow ones specifically are
gone you cannot what about my virtue someone stole it a long time ago and I've
been looking for it ever since you're not gonna find it you're not gonna find
it at Aldi pal what about my my pearls has anyone stolen my pearls god damn you
know I think I'm gonna try and incorporate that bit but I think it's
gonna become more common because our power grid is gonna start failing a lot
more often so anyway you don't have to take a cart at Aldi ah bass cart
latter-day scoop we have a picture of a shopping cart filled with bass well done
that's a bass cart for sure good job so well done well you know you don't have
to bring a cart you can just bring your bag okay reusable bag and stick it in
there and then take that to the checkout line and stick it back in the bag which
what I usually do is I don't shop a ton of stuff very rarely do I use a cart you
can also just grab they leave boxes in the front so you just grab a box oh yeah
yeah from the product and throw stuff in a box check out and you're you know kind
of eco-friendly save some time it's nice I like it and also people forget their
quarter sometime and can't rent a cart so they just need to carry a box anyway
we're shopping around and I'm like ooh it's hot dog time there's hot dogs so I
grabbed some hot dogs and I'm looking at the hot dogs and they're like you know
what time it is it's hot dog time hot dogs are maybe maybe three bucks maybe
all right great good and then I look a fair price for a hot dog and right neck
well for eight hot dogs I look right next to these hot dogs and there's
another pack of hot dogs that are an all the in-house brand what how much how low
would you go on a packet you've already gone below the number that I would
once I see three dollar hot dogs I go nope I'm done these these I believe the
I believe the all the hot dogs I believe they were priced at a point where if you
took those up to the cashier the cashier would turn around and give you three
dollars along with the pack of hot well they should have these these boys were
paper these boys were 89 cents wow so I was like Mike Neal said in the chat you
guessed 99 cents you went over my friend I was like you're out according to
price is right rule I gotta try this I gotta see what's up 89 cents let's go
for how many any cheap any cheap yum eight wieners 89 cents so a dime and
change per hot dog yeah I swear to God I'm gonna get diarrhea listening to this
Leon is sending the right gift so uh poor Lindsey so he said sexy Barry
White don't don't come in with 11 cents like my 10 cents and change wasn't good
enough math 10 cents and change so I or 11 cents I had those in the fridge for
a while we hadn't I hadn't gotten to crack them open yet and today yesterday
it's the first of the month time time for the doggies to get their medicine
great and the doggies like their medicine for the most part but one Billy
Bones does not like his heart tick flea worm combo and he only loves his heart
tickin fleas he only takes it with hot dogs so we're like okay well I got these
hot dogs what better way to test them than with the doggies so I crack them
open I put a couple in the microwave and I sent vomit on comes walking a smell
like we have never experienced comes filling filling dog that cost exactly 10
cents and change yeah and you put it in the microwave oh that's the only way I
cook my wieners that's so gross you are a monster you are a monster
person only way I cook my hot dogs is microwave so the smell has infiltrated
the home it's really it's really rough scooper Nova girl and say you are eight
years old scooper Nova girl you are overestimate you're guessing hi so when
you when you bought those hot dogs they're like the savings come with their
own cost there was a monkey's paw yeah storm clouds rolled in as you got into
your car well when I did it and gave me a look was like okay and I found this
pack of hot dogs there were three dollars and something hot dogs like oh my god
what are we gonna do the two dollars and eleven cents we saved from buying
regular hot dogs well and I'd say well about part of a comic book that's
basically it next to these three dollar packs of hot dogs though there was a man
he was his hair was all slicked back and he had on a beautiful black silk suit
and he said Paul he knew my name he said Paul wouldn't you like to save two
dollars and something since he was right and this is where we got old Tom
Jacoby's hot dogs did you say Tom Jacoby oh he died Tom Jacoby died ten years ago
Tom no I just saw him today Matt you'll be happy to know that I did have my dogs
I did hedge my bets and on the way out I also picked up a pack of five straight
up fatty big old what do you call the broth grill dogs big broths you're on
you don't do those in the microwave do you oh yeah what the fuck they're cheese
infused brats Maddie cheese infused brats oh you are cheese infused brats I
passed on a chili infused ones it is like how did you how did you pass on the
chill if you're getting the cheese infused brats and putting them in the
microwave Paul don't pass on the chili infused ones I did I passed on two
pieces anyway we start cutting up these wieners and I'm I have to get pieces
between Bill and Ted basically where they call me when Paul's done I'm gonna
go hey I bought it yeah I start I start pushing I have to push ah push the pill
into the wiener meat to try and disguise it and then I give I give one piece with
pill into the dog's mouth and quickly offer him a second piece no pill so that
he'll wolf it all down cuz half the time Bill is smart he will eat the wiener
around the pill and spit out the pill he's such a little fucker so I get him
face Paul look at his face and I've had Botox this is all right fighting through
let me tell you so much emotion coming through Matt Donnelly's face here's the
problem through a chemical that numbs skin Bill spit out so many pieces that I
had to go in for more hot dogs I had to renew a couple more hot dogs is it
possible that Bill also hates your fucking new the second the sec now he
loves them this is the thing I was like and these things think so bad that the
dogs are gonna go crazy hot dogs it makes me fart like makes that already
gets it going yeah Matt Matt Matt microwave hot dogs I mean do you boil
water and boil them on the stove is that your move grill them like a human being
grill them where am I gonna grill a hot oh like on a pan that's a lot of stuff
barbecue grill man that's a lot of work no thank you nothing easier than
grilling a barbecue I would argue putting a putting a hot dog into the microwave
for a minute is far easy Paul Paul let me let me help you out here buddy let me
help you out go to Walmart today get you a George Foreman grill and just be done
with life no these are gross I would accept the George Foreman grill from you
right now I'm not I'm not gonna accept the hot dog in the microwave it's a meat
skin issue okay yes what's it what you don't like what happens on the tech
thing should be crispy well it gets crispy sometimes no that's impossible in
the microwave no you're lying to yourself but you're talking to a guy who
loves the texture of pudding skin so that's kind of what I've got with the
microwave wiener if that's your level crunch from a hot dog I'm gonna bite
into a hot dog with crunch gross you're a Nathan's guy huh yeah yeah no fuck that
shit I don't like me yeah I pay a whole 389 at Aldi's for a Nathan's hot dog you
like you like you like a natural casing do you also use lambskin condoms is that
how you roll I only I only eat lambskin condoms yeah but off you go grill you go
to go to Aldi buy some lambskin condoms go to IKEA and fill it with a bunch of
meatballs and my empty could you eat all the meatballs full of IKEA meatball I
stuff stuff a brat into a lambskin condom and I double grill it's like that's how
you get that extra crisp it's like a twice baked potato yeah that'd be more
like a jacketed potato right so so I get this wiener and I'm breaking up the
pieces of it and this is the second time it's been in the microwave a sec in the
chat is asking for a scoop fest refund because of the store and is like and is
like dear God we had to turn the fan on on the window to blow air out of the
house because it was so stank it was awful and then so oh I've been I've been
cutting up and squishing all these wieners and this is this is how you know
it's bad waiters again this is how you know it's bad I threw away what was left
I threw away the other four wieners you threw away you threw a 44 cents worth of
wieners never throw away food I don't throw away stuff I don't I rarely do
these were so bad I was like fuck this I can't I can't possibly but finally got
microwave his winners maddingly found the bridge too far
Leon said that fucking gift from I think you should leave is so good so I finally
got bill to take all his pill finally got all of it done everybody ate meat
torturing your dog I'll tell you I'll tell you what the cost was the cost was
the unmistakable stench of a dead cow's penis on my hands after four washings it
was still there it smelled like from under cheese at the circus it was so
bad anymore fucking bad I don't like the stink on my fingers would not I put dawn
soap on it I put all kinds of soft soap on it I I contemplated giving my fingers
an Epsom salt bath because it was that how it permeated my flesh look Paul do
you guys buy sponges you have sponges in your kitchen I do have sponges yeah you
get the sponges with the rough side on the back of it mm-hmm get those put a
little bit of dish soap on it and use that scrubby side to scrub your hands I
mean and you have to like you have to really scrub into it but that's that's
all I get like it would sit on your hands did you let the dawn liquid sit on
your hands did I let it sit on my hand or did you soak your hands and like
dish one oh remember remember the palm olive when you would soak your hands in
it remember that yeah who yeah that's that was a thing that ladies did Paul I
figured out who made your hot dogs who Al Qaeda Al Qaeda made your hot dogs
Al Qaeda Al Qaeda hot dogs everybody loves I'll have Al Qaeda Al Qaeda hot
dogs this is this movie up a wiener from somewhere in a cave there are people
celebrating the victory of selling those hot dogs and getting the permeate an
American household here's the thing and my investigative journalist wife we're
going to collapse them from within she quickly she quickly while she sat on the
couch many feet away from the kitchen smelling the death and trails she went
ahead and jumped online to find out what is going on with these wieners she found
a reddit a reddit thread apparently they changed the recipe on these just like
two months ago all right everybody is like dear God what is this this is not a
hot dog this is the phallus smelling things it is the nastiest thing people
were like I've been buying these for a long time now they're really disgusting
we looked on the ingredients there were all these weird our hot dogs will fly a
plane right into your taste buds they really did the secret ingredient is cat
shit says fro yag and he's right it was nasty there's all like cumin and lots of
powders and I don't I don't know like for a while it was like chicken and beef
for the top ingredients they're not anymore
yeah never forget the flavors right oh god yes he looked at the ingredients
after he was done yeah well I didn't eat any well and dared me to eat a little
bite and I ate a little bite and it was so nasty when was the last time you
purchased something from a grocery store that your wife then had to dare you to
eat or cause her to me they get on reddit to figure out what was going on
when I've been into it I chewed up a little bit it was like it was like kind
of like a falafel meat if it had been on a New York sidewalk for a couple days
like a gyro you mean yeah like a gyro but like really like I'm like somebody
stepped on this here gyro this big cut like the gyros that would come with it
would just be like the weird gray meat you never you never quite knew where it
came from yes yes yeah yeah yeah just a rotating pile of something yeah so it
was it was bad and and she was looking up all these different people saying oh
god these these hot dogs just are are the nastiest thing I've ever eaten this
is gross I don't know what's going on with this and then the kicker was she
looked on the on the bag to find out what the branding and everything it's an
all-the-in-house thing but she saw on the packaging it says explicitly do not
recycle this plastic
labels that says hey this plastic is not recyclable no but this one was like
warning what did it say why I can tell you my theory okay it's contaminated
there's something horribly wrong with it oh anyway it was really gross it was
really really bad oh I just did a search on our new Aldi hot dogs good is oh yeah
search that okay yeah one of the lines is people have had experience with bad
experiences with recent quality issues like the hot dogs being too greasy okay
too small okay or leaking yeah what a horrible adjective leaking the hot dogs
are leaking people hot dogs our kind of hot dogs the leaky is tweener you can
buy mom call the cops the hot dogs are leaking the hot dogs are leaking put
your thumb in it I mean this is sort of canary in the coal mine times though
guys we're on the front we're on the front lines of do not give those hot dogs
any canaries very relaxed very oh there's there they're probably 10% canary
very relaxed FDA guidelines at this point you know our food safety is gonna
go we're getting rid of red dye number five or whatever sure we are sure we are
and replacing it with important important asbestos from Russia pureed
sea turtle yeah huh you know who else is eating the leaky hot dog lately that's
the following sponsor today's show Matt and Madeline's ice cream social is
brought to you by Jacob's guide to taking notes on how things are sexy but
not sexual how young is too young and to make this distinction this is Jacob's
number one fan scoop submitting this in 2024 once again that product is so the
the name is Jacob's number one fan scoop that's who submitted this okay
November of 2024 good it's Jacob's guides to taking notes on how things are
sexy but not sexual how young is too young to make this distinction I don't
know the last I don't the tagline to at all hey listen no hundred percent this
is what it is what it is is bananas I'm talking about bananas now they're sexy
right they're not sexual I mean you can use them but I wouldn't but they're kind
of sexy right but how young is too young green green means too young if there's
green on the matter don't play ball that's all you gotta do that's that's
simple rule just stay away from green manners also leaky wieners stay away
from green manners and leaky winners mean too young too young I mean I'm an
old grandpappy pappy van Winkleman so give me my old man on drinks I want my
old all my drinks should be named after a very old gentleman all I want in my
mouth is elderly men that's it I don't know I'm gonna drink any young people
elderly men slurp gulp let's go papa van Winkle gentleman Jack dusty old
granddad's hat box fart McGee and terrible terrible uncle Arthur those are
my favorite one terrible uncle Arthur's tantrums is the most fierce whiskey I've
ever had terrible uncle Arthur's tantrums I guess I got a case of that
shit oh they bottle it in Lithuania I found out and they only sell it after
it's been aged for 40 months in the open air they don't have any they just leave
it out in a bucket in a very thin very shallow bucket terrible uncle Arthur's
awful tantrums or something like that it's called I can't remember exactly how
I phrased it uncle Arthur's terrible tantrum whiskey go ahead and get some of
that what it's basically they put it on I get you some they they age it in a bed
pan open open face bed pan 100% it check out you put those bananas and lambskin
condoms crispy I went and saw the Wizard of Oz at the sphere last night we
should have been sled with that we shouldn't talked about hot dogs for the
a block you know what you know what I just gave you 20 minutes of gold from a
fucking rotten pigs asshole shut up liquid fire shit gold is what you gave
me my also make Wizard of Oz the a block but then we fell into this pile of gold
and I can tell you this Judy Garland doesn't microwave up half as nice as an
Aldi wiener that is true that is true you take that she's real sticky you take
that back you don't disparage my Judy
holy shit the sphere is still amazing yeah the sphere remains amazing they I
I think they might have found their thing I think they might have found
their thing that's gonna make money every day when they don't have concerts
in that building just reboot movies I specifically this one this is okay so
that it's so weird so it's not the whole movie they have taken the movie they
have edited out big chunks of it so the whole thing is only like 70 minutes I
think huh I think I think the whole movie about 70 minutes they've used you
know there's a ton of AI there's a ton of processing there's all these things
because basically they're taking all the scenes that are zoomed in so like if
you're if you're zoomed in on Annie M for instance in one scene where she's
standing in a room talking to people you don't just see her zoomed in you see the
whole room of filled with filled with like whoever's in the room that she's
talking to you got it so they they took things from the movie they took
implications from the movie and expanded those out and fleshed those out it was
really neat a lot of AI stuff a lot of a fit not a lot but a fair amount of
background characters I don't know how you guys are watching movie and TV
scenes with big groups of people I find myself always watching the extras I
think we've talked about this before oh no I don't they're little people I only
look at the stars
little people is the right thing to say yeah yeah guys eat all the hot dogs you
fuckers oh no no eat shit it's better for you that's it that's the new curse
all the hot dogs upon your house oh god the worst thing your house will be
uninhabitable it'll smell too bad yeah no I look at background characters in
fact that's actually my kids will do that too and they actually discovered
their own grandmother and numerous scenes because they realized that back
when my my mother-in-law was doing a bunch of background work all the time
right up in the background of some of their favorite shows and she'd forgotten
she'd done that show or something it's very yeah she had forgotten that she had
animated herself into spongebob squarepants she was an extra on it so
this is where they're using you know whatever AI technology CGI technology to
create you know larger groups that fill the whole screen and stuff like that
right that's right and they're making a whole new scenes and intro scenes like
when the when the house lands in Oz instead of just opening like like in the
in the movie Dorothy opens the door to the to the house that just landed and she
walks out into Oz she walks out into munchkin land in this there's the whole
storm scene and by the way they've got you know huge wind machines and snow and
all kinds of shit falls on you and the chairs vibrate and it's a whole 4d
experience but on a 20,000 seat scale instead of 100 seat scale at the at the
fair or whatever so it's really all this stuff they they start the movie after
Dorothy has already interacted with mrs. Gulch with the witch so like they start
the movie a good 15 minutes in basically they start the movie about two minutes
before she's seeing somewhere over the rainbow mm-hmm so I mean they just skip
through a lot of stuff but I mean it is it is neat and there it was full you
know 20,000 people in there or however many people they have is their occupancy
for the for the movie stuff well it's already it was like you know it's it's
doing the number one tourism thing which is people plan trips around coming out
to see it right and apparently we were talking to a buddy of mine who's one of
the people who run the show over there he was saying they've already sold over
400,000 tickets jeez Lord yeah so like they're just you know I mean because we
went to the show last night that was their second show of the nighters
that's every Raiders game for the season for the thousand yeah close yeah close
to right right that ballpark yeah for sure well I'll tell you what's
encouraging to me is seeing is seeing so many of my local friends getting acting
work inside the theater as extras and sort of like guests and hosts and all
that kind of thing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah a bunch of people a bunch of
people I know are working yeah I was like wow like Marcus is there and yeah
I saw a picture I was like this is just like a who's who of people I've worked
with in the past this is cool yeah yeah so well it eliminates all these other
shows and jobs it's nice that they picked up our friends on the way which
is good that's right well I mean we didn't talk about that last night we
talked about that with with a friend of ours James last night he was like oh no
one of the guys running the show he was like all these great shows in town and
we're just selling fuck tons of tickets I know it's hurting the other shows in
town yeah yeah I was like yeah it's true but I mean it's also part of it you know
it's biggest goes through changes and that's the song we all think of when we
hear changes and you know like every show you have every every casino you
have a production show right right like used to have some kind of big big show
that song song and dance and you'd have five every song every casino hired 50
dancers and sure just went away they dance on the Decca Lee Titanic watt-sank
that's right that's what it lasted longest Jubilee right yeah but but
everybody you know even the Penn and Teller theater the Rio used to have a
production show in there and that's why it's like such a big backstage area for
Penn and Teller it's because it always used to be also they used to also split
it with dance with a dance team yeah so it's you know it is interesting that
like you know Cirque du Soleil has been open for you know 30 40 years right in
this town right and and so you know it's interesting that like a literal death
star got built in the middle of the strip and you're like oh no but that's a
license they still haven't gotten they still haven't been able to just make
themselves into the Death Star this is when you're talking about the way you're
talking about this very experience this this was Star Trek this is Star Trek the
experience oh yeah yeah especially I mean the dome was what they built you in the
I don't know you went to that listen motherfucker they built the dome for the
original Klingon encounter which worked with the the actual motion ride carts
all right the vehicles and then when they put in 4d only the ending of that
was a theatrical 4d experience but it had seats that would poke you in the
ass and squirt you with water and shoot you with air and stuff oh dude I mean it
didn't have the dick sucking alien like I would propose we're getting there
we're getting there eventually it'll every day we're a little bit closer to
that dick-sucking alien did you see it happened at the corn concert did you see
it see what specifically there was a guy at a corn concert up in the up in the
nosebleeds jacking it during going at it during this is going whole hogs her in
the show and a bunch of people like hey dude knock it off and he's like no I'm
getting there like he went he went to completion on him he didn't give a damn
yeah so like the last corn that sir is the second nastiest thing that's been
discussed on this show today that is horrible so I don't know I didn't know
Lucy Kate likes corn everybody likes corn Matt all right they're hard to
digest though okay so all right Vegas politics and entertainment see change
and all that stuff aside yes let's get it what's getting the actual experience
of going to see Wizard of Oz we get that they open the doors I think 45 minutes
early so we get there they have decked out they've added a whole bunch of stuff
to the lobby so there's all new LEDs and all there's a mini sphere in the lobby
that people in the zoom chat just saw a minute ago so that they do all kinds of
Wizard of Oz scenes on that after the movie is over that's when they do a live
performance they do they do live performance afterwards you get to like
interact with the wizard they've got a huge hologram an interactive hologram of
the wizard that appears out in the lobby and sorry Jacob breaking news we're
getting updates in the chat about the guy jerking off with the corn concert
turns out people were punching him in the back of the head and trying to try
to basically stop him they were trying to stop him he did I don't think they
stopped him what they didn't realize was featuring out a bug to the guy Jack
like he's like he loves a good donkey punch he's like oh yeah no don't hit me
no please oh I hate that you're hitting me so much human contact certainly won't
put me over the edge no definitely not with strangers so was Darren the the
wizard when you were there Darren was not the wizard when I was there but our
friend James Simpson was he was the the guard the you know you can't see the
wizard nobody sees the wizard not nobody not know how that James is the used to
work at 50 shades right yes yeah yeah yeah you know James yeah he's good guy
very good yeah we even got we even got a special little just us picture with with
James and the wizard and in their costumes oh that's awesome yeah it's on
SJ's phone or I'd show it to you James James knows everyone everyone knows yes
yes he is one of those workhorses for Vegas that's right like every show yes
that's right so we were there it is so what I want to talk about it's so weird
to watch a movie that assumes that everyone is not only already seen that
movie but that everyone is very familiar with it yeah yeah yeah so like like I
said earlier like the movie doesn't start with all of the setup that the
real movie starts with it doesn't start with you're getting to know the
characters it doesn't it they're like you know these characters we all know
that you know these characters we're gonna skip over this part we're not
gonna have this 20 minutes in the movie where we get to know Dorothy and Annie
M and uncle Henry and all these people like you don't need to know that you
know who these people are we're going straight over the rainbow she's gonna do
the over the rainbow then pretty quickly after that we're gonna see Gulch she's
gonna be there trying to take the dog dogs gonna get away and we're going to
Oz so like 10 minutes in their defense we're there you have done you have like
80 years to see the original version you know I'm not really I'm not criticizing
it but it is the first time I've ever seen something that assumes that you
already know the full story of the thing that you're watching well the ruby
slippers are still the number one most valuable movie prop in existence oh they
have to be they are I'd be I'd be surprised if anything else was close to
it well I think they might get usurped soon possibly depends on what I just saw
that by what Jacob what do you think is gonna get you serpent go ahead oh okay I
think it'll be the giant robot from Pacific Rim Luke Skywalker's lightsaber
handle yeah you're closer there Matt yeah it's an original screen used Vader
lightsaber that is going up for sale oh Leon Kassab says that Rosebud is the
number two most expensive prop yes found in the trash that that makes sense too
yeah it was we don't want to any spoilers for citizen Kane to anyone has
not yet seen citizen Kane go ahead fast forward about 15 seconds while we do all
the spoilers for citizen Kane yeah I think the the next sphere show so make
sure you vote up on it I think absolutely no kidding around go to the
sphere to watch this again oh that'd be amazing actually I do that today that'd
be great I maybe don't get that that'd be really cool it would be really good
they could do a lot of crazy shit with citizen Kane so watching this movie with
the assumption watching a watching a movie play that is assuming that I don't
need to get any information from the movie is a weird experience already and
then watching a movie that I have seen I mean who knows how many times I've seen
the Wizard of Oz in my life I mean probably hundreds if not thousands of
times back when we were kids it was on TV at least once a year of course yeah
and I would watch it all yeah it was a big man TV yeah I've embarrassed my mom
by saying this before but my mom did famously asked me one time a few years
ago when they colorized the the middle part of Wizard of Oz oh my and I had to
break it to her that they had not colorized it they that's how the movie
had been made it was the first part in sepia and second part in color she said
oh no no no when I was a little girl it was all in black and white mmm I said
mom no no no when she was watching it she was watching it at her home on a
black and white television me exactly so it was all black and white just only for
her oh people who watched it on black and white TVs I was like now you were
watching in the black just you just be the family be carving up the recently
microwaved hot dog and they'd watch it watch it over at the old black and white
TV Thanksgiving math they never had the luxury of microwaved hot dogs in the
50s I didn't know the joys of the pudding just good a metal spirit through
it and put two lighters on both ends they did do that shit they fucking would
fork it and cook it like that all crazy that crazy remember do you ever see that
walk and cooked hot dog over a fire still sounds better than microwaved hot
dog sure did you ever see that hot dog cooker that you could put in your car
yes see that shit yeah it plugged into the fucking lighter and you could cook
hot dogs in your car like a monster now that's as good as the booze fridges
though the booze fridges that were built into the car well boy those were the
days you get like the the refrigerator built into the glove compartment and
shit yeah oh so good this is where you keep your martini shaker while you're in
the car they had that they had booze fridges hot dog cookers yeah places
where you could shit and smoke prostitute prostitute dumpers old cars
had it all man I was just the trunk yeah well I mean but it was sold as a
prostitute dumper nobody nobody carried their trunks back then yeah they didn't
call it the trunk they called it the prostitute dumper yeah we call it the
truck before I take it for a test drive how many gallons is this prostitute
dumper oh this is an 80 gallon prostitute dumper all right there's a lot
of prostitute dumper in there so I can get probably what three prostitutes in
there oh four four petite ones four petite prostitutes before I have to take
her in for servicing absolutely sir all right all right I'll take it good sir
you won't be you won't be disappointed and because you got it today just after
Labor Day I'm gonna throw in two prostitutes in the prostitute dumper free
of charge Wow prostitutes get the dumper start the hot dog machine and grab
yourself a cold seltzer oh I love seltzer well I have some cold seltzer in
my booze cabinet but only the seltzer is for the prostitutes toots don't get
booze no booze for toots no booze for toots no booze for toots
toots in the boot that's what the UK's called the boots called the toot boot oh
I'll tell you who else has put prostitutes in the boot of the car not
in the trunk just in the prostitute dump today's show is brought to you by hey
poops.com horse laxatives hay poops.com horse laxatives that's from rich scoop
in 2024 hello I'm mr. ed I haven't taken a good number two in a minute and what
I really need a constitutional high reach for hey poops the only laxative
guaranteed to put a pep back in your filly step oh good God Wilbur I'm tired
of my trainers reaching in feet deep with their gloved arms and grabbing at
whatever remains inside my digestive tract I've had full full bales of hay
pulled undigested from my lower colon and that's the game I don't want to play
anymore no this old sway back needs himself some help getting his sway back
if you know what I mean so give me some of that laxative that's maxative give
me some of that poop firing in spire in dump building no killed in fart
producing lumpy horse-juicing yeah I need me some of that hey poops
digestive make your shit hey hey poops it'll make your shit hey oh god oh oh no
oh I took a double dose and I've prolapsed oh no help me I'm inside sir you
have to leave the studio now well come on let me stay my anus is hanging out
here like an Aldi hot dog yeah that is part of the reason I need you to leave
you smell almost as bad as a microwaved Aldi hot dog look I've got a bag for it
oh oh that's fine I bring this I bring this bag and bass cart to tote around my
prolapsed anus you know people come to me after listening to this show they say how do you guys
come up with all this material writing meetings and sit around and really really
come up with different ideas and really workshop them and everything I go no we
actually come up with everything right there on the fly we just we just go
through and we talk about stuff and we have conversations and sometimes it
takes us to fun places like a horse a talking horse with us we don't we don't
think about that at all before the show starts that's just what comes up but
it's all we'll think about after no no still the second most disgusting things
that on this show basically got a radio flyer wagon designed specifically to
carry what's there - how do you carry your - I carry mine in a flyer way thank
you radio flyer what I like about the radio flyer it's the color match the
color matches pretty good it's fairly it's fairly unobtrusive and people who
don't know wouldn't wouldn't even know it's like I'm not wearing anything at
all it's very inconspicuous Wizard of Oz thumbs up worth going very expensive
expensive but but a fun ticket and definitely a different experience than
anything I've seen I think anywhere before right yeah yeah it's a crazy
thing it's a crazy thing for sure so you thought you think they're just gonna
like well I mean I guess they're gonna keep cranking that one is there is it an
indefinite run I think so yeah yeah I think it'll run until people stop buying
thousands of tickets for it I actually know it's not even fully finished that's
true they're still adding they're still gonna be adding more things to it yeah
and they're selling stuff is there a merch thing associated oh definitely oh I
got a shirt I got a Wizard of Oz shirt for sure yeah you know me and my merch
laughs at me every time we go to a concert or something Jacob will go buy
the merch is it a is it specifically sphere themed there's one t-shirt where
you it says you putting a pill into a hot dog meat for Toto mm-hmm they got
that in there Oh Oh if you don't eat this pill you'll get fleas and ticks I
know it makes my hands smell like the underside of a hobo's rectum but please
just have it just the underside yes the underside of the uncovered underside of
the whole underside of a hobo's rectum yes it smells like Binda leavings
enter a scoop to check out yeah yeah not totally finished with your scoop is it's
what they're calling it's in its edging phase it's in its right phase the
Wizard of Oz I also ran into a friend of mine we went to the sphere with our
cousins who were in town and they were laughing at us actually the same thing
that we were talking about with James earlier they were like holy shit is it
fun going out to entertainment things with Jacob and SJ because we just see
people that we know the entire time of course so one of the people that we ran
into was the artistic director from over at the new area 15 universal horror
nights and yeah so she like they've just gotten opened over there they're
cranking it out I think they're still gonna make some changes over there I
don't think they're done just like the sphere so I mean it is that that gives me
a little bit of hope when we're talking about the the entertainment jobs going
away and yeah oh yeah there's all there's old stuff that's getting hurt
but there's always new stuff coming in as well so it's always a fun it's funny
that you mentioned that getting going around getting recognized and being the
gad about that she is and working in all these coffee shops she is also
becoming like well-renowned we went sure we went to the Thai place for lunch
yesterday she goes in the first time my name's Anne the first person to see this
is a former employee of hers and they're having a nice sweet conversation the
whole time and then as she's walking we're walking us to a table a long-time
customer says oh hey I thought that was you and so she's just she's getting know
everybody in this Berg it's amazing so it's really lovely it's really lovely
somebody should know everybody in Pittsburgh she's very popular she's very
popular well she's in the Autobot Society she is brother a member in good
standing how much more popular do you want to be can't be much more popular
I'll tell you what's gonna make you very unpopular how badly you're gonna do with
this Jack versus nerd suck eggs how long till I'll take the OZ I'll take the egg
smell I'll take the sucking egg smell over the explosion of nuked meats I'm
gonna tell you right now I had a whole other jock versus nerd picked out today
I changed it over to this one once we start talking about the hot dogs okay
this is from Leon Kasab good afternoon gentlemen here is my brand new Mikey style quiz
oh that I am titled real or fake food brands okay I was inspired by another
podcast I listen to that will occasionally cover press releases for
new products from food change chains it is an endless well of what the fuck I
think it could be nicely modified into a Mikey style quiz rules are simple is
this food item real or fake I will provide a description that has come
directly out of a press release or news story on the product or description that
I made up you know how it works I'm pretty proud of this one enjoy so is
Leon and Leon is happy with this one so I'm gonna give you a food description
you're gonna tell me if it's real or fake okay Pizza Hut the world's largest
pizza company is bringing together two of America's most popular treats Paul
pizza and hot dogs in the form of its all-new hot dog bites pizza the American
rendition of the popular global pie features 28 premium mini hot dog bites
baked into the crust and is served with a side of French's mustard is this real
or fake it goes to me sure yeah it's real Paul says real Matt I agree it's
real we are committed to bringing more flavor and fun to the pizza category
than anyone else and our new hot dog bites pizza is an absolutely epic flavor
mashup inspired by two of America's favorite foods says Jared drink water
vice president of marketing at Pizza Hut last year Americans ate an estimated
150 million hot dogs over the July 4th holiday we've taken the appropriate
steps to notify the National Sausage and Hot Dog Council that they will need to
adjust their statistics for 2015 thanks to Pizza Hut's induction into hot dog
bites pizza that's horrible someone in the chats as they ate it and did not
enjoy it really interesting that's the person who didn't enjoy that first thing
I think of when I think of pizza is hot dog all right we got a one-to-one tie
right now Matt you're up first on this one and oh good news Matt it's Starbucks
somebody says hot dog I say so as you saw from the first one these are from all
they're not necessarily present so the the hot dog pizza I guess it was on 15
hot dogs on a pizza hey you got it possible he got a pretty good idea Jimmy
why don't we try to Jimmy Matt is Starbucks gravy latte real or fake
description this holiday season Starbucks is introducing the Thanksgiving
latte a savory beverage combining rich turkey breast broth with steam milk top
sage infused foam pair it with your favorite pie slice for the ultimate
festive indulgence pie slice as you know I get the fuck out of here as we know
Starbucks sits around and just daydreams about women in giant SUVs sitting at a
drive-thru for 20 minutes and that's right and pulling out something that has
a specific color and so this fits none of those categories and so I'm going to
say false false fake any fake I will say they do some stupid shit in the name of
capitalist chicanery that fucking CEO that came in a while back and he knew a
guy who knew a guy who had a fuck ton of olive oil they started putting olive oil
in some of the lattes like that was a thing like anybody ever put a fucking stupid
not a thing but they actually played nationally rolled that out sold lattes
with olive oil in it get the fuck out of here but no there's no way there's
gravy fucking coffee no they are doing protein foam which is close to gravy I
make some of that at home I make my home protein foam double crisp double crisp
the protein foam that means that is fake it is still tied two to two the holiday
special number three for you Paul okay scoffee cup from KFC scoffee cup scoffee
scoffee cup from KFC okay have you ever desired a sweet snack while you're
drowning that morning coffee on the run but really can't afford to use your other
hand to hold it well Kentucky Fried Chicken has a game-changer for you and
the fast food chain is pushing the limits of what we consider a beverage
container with its latest announcement it's called the scoffee cup an edible
cup made out of a wafer biscuit wrapped in sugar paper and lined with a heat
resistant white chocolate no phony baloney Paul says phony baloney Matt I
sure baloney phony let's go for it I would drink this the answer it's real
shut the fuck up what if our customers occasionally like to have their cake and
eat it why wouldn't we want them to have their cup and eat it instead that's from
KFC spokeswoman Jocelyn boney maybe told the USA Today the cups also feature
aromas and come with the scents coconut suncream and freshly cut grass the those
last few descriptions are disgusting but that is a lawsuit waiting to happen I
don't think rolled it out nationally though I don't feel like I think it's not
I've never seen that in my neighborhood yeah I don't know I don't know if that's
a current thing or a past thing I think that thing failed miserably well it's so
Leon Casaba saying it's British he wrote this thing so there you go but that
makes sense now thinking about it as it's a scone cup it's not scoffee that
does make sense right it's pot scone pot cup in it it allot me a cup a lot me a
scone why not we do both for the same thing governor give me a scoff a scoffee
it's probably pronounced scoffee oh I messed you up Paul I'm sorry tonight yes
when you said they scoffee I was like scoffing at their customers no I don't
Paul will continue this game of jock versus nerd under protest I don't give
up number four the nightmare King sandwich from Burger King math is for
you Burger King says its new sandwich is clinically proven to induce nightmares
in time for Halloween the fast foods change chains Nightmare King is
available through November 1st at participating locations nationwide this
spooky sandwich features a quarter pound of flame grilled meat a white meat
crispy chicken fillet melted American cheese thick cut bacon creamy mayonnaise
and onions on a glazed green sesame seed bun true Matt says true Paul what he's
saying true it is true according to previous studies 4% of the population
experiences nightmares on any given night says dr. lead say Bob and oh I
guess they really did a study after eating the Nightmare King the data
obtained from the study indicated that the incidence of nightmares increased by
3.5 times after eating that sandwich I believe you is the nightmare diarrhea
Latter-day scoop yes is this always the nightmare is this some fucking CIA shit
what is going on here this is CIA shit yeah MK ultra yeah yeah no I checked it
out it's MK ultra CIA shit okay that's what I did in president galactic
superstar Paul peanut butter infused water from a combination of Reese's and
Dasani two of America's favorite brands have combined combined to provide the
new peanut butter infused water a first-of-its-kind hydration experience
combining the crisp purity of Dasani spring water with subtle creamy peanut
butter undertones of Reese's cups peanut butter designed to provide flavor
protein and hydration for your next workout well Dasani is the worst water
so I would put nothing beyond them okay they they will do anything they have no
all has a stand and he will take it I will say this is a legit thing I'll say
yes Paul says legit Matt false it is false huh I'm struck I'm up to baby I'm
up to are you got me all choked up there Matt I'm so excited for your for your
lead Matt maple bacon glazed pop-tarts Kellogg's pop-tarts are getting savory
with maple bacon glaze a flaky toaster pastry filled with smoky bacon flavored
filling and topped with a sweet maple flop frosting breakfast just got bolder
this sounds like breakfast for every hockey player in Canada to me so I'm
gonna say yes yeah I hope that happens it's fake I'm sorry you can't keep you
can't keep baking in packets you can't keep baking won't last you can't you
can't keep the bacon packed up nope someone call Horton someone call Tim
Horton's I'd see Paul house wine and cheese it box the limited edition
product is a one-part delicious box of original cheez-its one part original red
blend box of house wine offered in a convenient package the innovative
pairing highlights the cheesy crunchy satisfaction packed into every cheese at
cracker and couples it with the red current aromas and juicy red fruit
delivered in a house wines original red blend a house wine and cheese it box is
the perfect pairing to all of your summer activities from music festivals to
beach parties to picnics and family barbecues this is Paul first this is what
this is you first Paul who who makes the wine it's a company called house wine
according to this house wine is the is the brand interesting is there it is
their red blend well I will say my last shift at the old Tarjay we just
unloaded a big old bunch of a new cheese it that's being unleashed
baconator flavor it's a Wendy's combo baconator cheese it so cheese it is not
above this I will say yes they are doing this this is real all right showed his
math and everything Matt I say it's real also it is real we are thrilled to
partner with house wine to combine their expertise and America's favorite one
hundred percent real cheese snack into one portable box chef delonis senior
marketing director for Kellogg's US snacks division many of our fans were
already exploring pairing different wines with cheese it's just like wine
and cheese you can build you can you can pair real cheese inside each cheese it
flavor with the perfect wine complement and find a pair to enjoy all summer long
so these cheese it in this box wine company are trying to break into the
charcuterie board market I guess yeah man they're like they're they're higher
their upper crust class their executive class I guess even Eames even Eames in
the chat brought up an image of it already there it is they're gonna be
selling that on the princess cruises it's a real deal I don't see why let's
do one more here cat and crunch delights from Taco Bell this item is Taco Bell's
first variation on Cinnabon delights a cream filled donut hole reminiscent of
Cinnabon's cinnamon rolls the new cat and crunch delights are a donut hole
version of a bowl of cat and crunch berries cereal with milk the pastry
evokes a giant crunch berry with the familiar flaming pink color not found in
nature the cream filling represents sweet cereal milk and the pastry is
rolled in a coating of crushed cat and crunch cereal yeah I know whatever it is
it sounds super healthy well I don't if this is this supposed to be ad copy or
just yeah that would be their ad copy or their their press release but they
wouldn't say they wouldn't say not found in nature I don't think oh
interesting that's my and the my other thought is Cinnabon having the the name
of that stuff like they're not gonna share that with another company unless
they're owned by the same parent company which I don't know they could be because
there's only like four companies but I'm good is it my guess no it's Matt's guess
okay but you're doing great yeah Paul give me a lot of help there I'm gonna
guess fake yeah Paul I too say fake Matt you got you got Paul the answer is real
oh shit I should have called it say real with Paul the rest of the way yeah the
new breakfast item went into test Tuesday at units in Bakersfield
California names to bring back sugary childhood memories of cat crunches
crunch berry cereal it's a nostalgic throwback brand from when you were a
kid said Amanda Clark Taco Bell's senior director of marketing we feel like it
will appeal to what we call kiddults or the kid adults out there about what the
hell what the hell kind of person would that be what do they mean what could
they possibly be talking about kiddult that whatever whatever that sounds like
some made-up bullshit that sounds like some kiddult get the fuck it fuck you
talking about that's that's bullshit craziness we got two more to do here
let's let's wrap them up Gatorade pickle punch Paul oh god
description hydration meets brine with pickle punch a new limited edition
Gatorade flavor formulated for athletes who swear by pickle juice for cramps
electrolytes combined with zesty dill in this bold refreshment man Gatorade
pickle punch being out here in the Berg everything gets pickled up okay they
have a fucking pickle festival pickles Berg they call it pickles Berg sure
everybody puts pickle on everything everything is pickle nobody puts pickle
in the corner limited edition Gatorade pickle I must say I know I bet that's
gonna be nasty tasting I'm gonna say no just cuz I think it's nasty and Paul
thinks it's nasty so he thinks it doesn't exist Matt true it is false now
got exciting now we're back down to a nail biter going only up by one right
the last question last question this one goes to Matt first
Tostino's salsa cereal there is no better snack duo on game day Tostino's
chips and salsa appearing so beloved that even die-hard football fans are
willing to take their eyes off the game to get the perfect bite but this season
Tostino's and legendary wide receiver Julian Edelman are changing the game
and introducing the most creative way to snack Tostino's salsa cereal for those
asking themselves what salsa cereal is it's exactly what it sounds like eating
chips and salsa with a bowl and a spoon it's a clever twist on the classic chips
and salsa pairing that has been a game day staple for decades but makes it
easier than ever for football fans to enjoy the game without ever needing to
miss a second of the action plus milk plus milk what the fuck
Matt you're up first false Tostino's salsa cereal false in Matt's opinion Paul
I'll tell you what gamesmanship and the only other thing is they included the
name of a player that could just do nobody could have included the name of
an NFL player without it being real no I got a gamesmanship I gotta I gotta true
it are you going true I have to to games true on the salsa cereal because this is
me and Matt oh I guess you're right I guess that is the right games play - yeah
I have to he guessed false I gotta guess true that's true yeah yeah so it is it
is the right gameplay move to make and and honestly the use of the name of a
player they don't you know there you go yeah they don't just throw names you don't have players
around like that like there's nothing that's true that is true it's real Paul
is right oh my god disgusting horrific as game day staples Tostino's chips and
salsa have always gone hand-in-hand with watching football said Leslie Vesper
vice president of marketing Pepsi Co Foods North America salsa cereal is the
latest way we're bringing fans new experiences to enjoy the game and snacks
to go with it no nope god damn it no not interested
Leslie Vesper not interested in that's horrific that is horrific but I knew it
as soon as they grabbed a player name bar doesn't make sense that that logic
doesn't make sense I mean you were correct and I'm wrong but it's very easy
to write a player's name into a fake thing but Matt we have discussed this
many many times I get to the right answer the wrong way all the time oh
Jesus there it is look see it's got his face on the chat Julian Edelman's salsa
cereal oh my gross that's gross how turned on I am by it yeah we'll see if
the corn concert don't hit me in the back of the head but that's the big
thing right now is having these players and people you know do these big
collabos yeah there was some person I was it's happening now to me to the
point where because I'm unloading all these boxes of shit and there's a some
cereal that's coming out with some music person I'm like I have never heard of
this person I am a thousand years old I discovered something this week
completely unrelated to anything else I've discovered the thing that I think
makes me feel the oldest what is it you guys have anything that when you see it
it just it just immediately makes you feel old young people working me working
these for me I believe it is the genre k-pop oh if I see or hear a k-pop music
I just got fuck I'm old yeah yeah cuz I'll tell you cuz I'm so stupid I'm so
old and it still makes me feel old I like more j-pop I don't really know
anything about k-pop I know some j-pop k-pop besides black pink I'm at a loss I
like icy pops icy pops are delicious what's your favorite flavor cherry for
now until RFK jr. takes it away he's coming after cherry it's going up to
cherry next now the only flavor you're gonna be able to get soon is just
pickle pickle pops barf I'm a sucker for the blue I want to
thank pencil it's great this podcast thanks Ben and I want to thank all the
people support us over on our patreon page it's a new month so we don't ever
thank you list yet this is normally where we thank people for supporting us
month and month out that's what we thank them for yeah yeah support and oh yo RFK
jr. looks like a microwave Mel Gibson but how's it smell being kind he smells
like a hot dog better than those dogs honestly if you have it within your
hearts in your wallets to support us please do so by heading over to
preachingfun.com today
or if you like your hot dogs to smell like death head on over to farts in a
bag dot biz that's farts in a bag dot biz that along with preachingfun.com it
takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as three dollars a month
you can help keep this show on the air head on over there if you think this
show is worth more than zero dollars sign up any level between three dollars
and infinitely high dollars those are the levels that you can sign up at you
see we've gotten you all these options from three dollars to infinity between
those two goalposts please someone select infinity we need infinity dollars
if you can sign up for infinity you'd be helping us out oh man it would make the
world even even just one month of infinity dollars would change our lives
I wouldn't be in San Antonio but yeah if you can help us out over there
preachingfun.com farts in a bag dot biz all these jokes about Aldi hot dogs
they're not free people they cost us a lot of money to come up with so if you
could go over there and help us out we'll come up with more classic bits like
stinky Aldi microwave hot dogs I did read on one of the reddits some guy was
like oh man I spent like forty dollars on these the other day and now I'm gonna
have to take them back and I'm like you bought forty dollars worth of 80 packs of
hot dogs there's more than 40 packs cuz it's not a full dollar right it's
probably like 45 packs oh winter saving for the winter gotta save these farts up
for the winter why these stinky dogs freeze up real good I tell you what you
know the smell it when you freeze it it holds the smell too when you thaw it out
it still has that smell that's how you know it's real folks are still buying
tickets to scoop fest so that's right this morning welcome welcome that's
that's wonderful please keep buying tickets to scoop fest you're gonna love
it make it make the effort get out there it's gonna be great
travel is coming to an end so hurry up you're right it'll be fine it's like the
National Guard is being deployed
everything's fine but you know we can also you know we haven't played in a
while was someone wrote me asking whatever happened to store jingle so we
also stuff for sale at our store and when you get there by going to store
jingle calm that's right you can get there by going to store jingle calm
which is that button can you get that I go into store jingle calm yeah all you
have to do is go to store jingle calm all you need and that'll take you right
to the more jingle dot-com that's my WWE entrance music right there oh Stephen
James writes so says SJ every night I'm sure there's a stinky hot dog in a
canoe down here somewhere anyhow thanks listen everybody we love you and we'll
see ya