"We're not privy to the Twitch chat, when we switch that off of our stack."
This is my favorite part of the show, this is the part of the show where we thank you,
the Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers!
It's crazy, we have a new list, I can't figure out how to look at all of it, who can say
what's going to happen in the future, but hopefully you don't even hear this and you
just hear me thanking people.
In case you don't, I decided to put this hilarious anecdote in right here.
If you want to become an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and I hope you do, preachingfun.com, preachingfun.com
is where you're going to sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows, the
life you save may be your own!
And now, a program.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Great!
Let's go!
We have some guests here in the churn today, Michael Fortune, Jimmy Somina from A-List
Casting, the web series.
Woo!
It's true!
Yee-haw!
It's time for Matt Mattingly's Ice Cream Social, sitting in Las Vegas, that's Matt
Donnelly, sitting in Pittsburgh, PA, that's Paul Mattingly, also in Vegas, it's me, Jacob,
the audio guy.
We're preachingfun.
Aww yeah!
But before we get started, fuck Landman right in the neck.
Fuck it, fuck that show, fuck that fucking piece of shit show.
I'm so happy that we didn't dive into this season from what I'm hearing about this season.
This season's been terrible, many people have been writing about it, but they did a scene,
okay, this is the second to last scene, the series is about to end, and they spend, again,
this is a show about--
The whole series?
Does the end end?
No, it should be, but no, it won't, it will go on.
We're heading to the end of season two.
This is a show that is about an oil company trapped in doing business with a drug cartel,
and the episode nine of a ten episode season, it spends 90% of it with really deep conversations
about relationships and about their daughter going to college and all this other stuff.
Now that's just a big waste of a premise, but in this episode, this is things, I watch
this show because it is mediocre, I watch this show because it's easy to watch some
of it and go to bed, that's why I watch it.
So I'm watching it, and the daughter goes to college, and it's this really sweet moment,
and she even makes a little prayer gesture and then opens up her door and walks inside
her first dorm room, and they have written a character to be a Charlie Kirk, every liberal
valued person becoming a nightmare possible.
It is a trans roommate who says that they are vegan, they can't hear certain words
because it's triggering, they said they have to meditate, they have a pet muskrat, they
have to take every possible thing that you could, every shitty liberal stereotype, here's
all, and not even stereotypes, stereotypes is the wrong word because it's not even stereotype,
because trans isn't a stereotype, but they just look at that and go like, well trans
is a problem, so we're going to make this into a list of problems.
Yeah, they took everything, any kind of liberal value and made it an antagonist, and tried
to make it an assault on the daughter, and they literally have the mother come in to
save the day where she rents a hotel, says invite all of your cheerleader friends because
the daughter's going to be on the cheerleading squad.
They literally sit there sipping margaritas, okay, everyone's underage except for the mother,
they're all sitting there sipping margaritas, saying this is what college should be like,
and then talking about the roommate and saying she's just unhappy with herself, so they purposely
misgender the roommate, and then lecture each other at the pool, saying, you know, basically
saying that if you have liberal values, you have no fun, you have no friends, but if you,
you know, just hate all those things, and just value totally being selfish and fun,
life works out for you, and I'm supposed to go to bed, and instead I am fucking livid
and angry that this fucking, for no reason, just multiple shots, anti-trans, multiple
shots across the badges, no reason, not for no reason, fair, fair. There's a reason. There
are several PSI ops going on right now, baby, but this is it. Like I get it. Like we watch
entertainment to give ourselves brief respite from this hellscape of issues that we were
constantly assaulted with from the time we wake up to the time we go to bed, right? And
on the one hand, we shouldn't be so concerned with the news, and on the other hand, real
terrible shit is happening, and it is affecting people. So where do we find a balance? I don't
know, but one place to try to find balance is like for an hour before I go to bed, right?
Can I make a recommendation as to my bedroom viewing routine? Just your own penis where
you put googly eyes on it, and you just keep wiggling it around?
Step one, because Bobbo, that's his name, Bobbo is always watching along, and he can't
watch without his eyes.
And before you do the job, you gotta put on the uniform.
You gotta put the googly eyes on, or Bobbo is blind. And a blind Bobbo, nobody wants
to see that.
That's not helpful, right?
Anyway, I strap Bobbo's eyes on, and I throw on Tubi. And Tubi has the giant selection
of mystery science theater and rift tracks, and that's all I do. I start a mystery science
theater or rift tracks and let it play in the background forever. It's a mediocre film.
If it has anything problematic in it, it is being lampooned by voices of reason, who happened
to be based out of Minnesota, by the way.
Mystery science theater was from Minnesota. That's where that all jumped off. That brilliant
stuff. So that's how I sooth myself to sleep every night, by watching old episodes of mystery
science theater and rift tracks that I have seen hundreds of times, and it's wonderful.
Yeah.
I will. Anything's better than what I'm doing. So I can't say whether I do or don't like
your idea, Paul, because I'm not a good judge of character as to how to spend an evening.
So great.
The best part about it, Matt, is that, especially with the rift tracks, you've got the voices
of the guys who are very left leaning. For the most part, Mike's not, but still he rolls.
I used to just watch mediocre dramas because comedy can get me into my analytical brain,
which makes it not shut off. And so I end up in a joke construction kind of whatever
and I can just stay up for hours and hours and hours and hours.
Gotcha.
So that's usually why I try to watch-
I think that's the best thing about rift tracks is because what you're watching is not funny,
but they make it silly.
And so-
Well, I tell you what, I can watch. I can watch season two of A-List Casting.
I say that's the best thing about our show, too.
Oh, yes.
The best thing about our show is that it's not funny.
The best alternative to Landman out there.
A-List Casting beats Landman, hands down.
I haven't even watched season two. It's already better. There's season two's definitely better
than the season two of Landman. I haven't even watched it.
Definitely.
Is it out yet, or are you just about to roll out episodes? Where are we at from the sake
of a viewer, boys?
We have five episodes out, so we have only three more. So you have some catching up to
do, Mr. Donnelly.
A deal. A deal. Clearly. My schedule is now open. So there you go.
There you go.
No problem.
Your viewing schedule has opened up.
So remind our audience about what your show is and where people watch it.
Absolutely. We are A-List Casting. Jimmy, our esteemed actor here, who keeps randomly
changing his wallpaper and currently has a massage table.
That's exciting. Who's? Never mind. I'm not even going to ask who.
I've been in that spa. That's Happy Beginnings. I know that place.
Happy Beginnings is where A-List Casting season two is located. Happy Beginnings.
Happy Beginnings.
I mean, not that I'm overly familiar with the industry, but I'm guessing that would
work actually better, right? Like, I think it's way more comfortable than a casting couch.
Let's just go with that.
Let's get that crazy part out of the way. And then now I can really relax in a massage.
Why put it at the end?
Fall asleep.
A-List Casting has nothing to do with that.
Okay, but I'm just going to say you're missing the marketing.
It's actually about a show about two casting directors and their assistant who have been
blackballed by Hollywood. And now they are stuck in Las Vegas because when Hollywood
spits you out, Vegas sucks you in.
That is Happy Beginnings' slogan.
What are you talking about?
That's true. I mean, you guys are writing season three as we speak right now.
Jimmy plays Roger, and Roger is the owner of Happy Beginnings. No, Roger, Jimmy started
out as a sad actor in the pilot episode. And we loved him so, so much in the pilot episode
that we gave him a name. And he's been a series regular ever since.
You got Urkels, buddy. You got Urkels. Look at you go.
Oh, baby. Did I do that?
Yes, it's a very proud day. You know, I'm a classically trained actor. I studied
Shakespeare, Chekhov, decorated with awards. And now here I am dressing up as a clown and
playing the sad actor before I actually get my name. So finally got my name and it's Roger.
Is there any Rogers? Do we know any like actual Rogers in the wild these days?
I know a Roger.
I mean, there's the American dad alien. And that's the other one that I could think
of. Yeah, those two, the guy that I know and the American dad alien guy.
Jimmy, I am stunned by this question. I have to actually look at my contacts whether I
actually have a Roger in my... Roger Whitaker.
Roger Whitaker. American treasure. Actually, I think he's English. English treasure. Roger
Whitaker. Do I know Roger Whitaker? Yeah, the only Roger that popped up in my phone is the one that I mentioned.
He is the only Roger that I have in my contacts.
You guys are acting as squirrely as Jimmy just asked the same question over and over
again while you guys continue to stretch the parameters of the question.
Roger Stone, I do not have in my Rolodex.
Do you get a Roger ring at the massage parlor?
Roger Dodger.
Happy Roger.
Roger Dodger on my Todger.
Don't have anyone with a first name Roger in my contacts.
Let me shout out to Roger.
That's it. I'm going to make another kid. I'm gonna name him Roger. The market's wide open.
I do want to say that his name almost was Kroger because when we were writing it, I
mistyped Roger and my creative partner, Zach, loved that it was Kroger. And he was like,
I love it. His name is going to be Kroger. I can rock Kroger. I can make Kroger work.
Well Kroger is not only the grocery chain, but you've also got the Nickelback fame Kroger,
right? Like that's Nickelback to Kroger.
Thank you for bringing up the Nickelback thing, Paul.
Jack Kroger is Nickelback, right?
That's why I had to cut it back to Roger. I can't have three Krogers.
Nowadays, he's known as Mrs. Avril Lavigne.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks for that weird marriage history fact there, Paul. Yeah, Avril Lavigne married Nickelback.
Did you guys not know that?
I thought Avril Lavigne died. Didn't she die? Well, one of the Lavines died, but there's
lots of clones of her.
Okay.
No, she didn't die. She got Lyme disease, right? Isn't she the one that got really afflicted
with Lyme disease or is it somebody else?
That's what's her name from Bikini Kill, who's married to a Beastie boy.
I'm with Jimmy on this one. I think Avril Lavigne got Lyme disease.
She might've, but Kathleen Hanna. Kathleen Hanna also got Lyme disease.
Kathleen Hanna, the initial riot girl.
What I'm taking from this is if you marry a musician, you get some kind of disease.
That's what I'm saying.
That's correct.
Avril Lavigne contracted Lyme disease from a tick bite in 2014.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Jimmy knows everything about Lyme disease.
You got to stop this camping shit.
I don't want to talk about Avril Lavigne except for her nickel-backed husband.
Kroger.
Who's apparently named Roger.
Jimmy, who else got Lyme disease?
Anybody who goes outdoors, which is why I never do it. I love the outdoors.
Yes.
That was really something that was brought to me as a selling point of just like, "Yeah,
we go out for a walk. We go through the trees. We pet a deer and then we go home and check
each other for ticks."
I'm like, "I don't want type two entertainment. I don't want it."
Who is giving you this entertainment pitch? This is a terrible salesperson.
Yes, you're right. Terrible.
Now, Jimmy, once your character went from a sad actor to Roger, did you start doing
a lot of like, "Hmm, I don't know if my character would say it this way or hmm, will my character
do that?" Roger doesn't seem like the kind of person who would like, "Did you really
take ownership now of your scenes?"
Right, right. Yeah, no. I had plenty of notes. Well, I didn't give the notes. My agent gave
the notes to Michael directly. I mean, I don't got time for that shit.
Thank you again for being here, by the way.
Oh, sure. It's my pleasure. The envelope is slipping through the door right now. My fee.
It's on its way.
Wait, we're paying him? Michael should be paying him. We're paying him?
Oh.
We didn't pay him in sandwiches.
As long as the money and the sandwiches are green.
Oh, this is going to be so awkward. I have them slipping a sandwich under your door right
now.
That would smell so good.
It is a Capriotti sandwich. It's a big sandwich. It's not going to fit under the door. It's
going to be a mess.
So, Michael, I know you guys...
Cranberry and stuffing just oozing out like play-doh.
Terrible.
Now I'm hungry.
You guys have.
Actually, we're ending the podcast right now.
It was Bobby from...
We're going to have lunch.
Bobby's the best. You guys have a studio where you're filming a lot of this, but are we looking
as you keep growing here to do more on-site possible shoots and things like that to make
Vegas even more of a character as the series progresses?
As I know, LA is quite the character in a lot of Los Angeles productions, so are we
hoping to make that more of a reality?
I know there were talks at one time of Las Vegas investing in some tax breaks for filming
and stuff like that that may have just been pissed in the wind.
Yeah, I don't think that's really come to fruition, but what's the ability to...
How film-friendly is Vegas right now for what you're doing?
Actually, I found filming in Vegas really embracing.
It's actually a lot easier to get permits.
It's a lot easier to find locations for people to film at.
The problem is it costs a lot of money to transport an entire crew and to rehearse in
a space and all that.
As soon as A-List Casting gets funding from a bigger network, we'll definitely be able
to take advantage of all these things, but currently we tend to pick one location outside
of our casting office to go to, and this time it was a local dance studio where we filmed
at.
In the previous season, we went to Millennium Fandom Bar, which I'm sure you guys are familiar
with.
Yes, Fun Bar.
We filmed there.
I think that if we could afford it, I would absolutely do, but this is definitely an independent
project where we pay Jimmy in massages and sandwiches.
So if any locations want to let us film there for sandwiches and massages, then we're open
to that.
Well, Millennium Fandom Bar is a great example.
That's a great example of local business chipping in and wanting to be represented on the screen.
And an example of businesses that love massages and sandwiches.
Jacob, what was that bar that you went to that turned into two bars the other night?
Maybe those guys need some film, they look like they needed some promotion, right?
Tony Two Bars.
Oh, Tony Two Bars.
Oh, the guy dragged you over to a second bar for a drink and then left you high and dry.
Yeah, yeah.
The owner of this bar took us out of his bar to a different bar and seemed like he was
going to buy us a drink and hang out with us in this other bar that he was taking us
to and then just left.
He was in the other bar for a grand total of two minutes.
What were these locations?
You don't want to mention either of these bars?
It was the weirdest thing.
Oh, I've forgotten both of the names of both bars.
Oh my God.
Well, see, that's one thing.
Well, then they definitely need some promotion.
So the second one used to be the downtown lounge, hot seat, hot seat, hot seat.
That was it.
It was the same word twice.
It was a nice place too.
Was it Boing Boing or something like that?
No, it wasn't Boing Boing.
We were calling it hot seat, hot seat.
So it rhymes with that.
Yes.
All right.
Hoochie.
It was like, it was like Potsy Potsy Potsy pot.
It was Potsy Pots with the other one was Potsy Potsy.
Good.
We figured it out guys.
Go ahead and film there.
Yeah.
We figured it out.
You have full permission to film there as far as we're concerned.
Well, at least I'm glad to hear that at least on the locals level, Vegas is still helping
each other out in that respect, artistically.
I also, I also volunteer at Jacob's house.
Oh yeah.
Jacob, well, how's your house?
Is it good for, does it have a casting couch and sandwiches?
So many.
So many cast the couches, so many sandwiches.
You'd be, you'd be doing me a favor if you got rid of some of these sandwiches, actually.
He actually has like a dog accessible casting couch, which is pretty amazing.
Yeah.
It has a little ramp up.
It's got a little puffy stair staircase that goes up to his couch for his puppies.
So it's a good, it's a good for a, for dogs and we'll sleep their way into roles.
Right.
Oh, I see.
I wasn't sure that was for me to get onto the very high couch, short, short, short person.
But no, seriously, like, you know, it's, it's, I think it is a love letter to Las Vegas,
not so much in terms of the landmarks or the, the, the, the places, but like the characters
that you'll find in Las Vegas, which I mean, I challenge you to find something that has
that sort of thing where it like kind of explores the strange, weird people who are in the entertainment
field on the fringes that are not Cirque or Spiegel or whatever, and how they make their
lives work in this town because you know, like LA actors left and right, but you know,
what are these lowly, sad lawyer turned actors and, you know, all these, all these other
kinds of characters.
So I think that's, that's one of the benefits of it.
I mean, no, no city on earth has better people watching than Las Vegas.
And so to have a show that is kind of dedicated to a bit of that spirit is, is a fascinating
idea and something that people should check out.
I mean, that, that's a, that is a weirdly niche thing that I think people are going
to really love.
And more importantly, Jimmy in episode three is dressed up as a birthday party clown trying
to steal craft, crafty, which is the catering at craft services and, and him and I get in
a shouting match with each other.
So is that because Jimmy came to the shooting from his side gig as a birthday clown?
No, no, no, no.
He is for, so the backstory of the movie that we're filming is that he's the clown in a
world of mimes and he's, he feels lonely and left out.
And so he has to, it's very dramatic, has to jump off a roof to end everything.
I can't wait to watch this.
This is all backstory.
This is all backstory that you will not know.
Of course, you're hearing it first.
I'm not even sure Jimmy knew this.
I was wondering why there were all these mimes and me there that, that was kind of confusing,
but now that makes, no, it makes total sense.
So now you finished season one, does suddenly like, did you always, are you going to make
the season two?
Is season two simply just like, I, we cast something of funny casting adventures to go
on or did you think of somewhere new to go with the show?
How did, how did it all come together creatively for season two?
Well our writer, Nick Adams, he had already started writing season two unbeknownst to us.
So we were like, we did season one and our executive producer, Chuck Prater, was like,
you know, I, I think that we need to get a season two going away.
I'm going to get some funding for you guys and stuff.
And then Nick was like, funny enough, I have eight episodes ready for you guys to go.
And I was like, that's great.
I was like, okay.
And I was like, this is great.
Now we need to make them twice as long and with much more characters and much to my chagrin
doing 27 pages a day.
I was in three days.
We talked about this last time I was on, but we tend to shoot three episodes per day.
And that was, it turned out wonderful, but also I was like, I'm never doing this again,
which I say after every season, I'm never doing this again.
I was going to ask you when he, when, when, when the, when the writer said, Oh, I've got
eight more episodes in the, in the bag ready to go.
Were you more excited or more terrified?
Which, which direction did the needle lean?
Cause I know it, I know both, both were on the scale for sure.
We were very excited actually because you know, we love doing this.
This is, you know, at Jimmy having this whole family together and having everybody on the
set.
It's, it's definitely been an experience.
We've been doing it for five years.
So bringing the crew together and, and doing everything.
It feels like at the end of 16 hours, like everybody's just like, Oh my gosh.
But then you get to see what you did and what you achieved.
And that's that in itself is always, always gratifying.
And actually Matt and I had a conversation about magicians.
You said you would never do that.
You said you never out me on this.
You said you were going to keep this anonymous.
You're supposed to say a magician friend.
I know.
Well, we, I told it to the writer and so now it's too late.
So if there is a season three, there's going to be a magician episode.
So hopefully we can get some magician adjacent type people.
Maybe Matt Donnelly will make it up here.
I was just saying, I can't tell whether you're saying I should do this or stay away from
it.
I'll do it.
I would love to do it.
Oh my God.
If you can see on the background, there's, there's a little, there's Jimmy's spoilers,
but that's me.
Wow.
That's pretty dope for the video for people who aren't on, on Twitch or zoom.
Yeah.
There's a little, little bonus something I'll let you know, I'll just speak as my agent
for a moment.
You should make Matt part of the last episode because he tends to cause schedules to go
off the rails with, with stuff.
So you definitely want, you don't want me holding up another episode.
I'll just tell you that much right now.
Oh, you'll be the grand finale, baby.
There you go.
I'll get you when you have your least amount of patience and I'm doing the most amount
of improv.
You're going to love it.
This is why the show ended.
Oh, that hit so close to home.
Oh man.
Yeah.
I had a friend working on a project that I was like, oh, I would have been fun to work
on that one.
And they described the working processes like, oh, I would have been a nightmare.
Thank God.
I didn't try to be a part of that project.
I would have just pissed everyone off.
They would have hated me, but it's good somebody just put Jimmy with the dude wipes dressed
as a clown.
Those pumpkin spice dude wipes I'll have, you know, that's a Blumpkin spice.
That is not Photoshop.
That is legit.
That is Blumpkin.
I remember that day.
Yep.
I'm happy to see that picture.
I didn't have that picture.
Yeah.
Jimmy.
Wow.
That's good lighting.
Look at that.
Download that shit.
Yeah.
That's a good picture.
Jimmy, how many, how many months now with no podcast, do you miss it at all?
Do you hate not being part of the audio world?
No.
See now like this is the perfect opportunity for season three.
All a list casting goes all podcasts.
Just goes to total.
Audio only.
Man.
Michael, I'm going to tell you right now.
I'm going to say G. You know what, if it's not 16 hour days and we're doing three back
to back podcasts, I'm here for it.
It's way shorter days.
It's fine by me.
We only do two on, on our hardest days.
We do two in a row.
We've, we've tried three in the past and it doesn't work.
If everything falls apart.
They don't even go on location anymore.
No.
They just do it all from home.
Yeah.
Or cruise ship or wherever the hell they are.
I like to take cruises.
What can I say?
We've evolved.
No, I'm, I'm good.
I'm, I'm, I'm good.
Saving my conversations for my therapist and not for, not for some two dudes that I, that
I work with that I love.
Yeah.
You guys still getting together for the occasional meal.
You still keeping up with the guys.
It's just not as regular or.
Yeah.
Sure.
You know, it's, you know, and you know, we've got the dressing room hang.
So you see each other all the time.
Wouldn't it be great here?
If it was like, actually we, we have built walls between our stations and the dressing
rooms.
It kind of looks like literally not spoken since that last episode.
Like, you know, when like restaurants were desperate to open during COVID.
So they put up all those little micro walls and stuff.
Yes.
That's what the dressing room is like now at the stair.
And the best part is all you need for Jimmy to stay private is a micro wall.
Oh boy, stay down the stairs, get the part, get the part buddy.
You want to get on the massage table.
You've got to climb there.
Come on.
You got to get up there by yourself.
You guys, so the last time I was on this episode, all we could talk about was docking.
So I was like, I'm going to bring Jimmy on.
So at least like, he'll keep these guys in line and good job, Jimmy, good job, Jimmy.
Actually, I'm glad you brought up docking because I have some things I want to discuss
with that.
So thank you.
Jimmy, maybe, maybe this is unfair to put a button on it, but we should say you, since
you last were on air, your case got thrown out.
You were, you were not being, you were not exonerated.
You're not being, you're not going to jail for going to your own place of business from
a bar.
Yes, it is.
It has been dropped, but it still could be, I guess I just found this out the other day.
It could be, it takes a year for them to like actually close it.
So like at any point, if I act up or, you know, oh Jesus, you're still like, yeah.
So you're on a list.
Is that what we're hearing?
Can you tell me that Las Vegas has like a delete folder for 365?
So like if you move into delete, but it actually stays in this folder for a year, exactly.
So I still got to mind my P's and Q's.
No happy endings at the massage parlors.
That's it.
Yeah.
Got to.
But beginnings are on the table.
The happy beginnings.
Oh, the happy beginnings.
I mean happy beginnings.
Yeah, absolutely.
Absolutely.
But for all intents and purposes, that case is now done and the future is still is unclear
and my lawyer says I shouldn't talk too much about it.
There you go.
That's fine.
We'll leave it.
We'll leave it alone.
Only 20 more minutes.
Let's leave it there.
Yeah.
I was wanting to celebrate.
Now I have to put it like a little note on my calendar, like wait a year to celebrate.
Yeah.
Good to know.
June 11th.
The fateful day.
Well, I have, I have faith in the fair and six 11 you turned around.
It's nine 11.
It's my nine.
Wow.
Illuminati.
You never forget guys.
Machiavelli.
You know, when we started this episode today, I thought to myself, you know, I really hope
I could find out one day what Jimmy's slow Nina's nine 11.
What is Jimmy's personal 11 it's just actually now going to be an ice breaker for all of
our guests.
Hey, what's your nine 11?
My nine 11 is finding out my character's named Roger when it could be Kroger the whole time.
Oh, he looks so much like a Kroger.
My nine 11 is watching episode nine of of land man over and over again.
There's a character in a list.
God help us.
Her name.
Her.
The actress name is Katie.
It turned her.
Yeah, she's hilarious.
You'll see her in episode five and she's selling episode three, but she's featured in episode
five.
And unfortunately, we made it a bit that her name is tall actress.
So that's what she's called in the show and she doesn't get a name.
No one can remember her name.
It's just sort of nice.
So she hasn't been given a name and she is very careful to remind us every time we do
any kind of promotion that she doesn't have a name yet.
And I'm like, don't worry.
It's going to be a big reveal in season three Kroger or five.
Her name.
Her actual name is Elevator, Elevator thespian.
So her real name is tall actress.
Elevator.
Her name is also Roger.
Yeah.
Also Roger.
Oh, man.
Everybody is Roger.
This is all on YouTube, yes.
Yep.
You can find it all on YouTube.
I think you just look up A-list casting and you will see me, you will see Jimmy, you'll
see a lot of Las Vegas actors and some not Las Vegas.
Jonas Wilberton.
Oh, wow.
There's so many people that you guys know.
Yeah.
It's a who's who of Scoopguess.
Yes.
Tons of them.
Carina Harney-Jones.
Yes.
Nicole Unger.
I heard there's a lot of pressure to up the sex appeal for season two to boost the ratings.
Is that true?
That's very true.
Jimmy shows his nipples on every podcast and whether he's asked to or not.
Yeah.
And much like Brett Alters, he gets naked at the top any chance.
You don't have to ask Brett once.
I've got one more testicle than that guy has.
True story.
Somewhere Brett Alters is just getting like kings in the universe.
Oh, Brett Alters is doing fun.
Hey, he's got a little baby.
He's doing fine.
He's got a little baby.
One is enough.
The ringmaster of Big Apple Circus.
Yeah.
Now he's touring with Piff again.
Fuck that guy.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Fuck you, Brett Alters.
And your nudity.
But we'd love to have you back on the podcast.
Oh yeah.
Come on by Brett.
Anytime.
Yeah, Brett.
No pants.
I don't think we ever had Brett on.
Which is a mistake.
No.
Did we have him on once?
Maybe a long time ago.
Oh yeah.
We've done this podcast for too long.
I don't know.
He'd have to tell us.
Now between this podcast and Piff stuff, yeah, I have no idea.
You guys talk about how if you, you know, you had a budget, you go maybe shoot some more
locations and that kind of stuff, modern entertainment is a fucking crazy, making entertainment was
always hard.
It's harder than ever to take an independent project like this to a major streamer.
But small entertainment like this, like these smaller episodes and being able to watch from
your phones, that kind of stuff, like that's all on the rise, right?
Yeah.
Has, have you thought about possibly simply trying to do like a Kickstarter or a crowd
funder to try to maybe see if you could just get a budget you'd want for, to maybe make
this a little, a little more dynamic and spicy for you guys?
Yeah.
I mean, that's definitely on the portfolio.
You know, we're looking at where things go with this current season, and then we're going
to get together and talk about, okay, do we crowdfund?
Like what's our goals?
Like what are we going to do with season three?
What can we do to make a season three happen?
You know, that sort of thing, or, you know, with the help of all the scoops in the chat
and everything, the subscriber base and the viewers watching everything goes up so high
that we can, you know, take that to more of a network type style.
So there's two different ways to go.
We kind of have to step back and examine exactly where we're at.
I would love, like, you know, this, this show is, is definitely a love letter to Las Vegas
and, and to entertainment here.
So I would love to continue making it and everybody enjoys the process of doing it.
So there's many, there's many opportunities we're going to be looking at, but hopefully
one of them would be to crowdfund and to kind of get it enough of a budget to make a season
three.
The other option, you know, take it to some more networks again, now that we have more
of a fan base and stuff and show them the analytics and that kind of thing and see if
it gets picked up.
So a couple options.
If you do crowdfund, Paul, Jacob and I are in for $5.
Yes.
Total.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Five.
Between the two of you.
How dare you, Jacob?
I would appreciate it.
What's up?
How very dare you.
Jacob has switched his Zoom background to Jimmy and Jimmy's background, which is pretty
good.
Inception.
It's a Russian nesting doll of weirdness.
This is what you're missing.
I put the link, I put the link to the A-list Casting channel on the chat.
Very nice.
Go there and hit that, smash that subscribe y'all.
Yeah.
And if you're not on the chat, A-list Casting, just do A-list Casting, search it on Google,
search it on YouTube.
It pops right up.
Yeah.
Subscribe to it.
It's going to be fantastic.
You're going to love it.
All right.
Well, gentlemen, we're going to do a little ad, we want to thank you for plugging the
episode.
You're welcome to stick around and fuck around with us, but we're going to move on to other
topics.
So if you want to go, I get it.
No problem.
I do have to run.
Okay.
All right.
I love you all.
Love you.
Love you, Jimmy.
Great to see you.
Bye, buddy.
Love you too, Michael.
Thanks.
Thank you so much for being here.
Yeah.
Our pleasure.
Thank you, guys.
All right.
Thank you.
Yes.
Happy beginnings.
Happy beginnings, everyone.
You know, who else is really happy to be on a show that has so much talk of dirty massage
parlors?
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Captain Cutberry Cereal.
That's right.
From the Microscoop.
That is Captain Cutberry Cereal in 2021.
It's taken four years for this gem to make it to the top of the shuffle.
And here we are.
Captain Cutberry Cereal.
Ahoy there, everybody.
Captain Cutberry here.
Boy, oh boy.
My pussy's as dry as a Sahara.
I need something to lube up this twad of mine.
What's that?
What's that ahead?
Oh, it's the soggy's.
Well, come on over here to my place, soggy's, and get in my poon, because I'm as dry as
a 90-year-old's cough.
Yeah, oh, Captain Cutberry is, I've got sandpaper twix my nethers right now, you know what I'm
saying?
That's why I definitely need the help of the soggy's, and you can do it too.
Go look for Captain Cutberry's Soggy Lubrication Affiliate.
That's right.
The Soggy Lubrication Affiliate goes right in your zone, drips on down smooth like a
roaring river, and stays there guaranteed for at least three hours, plenty of time for
ingress and egress.
That's all you really need.
Get it in, get it out, get it done.
That's what Captain Cutberry says.
Ahoy, soggy's, stay in my poon.
And her hay scoops at checkout.
Stay in my poon.
That's the famous-
That's the famous steal there.
Ay-ay-ay.
Jacob, do you have a time, I have a topic, if you don't have a topic, a topic you got?
I have a topic.
I have a couple of topics.
Pick who feels strongest about their topic.
I got two quickies.
First of all, I'm gonna let y'all know I got to experience a little slice of heaven the
other night.
Let me tell you what a slice of heaven is.
So I went to this massage park.
A slice of heaven-
Happy beginnings.
Is a Pennsylvania Costco on a Steelers playoff Monday night.
Oh man!
It was, it was a ghost town, and it was wonderful.
Anne and I had the run of the place.
There couldn't have been fifty people there, workers included.
It was wonderful.
Were the workers all furious that they were there?
No.
Nobody in their right mind wanted to watch that game.
Give me a break.
Are you kidding me?
Anyway, I watched a few minutes of it and then just dozed off, woke up at some point
right around, it was almost halftime, I mean it was right after halftime, and looked at
the game and went, "Nope," and turned it off and got up and just did other things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
As someone who loves watching Aaron Rodgers lose and be a dick about it, it was a fucking
chef's kiss.
You can't get any more perfect than an interception-turned-touchdown as your final playoff.
Yeah, after he's bitched everyone else out on the sideline and they just showed up shouting
at everyone, and I was like, "Oh, this is really nice."
Well, he's the reason I didn't watch a single lick of it this whole season, and I'm a better
person for it, and now I'm completely off football again.
That, and you don't care about sports.
You moved to Pittsburgh and you forgot that you don't care about sports.
I reminded myself real quick.
Aaron Rodgers just reminded you.
If anything, you owe Aaron Rodgers.
Well, part of it too was for two years I was basically immobile from my damn leg.
Well, that's true.
I didn't have a whole lot of options, but to connect with the outside world through
live sports entertainment.
It was either like sports or become a card magician.
That was kind of it, and so I think I chose wisely again.
All right, so that was a great-
I love that.
Our scoops right now are all catching each other up on football, and they also don't
care and know that much about it, so right now the chat is just a litany of like, "Wait,
bears?
Wait, packers?"
Somebody just mentioned the Brooklyn Dodgers.
Who cares?
I don't even know.
Who even cares?
Yeah.
Well, that was great fun Monday night going shopping with Ann.
That's really funny to hit Costco during a playoff game.
That's truly the perfect time.
It was the perfect time.
It was insane.
Like, I mean, ghost town.
So there was that, and then Ann for holiday through her work got a gift card from one
of her associates for Applebee's, so we decided to burn that Applebee's gift card yesterday.
I don't know if you guys have been to Applebee's recently.
You should have used it at Applebee's.
We had to use it at Applebee's.
Oh, you shouldn't have burned it.
Oh, well.
That was a waste.
You know, it might have been a better move.
I don't know.
But we went to Applebee's.
Applebee's currently has on the menu.
On the menu currently, they have an item called the O.M. Cheeseburger.
O.M. Oh, this is the one that's-
Yes, I just saw the ads for this too.
This was on every playoff game this weekend.
So they cut a cheeseburger in half and let it rest on a melted dish of cheese?
Not just a melted dish of cheese.
The wording is served in a molten pool of cheese.
Oh.
Served in a molten pool of cheese.
This is-
Matt and Madagley's Ice Cream Social served in a molten pool of cheese.
And I was like, yes, of course.
I'm going to have to move, I'm going to have to move Throshen to second place as to what
to do with my dead body.
Put me in a molten pool of cheese, please.
Put me in a molten pool of cheese.
Why wait until you're dead though?
Serve me.
It's like a cheeseburger fondue.
So, a whole cheeseburger fondue.
Do you put like a long fork in it?
Oh.
You have to get a fork in there to get the cheese that's left.
And I'll tell you this-
Oh, Applebee's missing out on giving people a long fork for their hamburger to dip it
in the cheese.
I didn't eat super fast.
Like on the cob.
And by the time I went for the second, the second half of the burger, it was not coming
off the plate.
It's congealed.
Completely congealed.
You're too late, bozo.
You missed your train.
It was exactly where I was like, oh fuck, half my burger is staying on the plate.
And I saw on the menu, I was like, limited time only.
I'm like, yeah, you have a limited time to eat it before it glues itself to the dinnerware.
There it is.
So that was it.
Exactly.
Just cut the thing in half and then put the two flat halves down in just a plate of cheese.
That's it.
Andy's got the video up.
There it is.
This feels like something that like some mother does for like one of her kids.
And like, can you serve it to me with the cheese on the plate?
Can I have melty cheeseburger tonight?
Can we do melty pool burger?
And then that kid goes to sleep over for the first time and he asks him to cut his cheeseburger
in half and says, can you put more cheese on this plate?
Do you guys do melty pool burgers?
And they go, what the hell are you talking about, kid?
And then he shows them and they never eat a cheeseburger the same way again.
And then those children went on to open an Applebee's.
Well, like I said, I'll say it wasn't bad.
It's just that that second burger experience.
It should come like fondue.
It should have a little fire.
It should have a little heater.
Yeah.
It comes on a skillet.
So it comes out bubbling like a fajita plate.
So it is truly like blah, blah, blah, blah.
Like it is molten cheese.
Like you cannot fuck with this thing.
Blah, blah, blah.
It's a cheeseburger.
Eat me.
I dare you to consume me.
Is the cheese just, is the cheese in the little pan just like cheese, just like cheddar cheese
or something?
It's like a Mexican cheese blend, I would say.
Like a Monterrey Jack style.
This is a fucking, this is a fucking miss on their part, not to do it in a pan of queso.
Yeah.
Wiz.
I mean, yeah.
If you're, if you're going for it, you should go for it.
Like they do serve like skillet, just do some skillet queso, throw a couple of cheeseburgers
in there.
You're done.
I think they serve skillet queso at Applebee's.
Come on Applebee's.
I don't know.
I'm giving you gems here.
So I went to Sonic the other night and uh, I, you know, they have a pretzel twist with
like a cheese dip, but they're at a pretzel twist.
So I still ordered the, the, the, the, uh, uh, yeah, I ordered the dip and put my tater
tots in it.
Tater tots.
Smart.
Eat shit Applebee's, eat shit Applebee's.
Well, I think, I think they're onto something, but I think you guys are exactly right.
If you're going to go for it, fucking go for it.
But then I think it becomes just a, you're spending too much on your cheese.
And so I think it just becomes an arms race at that point.
I think then all the restaurants are racing to see who can put what in queso.
Yeah.
And I mean, it would probably just end the world.
I mean, if, if you, so if you put on your menu menu in queso emergency, eat cheeseburger,
I am, I am buying that sandwich.
I will be at your restaurant every day.
Every day in queso emergency, eat cheeseburger.
Fuck yeah.
And go ahead.
Like make that just an option in case of emergency as an option.
So I ordered a chicken Caesar wrap, cut it in half, dip the two hands into a bone thing
of cheese and give it to me.
Can I get that in queso emergency style, please?
Sir, you, you ordered a drink.
You ordered a Coke.
I'm aware of my Pepsi fountain drink order.
I also would like it in queso emergency style.
Very good, sir.
Are you unwilling to place my Pepsi in a molten pool of cheese?
Oh no, no, no, sir.
Here, please never let it be said that I will take my business elsewhere, sir.
No sir, please come back.
I will go eat in another establishment, willing to dip my Pepsi in a molten pool of cheese.
You understand me.
This is not an idle threat.
I am ordered by Pepsi in queso emergency style.
I shall not be refused.
I am the owner here.
What is the problem?
I will not be refused.
Hello.
Theo Appleby at your service.
Mr. Appleby, have you a bone that I might pick at, sir?
For I have a bone to pick.
Oh, I have bones.
I have bones because I myself, I just ordered Buffalo wings in queso emergency.
So, I cut each wing in half and I put the top and the bottom end of the wing in queso
emergency.
And the shards, the shards fall where they may.
The chef has like a bone saw back there and just we line them up and just.
Yeah.
Split the riblets and send them into the fucking cheese sewer.
I like this whole chicken in queso emergency, please.
I have brought my own Kirkland brand chicken, sir, and I would like this served in queso
emergency style.
Charge me whatever.
Yeah.
No price too high.
What is that?
Is that like a corking fee?
Yeah.
Do not deny me.
Spatchcock it if you must.
Oh, in fact, please do.
But put it in a pool of molten cheese, please.
In queso emergency style.
Oh, I even.
That is ours.
So, Nick Newman famously taught me the Sonic secret hack, which is that they often say
their name.
Welcome to Sonic.
My name is Deborah.
How can I help you?
Whatever would you like to order?
If you say their name back, they give you a discount.
And I remember this every time I go to my local Sonic.
But every time my Sonic people don't say their name and it drives me crazy because I'm like
ready.
I'm ready.
Like a ninja to say their name.
And the last three times I've gone to Sonic, they don't introduce themselves.
And I was like, just make up a name and start addressing them as that name.
Yeah.
Thanks, Tara.
Thank you, Roger.
I'll have some nuggets.
What's the why?
Tots.
Jesus Christ.
I'd like some potato nuggets, please.
I have the chili dog or the corn dog nuggets.
I had my brain in case of emergency.
So I just have it just floating in the bat of milk.
I can't remember the name of tater tots.
You split both hemispheres and put them in a pool of molten cheese.
Oh, cheddar bites in case of emergency.
Yeah.
We got it.
The Apple is about to find out how lazy they are.
It's going to happen is that they've opened a door here and now other people are going
to walk through.
It's going to be.
That's exactly right.
They have given away a real move to just throw your food in a bunch of cheese and people
are going to go hog fucking wild.
Isn't it chilies that already has the skillet queso?
Yes.
See, that's going to start cutting their burgers in half and throw it in the skillet queso.
Well, you can do it with the big mouth bites.
I mean, if you're not getting triple dipper, you're not getting eaten right at Chili's
anyway.
I don't know.
I don't know who's going to Chili's order or anything besides a triple dipper.
That's right.
Shots fired.
Fucking fools.
Idiots.
Uh-huh.
Been a minute.
Come on now.
In case of emergency.
Oh, Andy's asking if we've seen the new KFC bowl, but I haven't tried it yet, Andy, but
I've seen it.
Oh, that's a seasonal items.
And my friend Jen said the funniest time saw, saw an advertisement when we were living
in New York at a bus stop.
I was at the, for the KFC bowl and she just looked at it and goes, for those who've just
given up, but man, if you go through a KFC and get you a KFC bowl, you're not going to
be mad about it.
No, you're not going to be mad about it.
You're going to be perfectly good.
Yeah.
How about some KFC bolognese?
Throwing some queso?
It's going to be great.
Oh, KFC bolognese.
Pass it up.
KFC.
I'll tell you who else wants to put some bolognese and some queso and that's the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by slunks for skunks.
That's from magic shell scoop in 2024, the product slunks for skunks.
Hello.
I am.
How do you say Pepe lap you?
I am here to kiss a dead calf.
Oh, I am looking to smooch on a expired cow baby.
Give me some dead cow babies to kiss, smooch, smooch, smooch.
Where can I find such a service?
Oh, slunks for skunks.
Oh la la.
This is the answer to my prayers, mon chrie.
Oh, look at this beautiful dead calf, this stillborn baby heifer who I will smooch.
Your skin, it is like a dead cow.
Has anyone ever told you your cold dead eyes remind me of the sea?
When I give you tongue, I can take the entirety of your cold slimy dead tongue into my mouth
and you don't care, you don't find it.
Slugs for skunks.
You have answered my prayer by giving me a dead cow to kiss.
Do you have a friend or a loved one that believes that they are cartoon skunk?
Send them over here to slunks for skunks.
We'll take care of your family, friend or relative and we'll just put them here in our
warehouse filled with slunks.
They can't hurt them.
They just played with them.
They have a real good time.
Come on down, slunks for skunks.
Enter Hey Scoops at checkout.
It took a dark turn.
Let's do a little jock versus nerd.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is time.
Yeah, we got a scooper today from Chris angel has a Chimera.
The categories are photos and movies, number one singles, sixties through nineties, binders
full or name the candy.
Oh, man.
You're at first.
All of these.
I know.
Uh, let's do binders full please for 200.
What group of people have the first names?
Vesper, uh, honey, honey child, Pussy, Tiffany, Solitaire, and Holly.
I know exactly what this is.
Um, oh, I don't call it.
It is.
It is a group of people, uh, and all of these people have, uh, something in common.
Yeah, Paul, I'll have to pass.
I don't know this one.
Those are all bond girls.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Vesper.
Paul, uh, let's do, um, Oh, I'll try number one singles for 200 1983 recognized as the
song with the most radio plays in history.
What at first sounds like a gentle love song is actually more like something a stalker
might sing to their target.
Someone call the cops.
Ah, this is, uh, every breath you take from the police.
Every breath you take.
Indeed.
I'll be watching you.
Good clues.
That's me.
I'll try.
I named the candy 200 taste the rainbow Tuesday evenings.
Oh, skittles, smarties.
Yeah.
Um, I'm going back for binders full, I got to get this right.
All right.
For 400, what group of people have the first names?
Catherine and Jane and Catherine and Catherine, uh, I don't know this path, Queens, Queens.
Let's try Queens.
Wives of Henry the eighth.
All right.
Wives of Henry, the eight coach rat bastard literally did the double head smack, uh, disappointment
that we couldn't, we didn't know that one.
Why?
They're Queens.
I think, did you, did you mean Queens?
Like they're, did you know that their wives were 100 of the eight?
Cause I feel like that's the bigger, important part.
Right?
Yeah.
I mean, but they were all Queens.
Nope.
That's a no.
You said, yeah.
You answered no, we were both ready to give it to you if you said like, oh yeah, they
were Queens because they were all married to Henry the eighth.
You know, cheers episode to age myself or Cliff answered, who have people who have never
been in my kitchen, uh, for final jeopardy.
Well, technically true.
Yeah.
Paul.
Um, I will try sixties music out or the sixties to the nineties for 800.
Let's go for the big money.
All right, 1973, this song ostensibly from a, uh, paroled prisoner to his girlfriend asks
for a sign that she wants him back.
It was covered by Bing Crosby, Perry Cuomo, and Dean Martin and had renewed popularity
in 1979 during the Iranian hostage crisis.
Oh boy.
Huh.
I am going to guess tie a yellow ribbon.
All right, let's try it.
Tie a yellow ribbon around the old oak tree.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Paul.
You just said tie yellow ribbon.
Oh, come on.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
That's not enough.
They're all Queens.
The whole song.
Queens.
I got it.
Right.
That's me.
I'll try.
The chances of using me, Nick, Nick Newman just got up and grabbed a yellow cloth and
tied it in front of the camera to give it to Paul.
I didn't see that.
I know you didn't.
I'm just, I'm just shouting out our amusing scoops here.
We have some very funny typing in the chat is lazy acting it out on camera.
That's that's that's improv shit right there.
Yeah.
That's a fine lifeline shit right there.
I'll drop binders full for 600 who are Jane.
Oh, this is a, this is a bad start.
Come on, Weedland, Belinda Carlisle, Charlotte, Kathy, Gina stock shock and Kathy Valentine.
Huh?
Come on, pass it.
The Bronte sisters, they're all Queens, they're all Queens.
That doesn't even like ring a bell in my brain.
I pass Matt.
Is it Oingo Boingo fucking Belinda Carlisle?
You're halfway there in me or you're more than halfway there, I guess.
Linda Carlisle was, it was in a shit I'm blanking it.
All right.
Paul knows it.
I'll pass.
Oh, it's the go-go's that's a map.
Okay.
So far, I've been bad at everything.
Let's go to photos and movies for 200.
Let's try something new.
A group photo of the guests at the July 4th ball in 1921.
The guy front and center looks awfully familiar, but I think the last time we saw him, he'd
just had his hair and everything else frosted.
What's the movie?
Beautiful moment.
Yes, of course.
My buddy Dion writes for the Tonight Show and he did a bit with, as it did like a bad
improv singing bit with Jimmy, with Jimmy calling him on like just doing the same thing
over and over again and he says I'm off stage and for no reason the show gets really crazy
and Dion was so proud that it just cuts to a photo of an old ballroom and Dion's character
is in it singing in this old shot and he said it's from The Shining and I go buddy you don't
even know like what you've done because in that movie he says here's Johnny that's the
Tonight Show and you wrote that bit for the Tonight Show you didn't even realize it.
Inception.
Yeah.
We're just all.
Incepted.
Looking at each other's inner eggs.
Okay.
It's pretty, pretty cool, man.
It was pretty fun.
Ball.
Oh, great.
I'll keep going with the singles.
Let's do it.
For 400.
1965, the only Rolling Stones song to be included in the Library of Congress recording registry.
Notable cover versions were recorded by Devo and The Residence.
This is a number one.
Paint It Black.
Paint It Black's gone on my guess.
Yeah.
I was thinking about that.
Satisfaction.
Shit.
My dick.
You fools.
It's me.
I'll try.
I'll try singles.
600.
1999, this song pioneered the use of auto-tune to distort the vocals and won the Grammy for
Best Dance Recording, the only Grammy this legendary performer with a multi-decade career
has won.
Becky.
Wait.
So you want the song or the artist?
Both.
If you get one, you're getting the other on this one.
I can't think of the song name, though.
Oh.
It sounds like the past.
You tell me the artist.
You got a past?
Oh, is that Turn Back Time?
Is it Cher, Cher Turn Back Time?
No.
No?
Oh.
Well, Paul doesn't know.
Paul just thinks that's not it.
Just to be clear.
No, I know.
Right.
Okay.
He knows it.
All right.
You're on the right track.
It's not the right song.
It's Cher or something, right?
Yeah.
It's because Turn Back Time is the one on the battleship.
Yes.
Yeah.
So that'd be too late.
That's too early.
The battleship was too early.
That was in the '80s.
Oh, is that too early?
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
Yeah, sorry.
I'm '99.
I was just saying, Nick Newman is singing his heart out, if you want to, if he's mouthing
it, he's singing his heart out.
I can't even see the chat or the people because I'm sharing the screen so that everybody can
see the scooperty.
Yeah.
I win.
Because I'm seeing an amazing performance.
It's just true.
I can't fucking think of the song.
I pass.
Matt?
If I could turn back time.
No.
It is Turn Back Time.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
It was, "Do you believe in life after love?"
But I did the, whatever the thing is where you switch the thing.
This is why I'll never perform a hand stab in my show.
Good.
Because you did get this.
In this case, you only lost some points.
Yeah.
You didn't stab yourself in the hand.
Didn't lose a digit.
I literally was thinking, do you believe in my head over and over again and then the other
words came out of my mouth.
And here we are.
Yep.
Do you believe you can turn back time.
Matt, get those points back.
I'll take more share trivia, please, Jacob.
Let's do photos in movies for 800.
I'm thinking of a celebrity that was married to Sonny Bono.
Share.
Correct.
Yeah.
An autograph photo is stolen off a restaurant wall and gives this movie its title.
The photo is of a Tony award winning singer, dancer, and actress famous for a recurring
role in an iconic television series, Meow.
What's the movie?
What's Eating Gilbert Grape.
No.
What's eating?
It's just a picture of a grape.
To Wong Fu, Julie Neumar.
Close.
So Julie Neumar was Catwoman, but that's not, uh, you got, you got half of it.
What's in the middle?
You got the right movie.
You just got the, you have to get the title to Wong Fu blank.
Julie Neumar.
Yeah.
Oh, well, here we are.
I made it this far guys.
It's been good pass Paul to Wong Fu.
Thanks for everything.
Julie Neumar.
I was really good.
Thanks for everything.
No matter how much Newman acted it out, I wouldn't have gotten it.
That is a tough one.
That is a toughie.
I was so sad that was passing to Paul.
Paul, you're up.
Binder's full, please.
Let's go.
For eight hundo, closing it out.
Who are Winona LaDuke, Geraldine Ferraro, Sarah Palin, Kamala Harris, Sissy Farenthold,
and Lena Springs?
I don't know.
Who are Winona LaDuke, Geraldine Ferraro, Sarah Palin, Kamala Harris, Sissy Farenthold,
and Lena Springs?
I don't know.
Who are Winona LaDuke, Geraldine Ferraro, Sarah Palin, Kamala Harris, Sissy Farenthold,
and Lena Springs?
Queens.
These are Queens.
Oh, wait.
Did they?
Yeah.
Women who ran for vice-president.
Okay.
Okay, female vice-presidential candidates.
Yeah.
That counts.
That is correct.
Queens.
And Queens.
How long I'm Queens?
Queens.
It's me.
I'll try.
Name the candy.
400.
Oh, it's a Daily Double.
Give me a break.
Nell Carter.
Give me a break of that Milky Way candy bar.
Okay.
Turn back time.
It's not a battleship.
Yeah.
If I could find a way here.
Name the candy.
800.
Make miles happy.
My dick.
Oh shit.
That is candy right there.
In case.
So emergency.
My wean-ween.
Oh, mounds dicks in case.
Oh, my house, slim Jim's, um, not to you.
Oh, that's your opinion.
Oh, gross.
Give me a candy slim Jim, please cover the sugar in case of emergency.
Yeah, uh, snickers Milky way.
I don't know.
Uh, pass Paul Twizzlers Twizzlers is make smells happy.
Yeah, I was close to slim Jim.
I mean, in a, in a licorice sense from, from, from like an alien's observing humans.
A general shape, shape, shape sensation.
Yeah.
Like a thermal camera.
You can't tell the difference between a slim Jim and a Twizzler.
Oh God.
How many of our poor boys in uniform have suffered that indignity?
I was on the thermal sergeant couldn't tell the difference between a slim Jim.
Oh, it was so upsetting.
I don't know how to name the candy for 600.
Isn't life juicy?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, I think Kardashian, it's Kimberly J Kardashian.
I think it's starburst starburst is Paul run in the candy category.
Huge lead 3,800.
I have 800 Matt has a negative I will tell you I was on, I was on an online candy store
last night.
Look at it.
Candy.
Of course you were.
Oh man.
It looked, there's this damn tick tock shop got me.
I didn't go on a tick tock shop, but they, they do this thing where they scoop the candy
in a very ASMR kind of way.
All these different, very exotic candies.
Oh man.
Ooh, so many exotic candy.
That's exactly what their old gig is.
I'll go photos and movies for 600.
It's the other daily double.
This is my chance to keep second place, a framed photo of the protagonist's brother's
girlfriend.
To avoid insulting a young actress, the photo was actually of the art director's son in
a wig.
Woof.
What's the movie?
This is, oh no, it's not that shit.
You fool.
Oh wait.
No, no, no.
I think it is.
I think it is home alone.
Oh, I think it's home alone.
It is motherfucking home alone motherfuckers.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
Jacob, you're really, you're an angry winner.
It's a Macaulay Culkin's brother, he like has, I can't believe that just popped into
my head.
Is it the, is that Butch or whatever his name is?
Yeah.
And they, and they have like a picture of his girlfriend.
I got a Canadian girlfriend.
Yeah.
And it's like, it is like a silly looking picture.
Matt closing out the category and the game photos in movies, Matt trying to hold on to
third place for $400.
Let's go.
A photo of three siblings where two of them seemed to, seemed to fade out of existence.
That's heavy.
What's the movie?
Also, weight has nothing to do with it.
Baron von Munchausen.
Munchausen by proxy.
Fade out of existence.
What is the-
Come on, you know this.
I do?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Everybody knows this.
This is the reason that for like two years I wore a Mickey Mouse shirt.
If you don't get this right-
It's because this, this photograph in this movie.
If you don't get this right, I'm going to call you a Huey loser.
Wow.
Hip to be square.
Close.
That's it.
In high definition.
Okay.
That's it.
Matt, Matt, if you don't get this, I am going to go outside.
I'm going to get into my lifted Toyota pickup truck.
I'm going to drive over there and I'm going to take you on a camping trip.
With Elizabeth Shoe.
Elizabeth Shoe.
She's going to be there.
Harry and the Hendersons.
No.
Oh no.
Adventures in Babysitting.
Matt, you're going to feel silly in the future when you don't get this.
That's fine.
Let's just, let's just make that the present.
Paul.
It's back to the future.
Back to the future.
Oh, right, right, right, right, right.
I did not love those movies when they came out and my friends did and then I was always
on at like parties and sleepovers and stuff, but I was always half paying attention to
those things.
It was a seminal movie for me.
Well, it's an age thing too.
It is for a lot of people.
No, it is for a lot of people.
It's an age thing.
Yeah.
I'm a little older than you.
I forget sometimes.
And those early years are big, right?
Like that was a big movie in the theater for me.
Well, and that was, it was big for me because Back to the Future 2 came out at, I was, when
whatever, whatever age I was, when Back to the Future 2 came out, I was the perfect age
for that.
And so that got me hooked like back on Back to the Future 1 and then, yeah, then I was
back in.
Uh, that's the game by the way, Paul crushed us.
What?
4,200 points.
I have 1600 points.
At least I'm respectable because Matt only has negative 400.
But if I'd gotten that share question right, I would have only gotten the third.
That's right.
So you got that going.
So you got that going for you.
Which is nice.
Uh, what was it?
That was actually a very well-written, uh, uh, tribute.
That was great.
That was really good.
I love, I love that scoop.
Even though I got all over by it, it was really good.
Um, thank you for writing it.
If you want to send us a scooperty or any kind of jock versus nerd, HeyScoops.com is
where you ought to go.
HeyScoops.com right there on the homepage.
You can make us a jock versus nerd quiz to play on the show.
You can also send us some emails, send us some scoop mail right over there at HeyScoops.com.
Do it now.
Um, I definitely thought I was going to have, uh, name lists by now, by this point in the
episode to thank people and I don't, but we're going to thank a lot of people.
Are we working on it?
Are we going to add it in or do you think we're just going to go one more episode?
Uh, because this one comes out tomorrow, I think we're going to go one more episode.
Great.
Well, there's no time.
We thank all the people who support us on Patreon.
Obviously we're in a transition of going from any to no one.
Um, other people, a lot of people have offered to, to hop in there, um, we're still getting
our, our, our, because we did, and we may still take them up on, but we are going to
experiment and see if we can do it ourselves, which is a little weird, um, but, uh, uh,
we should be thanking everyone the way they should be doing it.
But the way we simplified our Patreon, it seems like we will be able to just be able
to get lists ourselves and be, we don't have a lot of, uh, uh, crazy deliverables anymore
so we can't have people write us and yell at us, um, which is also why we had any, we
think we're safe.
Sure.
I think with the way it's digital deliverables, safer, the digital rules are mostly doing
kind of hang stuff and that kind of thing.
So yes, um, which is coming up soon, uh, beyond the lookout, we'll have that sometime next
week.
I'm planning.
Great.
But we've been more community oriented with our Patreon and it shows is our patron has
gone up a little bit and we appreciate that.
Uh, it really helps us out tremendously, it helps us in all that we do for us and our
entire scoop community.
Yes, indeed.
If you want to contribute and you have room in your heart and your wallet for, uh, to
support us, head on over to preachingfun.com
magazine.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preachingfun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page where
for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
I was just looking through our Patreon, uh, page earlier today and, uh, I was looking
through the, the full list with like everybody who has ever been on our Patreon at all.
And it was just a little walk down memory lane.
It was so great seeing all the names of current and former Patreons and people who have been
on there for a long time.
Uh, it has like, they, they go away and they come back and then they, and I think, you
know, and they go, sorry, I had to take a break.
I look, you know, no explanation needed.
Anytime you can find a little time to support us is just amazing.
And we're so grateful.
And if it can't be for your entire lives, that's, that's okay.
You know, uh, we appreciate it.
Um, and of course we appreciate our long time, uh, supporters, uh, as much.
So, uh, but we truly, we truly have such a soft spot in our hearts.
For everybody who supports us over there at preachingfund.com and fartsinabag.biz, uh,
because we couldn't do the show without you.
Just very frankly, we are dependent on our Patreon supporters.
We are dependent on our paid subscribers.
So if you think this show is worth more than $0, preachingfund.com, fartsinabag.biz, that
is the place that you can go.
Uh, oh, uh, AWOL scoop, thank you for reminding me.
Uh, we do have our billionaire experiment still in the works.
Uh, the experiment is you're going to give each of us a billion dollars.
So we need $3 billion, uh, before taxes, $3 billion gross.
I don't think we've been completely clear on the financials here.
It can be crypto.
It can be fine with paying it, paying back some of that.
Yeah, yeah.
No, if we have to tax on it and whatever is income or however we have to do that, we'll
figure that out on our end.
You don't worry about that.
You just come up with the 3 billion even.
We might even bring Annie back to help us figure that one out.
Yeah, we might, we might, uh, maybe a contractor fee.
Yeah.
Uh, but yeah, you give us the $3 billion and we will see if we are better at being billionaires
than the current billionaires out there.
You know what?
I'll go ahead and say it.
We'll even bring back the hands-less eating, uh, reward.
So there you go.
Challenge returns, but we learned the first time around, we have to do it all in one.
We can't do like multiple sessions, one hands-less eating session.
You know, Matt, you know, that has to be available at the, uh, where do we go eat that famous
Los Angeles?
Pepper mill, pepper mill, pepper mill menu.
The big step.
Lucky for you.
Everything's on the pepper mill.
Right.
You need to just sit seriously, reinstate that on the Patrion at the $3 billion level.
We need to make a legit $3 billion level on the Patrion.
You're right.
Because that's hilarious.
Eating videos, eating video, $3 billion.
No, no, no, for $3 billion.
You get three, you get three, $3 billion for $3 billion.
You get one from each of us.
Yeah.
I like that before the government, even right away, we're giving away 5% to Patrion.
Like we would increase their stock price.
Right.
Yeah.
It would be, uh, it would be a big win day for them as well.
If someone had three billion, they give away, they're going to do it through Patrion and
not contact.
That's pretty great.
Not just give it right to us.
I mean, but you know what?
Maybe they really want those videos and the other benefits that come from being a Patrion.
There are incredible benefits that come from being a Patrion at PreachingFun.com and Fartsinabag.biz.
Have you not hit the production meeting of music?
This is killer stuff.
I'm going to put $150 million by the way, is what Patriots cut would be.
Amazing.
We would be giving Patriot $150 million.
I'm okay.
I'm okay with it.
All right.
We'd be, we'd be a Patriot on celebrities forever.
My, my, uh, we'd probably get an invite to their parties.
Improv group, possible side effects.
We took out fame now.org, uh, cause it was a, for a place for our fans to demand our
fame now.
Uh, so these are the kinds of things you got to put out in the universe, baby, $3 billion
Patriot level.
I'll just, you know, not, not to let one, you know, influence the other too much, but
I'll let you know how the fame now, uh, worked out.
That was a different timeline.
It was a different time.
The internet was a different place.
Jesus 3 billion, three hands for eating videos does not include lower tier patron.
Jesus 3 billion, three hands for eating videos.
Asterix does not include lower tier rewards.
We should, it's a, it's a tear all to itself.
As we continue this bit, we should credit like every manifesting author there is out
there.
Like everybody just keep, um, all right, actually thanks to the secret.
Thank you for Jimmy and my, my parking has been exceptional lately.
I don't know about you guys.
Good.
Thank you to Jimmy and Michael for stopping by.
Got to go, go like, and subscribe to a list casting on YouTube.
Uh, thanks for this podcast.
Thanks everybody.
Join us, uh, by putting us in their ears this week.
We really appreciate you.
Listen to us weekend and week out.
Um, stay safe out there.
We love you.
And we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
See you at the Coles.
See you at the Coles motherfuckers.
Like Chicago, the city we call home, O'Hare International Airport is never done.
And we're never outdone.
We imagine, evolve, and build what's next.
That's what we're doing with ORD next.
We reimagined its core and started on the largest terminal expansion in its history
to enable smoother connections.
First yet, we're creating jobs for all Chicagoans.
See how ORD next will elevate travel and Chicago's economy.
Go to ORDnext.org, elevating every journey.