Oh hello there I didn't see you but I'm so happy you are here because I want to thank you, the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Right now I'd like to thank Jake Schneider, Jason Klepper, Jeff Harris, Jonathan, Lori Ellsworth, Leon Kasab, Malia, and Mike.
If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver just like these fine folks, PreachingFun.com is where you can go.
Head over to PreachingFun.com right there on the page, sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver.
Deliver that fucking Ice Cream straight to people's fucking ear holes and who knows, the life you save may be your own.
Here's the program.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social?
Yeah I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
Hello from a secret location.
I mean it's Jersey.
Right.
Oh shit, was that a secret?
Damn it.
I suck at this.
It's time for Matt and Mattingly's Ice Cream Social.
Sitting in New Jersey together, it's Matt and Mattingly, Matt, Donnelly, and Paul Mattingly.
Sitting in Las Vegas, it's me, Jeff, I'm the audio guy.
We're PreachingFun.
We are not in Jersey, but we can't say where we are.
We are sneakily outside.
Oh that's right, you are post Jersey.
We're post Jersey, yeah.
We're at something that we'll definitely be talking about in the next episode.
But we are not allowed to talk about it yet.
But we have other things to talk about, which is like, Paul's really upset, so here Paul, here's five bucks, I'm sorry.
Paul just keeps really on me about those five bucks.
He came at me last night and he's like, "Hey, you got five bucks for the vending machine, they don't have any changes at the front."
I'm like, "Here's five."
And then this morning he's like, "Oh yeah, I owe you five bucks."
I told you last time I was also good for it, which I'm a man of my word.
I know, you're good for it. I don't, I'm good.
I just feel like it's been a subtext this entire morning, we just haven't, you know.
If I don't have something to hold over your head.
Paul's just...
It's acquiring interest.
I did scare the living shit out of Paul this morning.
Paul thought I died.
Yep.
Were you guys sharing a room?
No.
Okay.
In that case, I have even more questions.
That's a key factor, actually, is that we are not sharing a room.
We parted ways last night and everything seemed to be fine.
I went and got my sleeps on.
We had said 10 o'clock meetup in the morning.
And I get ready, do my thing, 10 o'clock rolls around.
I look around, no Matt.
I go out to check the car, no Matt.
Okay, that's odd.
I'm chilling for a little bit.
10, 15, okay.
I get on, I text Matt.
Let it sit.
You know, nothing.
Don't hear anything.
Yeah.
That's weird, you know.
And I let it go and Ann calls and we're chatting.
And then it's 10.30 and I'm like, well, shit, I better call Matt.
So I call Matt.
Nothing.
It goes right to voicemail.
I call him again.
It goes to voicemail.
So I'm like, oh no.
And then I look at the phone and I start looking at the text.
He sent the text last night and it was in a chain text.
And he hasn't responded to anybody else's stuff.
He hasn't liked anybody's stuff.
I'm like, he hasn't touched this in hours.
He's incommunicado with me completely.
So I'm like, okay, I gotta go check on it.
So I go to his door and I knock and I wait a little bit.
Nothing.
I knock again.
A little more urgently this time.
The fucking tomb of Imhotep.
I'm like, well, I'm going to the front desk to report my friend's dead.
We were supposed to meet at 10.
It's like 1040.
Then I start walking to the fucking desk.
And sure enough, I'm almost to the front desk and I get a buzz on my phone and it's Matt.
And he's like, oh, I slept through my alarm.
Yeah, you fucking did.
He thought I was the housekeeping again.
Yeah, the knocking.
I thought it was the housekeeper being like, well, my alarm isn't going off yet.
So the housekeeper is too early.
And I'm just going to go to the housekeeper.
And knock twice.
Hard.
Yep, that's true.
In the same bit.
I was expecting the door to open, you know, in housekeeping.
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah.
So I put the door to open and just go like, no, thank you.
This is the door open, you know?
Yeah.
And then it never opened.
So I was like, oh, all right.
The housekeeper took a hit.
When my alarm goes off, I'll talk to the housekeeping.
Yeah.
Then all of a sudden my brain is like, there's no way I slept through my alarm.
And then I got up and I sure enough slept through my alarm.
Turns out when you actually only have three hours of sleep and then you go right from the airport to Tierney's Tavern and then to, you know, two hours of comedy shows and then drive a significant distance after that to go to a secret location and check into a hotel.
You're more tired than you thought.
You're more tired.
Where's you out?
It turns out.
Where's your ride out?
And I could see even in Paul's retelling of it just now, I could see how stressed he was that he was never going to get that $5 back.
Exactly.
That was the first thought on my mind.
I was like, I'm out.
Son of a bitch.
I'm going to have to get that $5 from the estate.
This is going to be a huge pain.
I promise you in the four minutes it took me to walk down the hallway.
Not even four minutes.
Three minutes it took me to walk down the hallway.
I'm going down the hallway through different things.
I'm walking towards the front of the gate and like I get to the second like hallway gate change and I just, my face just drops.
I'm like, oh my God, this is it.
It'd be so weird.
I was like, first of all, how am I going to explain this to Sarah?
How am I going to explain this to his kids?
What's my responsibility from this point forward?
And then I was like, this can't be it.
This would be the end of everything.
Not to mention the cars in my name.
Oh my God.
Forget it.
All that shit.
I was just like, fucking forget it.
I wasn't even worried about it.
I was like, I was kind of going, well, I'll be stranded here for a day or two, but we'll figure it out.
But that's not what's important now.
What's important is my friend is dead and I need to attend to his affairs.
I'm going to have to adopt his children.
I mean, I might have to, you know, move back to Vegas for a little while to help out.
Certainly I'm sure the first services will be held.
I don't know.
Do I need to contact Tierney's?
Who else needs to be notified?
Is Tierney's Bats official next of kin?
Sarah.
Tierney's.
That's the order that you...
But no, don't act like that's some bullshit move.
He knows like 85 people that work in that fucking building.
It's not far off from next to kin.
This is the right move.
I think if I told the Tierney's second, that would have been totally fine.
It would have gotten out to the entirety of Jersey in like five minutes.
But then, of course, then selfishly it starts to overwhelm me.
I'm like, I'm just getting on my feet.
I'm just...
The house just got painted.
Jesus Christ.
Just getting my income straight.
This is one of the few outside gigs.
This is because of our partnership that I'm able to do these things.
It's all...
I can't fall apart like this.
I can't.
The president in chat is saying, you know, I'm laughing, but this isn't funny.
No, me being dead is not funny.
The amount of planning Paul did in four minutes is amazing.
I was all the way...
I mean, I was raised in a house of catastrophizers.
So, you know, that's where my brain goes real fucking quick.
It doesn't take me any time to be like, I'm destitute.
The podcast has had to stop.
I don't know if I can even improvise anymore.
You guys have already made it very clear that you felt that I was very replaceable on this show.
We've already done this round the clock.
I mean, I've even done this before.
I've been the one to call and text Matt in the mornings when we're doing all these things.
And Matt's like, now he's asleep.
Matt sleeps through shit sometimes.
It just happens.
Matt is a heavy sleeper.
He sleeps through shit sometimes.
That's it.
I'm a heavy sleeper, too, to the point where I have to have my door propped open and everything.
But in a hotel, when it's a different place, I don't sleep nearly as heavy.
I don't have my white noise going like crazy, so...
Yeah, when Matt's in a hotel and not near his kids, he does sleep heavily.
Oh, yeah.
That's absolutely true.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
Also, the night before I came, my cats were dickheads, right?
Sometimes I've done things where I leave our doggy door...
It's a cat door.
I have cats, but it's a doggy door that's built in our house.
I leave our doggy door, we have a little slide, and I leave it open at night.
Other cats have come into our backyard and sniffed around that door in the middle of the night.
And all of a sudden, they'll be like a big cat fight.
And that's woken me up a few times.
And I...
Is Sarah downstairs just yelling, "You bitch! You bitch! You bitch!"
I had to get up at 5, 515 to make the flight to Vegas.
Okay.
And my cats woke me up at 415.
Ah!
Assholes!
And then I went down to be like, "Did I leave the fucking cat door open?"
And I get up in a panic because Sarah gets up every morning with the kids.
And so waking her up early is just a much larger mistake than me and my little flight.
Yeah.
And so I get up right away to what I think is close the cat door.
And I came down, and my cats were just fighting each other.
That's it. The door was closed. I did everything right.
They just decided to be fucking assholes at 415 in the morning and fight each other.
They normally get along.
Yeah.
They decided to fight each other at 415 in the morning, and then I was up.
Right? And so that's it. I got three hours of sleep, and that was my day.
And so then I was off to the airport all day and all that stuff.
So yeah, I was more tired than I thought. My cats are dicks, basically.
And then have you discussed with Paul what you're going to have to do from now on,
now that you have pets that do hate each other, how Paul keeps all of his pets separate?
Yeah.
How you're going to have to start doing that now?
I have to build some kind of Panama Canal of fences and things in my house.
That's right. It really is. It really is. It is a fucking lock system.
Now, here's the thing. So before I left, we had to go take Giz out to grandma's
so that she wouldn't be more trouble than Anne could deal with.
So Anne's just got three cords.
But that was an extra trip that we had to do on and off.
Wait, when you leave town, you take one of the dogs to the dog sitter
so that Anne doesn't have to deal with all the animals that hate each other
being in the house without you there.
I didn't know that.
That is very sweet.
And Matt, I want you to know that I will not be taking one of your cats next time you leave town.
You would love the deeks. You would love schmicky deeks.
You would love schmicky deeks.
She's such an attention hound.
It's only a three hour round trip to go take the dog and drop her off and come back home.
It's really nothing.
It's really no trouble at all.
Yeah, it just eats up the great majority of your off day.
Especially because one of those 90 minutes is with a dog in the car.
Honestly, we don't mind it.
With a classically well-behaved dog.
A dog that we talk about all the time, how well-behaved it is.
She is really well-behaved unless she's around Adora.
That's it.
The shit of it is Adora and Giz are very similar in temperament and everything.
And that's why they hate each other.
And they really get territorial around Anne.
That's all there is to it.
All I have to say is we had a really good show at Terry's Tavern.
We sure as fuck did.
That was the main crux of yesterday.
Getting to that.
And we did it.
And I'm very, very pleased.
It was super exciting for me to perform with these players that I hadn't played with in a long time.
I played with Didgeridooche in the past, but it didn't mean it.
And he fucking brought the fucking fire.
Everybody was just top of game, man.
Everybody was really good.
Pat Shepard drove on the shore.
Steve came out from West Jersey.
Probably about 30 scoops came out.
There's probably about maybe 20 other people just from town.
One guy who read about Only Me being a magic show and was disappointed that it also had Dion Flynn from The Tonight Show and Kurt Braunhuler and all this pesky improv stuff.
All this hilarious comedy that the entire room is enjoying except me.
Wow.
This is a good sign, though, Matt.
This is a good sign.
That means that people are getting back into magic and they're taking it seriously.
Because what the mind noodler wants are people that take magic very seriously to watch his act.
That's it.
So this guy is this douche.
I'll just call him a douche.
This douche shows up.
And he's there with his wife.
This hero.
This hero shows up.
He's a douche.
He's like, "Yeah, I'm not here because I heard you're doing magic."
I go, "Yeah, well, I've been doing some magic for sure, but this is more of like a comedy night."
Now, everything that I put out said random comedy night.
Yes.
That was the name of the event.
Yeah.
And it's an improv stand-up and magic blast.
Yes.
Right?
And so I know for a fact that I didn't overly emphasize that this is going to be a magic show.
But I guess on Tierney's social media, one of the posts was like, "It's going to be a magic show."
Ah, gotcha.
Right?
Well, let's be fair.
This was proudly displayed on the dumpster.
Okay.
So that is a banner they made just for the event.
Uh-huh.
And it was located on the dumpster of Tierney's Tavern's fence around its dumpster.
It is a picture of Matt Donnelly in front of a banner there.
What's it say, Paul?
What's the banner say?
What it says on the banner is...
"Join us October 23rd for an intimate night of my noodling with Matt Donnelly."
It doesn't even say magic.
It doesn't say magic.
An intimate night.
It still doesn't say magic.
Yeah.
"Intimate night's weird phrasing and my noodling."
And it's brought to you by Guinness.
Yeah.
Guinness sponsored it, so I'm official.
Matt Donnelly will fuck you if you come by on this night.
And I laughed.
So basically we said doors at seven, but that's just because I just wanted people in there
because I knew that we had to drive a long time after the show.
So I was like, I'm going to...
Yeah.
You know, I just want to get everybody in.
And I was like...
And I got up and I told everybody the whole situation, why we're there, why this night
came together, that two people were coming literally from writing for Jimmy Fallon and
literally taking a car from the city to Tierney's to make it to the show.
I said, "They're going to show up whenever they're going to show up because Jimmy Fallon
can keep them for as long as he wants."
Right?
And so I was like, "We're going to do some improv.
We're going to have some standup sets.
I'm going to do some magic.
It's going to be a cool hang."
Right?
Get everybody on the same page.
And so at like 7, 15, we did an improv set with Paul, me, Steve, and Patch, the four
of us without Dion and Kurt.
And we really had a great set.
It was really good.
The audience was just eating it up and laughing it.
And we finished and the douche is sitting there going, "I thought there was going to
be a magic show."
I go, "There is going to be a magic show."
Like in my head, I was like, "I just explained this actually as a matter of fact."
I was just on stage talking about this.
I go, "Yeah, there is going to be a magic show."
He's like, "When?"
I was like, "Next."
But he was the one tool bag in a sea of lovelies.
That's the other thing.
Everybody was...
We had a great night.
It was amazing.
It's a podcast.
I'm only talking about the one dumb thing.
Right.
Yeah.
So I go, "Next."
He's like, "Well, good."
Or whatever.
And I go...
And I literally go, "Did you not enjoy what you just saw?"
And I say that because I was so comfortable.
The audience was roaring for the whole thing.
It was just confusing.
So I literally was like, "Can we chill out?"
And I thought he was going to laugh it off.
Maybe I'm interpreting him too hard.
Maybe he isn't a douche.
At this moment, at this moment of the conversation, how many feet from the stage that you were
just performing on are you?
15 feet.
Yeah.
Great.
Okay.
Yeah.
This is not down the road.
This is not in the next building over.
This is next to the stage that you were just on.
Yeah.
And so I expect him to laugh.
They're like, "Oh, yeah.
No.
That was great."
Or whatever.
And he goes, "Mm.
Improv."
And I was like...
I was having a conversation with the scoop when I first got in there.
This is great.
When I first got in there, I was talking.
And I'm talking with this scoop, and they're telling me some heartfelt stuff about what
the podcast means to them.
Great.
You're having a nice conversation.
And that motherfucker came in and inserted himself right in the middle of me talking
to the scoop.
Oh, great.
I'm like, "Asshole."
And so from that point on, I wrote that motherfucker off.
Right.
He was a shitbag.
And I think he's come out to other events there that we've done.
I don't think he was...
I think I recognized him from previous things.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Was it Brogan?
No, no, no.
It was Brogan.
It was not Brogan.
Brogan was awesome.
Yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Full side note.
Brogan fucking flew in from Scotland to see the show at Tierney Tavern.
Insane.
That's insane.
Yeah.
Brogan's the best.
They brought me...
Carolyn and Paul came out.
Yes.
Carolyn and Paul.
Oh, good.
They were very upset because they definitely had traveled the furthest to be at Tierney's
show of anyone.
Right.
And then Brogan torpedoed them.
Almost.
Yeah, yeah.
But we found...
They let us know that they met at our second Tierney's event.
That's where they met each other.
That's where the connection happened.
That's right.
I forgot about that.
Yeah.
So that was really sweet.
And they're still together.
I think so far that's the only successful couple in the world.
That's not dwell on the past, Paul, so focused on the present.
It's not the only successful one.
We've had a few successful ones.
We've had some unsuccessful ones.
That's also true.
Whatever.
But yeah, Christine came out and...
Winner scoop successful in quotes.
Carl and Amy showed up.
Yeah.
And...
Nicky.
Nicky was there.
Yeah.
And then...
This is the part of the show where Paul names people he saw.
Look.
And then we get in trouble for not naming the people that also came.
Michael Scoop was there, of course.
Good, good.
Yeah.
Yeah, tons of people were there.
And it was awesome.
And then what I really loved was at the end of the show, I came up to a couple who was
sitting there at a table and they had had a blast.
They loved me.
They're like, "This is our first time we've ever come out to a thing.
We just wanted to come out and see what's up."
I thought there was going to be more magic.
No.
Where is the more magic?
These guys were like, "This was the funniest thing.
I'm hurting from laughing."
I'm like, "This was very funny.
It would have been so much better if there had been magic."
Thank you for taking a chance on us.
I got him a chip.
We're obelisk people left and right.
It was great.
A couple came up to me and said that we love the podcast.
We're going to head out.
They said, "We love it tonight.
We'll check out your podcast.
We're going to head out."
And I said, "Oh, do you have chips?"
And they said, "No."
I was craning my neck for Paul to look at me as I went over and got two chips out.
Matt pulled his shoulder, pat himself on the back.
Learning the ways of the obelisk.
I'll tell you who else got chips from Matt Donnelly last night, and that is the following
sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by Matt Donnelly's Magical Manual for Manipulating Matt's Cats.
It's from 2024.
It's from Big Sexy Digital Nomad.
Some of you may know that Matt has two cats, Shmeeky and Shmooky.
Both of them are certified assholes, bird killers and General No Goodniks.
They cause bullshit after bullshit.
But if you have cats that give you trouble, Matt has a way to solve it.
Yes, in fact, it's Matt Donnelly's Magic Manual for Dealing with Cats.
The wonders of this book are that it can enclose said felines.
All you need to do is lay it open on a coffee table, hanging towards an edge, where they
are tempted to knock the shit out of it.
When they come up to try and do that on the book, they will fall into a great abyss of
a hidden compartment inside the tome.
You can quickly slam it shut and you have trapped kitty.
The book itself is just an animal trap, and that looks like a book.
No pincers, nothing sharp.
The animal will not be harmed, merely contained.
So if you're having trouble with your pussy, why not lock it up in Matt Donnelly's Magical
Manual?
Yeah.
And you can use it manually.
And our hay scoops at checkout.
Paul, I think when we left, you were listing off people that you saw yesterday.
Okay.
So then I saw Kurt Prodler, and oh my god, Kurt's stand up was hilarious.
He really had me losing my shit.
So fucked up.
Oh, he's got it.
He figured it all out.
He got it all put together.
I think he's finally figuring it out.
I think he's really coming.
Good.
Good for him.
He's so fucking good.
No, he was saying that he doesn't do stand up as much because he got the gig working
for Fallon, and it takes up so much of the week that you don't get out.
So he was very happy to be doing stand up last night, but he crushed.
He was so funny.
And we were able to cajole him into playing with us for the second half too, and he was
very happy that he did that, and it was awesome.
He was so funny in the improv, too.
So just to put some buttons on the douche, so I do a magic set.
I felt like it went really well.
I really enjoyed the magic set.
This was one of the better magic sets I've seen.
I wish the whole show had been like this.
No, he said nothing.
He said absolutely nothing.
No, he did not say nothing.
He said nothing.
He did not do all of that and did not say anything after the magic set.
He did not say nothing.
The only thing that was...
Come on, dude.
I mean, everyone else was having a great time, but specifically what brought me a lot of
joy was his wife was having a fucking blast.
His wife was laughing at everything while he was stone-faced.
And so I'm going through a magic set, and I did a magic set.
I did some cool magic.
Yeah.
It's impossible.
Matt, I believe that you did good magic.
I believe that you did really good magic.
Your magic was great, Matt.
At this point, I'm like, "What was he expecting?"
If this...
What I'm doing, right?
I did the fucking ring bit, the arm chopper bit, and then the straightest jacket escape.
And the ringed ones tends to be most magicians' favorite little magic thing is the ringed
one, right?
The ringed one is an excellent one.
The arm chopper is one of your newer ones, and it's very good.
The straightest jacket, a classic.
It's got good comedy.
It's got good magic.
What do you want?
And I was just like, "What...
Did he want doves or a floating bar stool?
What was he looking for that he needed that he was not doing?"
He was looking for intimacy, man.
That's right.
He was looking to be intimate.
Maybe he was just looking for just love, maybe just a human connection between two people.
Here's the thing.
For those who were in attendance, he ended up being a focal point for part of Matt and
Dion's improvised two-man set.
So Dion Flynn, right, Dion who plays Obama on Fallon, Dion is, I would describe, a beautifully
intense person.
He has no kind of aw-shucks-y bullshit mode.
He's only...
Oh, I love that.
Yeah.
He's only talking real all the time, and that's why I love hanging out with him.
He just cannot...
He does not small talk.
And so for his bit, he was like, "Hey, everyone, I don't even know what I'm fully doing here."
He came in in the middle of my intro, and he goes, "Yeah, I just felt like where you
were in your intro, that felt like a good time for me to come in and sit down.
So I'm going to start talking now."
And he just kind of comes in, and he makes the whole audience move chairs and move closer
and come up.
Great.
And he's like, "We're going to go to different people."
He's like, "I'm just going to have you raise your hand.
I might not have been calling you.
You might not even talk."
Then he's calling someone, then he did have him say something, he goes, "And that's all
we're going to take from you.
That's not to say we're not curious about Rishank, but we're moving on."
And he just started bouncing around the room, and we kept doing scenes whenever he felt
like it off of information from the audience.
It was just beautifully fluid.
This is great.
I love this.
Yeah.
And so after we did a couple of scenes, he's like, "I'm going to look for the most stoic,
least involved person in the room."
At that moment, did you already know who it was going to be?
Well, yes.
I did.
And then he pointed to a woman, he goes, "And that was going to be you, but then you just
laughed at what I just said, so it's not you."
And then he just goes, "But you've had no smile the whole time."
And he points to him.
You haven't looked up.
Well, and then Deanser's asked him questions like, "You went to high school, tell me something
weird about your high school," or whatever, and the guy goes, "I went to high school where
we had to wear school uniforms, but when we joined the swim team, the first day we just
swam naked.
We were all naked for our swim team."
All right.
They made all the boys swim naked for P.E.
Yeah.
Well, that's just going to increase drag.
It's true.
That's not even good swimming practice.
Yeah, that high school had the worst swim times of the state.
And so, but the thing was, as soon as it was about him, he was fucking eating it up.
He was loving talking.
Oh, I got you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, is that what he wanted from the Magic?
Did he want to be a helper for one of the tricks in the Magic show maybe?
I looked out.
I asked.
I mean, I use a lot of audience volunteers.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
He did not keep a volunteer himself, but I was like, "This guy is basically like 20%
of my cruise ship people is this."
It's just guys a little older than me and have a couple of drinks who are like, "I'm
pretty awesome.
Why don't you use me more?"
I am great.
So we did bits with him or whatever.
And so, at this point, I'm like, "Fine."
I'm done with the amount of attention he has.
Yeah, yeah.
We're done.
But Kurt goes up in a standup and in it, he sets up a joke about how terrible his dad
is by putting him in the same category as Trump and Pol Pot or something like that.
And then, we actually identified maybe one of the issues why he wasn't having the best
time.
Oh, because he's a big Pol Pot fan.
He's a huge Pol Pot.
Yeah, yeah.
That makes sense.
He was wearing a Pol Pot 2028 shirt.
I should have noticed that.
And Kurt had a dead Canada shirt on, so it was automatically like, "Oh, yeah."
And then he did a bit making fun of Black Rifle Coffee.
And he was like, "Good, because we really need to know the politics of every product
that we have.
I'm glad coffee is finally letting people know that they're pro-gun."
Yeah.
He read this hilarious email that he wrote to the Black Rifle coffee company.
He actually, Kurt, posed for the cover of one of Mike Sack's recent books called Passing
on the Right.
Have you seen that?
No.
Kurt worked with Mike Sack on this book, Passing on the Right, and I think Kurt did the audio
book for it.
And it's this very, you know, like, faux infiltration of the very right-wing media sphere.
But that's kind of what the way Kurt wrote this.
Yeah, yeah.
This email.
He wrote a letter as someone who is a fan of the politics of Black Rifle Coffee and
saying they aren't taking it far enough.
That's the premise of the thing.
But he read the actual email.
He sent Black Rifle Coffee.
Black Rifle Coffee had a mocha flavor, and he was like, "A mocha flavor?"
There's a copy that has Kurt on the cover, if you look it up.
But there's a version that has Kurt on the cover.
Mike Sack's.
In the middle of this letter, our friend decided it was time to go, and he left.
Oh, was that when he left?
Yeah.
Oh, hilarious.
Hilarious.
That's enough for me.
Okay, perfect.
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
He might have been a stockholder of the coffee company, I think, or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was Ted Rifle.
He couldn't stand being the rifle butt of the joke.
So Kurt was awesomely unapologetic about it.
He's like, "Did that guy walk?"
And we're like, "If he thinks so," he's like, "Okay."
If I had known, I'd have been like, "Thank you.
Thank you, Kurt."
Oh, totally, because literally, I'm writing this because the podcast, it's fun to focus
on this guy, but there's a very small part of everyone else was just eating up fucking
everything we were doing.
I mean, here's the other part, of course.
We had a very nice contingence of scoops, and scoops always elevate every fucking event.
It was the thing of, I've been doing some improv now again in PA, and it was just so
lovely to step on stage, throw out a line, and get hit with a round of laughter, just
like boom.
I'm like, "Oh, yeah, I'm here with friends in support.
This is going to be great."
Yeah, it was really, really lovely.
Which made it even worse later when he thought Matt had died.
It did make it worse when I thought he had died.
I was like, "Oh, fuck," and all these scoops, I was like, "Oh, it's going so well."
Yeah, exactly.
Everything's going, everything's starting to work.
Wait.
Well, at least they got to see him one last time.
I'm telling you, man, I went from zero to a bajillion in like eight seconds.
Yes, you did.
It did, but what would your assumption be?
You're in a hotel.
You haven't heard from him.
You can't text him.
You can't call him, and he doesn't respond to a knock on the door.
Paul, this has happened to me.
This exact thing has happened to me traveling with Matt Donnelly.
I don't have to tell you what would have come into my mind.
I can tell you what came into my mind.
Oh, shit.
My assumption was, "Matt is sleeping through this."
Okay.
Well, that will be my default assumption from now on.
Raptured.
Sweetest scoop I've ever made.
It finally took, today of all days.
Oh, that guy was only off by a couple of weeks.
If I had slept five more minutes, and I would have been woken up by a wellness check, that
would have been a very bizarre start to my day.
I am so mad that the hotel did not come.
Yeah.
He got me before I got to the front desk.
That's all.
Oh, I'm so mad about that.
Because I've done everything in my power.
I was like, "Text, call, call again.
Knock on door loudly.
Knock on door loudly twice.
Matt's dead."
That was it.
No other possibilities.
Matt has died.
My friend and business partner has passed away unexpectedly.
I'll tell you who else was more concerned than you would have imagined about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and
who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who
else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's
death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was
more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more
concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who
else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about
Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned
about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else
was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death, and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
and who else was more concerned about Matt's death,
(laughing)