Oh hello there, I am so happy you're here, because I want to thank the ice cream truck
drivers.
Thank you so much ice cream truck drivers.
It's a new month, I don't have a new list just yet, but we will thank each and every
ice cream truck driver before the show, uh, this month, we'll do it this month.
We're gonna get it done.
It's all gonna get done, people.
Nobody panic.
In the meantime, if you want to become an ice cream truck driver, head over to preachingfun.com,
where you can go to sign up to be an ice cream truck driver and who knows, the life you save
may be your own.
Oh yeah.
Oh baby, this is what I like.
Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an ice cream social?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Great, let's go.
That song did not age well, none of that stuff, none of those old 50 poppy songs, I was just
listening to one this morning, it's the uh, Splish Splash, it's basically you're arrested
and not a list for life.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It's time for Matt and Mattyley's ice cream socials, sitting in the bathtub, that's Paul
Mattyley, sitting in a different bathtub, it's Matt Donnelly, and sitting in the shower,
it's me, Jacob the Audio Guy, we're preaching fun.
Yeah.
Splish Splash, I jump back in the bath, how was that, I know there was a party going on,
it's so strange, they didn't have headphones back then, what kind of a, what kind of quiet
ass weird party is happening outside your bathroom that you can't hear it and you come
out with a towel, and he had a towel on, he claims, and then he's like, I mean, I think
the answer to your question, Paul, is swinger party.
I think a swinger party is going on outside of his bathroom door.
Is that what it's about?
There's an orgy.
I'm thinking that right now.
There's an orgy happening and he's like, oh God, yeah, a whole orgy, a very very quiet
orgy.
I gotta get back in the tub, cause my boner is going crazy.
There are 18 different, no, 19 different people having sex out here very quietly.
There's one odd man getting double digits.
Oh, that guy is a good sport.
Look at him go.
I turned him into a bowling ball.
Oh, that's nice.
Ooh, that was a spare.
How are you doing, Matt?
Where are you?
Good.
I'm still in San Antonio and we received some feedback that my audio is super weird and
bad.
One, this is addressable, definitely going forward.
I have traveled with a directional microphone before.
It's just, I traveled with so much stuff that I was like, oh, if I just take a room recorder
with me, that's easier, but we're going to go ahead and call that experiment failed.
But we're going to keep the recorder and I think what we're going to do is do it.
This is just a good, here you go.
We're going to do like a headset mic or something like that into Matt's recorder so that he's
only going to carry, there's going to be a small additional thing to carry when he's
on the road.
This is something that we were going to address anyway and then some people said something
about it as well.
And so yeah, here we are.
Would you like like an airplane pilot headset?
Why not get him the, the, the, the cans that have the mic coming off of it?
Would that work?
Too soon.
Bring up airlines right now, Paul.
This is too soon.
Oh, buddy.
Are you, are you feeling the crunch?
I don't know yet because I don't, I don't know if San Antonio's airport qualifies as
one of the top 40 airports in the country.
It's only the top 40.
It's the top 40, but Vegas definitely does.
So the airport you're flying into definitely qualifies.
And here's the top 40 airlines in the U S coming in at number 40 it's STL St. Louis's
own hub of choice.
That's right.
And it's getting fucked raw dog style by our own American president.
If you can fucking call him that, what a ridiculous waste of skin.
All right, let's see how else he can destroy the middle class even further and kill small
business with his fat, stupid thumbs on every goddamn scale in the States.
What a bitch.
Dear Casey, my dad used to buy me that popcorn Oprah like the Chicago's O'Hare airport.
I was wondering if you could play Chicago O'Hare for my dad.
Here we go.
Coming out at number 39 with no kernels, it's popcorn O'Hare.
You guys got sending me these dead dog stories.
I got to read these dead dog stories and then go right into a pop pop hit Casey Casey.
The mic's still on.
Mike's on Casey.
Yeah.
Well, it's going to be on your ass.
You fucker.
Fuck you.
Casey.
I'm gone rogue.
Look, I'm bumblebee.
No, I'm cliff jumper and shaggy.
So eat my shit.
So Mike in the chat says, I don't know what the airport thing is because of air traffic
controllers being part of the budget for the government and the government being shut down.
The transportation secretary has asked 10% of flights to be canceled and they're targeting
40 of the top 40 major airports to cancel those flights to decrease air traffic since
so many air traffic controllers are either quitting or working a second job and calling
it out because they're not getting paid.
They're not actively not getting paid.
Gross.
It turns out they have bills.
We have air traffic controllers who listen to the show.
Yes.
I know several.
Yeah.
And my heart goes out to you guys.
Thank you for all the incredible hard work you do.
Also God damn my old hometown stomping grounds.
You see that horrific shit that went down in Louisville.
Sorry.
I can't hear you outside of a Casey case invoice now.
I'm now stuck hearing you in case.
Well friends, it turns out we went back to the bluegrass state and the bluegrass state
is now blue and charred, charred black with the remnants of thousands and thousands of
gallons of gasoline, jet fuel that dispersed all over human and animal alike, killing them
all in one fell swoop.
UPS made one special delivery to hell.
Oh, that that one is what you're talking about.
Yes.
I did see that one.
Casey.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's a horrific event.
Casey Kasem is just here to do the horrible.
Perhaps it's a little too soon.
Now I guess that's the way you do it.
Casey Kasem from now on.
All horrible news is covered by Casey Kasem.
No, it's, it's really sad.
A terrible, no, it's horrible.
I that that I used, I flew out of that airport to come to Vegas.
I flew out of there to go to go to the air, Chicago.
That was my one way trip.
There was a Chicago, then to think what there is on the plane, not the airport.
Right.
Yes.
But the airport got fucked and their surrounding areas got.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It literally crashed into businesses.
It's terrible.
It's, it's horrific.
Yeah.
It's really, really scary.
And they basically closed down Louisville for a day because of the noxious fumes and
shit.
Uh, is that what they, is that what they're calling the area around your house?
The area of obnoxious fumes, the area of noxious fumes.
Yeah.
Especially if I've had microwave hot dogs.
That's right.
Oh Jesus.
Can we close this down for just, just a couple more hours?
Cause he is about to shut down Pittsburgh.
Oh, green cloud trying to come to cause you just doing, doing this service for mankind.
My guy, my guy has not been happy with late.
I will say that.
I will say that we're climbing and there's a cloud of Paul.
Uh, yeah, it's terrible.
So the airline stuff is really awful.
It's really, really bad.
And I'm just great.
Oh yeah.
No, it's bad.
I reflect on it.
And I think how grateful I am that I'm not flying anytime soon, but then I think there's
so many people that are.
And yeah.
And then, and we, we narrowly missed coming into some shit with scoop vest and fuck.
Who knows what the next one's going to be like.
Yeah.
We're screwed.
I guess we're done.
We'll see you soon.
All right.
Uh, okay.
See you next year everybody.
Happier news.
Okay.
Tomorrow.
Happier news.
Are you asking for it?
No, I've got it.
Tomorrow marks 19 years married to Ann McPheeters for a while.
How about that?
Oh, that'll be good.
Yep.
Tomorrow's our anniversary.
Of course she has to work and so, so we spent, she works that ass all the time.
Uh, so I want you to guess.
We took, we decided today we were going to do our anniversary.
You will never in a million years guess what we did for our first dog in, in the Chili's
parking lot.
You're not that far off.
Put on, put on bee costumes and culled your own honey into jars?
Nope.
Okay.
Shit.
That was my next guess.
What is that called?
What are beekeepers called?
Beekeepers?
No.
No, there's a, what's the hobby called?
Keeping bees.
A, apists.
That's it.
Thanks, Leon.
A, apiarist.
There's an extra syllable in there somewhere.
Apiarists.
A, apiarists.
Rapists.
That's it.
Not rapists.
Nope.
Yeah.
I keep bees.
I'm a rapist.
Apiary.
It's an apiary.
That's right.
A beehive is an apiary.
So api-ists, I guess.
Api- I'm the api-ist here.
We're, we're doing an api-ist talk.
It was called that because an ape invented it.
Oh, beehive.
Says Rich Scoop.
Good one.
Bees.
They're gre-pe.
Uh, no.
We decided earlier this week, really and decided, but I, I was totally in on the plan.
We decided that for our 19th wedding anniversary, we were going to go join Costco.
Oh, man.
I didn't want to cry on today's show, but I really just-
Too bad.
Too late.
Here come the Waterworks.
Oh, my God.
Everybody in the chat is weeping openly.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, Costco.
How I love thee.
It was-
I love that Paul refuses to talk over his own song.
He's like, I will not use my own song as a, as an underbed of music.
We will just sit and listen to it.
I'm still sippin' on my, I'm sippin' on my Costco Coca-Cola.
I did get a hot Costco hot dog on the way out.
We both, we both did.
We had our dinner.
Did you, you ate from one side, she ate from the other.
Yeah.
And you guys ate the hot dog until you got-
Totally, totally.
In the middle.
The fuckin' lady in the tramptit.
Who was who?
And then you both tried the same with the Costco pizza, but you tapped out like halfway
through because it's just the amount of dough in your bellies.
We did.
We did a Pete, we did a slice and a dog each, and we both tapped out.
We were like, okay, this is too much food, but it was really good.
It took me too, as someone with children, I've been a Costco member for some time, it
took me too long to realize I should never order two slices of pizza from that place.
Did Matt just freeze?
He did just freeze.
Matt has just, Matt just froze in the, in the, he's unfrozen now.
We can see him again now, but he froze in the best pose that he could have possibly
frozen.
It was good pose.
You looked, you looked striking.
All right.
Sorry, we lost you there for a second.
You've been a Costco member for a long time.
The audience heard it.
They heard your recorder, but what we didn't hear it.
Oh yeah.
Uh, but I'll repeat it here.
Uh, um, uh, it took me too long to realize that I shouldn't order two slices of pizza
from Costco.
God no.
Yeah.
I'd be in the middle of that second slice and be like, what have I done?
Just like the whole-
Why do I do this?
The whole world becomes slow motion.
It's almost a quarter of a pizza.
Yeah.
It's a ridiculous thing.
How are you guys at leaving food on your plate at a restaurant or something?
I'm only just now in my life getting to where I'm able to really do it and be comfortable
with.
Yeah.
I'm getting better at it, but I don't usually do it.
Dick, if you're actually bringing up a big thing for me, to be honest with you.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
As someone who's trying to be a recovery fatty, I'm going to tell you thin people leave stuff
on their plates all the time.
They do it left and right.
They don't give a shit.
They've never grown up with a clean plate club or whatever.
The amount of people I know I go out to eat with a skinny person and they just know they're
done and the fork's down and they're still half the way in the plate, and they're casual
and confident about it.
They just wait forever and finally the waiter comes over and goes, "Are you done?"
They go, "Yes."
It's been sitting there the whole time.
They don't finish their fries.
It's an amazing trait of a thin person.
I have simply tried to imitate this to possibly become thinner by being like, "Can I do what
it is?"
Meanwhile, I'm secretly sweating because I'm just like, "When is that waiter coming?
Take that fucking plate away from me.
I still won't eat this entire thing, but I want to be like a thin person and I want to
leave it."
There's no like, "Oh my gosh, you're starving children in Africa," and all that stuff.
None of that holds true for a thinny person.
They don't care.
They do it all the time.
That starving child in Africa is not getting the food on this plate regardless of if I
eat it or not.
Yeah.
Now, my wife is a skinny person who always insists on taking everything home, which all
this does is light a fuse for three days later, "Why is there so much shit in our fucking
fridge?"
Right?
It's like, "I think you need to go in the bathroom, look in the mirror, and ask that
question to yourself."
Which is always a safe answer to give when your wife asks a question that she's upset
about.
Oh, no.
In the kitchen, I'm like, "Oh, I don't know.
God.
Goddamn."
What could it be?
Oh, man.
I don't know.
They're multiplying.
We got to get to the bottom of this.
I never got to eating all that leftover food I took home.
I never got to do that.
Hold on.
I'll go beat the children.
They must be putting stuff in the fridge again.
That'd be a good habit to develop, but no.
You have house guests, Jacob.
Paul, you don't really get too many guests at the house.
No, very rare.
Jacob, do guests at your place take food home from restaurants and put it in your fridge?
Wait.
Do they bring-
If everybody went out to eat together, and then they're coming to stay at your place.
So you guys all go to a restaurant, and they go, "Oh, I can't finish that.
I'll take a box."
Do they take a box of food and put it in your fridge?
Rarely.
Okay, it's probably my biggest pet peeve of having a house guest.
Because I'm like, "You're in Las Vegas.
You're not going to go, 'We should eat leftovers' at any point during your vacation."
You are never going to be like, "Never mind.
Let's just bust out the leftovers and have a leftover festival at the table my last night
in Las Vegas."
That's a dumb thing.
Now, what I will do- Yes, that is all correct.
Also, what I will do is when the guests are in town, like if we go out somewhere and not
nice, and they get a nice meal or something like that, and they're like, "Oh, I'm not
going to finish this other piece here," I'll be like, "I'll take a box for that.
I'll take that home, and I will eat your leftovers later on."
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
That's a pro-move.
If it's something that I've had my eye on anyway, that steak looks good.
My mother-in-law just ordered a 16-ounce steak.
She's going to eat eight ounces tops.
I'll just reach over and cut that thing in half right at the top of the dinner, and just
slide one half over to her.
The other half's right there if she wants to get to it, but if she doesn't, it's coming
home.
Smart.
That's smart.
Speaking of ordering steak and Las Vegas parking and weather-
Hit it, Jacob.
Yep.
It's over here somewhere.
All my buttons have moved around.
God damn it.
Oh, my buttons.
My gumdrop buttons.
My buttons.
My page.
That's why.
My sweet candy buttons.
Vegas, parking and weather, no one does it better than ICS.
It wasn't my buttons.
It was me.
I was on the wrong page.
To prove that Vegas is always on the innovation space of the world of entertainment, they
figured out a way to close a show without closing a show over at the Bellagio.
What happened?
Oh, the poor Mayfair.
I feel so bad for everybody over there.
The Mayfair Summer Club is staying open at the Bellagio, they simply fired everyone.
Their whole thing is dinner and a show.
They have singers and dancers and performers, they have a stage in there, there's lighting
and sound, and you sit around it, and it's a very nice restaurant on top of it.
It's a Michelin star, I think, restaurant and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah, they have fired the entire entertainment cast.
So now it's dinner and a TBD over at the Mayfair Summer Club.
Apparently someone is coming in to make up some kind of new entertainment, and that is
the amount of news that has been released on that.
Oh no.
It's funny, I got a message from someone saying they're submitting an audition for the Mayfair
Summer Club, and they're coming to check them out.
They don't live in Vegas, they live in another city.
I was like, in my head, I was like, "Huh, that's weird that they're auditioning someone
to do a whole new thing."
And then I got the news, and I was like, "Oh, it all adds up now."
It's a shame because the Mayfair Summer Club hired locally.
They hired a local talent.
Man, that's a bitch.
That's 30 Las Vegas residents who had show business jobs that are gone, several friends
of ours.
That's killer, man.
Yeah, several friends of ours.
A lot of them, because they're Las Vegas performers, a lot of them have multiple gigs, but it just
sucks.
You lose that gig.
You might lose a third of your weekly income or so.
Well, I'll tell you another thing that happened while we were at the Costco.
We had to get the membership, right?
So went and got the membership, and the gentleman there, super friendly guy, we got to talking,
and we were talking Vegas, and then we were talking improv.
Believe it or not, he's an improviser over at the arcade space.
Hilarious.
I was like, "Holy shit."
So we exchanged info.
I got him a chip, because always.
You're so good at it.
Got to do it.
Got to be on it.
Okay.
Yeah, so we'll talk.
But in my heart, I felt some, I don't know, relief, kinship, because I, too, am a retail
employee who moonlights as an improviser now.
I'm just getting back into the teaching.
By the way, I don't know if I've mentioned this.
My level one class at Skit is going phenomenally well, and I love all those students.
They're amazing.
Oh, wonderful.
That's good to hear.
You have not said that.
That's great.
Fan-fucking-tastic.
A couple of them are listening to the podcast now, and tell me that they know that I shit
my pants, and stuff like that, which I'm just over the moon about.
Which is great, because if you ever leave the classroom going, "It's happening," they'll
know why.
Yeah, if I leave the classroom squealing, "It's happening!
Oh, no!
Oh, no!"
They'll figure it out real fucking fast.
Maybe one of your students will kiss your ass and come up with a thermos, a freshly
steamy microwave hot dog.
It's like they'll open up a little plume of steam coming off the top of a thermos and
just a nice dangly wiener for you to chomp down on.
I saw the fuck.
Somebody sent me the Pope-Peele one.
Nice dangly wiener.
It's so nasty.
The Pope-Peele one.
Have you seen it?
The Pope-Peele hot dog thing?
No.
Please stop saying Pope-Peele.
It would slice the wiener when you put it in, and then you'd lay the bun on top of it,
and there was a bun case, and you microwave it, bun it all, and I'm like, "Don't put bread
in a microwave!
That's sacrilege!"
It's so gross.
My anaconda don't want none unless your bun's got a case!
That's right.
You could do side bans or sit-ups.
Sit it and forget it.
You know who else wants a thermos of hot dogs delivered directly to them?
And that is the following sponsor.
Today's show is brought to you by The Internet, from Danny O-Wide in 2021.
Today's show is brought to you by The Internet, with a capital "I."
Hey, the end of democracy and your sister's fucking a dog.
That's The Internet.
Enter Hey Scoops at Checkout!
Oh, yeah.
I have a little update on that.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Please.
So my buddy Sammy gets a call, and it's another, you know, you've been approved for some loan,
or you want to do something in the medical care system or something.
Oh, shit!
Right?
Another Indian call center thing?
Yeah, another Indian call center with a scam.
And Sammy goes, "Oh, yeah, no problem, yeah, sign me up, let's do it."
You know, whatever.
They go, "Your first name?"
He goes, "Ben."
And he goes, "Sorry, what's your first name?"
And he goes, "Ben."
And he goes, "Oh, yeah.
And I know what your last name is, too."
And he hangs up.
I got him!
Oh, shit!
Before he can even— Got him!
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
For anybody who didn't hear that episode, my friend always says to a scam caller that
his name is Ben Shod, which translates in Indian to "sister fucker."
Right.
And apparently, that's the worst thing you could say to someone in that country.
But it's spreading.
That means that that prank is spreading.
Exactly.
It is.
I don't praise or condone.
I simply report what's happening on the front lines.
Uh-huh.
That's right.
You are Walter Cronkite.
We go up with a current reference.
I'm still shocked that Uncle Fucker never really caught on as hotly, but I guess it's
'cause everybody likes uncles, and so nobody—it's not really derogatory.
It's like, "Oh, well, yeah, I mean, you fucked your uncle.
Great."
Everybody has a good— He caught on for a slur for Canadians for
a while.
I guess.
After the South Park movie.
I love that.
That's the whole thing.
That song—god damn, I never laughed so hard in the theater.
Still, to this day, that was the funniest moment.
Was that the one that—was Uncle Fucker the one that Robin Williams sang on the Oscars?
No, he sang "Blame Canada."
That's right.
Uncle—if he sang Uncle Fucker, that would have brought the house down.
Well, 'cause I remember—'cause it had all of the terrible things that it—
It still had some—
I remember everybody was still terrified of what Robin Williams was going to do on the
live broadcast for the Oscars.
Right.
How's that guy doing?
Robin Williams—
It's just a fucker.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Bossy.
Oh, man.
Yeah, so we're walking through Costco for the first time, Anne and I, as husband and
wife.
She carried Paul over the threshold.
We seriously just kept looking at each other in awe and amazement.
We were really taken aback.
We had a membership to Sam's Club back in Vegas for a little while.
Nothing like this, this was just amazing.
We got—
Nothing compared to you.
We got a bunch of stuff.
We got mostly dog food.
I don't know why.
As someone who's been a lifelong Costco member, I don't know why I really condescendingly
look when people bring up Sam's Club at the same time as Costco.
I'm mostly like, "Sure.
Okay."
No, you're right, 'cause it's garbage trash, comparatively.
We didn't know we were missing with the Costco thing.
Jacob's a big Sam's Club guy.
I'm not.
There's just—there's a closer Sam's to me than there is at Costco.
Leon's asking if I—
The Sam's Club that I go to is great.
If I saw—
I don't know.
Big justice at the Costco guys.
Now, Rizzler was working the cash register when I came through, so we got a bunch of
cool stuff.
It was fun, 'cause we had—
Yeah, scan and go at Sam's Club.
Does Costco have the scan and go thing yet?
Holy shit, this guy came up to the—no, we've got it.
This guy came up to our cart.
Oh, that's where Sam's Club's got it.
This guy came up to our cart and was like, "You want me to scan you guys in?"
We're like, "Yeah."
He pre-scanned everything in the cart, sent it to our account, and then all we had to
do was present our card at the register, and we're done.
Yeah.
That's good.
Sam's Club has—Sam's Club's scan and go with your phone, though, is superior.
I would say it probably is superior, but it's also more open to fraudsters.
Unfortunately.
Or does that matter to me?
It doesn't matter to you.
I'm just saying—
Yeah, there you go.
No, 'cause the one in Vegas now, the one that I go to now, which I think is a really
nice Sam's—I don't know why I'm defending Sam's Club, by the way.
I'm just saying if you put—
'Cause you love it, Jacob.
Don't be ashamed of your love for Sam's Club.
If you put being able to price items in the hands of the consumer, they will fuck with
it.
That's all I'm saying.
I don't care about that.
I know.
And if Walmart loses money because people are gaming their system, that doesn't affect
me at all.
I'm fine with that, too.
Okay.
But yeah, the one that we have, they don't even have to check your shit at the door anymore
like they used to with the scan and go stuff.
It's all x-rayed in there.
It's all like—yeah, there's a sensor thing and everything.
It's so easy, and it's great now.
And I think it's for anything under $700, like if you're spending less than $700.
So when I check out for ScoopFest, I have to do it the old-fashioned way.
We got a bunch of cool stuff, like I said, mostly for the dogs, but then it was really
nice.
We had watched a video or something.
We saw this really nice collection of Jane Austen's books, right?
Okay.
Especially bound in these—it's a very nice thing.
And then we saw that it was—
She's the romance author, right?
She's got like Fabio on the cover.
Fabio always.
And it was Costco only.
And we were like, "Oh, no."
But when we went today, we were really hoping to find those books, and we found them for
Anne.
So it was a good day.
She got her special edition Jane Austen collection.
It was really nice.
It was very sweet.
And they're really pretty, actually.
They're like in a faux leather binding.
They're really nice.
So yeah, she's on the up and up with her little book collection.
Yeah, Jane Austen wrote a special edition just for Costco.
We got one of the signed, very limited signed copies from Jane Austen.
She reached up with her dead hand, and she turned into the Joker.
You don't know how I wrote these books.
I saw it.
It's all true.
"Boss Grissom reached up with his dead hand, and he signed it over to me."
Did you make Anne push you out of the giant cart?
I pushed the cart.
Anne pushed it at first.
But then I pushed it most of the time, because she was like, "It's getting too heavy."
So I pushed it.
It was a bunch of ... I don't push carts like that.
I don't push carts like that full of dog food.
But man, the money we saved.
Holy shit, the money we saved.
The savings.
The savings dude, seriously, we already paid for our membership.
Just getting dog food, we already paid for our membership.
It's ridiculous.
Right now, any ... Some from Costco listening just was like, "Got 'em."
Yes.
They did.
They got 'em.
And the thing is, they got Anne.
That's all that really matters.
You can get me all day long.
Oh yeah.
They know that.
Big Bad Toy Store?
Got 'em.
Lego?
This is the first for ... Since I was eight, six.
Since I was six, got 'em.
But if it's got Anne, oh, it's a whole 'nother thing.
Do they have any sample people out there, buddy?
Oh my gosh.
She did almost ruin my day.
She gave me this fucking falafel ball and this fucking dip.
I was like, "I didn't really want it," but she was like, "Oh, I'll get 'em."
And I ate this.
I was like, "Oh."
It was so gross.
So many vegetables, wow.
It was in this mint and cucumber dip or some shit.
I was like, "Oh, God."
But I ate it.
It sounds delightful.
Oh, it was awful.
I ate the whole thing.
It was full awful.
Full awful.
Full on full awful.
Yeah, so that was my free sample.
I was like, "Barf."
It wasn't green.
It was fried up.
It was gross.
Part of it was once green.
Just a little fried up little ball of something.
We finally did a little zhuzhing of our Patreon.
We should talk about that a little bit.
We did.
Oh, yeah, we should.
Production meeting.
Again?
Sure.
Yeah.
More production meetings.
Twice in a row.
Twice in one episode.
Production meeting.
When we talk about how sausage gets made.
Blammo.
Oh, suck it.
Oh, fuck you.
Go fuck yourself.
Fuck you in the face forever.
We raised our lowest tier from $2 to $3.
Let's just get that out of the way.
Huge money grab on our parts.
Talk about Costco.
But if you ... If you get a Costco membership, though, you'll be able to afford it.
If Disney+ wants to charge me $38 just to watch SportsCenter now because it's no longer
on YouTube TV, I think we can go up to a dollar on that one.
Yeah.
That's the only tier we raised any price on.
And as always, if you are a $2 member, we do not take that away.
So you are-
You're grandfathered in.
Yes.
Of course.
So that still is unlisted.
We actually still have like 28 people still at the dollar a month.
I was like, "All right.
Look at that."
Hey.
Look at us go.
By the way, if you're still at a dollar a month, A, congratulations, B, feel free to
revisit your Patreon, and C, thank you.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Yeah.
We make 12 of those.
I mean-
We make about 12 cents off of the dollar a month club.
We make about $6 off of your $12, so thank you.
So but we also took away, we're no longer delivering stickers, and then we are going
to do any kind of like triple threats or any kind of songs from Paul.
Those would be like off air deliveries.
In return, Paul has organized a newsletter, he sent one out already.
Yes.
Paul will be organizing a monthly newsletter, and basically people seem to really enjoy
these hangs on and off air where scoops get to interact with each other.
Just like the strength of Scoop Fest is that scoops get to see each other and hang out
with each other.
Knowing that we're not really the big headliner sometimes for some people in this world that
we've created, we're going to do Zoom hangs, off air Zoom hangs for everyone to hang out
once a month as well.
Yeah, so if you're a Patreon subscriber at any level, you will get the invites to the
Zoom hangs, and then they're- what level is it?
It's over a level.
It's I think the $10 level.
Yeah, $10 level and up, you get Zoom hangs once a month.
This is all information we could have had in front of us.
If only we had known we were going to talk about this.
It's on the Patreon.
It's the only thing we knew we were going to talk about.
I gave you guys five minutes notice for the episode.
It's true, you did.
It is the only thing we knew we were going to talk about.
Well, and we say we're not sending out stickers, we're not sending out physical stuff.
That's all.
We've just taken off the physical stuff.
We're still sending you the digital files, or we're now sending you the digital files
so that not only can you make stickers if you want, you can make fucking anything if
you want.
You put that on any kind of product, you know, anywhere you want to put that.
There are so many sites.
Can you upload images into T Public and make stuff right in our store?
Oh yeah.
So, you know, you can even go through our store, use our T Public store to order custom
stuff using custom art that we've just sent you for that month and double dip us a little
bit.
Oh, oh, they can't do it.
Oh, no.
Are you asking?
No, I thought you were asking if I could do it.
I was like, I can do it.
Yeah.
Oh, you could.
But yeah.
Okay.
The newsletter came through Patreon.
So if you're getting your Patreon emails, just check your Patreon emails for the newsletter.
Yes.
Coming in through the newsletters put out through Patreon added a newsletter feature
to the.
Well, I'm trying to learn the newsletter.
I'm trying to learn the newsletter proper.
It was just a post this time.
Yeah.
And oh, and the and the zoom hangs are different from the shows.
So we have the we have the the patrons that are with us on this show recording right now.
That stays for everyone.
Yes.
Everybody on Patreon.
Every member gets access to our ice cream social recordings.
Yes.
Yeah.
The zoom hangs are a different thing.
Those are the all fair things.
We did one this last month where we just had everybody on Patreon do it.
We kind of did the beta test for it last month.
But yeah, that'll normally be at the ten dollar level and higher.
Leon, thank you for the reminder.
Make sure you do your Patreon through the website, through a browser and not through
the Patreon app, because the the Apple app takes a big cut.
Yeah.
And then do it.
And here live on this broadcast, I believe Meyer just post the link to the newsletter
for anyone who might have missed it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
The Patreon post.
So this is the Patreon post.
Oh, Leon, if you can't read, that is a different Patreon level.
There is a Patreon level, though, for you, if you can't read where I will just read the
newsletter to you.
Don't worry.
We got you, Leon.
But I'll still be sending out my original art piece, and then we're going to send out
old school stickers, new stickers, new, you know, we still keep generating tons of artworks
and people get access to that artwork.
It's just the actual practice of printing and shipping stickers.
And basically, people have like built dog houses out of the stickers we've sent over a decade.
Yes.
It's a diminishing returns.
It's a lot.
And also, if y'all haven't noticed, postal shit's getting weird.
Yeah.
If you feel like you're still owed stickers from the past, please send an email to jacob@hayscoops@med@hayscoops.com.
Yes.
Yeah.
But yeah, moving forward, it's going to be digital rewards, but oh, man, Amy just wrote
in chat that we'll read the newsletter as Dom DeLuise does the second time this week.
I've been compared to Dom DeLuise and as someone who's been slowly losing weight and trying
to get their shit together, it's a real fucking kick in the balls to be compared to Dom DeLuise
twice in a week, not to say I don't get it, not to say I totally don't get it.
I get it.
I love Dom DeLuise so much.
You know who else loves me compared to Dom DeLuise all the time, and that is the following
sponsor.
All right, today's show is brought to you by 1-800-BITKILL.
Are you stuck with someone doing a bit that's gone way too long?
Call 1-800-BITKILL and our agents will come kill that bit.
That's from Dungeon Scoop in 2024.
Do you need a running joke kicked in the dick so hard it'll never recover?
Call 1-800-BITKILL and we'll be there immediately to dick kick any running joke that has been
going on in your household or family for any amount of time, as long as it's been more
than five days.
Any bit under five days still is in the incubation period and may or may not survive to day six.
After day six, a bit is firmly and securely intertwined into the DNA of the host and then
can only then be truly exterminated from said host.
I mean, is that like a procedure or is that like something you just come out and do?
What is that?
Kick you in the dick until the bit is removed thoroughly.
What, me or the person doing the bit?
Your choice.
Excellent.
We're not that far off from prostitutes.
Are we?
That's right.
None of us are that far off from prostitutes.
Don't ever fucking forget it.
Sex work is work.
We just did a breakdown of our new patron levels.
I agree.
Yeah.
Sex work is work, everybody.
We're all of this whores in this economy.
Enter Hays Groups to check out.
Welcome to it.
Yeah.
I just sent you in the chat a very nice felt picture of Dom DeLuis from 1975.
Everyone knows that's not what they're talking about, Jacob.
No, I'm pretty sure that's a young Dom DeLuis in a very vibrant shirt.
They're referring to his slim and trim days.
That's right.
No, one person said-
The early years.
An actual pic saying I had to do a double take and they were wearing a similar flat
cap.
He was wearing a similar flat cap to me.
Was it Smokey and the Bandit 2?
Is that where he's wearing?
I think that is where he's wearing that one.
I had to be like, I want to tell my friend, listen, if you ever think you should send
a photo of Dom DeLuis to someone and be like, I had to do a double take, don't.
Don't do it.
Oh, no, you're safe.
Smokey and the Bandit 2, isn't it?
There it is.
There's Leon helping you out, buddy.
That's the one.
Leon in the chat, helping out, but he looks so happy.
Look at him.
Jolly even.
I'm a happy guy.
Yeah.
I don't understand the comparison.
Oh, my God.
I said this like great night, but one person on YouTube called the Orson Welles and I was
like, actually, when you look at a picture of Orson Welles next to me, like that's actually
who I look like the most.
I'm like, I actually have to hand it to you.
I really do look a lot like Orson Welles, late Orson Welles.
Oh, I saw a great video the other day of Orson Welles' outtakes from a wine commercial that
he was doing.
Oh, that's a classic.
Famous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
Because that was like the last thing he did, right?
In one of them.
It's definitely a later in life one.
He was drunk.
Where he's just drunk.
Yeah.
He is just like slurring speech drunk.
The last thing he did was unicorn.
That's true.
Yeah.
The reason you need to go look at this video again, though, if you haven't looked at it
lately, or if you've ever seen it before, look up this video, Orson Welles outtakes
wine commercial.
The two extras that are standing next to him that are just doing take after take with him.
Oh, yeah.
They are heroes.
They are amazing.
They never comment.
They never look at him sideways.
They never do anything but exactly what they are there to do.
Well, even then he was royalty, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, you know, yeah, he's a legendary director.
I mean, he'd already done Citizen Kane and yeah, like all that.
Yeah.
Brian Brushman sent me a clip of John Candy playing Orson Welles in a bit on like a late
night talk show, and it's really, really funny.
Latter-day Scoop goes with a thin picture of Orson Welles.
That's not who we're talking about, Latter-day Scoop.
Young Orson Welles.
That's not who I'm being compared to on YouTube, I'll tell you that much right now.
On my screen, that picture is next to Matt's face right now.
Nobody's talking about that.
I found out something in the Zoom chat before we started today that has changed my world
forever.
Oh, God.
And that is, apparently, if you do a reverse image search of any house that was ever listed
on Zillow, that's enough to do a reverse image search of a house.
What?
Wait, what?
And like, and find out where that house is.
Wait, say that again.
So if you just have a picture of a house—oh, Scoop Jesus, there you are.
Can you unmute and come on?
Scoop Jesus was telling me about this before we started today.
Okay.
I'm actually in the house with that happened with.
Oh, great.
Yeah, so a friend, a name friend, posted a picture of their new house on Instagram that
didn't show the address number or anything, and my wife took the image, reversed image
search, and it popped up and showed the Zillow listing and got their address.
And I just drove down here with that address.
So you were able to find a house with just the picture of the house?
Yep.
I'm terrified.
I mean, there's, if we're doing that now, what do you think the government's been doing
for the last 15 years?
I mean, a lot more and a lot worse.
Yeah.
Just constantly checking the value of my house.
They've been reverse imaging.
They've been reverse image searching my colon, for God's sakes.
They know everything.
We got a note from our HOA about our basketball hoop being out, that we have to put our basketball
hoop away.
No.
And their argument was that it could hurt the value of the homes around us.
And I just want to be like, you go ahead and Google the value of homes in this neighborhood.
You tell me where the dip happened the day I put up my fucking basketball.
Right.
Yeah.
No dips anywhere.
There are no dips yet.
Right back to him.
You know what lowers the property value in this goddamn neighborhood?
All these fucking kids running around.
You know what really lowers...
Get these fucking kids, and then I won't have a reason to put up a fucking basketball hoop.
You know what really lowers property values in Las Vegas?
What really lowers property values in Las Vegas is not being able to fly to fucking
Las Vegas.
That does hurt property values.
Yeah.
It puts a real dick in it.
It sure does.
A bunch of bullshit.
So what was your solution?
Have you put up the basketball goal, or are you going to fight them in City Hall?
I'm going to fight them in City Hall.
I'm actually waiting for the second note to come.
Good.
Because I feel like we definitely don't have the only basketball hoop out.
So I figured someone who's much more of an organized rage person than me is probably
answering them already.
There you go.
Yeah.
HOA's is the waste.
The waste.
I have a very reasonable HOA.
I'm actually not that upset.
We used to get a note about our leaves.
I know, Paul.
You're very well-known.
I just really, I hate the whole idea.
It makes me rage, rage, rage.
Paul, I'm around people in Las Vegas who definitely, with no HOA, would definitely lower the property
value of everyone around them.
Yes.
I get it.
Yeah.
But see, this is me.
I don't care.
I might go nuts.
I mean.
Do your thing.
I mean, here's the thing.
Unless you're burning the house, unless you're causing structural damage, or you're toxifying
my land, go nuts.
Here's the thing.
I have neighbors whose houses definitely are currently lowering my property value.
If they would spruce their houses up, I'd appreciate it.
But yeah, it's not worth being an HOA for me.
I'm with you, Matt.
Because I had a reasonable HOA before I lived here.
They were fine.
They didn't bother me.
It's a critical.
I like having a little bit of a nice sidewalk neighborhood, little gate area.
They can just get out of control so easily.
They really can't.
They can get out of hand.
Yes.
No, without a doubt.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, like all my friends in New York, what they have to go through.
Oh, God.
I can only imagine.
It's just like to own their home.
It's like, it's fucking nuts, man.
No, no.
Yeah.
There are, like this HOA is not that crazy, is what I'm saying.
We used to get notes.
A friend of mine just this week was talking to me about their HOA and they were like, "Oh,
our fees are so reasonable."
I said, "Oh, that's good.
What's your fees?"
They go, "500."
A year?
That's what I thought.
Uh-huh.
I genuinely was like, "Oh, 500 bucks a year, isn't bad."
Oh, no, no.
A month.
Oh.
That is terrible.
Oh, eat shit.
Eat shit forever.
Oh, my God.
That is horrible.
That's ... no way.
We have a pool.
We have a gym.
That's cool.
A pool and a gym.
Yeah.
No, son.
But I bet that person also has a membership to a gym outside of their home.
I have a toy collection.
I would think so.
I could not keep my toy collection going with that kind of money going out.
That would end it.
Okay.
You're making a lot of arguments in favor of it now, Paul.
No, no.
Please.
This glorious basement of nerditude has increased the value of this home tenfold.
The moment a prospective buyer walks in, they're like, "Good God, may I keep the finished
basement and all the trimmings?"
I go, "No, sir.
No, sir, you may not.
That's a lifetime of collecting."
You can't, however, keep that squirrel.
Let me make an offer that you cannot refuse.
I need all of this bullshit.
Says no one ever.
Says me.
Saving me an email.
Thank you, Steven Marson, who just became a year-long member of the $10 here.
Thank you, Steven.
Oh, nice.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Your thank you note right here, buddy.
Thanks for doing it.
That's incredible.
Much appreciated.
Yeah.
We've gotten a lot of great support.
As soon as I put up the post on the Patreon, we got some really nice supporting messages.
Thank you all for rolling with us and for moving forward into this new digital age.
It's going to be cool.
Yeah, I'm going to muddle my way through learning how to put this stuff together and get the
chats going and all these different things.
We're going to have a lot of fun.
We're going to put a period on it, the newsletter is at all levels, right?
Yes.
Everybody on Patreon should be getting a newsletter, no matter what level you're at.
If you are not getting a newsletter, check your Patreon email, check your Patreon, do
all that kind of stuff.
Well, you're saying newsletter.
There's a new newsletter thing.
I haven't figured that out yet.
All I did was put up a post.
This first post went to everybody, so if you're on Patreon at all, you've got that post that
just went up.
So you're scheduling the posts, Paul?
The first one was just Patreon update.
Okay.
So that's probably why a lot of people might not, because when Patreon puts an update,
they also put Patreon update.
There you go.
See, I didn't know that either.
You should probably change the title of it.
So next time I'll say Ice Cream Social Newsletter for Blankety Month.
Yeah.
Well, I think you should put the name of the month.
I like Blankety Month.
I mean, you can figure it out.
I'm recording it.
You know what month it is.
I'm recording it into a blankety month.
Ice Cream Social Newsletter for Blankety Month.
Blankety Month on such and such date.
Can I make a suggestion?
That's legally binding, isn't it?
What?
Can you what?
Can I make a suggestion?
You can.
I don't know why that was so baffling to you.
I couldn't hear what you said.
Okay.
Hey, it's Paul.
I think you should write, and then that should be the title.
Here's the newsletter.
Oh, okay.
Hey, it's Paul.
Great.
Okay.
I'll start with Hey, it's Paul.
Hey, it's Blankety Month, everybody.
And it's definitely now called the Blankety Month newsletter.
It's Paul Mattingly.
Yeah.
Paul Mattingly's Blankety Month newsletter.
Hey, God, it's me, Paul.
Yes.
That'll work.
Because the more you try to make it sound official, the more it just sounds like a patron
email, which is what people, I think, delete all the time without reading.
That makes sense.
All right.
So I'll say, Hey, everybody, it's fucking Paul with the Blankety Month bullshit.
What the hell?
What is this?
Paul's character allotment was used up in the title again.
Exactly.
Well, that was the other thing, too, is we're also putting up candid photos as well as the
other digital images, and I put up the max images it would let me do.
And then I used the last image space for the header where I put my new artwork up.
And that was everything I could do.
So maybe they let you put more stuff in the newsletter.
I don't know.
We'll see.
I think they do.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I'm still learning the ropes.
Still learning the ropes.
That is actually one of the more fun things, I think, for people who are already on Patreon
that are going to enjoy this new Patreon even more is you're going to have more direct
interaction with Paul via Patreon.
Well, that's for sure.
And that, I got news for you, is going to be fun.
Well, it's going to be a lot of fun.
It's going to be a lot of this, but it's also going to be a lot of fun.
Yeah.
And I'll take criticisms and tips all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, Paul wants notes.
How the fuck to make this shit work right, because yeah, I got to learn the ropes.
So I got some off days coming up, and I'm going to try and spend some time learning that.
And I will probably fire off a test Zoom chat again before too long just to figure that
out.
So it might only be 10 minutes, but keep your eyes peeled.
Well, I'll tell you what else Paul needs to learn, and that's the answers to Jock Versus
Nerd.
We got a scooperty coming to us today from Smitty Scoop Gentlemen.
I apologize.
I have not submitted a scooperty lately, but Jacob's plea on a recent episode motivated
me to prepare a scooperty.
Here are the updated Smitty Scooperty statistics.
All time victories, Matt has 13, Paul has three, I have eight.
All time points, Matt has 32,000, I have 12,400, Paul has negative 27,800.
I've got to keep it up.
Negative 27,800.
Combined accuracy in the last three Smitty Scooperties, 75.6% of questions answered correctly.
Good job everybody.
Combined accuracy on all previous Smitty Scooperties, 51.4% answered correctly.
So we've improved over the last three, so that's good for us.
Average combined score for the last three is 6,800.
Average combined score for all of them, negative 1,267.
So we are trending in the right directions.
Let's see if you can beat your all time high score of 12,800.
Good luck.
This is a Smitty Scooperty.
Let's go.
Oh, by the way, two shout outs.
One shout out to DJ Stormageddon in the Twitch chat right now.
Old friend of ours, DJ Stormageddon from back on the Scoop Cruise days.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
He's got his fucking honeymoon.
Got Obelisk on his honeymoon.
That's right.
Obelisk on his honeymoon.
And also, happy birthday OG Scoop.
Happy birthday, Andy.
Yeah.
Here we go with the Scooperty, the categories are the most, geography, initialism, and multiple
choice.
Okay.
Paul, you're up first.
I'll try multiple choice.
For 400.
Which of the following films was not directed by Amy Heckerling, Clueless, Fast Times at
Ridgemont High, Look Who's Talking, or Now and Then?
Fast Times.
B.
Fast Times is incorrect.
It's Now and Then.
That was directed by Leslie Lincoln Ladder.
Paul keeping up his negative score trend here on Smitty Scooperties.
Got something to prove.
Already.
Matt.
Geography please, 400.
Which state bordering Nevada is the largest in area, Alaska, Arizona, California, or Idaho?
Trying to get me in Alaska, bordering Nevada.
Nice try.
This is where we find out that Alaska somehow borders Nevada technically.
It could possibly.
Who knows?
California, see.
Got to be, right?
Yeah, California, 163,000 square miles, and Arizona and Idaho both have less, and Alaska
does not border Nevada.
It's a good call on all of that, Matt.
You got that entire question right.
I'll know what the most for 400.
Which of these NFL franchises has won the most Super Bowl titles, Bears, Colts, Seahawks,
or Vikings?
Is this going to bite me where it's like, oh, they won the NFL championship, but it
wasn't the Super Bowl yet?
I think it's the Bears.
I'll go A, Bears.
The Colts.
Colts two, Bears one, Seahawks one, Vikings nothing.
Wow.
Oh, all right then.
Paul.
I'll go initialism for 1200, because why not?
Oh, shit.
I gave you 400.
All right.
What is FYITF short for?
Fuck you in the face.
Nice job.
Or were you just talking to me?
No, both.
Were you answering?
Oh, OK.
Both.
Two birds, one stone.
I will take geography 800.
Galica is the name of the Northwest region of what country?
Austria, France, Italy, or Spain?
I'm sure I'm not saying that right.
G-A-L-I-C-I-A.
Galicia.
Galicia?
OK.
Galicia.
I'm just going off the correction of my around the chat.
Oh, great.
Galicia, Austria.
Galicia, France.
Galicia, Italy.
Galicia, Spain.
Pass.
Oh, no.
They can pass this to me.
Let's see.
I'll do the same thing that Matt was doing.
Galicia, Austria.
Galicia, France.
Galicia, Italy.
Galicia, Spain.
Galicia.
That's right.
It's definitely Italy.
I think it's Italy, too.
See, Italy.
Shit.
Spain.
That was my second guess.
Galicia.
Let's see.
I'll try geography for $1,200.
Why did I go back to geography?
I don't know.
Which U.S. state capital is located at the highest elevation, Colorado, Idaho, Nevada,
or New Mexico?
Oh, this is probably a trick question.
I'll say Colorado.
No, it's New Mexico.
6,900 feet for New Mexico, for Santa Fe, only 5,200 for Mexico.
Oh.
OK.
I'll try geography for $1,200.
Oh, it's New Mexico.
6,900 feet for New Mexico, for Santa Fe, only 5,200 for Denver.
Wow.
There you go.
Who knew?
Paul.
Initialism for $1,200.
What is CPR short for?
Cardiopulmonary resuscitation.
Cardiopulmonary resuscitation is just correct.
Wow.
I was thinking compression.
Yeah.
No.
Matt, you're up.
I have a-- I think I have a CPR card right here.
Yeah?
And you didn't know?
And I don't know what it is.
Did you ever suck face with Recessa Annie?
Yeah.
She knows how to do it.
She does.
Matt, you're up.
Geography, $2,000.
What African country recently became the second least populous country to qualify for the FIFA
World Cup?
Cape Verde?
Djibouti?
Iceland?
Or Togo?
Oh, man.
Go with Djibouti.
I've been watching Djibouti bounce all day.
Yeah.
This is $2,000.
So I'm going to pass.
That passes to me.
Man, I want to go Djibouti so bad.
Do it.
I want that Djibouti.
I kind of think it's Togo.
Yo.
All right.
It's going to be Djibouti, but I'm going Togo.
OK.
Nope.
It's neither.
Cape Verde.
An island nation west of Senegal near the Canary Islands.
Iceland is the least populous country to qualify for the World Cup.
So there you go.
OK.
It's me.
Man, I'm terrible right now.
I'll do multiple choice for $2,000.
Daily Double.
Frequently hidden in nativity scenes in Catalina, children search for--
Catalonia.
Oh, Catalonia.
Children search for L--
Cogener?
OK.
Who is generally depicted as a peasant in a Catilian red cap doing what?
Breastfeeding, drinking wine, pooping, or sleeping.
Pooping, Giggles.
I think it is pooping.
Is there just-- in nativity scenes?
Yes.
Is there just a guy pooping in the background?
In certain places, it's a traditional thing.
It's like a where's Waldo kind of thing, but it's a pooping guy.
I'll go with you because I don't have any other guess on this.
So I'll say pooping.
It is pooping.
Yeah, told you.
Picture Chef Boyardee popping a squat with a conical turd below him.
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
It's the most wonderful time of the year.
It's the most wonderful turd of the year.
Just goes to show that even people who believe don't really believe.
Paul.
Initialism.
2000.
What is HIV short for?
Ruining the good mood of a podcast, am I right?
Oh, I believe it's human immunovirus.
You going with that?
Yeah.
All right.
I think that's correct.
Yeah.
Human immunodeficiency virus.
I think you're close enough.
I would say so.
Yeah.
Matt.
I will go with the most for 800, please.
Which of these countries has the most people?
Egypt, Ethiopia, Nigeria, or Tanzania?
Let's see here.
I know the population of Tanzania.
I just don't know the other three.
Right.
Pass.
Okay.
That passes to me.
I'm going to do my math out loud.
Egypt has a lot of people in it.
Ethiopia has a lot of people in it.
Nigeria, they've got a lot of people there.
Tanzania, boy, do they have a lot of people.
Egypt, A. It's Nigeria.
213 million.
Ethiopia, 120 million.
Egypt, 109 million.
Tanzania, 64 million.
We're really throwing off the curve today.
I'm losing a lot of money.
Paul's making a lot of money.
Yeah, baby.
Yeah.
The world is upside down.
Oh, I need points back.
I'll do the most for 2,000.
Which of these NHL franchises has won the most Stanley Cup titles?
The Bruins, the Maple Leaves, the Penguins, or the Red Wings.
Hmm.
I would like to use my 50/50.
Paul, which two answers are definitely not correct?
I would say Penguin.
Wait.
Is the one the most Stanley Cup titles?
Yeah.
Penguins are on my short list.
Penguins have like four.
The leaves, the most.
You think the leaves have the most?
I think it's either the leaves or the wings.
Yeah.
I'll say the Red Wings.
I'll say Detroit.
Nope.
It's the Maple Leaves.
It was the Leaves.
13.
Red Wings are 11.
It was the Maple Leaves.
Jacob continues losing points.
Paul.
I'll go with Initialism.
For 800.
What is IQ short for?
Intelligence Quotient.
Intelligence Quotient is correct.
Paul must have a very high IQ to know that indeed.
Yes, clearly very IQ-y.
Matt Donnelly, you got the most or multiple choice.
You have 400 points, by the way.
You're well ahead of me.
I have 5200 points in the negative.
And Paul has 4000 points.
So Paul is one order of magnitude ahead of you.
There is one daily double left.
Your only hope is that Paul gets it and loses.
Right.
A man can hope.
I will do multiple choice 1200, please.
Daily double!
Right off the bat!
In the 2024 U.S. presidential election, what is the one state that Donald Trump won that he previously lost in both the 2016 and 2020 elections?
Arizona, Nevada, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.
Nevada, Tom.
My name is Jacob, but it is Nevada.
And Paul and Brett Mukai have been blamed for this.
For moving out of Nevada.
Two votes.
Slow down.
You don't know who they were voting for.
I'll go with multiple choice for 800.
The San Marzino tomato originated in the small town of San Marzino del Surro, which is located in which Italian region?
Calabria.
Campagna.
Sardina.
Or Sicily.
This, I talk about this all the time.
I talk about Italian tomatoes.
All types of Italian tomatoes.
Nobody loves Italian tomatoes more than I do.
And that is why I will go with A.
Which is incorrect.
It was B.
What is that?
Oh, the province of Salerno and the region of Campagna.
Oh, it was the region that threw me off.
That's what got me.
I was in the wrong region.
Paul closing out the category and the game that he's already won the most.
For 1200, which of these major league baseball franchises has won the most World Series titles?
The Athletics, the Cardinals, the Phillies, the Pirates.
And I believe the answer was given in the question here when Smitty typed out this stupidity.
Because below that, it says Cardinals 11, Athletics 9, Pirates 5, and Phillies 2.
So, Paul, with all of that in mind, which of these MLB franchises won the most World Series titles?
Athletics, Cardinals, Phillies, or Pirates?
I'm going to have to go out on a wing and say Cardinals.
Oh man, I hope that those are just incorrect stats there.
That'd be funny.
They're not. It's the Cardinals. Paul gets more points.
That's the game. Thank you, Smitty Scoop.
I won one. I won one, Smitty.
Paul crushed it with 5200 points. Matt's in second with 1600.
I am in third with negative 6000. Jesus fuck.
I'm creeping towards the positive.
Now you know how I feel on most of those.
You are. Look at you go.
If you want to sit in the scooperty just like Smitty did there, head over to HeyScoops.com.
HeyScoops.com. You can head over there.
Make us a scooperty. Make us a Price of Skrite Jock vs. Nerd.
Make us an Obelisk Jock vs. Nerd.
All those things right over there at HeyScoops.com. Do it now. It'd be great.
All right. I want to thank all the people who support us over on our Patreon page.
We don't have a new list just yet.
But it's one of the things we're working on by streamlining some of the processes here.
We'll get our thank yous earlier in the month.
Anyhow, if you support us over on our Patreon page, we really appreciate it.
If you love our show and you like that it comes out all the time, every time, no matter what,
then support us today by going over to PreachingFun.com.
Yeah, you really should!
Or if you kind of look like Orson Welles, head over to fartsinabag.biz.
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with PreachingFun.com, it takes you over to our Patreon page,
where for as little as $3 a month, you can help keep this show on the air.
We can't do this show without our Patreon subscribers.
So please, if you think this show is worth more than $0, PreachingFun.com, fartsinabag.biz.
You can go to both of them. Make two different accounts. We're fine with that.
Hey, don't forget, we're creeping up on the holidays.
What better gift than the gift of an ice cream social Patreon subscription?
You can give a yearly gift. Boom!
That loved one will receive our update emails every month.
They'll be getting the sticker digital art. They'll be getting my digital art.
They'll be getting candid shots of us, possibly, depending on what levels you join on to.
They can come in for the chats if you'll join in at a high enough tier.
There's all kinds of rewards and fun shit to get in on.
So give the gift to someone you love or treat yourself.
Yeah, treat yourself.
Treat yourself. I want to thank Penn for creating this podcast.
Thanks, Penn.
I want to thank all the scoops who could join us for today's broadcast here in our Zoom.
Yes. Lovely to see everyone.
Absolutely. And everybody over on Twitch as well.
That's right. And take care of yourselves. We love you and we'll see you soon.
We'll see you soon.
We're Preachin' Fun!
See ya!