Oh hello there I am so glad you are here this is the part of the show where we
thank you the ice cream truck drivers thank you so much ice cream truck drivers
we are having issues getting our list this month but we will thank each and
every ice cream truck driver at this part of the episode before this month is
over even if I have to go in and learn I don't know different languages and get
the lists myself through translation I'll do it to thank each and every ice
cream truck driver who are the ice cream truck drivers want these are the
fucking assholes that deliver that fucking ice cream straight to your
fucking ear holes if you want to be an ice cream truck driver and I hope you do
head over to preaching fun comm preaching paying extra for tire care is
BS you know bad service so at Midas we're rolling out our BS free tire
guarantee included with paid installation and tax on every purchase you'll pay
nothing for flat replacements nada for flat repairs and zilch for tire
rotations every 5,000 miles that's zero dollars for all that so with this
limited lifetime tire guarantee you'll pay a whole lot of nothing compared to
what the other guys charge for tire care that's the BS free tire guarantee only
at Midas fun commas ring gonna be an ice cream truck driver and who knows the
life you say maybe your own here's a program hey Johnny do you want to go to
an ice cream social yeah I'd love to great let's go
Matt the more I've thought about your friend who gave your son cologne
yeah or I'm convinced that that person hates a teenager and just give it a
teenager's they should spell it's time for Matt Mattingly's ice cream social
sitting in Las Vegas it's Matt Mattingly sitting in Pittsburgh Paul Mattingly
sitting in Las Vegas it's me Jacob the audio guy we're preaching fun yeah like he's
gonna be a teenager and teenagers don't have they pour too much stuff on
everything that's right like he's just gonna smell like stinky teenager dunked
in cologne are you worried that he's just gonna develop like a new expensive
habit is that what your problem is with it you think he's gonna do I didn't even
thought about that oh yeah now he's gonna become a real scent connoisseur I
think he's just gonna be stinky well I mean it's crazy you go shopping for some
of those those perfumes they're big money some of them I bet they are I bet
how much is a like like a standard bottle of cologne now how much about a
standard bottle of cologne 20 bucks well I spent I spent almost nine for my
generic I'm ahead of you on this one what we have done is we have ordered
ambergris in bulk and we're gonna do a DIY cologne kit in our backyard because
it's cheaper to just order the whole whale eat the meat and get the ambergris
out then to just buy the ambergris separately and plus that gives you oil
for your your whale oil right if you like the home if you like the meat you
might as well just buy the whole whale that's it why fuck the ambergris when I
can fuck the whale for free wait is that how how does it go that's not an
expression anywhere but yeah no I'm making in my new expression why smell
the ambergris when I can fuck the whale for free there you go there you go yeah
we're gonna put a bunch of vats in the backyard but like you know bourbon in
one and then like you know some kind of weird floral arrangement and another
we'll just see how it goes yeah this is this is smart this is this is that Matt
Donnelly smarts that I tell people about oh again disruptor of the space disruptor
of the perfume space we're going to we're going to in styles 16 best
smelling colognes for men according to the real sniff tests top picks Giorgio
Armani aqua did you what what said did did you get for your kid or did I put a
Gio did no I don't know I don't know no I don't know I don't remember I don't
know best yeah best long-lasting as far as I can tell they all they all smell
like anyway Creed Aventus on Amazon best spicy cologne for men Eve Saint Laurent
then you did home at Sephora you mispronounced Tabasco best
under 50 bucks cremo spice and black vanilla at Amazon best vanilla Cone
cologne for men for tobacco veneer I was looking at first really expensive step it
up I told him to step it up and I haven't just put muscle cream on just to
make him smell more mature yeah smell like he just worked out I figured
that's the way to get the ladies is like he wouldn't be wearing muscle cream
unless he did work it out right he's a real what's that Charles Atlas kind of
guy yeah okay okay here's where here's where the rubber meets the fucking road
okay there is a limited edition special deluxe Dior okay and this Dior
fragrance comes in a special trunk okay okay all right now it's a little case
yeah and that trunk goes inside a collectible canoe and then you put the
canoe into the ocean you say how do I how do I steer it and you say use Dior
this is this is actually just a trunk it doesn't nothing from Mattingly nothing
from Mattingly on the ore oh I'm you're too excited facts off your phone I got
confused because I thought it was the expensive clone it's just a box for your
cologne oh the cologne box is expensive guess how much that fucking box cost
that Christian Dior limited edition cologne box and you I don't think I
don't think you can kick this one in the dick nope higher twelve hundred dollars
hundred hundred dollars no twelve thousand dollars six thousand dollars
for that one hundred twenty eight million dollars to just hold my cologne
just your cologne in a box how does that so for that purpose I'm supposed to walk
into like work or wherever or a party am I supposed to walk into a party with my
cologne bar this is where you put my briefcase I just walk in what do you
call it what you call it before your your fragrance wardrobe this is where
you store your your scent wardrobe I don't understand spending that much on
something like look you spend a lot of money on a watch people see the watch
yeah I don't I don't think you bring your cologne with you to other places
right I mean if you're traveling all the time you want something nice to keep
your smells in Matt you're traveling all the time I didn't realize that my client
he's got fish to keep his smells in you are the target demographic if you if you
see me three weeks on a cruise ship holding up that box with the title I
work for free you'll know why you'll know why there's that Jean Paul Gaultier
the mail that one that looks like a dude's torso yeah and 20 bucks so yeah
some of these things are fucking oh my god Creed Royal English leather Jesus
Christ from the band yeah I just heard I just from the band I just smelled as
much as a day we can do this the whole pod but I think you can continually find
things that are too expensive in the perfume world if you keep searching the
internet I didn't search very hard and it already gave me a lot just thought
that was the very first spray with arms wide open those are the instructions
oh I'm so alone I sprayed too much cologne and now I'm on alone hey off
air we came up with the best solution for yesterday's sorry last episodes
rather excuse me last episode scoop mailer saying what do you tell people
when they ask about your son's circumcision right and off-air I said
oh you should check out this podcast I listened to called some other kids dick
Chronicles turn them on to that podcast curious about other kids dicks you should
check it out you podcast clearly into it yeah yeah yeah other kids dicks I already
know you love other kids dicks I love this ML Kennedy is batting a thousand
here at the Creed cologne smells like a worse version of Pearl Jam's use my
atomizer it's got step let it spritz you clean and clear step spray me with that
spritz use the atomizer off-air we're gonna do it yesterday which was I've had
I've had a couple of clips go maybe virals too strong of a word but my most
popular clips clips I've taken off I get stats right and so these these one a
couple of clips do well a couple comes do well and also I get stats that say
you know 75% of people watching and commenting are not your followers right
that's like a sign that's a sign that's what you want right right yeah external
engagement and it's one where I'm handling a dickhead it's just two videos
part one and part two I'm handling some dick at one of my shows this is the
state of the world man all people want is crowd work and I and it's funny
because when things go popular means I'm gonna get criticized right so there's a
lot of like you're thin-skinned you're a terrible person that guy's making
reasonable requests to a show that guy went to a show and then during the show
opened his mouth and just had a conversation with the person on stage
about what he wasn't doing these are the people who are on their phones the
entire time that a movie is happening and we'll do some backstory I'm at
Mystique dining and Folsom when with that clip right and they just have like
a security camera and if you know basically for like liability purposes
like his a magician loses it which I came close to so that's not my camera
that's just the the don't get sued camera at Mystique dining so a couple
things he's one in the first clip he's lecturing me about how he saw some other
magician and he went to bed that night he figured out the card trick and he
won't let me move on my show unless he tells me the story and Mystique dining
is a parlor environment right so it's me at a table surrounded by 24 people in a
room right and I perform at the is that a stage where the front row is 30 feet
away so when you when you told me the story yeah there was more to the story
than I went to bed and figured it out in my sleep there is more to the story in
that like okay so what happens is I start going I said the first joke is like
and no one cares right and it gets this it gets this big laugh from the audience
and the reason why it's because the way Mystique dining works is you you go
there and you have this opulent beautiful meal with everybody in the room
before the magician comes out the magician is the last 45 minutes of the
of the experience right so this gentleman had been the mayor of dinner
yes so when he told me that story it was probably the fourth time the audience
was hearing that oh my god and I'm hanging out right I'm back I'm on the
backstage area waiting for the things so I know this I've already been told this
guy keeps telling the story about how he figured out a magic trick and he won't
stop telling people he told the he told the one waiter told the other waiter he
told Steve the the emcee and Booker Steve Branham who runs the room told him
and then interrupted my show while I was trying to start a card trick to do it
and so it just been blitzing people the story the whole time so when I start
laying in him I it's getting these huge laughs because they've freaking hurt it
they're done with it yeah they're done with it now it's weird to have this clip
take off for me personally like I I mean he's an old guy right it's like I am
picking on an old guy right like I do feel bad like he's not he's not being an
egregious drunk heckler you know he's just make himself mayor of the room yeah
right and then the second clip is when I start to get into my card trick he
starts busting my balls for not having a sealed deck to start off the thing with
okay and some other magicians have chimed in going like it's a reasonable
request that is magician bullshit magician to magician abuse and you don't
have to take it man man there's oh oh I feel you brother I feel you that is that
is a nonsensical that is awful this business too long bullshit magician
responses I've been performing for other magicians too long also is the only
people that that would be reasonable from is another magician at like a magic
conference or something like that or in a fool us type setup where they're doing
any of that bullshit because what you're doing isn't doing you're not teaching
people how to do fucking card tricks you're doing a show but not even that
it's one of those things that speaks to ignorance because any magician worth
their salt knows that sealed or not it doesn't really matter yes you can gimmick
a deck to be sealed yes sealed it's an ignorant comment it comes from a place
of ignorance and trying to be ignorant it's trying to wind up it's trying to
want it one up no I don't even mad at some I dealt with some similar shit at
the guy who disrupted the show I'm really angrier at the magicians who are
defending I don't know in a in an improv way recently and it got me it sent me to
11 immediately I'm just like shut your teaching no no no no no discussing
discussing intros of all things oh and I was just like shut the fuck up you are
you are just talking shit to talk shit now yes yeah it's just like the like
devil's advocating on the fly to make it seem like you're being smart apps of
fucking giving giving an exam oh my god my dogs are going crazy yeah no I was
just I was talking about it too they're angry no no I want to I want to hear
your opinion on this Matt so I was just talking about introing and one of these
simplify an intro because we had previously done an interview and the
interview got really dark and so at the end I grabbed your line which the this
is all intended to be comedic in nature yeah yeah to get us out of that death
spiral yeah and we and we were fine but I said hey in light of the fact that I
don't think anyone has any fun stories to tell right now about their day-to-day
yeah why don't we just go with song titles or rather song lyrics for a git
right yeah and and I was describing the thing and this is the way I put it I was
like so we'll get a song you know we'll get a lyric and I want you guys to just
think about a lyric that you're gonna call out don't you know really pondered
think about something that actually means something to you don't just shout
out who let the dogs out just give me a lyric and you know what as a matter of
fact give me a couple give me like two or three and I'll pick my favorite one
let's see what we do and I got oh you don't want to be fishing yeah wait yeah
someone is accusing you of trying to cherry-pick the most immediate just in
the description of how we could do how we could do it not in doing it just in
the description of saying hey no just give me three I'll pick my favorite and
was saying oh we don't want to be fishing I'm like you are so wrong on
this you couldn't be more wrong I know that that's and so I kind of laughed
because I was mad to the point of explosion and I was like well you know
there's burning kind of - we're burning the who let the dogs out yeah that kind
of thing and and you know I did I couldn't in the moment get my head back
around but like like even Liz the great Liz Allen has articulated to me you can
do that you can pick you know it's not like you're not I'm not you know first
of all look most of the time the audience shouts out a bunch of different
suggestions at the same time anyway usually exactly you heard any yes so you
end up you end up assessing the situation anyway the idea no but the
idea is that you were you were disparaged that's what happened and it
precisely and it made you so angry in the moment you couldn't get your words
back around on you and I get that completely yeah but the idea that
someone would use you of like you're literally trying to like you he
literally just like made you into some kind of cheap cheaper artists some sort
of hack yeah yeah meanwhile you're actually like trying to spread a wide
net yeah that that would drive me crazy yeah I needed I needed some validation
from a fellow it's not a quiz it's not it's not a test it's not like let's see who the
best improper is by seeing who can tell suggestions the fact is it not and do
this is a goddamn show no shit dude well that's that the ultimate the
entertaining the that's the ultimate thing is like okay let's go around all
this loop-de-loop and then the end of the day you're gonna you're gonna show
me something on stage worth a fucking right it reminds me the time the
emphasis brigade was on Conan O'Brien early days right so so they were on the
the core for including Amy or Amy Poehler were on the stage and they go
like Conan brought us out there cuz he you know we really love improv and I got
hooked into this I was like oh they're gonna let them do improv on Conan like
this is awesome and they go like oh can we just have like you know a setting or
whatever and they're like oh the Swiss mountains they're like oh and then can
we have like a character from fix you know history like Buddha and like oh
and then we have like you know whatever something you might get it's like it's
like cakes or whatever and like okay we take you to a mountain where Buddha is
having a birthday cake and they make like noise in the curtain raises up they
have a perfect set of the perfect set just made exactly for that thing right
exactly so the idea like so this is you're like you're like oh wait let me
see if I can get it close to my my right yeah yeah yeah I'm really hanging on to
ain't no holla back girl soon as I get no holla back girl then I can strike
because I've got a great I've got a great Gwen Stefani in the pocket like
what the fuck I came here to do a Gwen Stefani impression and I'm not leaving
until I do it it just made no fucking sense to me I'm just like you want to
see what you're finishing what environment was this where were you I've already said
okay okay it's a weird that's a weird one yeah so I should just say like more
more on the the clip because I told everybody in the zoom there was more to
it the clip goes on I do get it I do get a sealed deck so like right part of part
of the things that I'm like grappling with as I take on the dumb internet
comments is I think I'm being funny the whole time I know I'm I know that I'm
I'm being upset but I think I'm being upset in an amusing way if I thought I
was being upset in a way that wasn't amusing I would have stopped I would
stop and that's the hardest thing to convey right like like if you look at
the who dat goat episode that we did with the with the guys right if you go
back and listen that episode on our feed I am the butt of that episode and I tee
myself up for it numerous times you you open that door over and over again yeah
but it's what the show needed right so I'm purpose and you served it yeah I do
it right so a couple people came up to me and they're like hey man that was
really tough up there I go what no that was exactly everything went exactly the
way we wanted you know I'm addressing Robert Young shooting people like no you
don't know what's going to go away stop talking to him like no I did what was
supposed to be done in the show right I'm very happy and so it's very hard to
convey that like I am taking the piss out of the guy I think he knows it a
little bit I know it and the audience is going with it and so I thought the
odds would go with it on the internet as well and for the most part they have
right I'm pointing out the the few dicks but I will say what my social media team
edited out what's me finally opening up a sealed deck which probably took forever
because that's another thing about the that's the other joke about like why
are you using a sealed deck the primary reason is that it is a pain in the ass
open a fucking back of cards and I used to open sealed decks for my tricks and it
would sometimes take forever and deal with the cellophane yes you got to deal
with cracking the box yeah then you got to dispose how many just that cellophane
the two tops and the two bottoms you have the two jokers on the bottom and the
two cards on the top instruction cards yeah and then you got to shuffle them and
else other stuff right and so I do I do I do oftentimes skip ago here's here's
the deck I've been using from last night look they're all shuffled and I have the
person look at them and I give them a quick shuffle or they can give a quick
shuffle and it's just for time it's just for time yeah it's just but also
if you look and you see that it's a real deck and if you're handing it to other
people that's it's 99% of the time that's gonna be just a deck you're not
gonna hand a gimmick deck to a person right there are tricks I do where I
don't have the deck sealed but if they if they're looking at the deck and
they're able to shuffle that deck and hand it back to you that is better than
an un-freshly unsealed deck that is as clusterfucky as you can get mathematically
right so it's so it's edited out as I finally get all the cards out and do
whatever and I put the cellophane and the advertising cards and the stuff
right in front of his face okay I go here I'm gonna shuffle while you inspect
this garbage I actually thought it was fun for the eyes to actually be annoyed
but then follow through on all of his demands right so like I did I did I
actually did yes and him and do my card trick under test conditions but that's
not social media right so so that's the hard part is so I'm getting accused of
like not playing fair with the guy and you're like no I actually if you saw the
whole thing you did another guy goes I don't get it every every clip I see you
and you're just some thin-skinned guy losing it and I was like that means you
just saw two clips yes because my other clips don't show that my other clip
don't have it at all so I was like all right Jesus it's called a brand so yeah
I got the report like I have a tick-tock page I don't even look at that my social
runs entirely goes that clip killed on tick-tock and I was like oh man this is
not it's always the stuff you don't expect though right I know no I mean I
put that up there thinking it was gonna be something I when I said the because
like I said it's a security camp footage so I said right I said this is this is
bad this bad quality but I think this will play and so I was actually right in
that yeah I'll tell you else only wants to see seal dicks today's show Matt and
manly's ice cream social is brought to you by night as in nights of the
roundtable nightmare the night mayor dedicated to wordplay that is hopefully
still funny when I'm sober that's from goofs scoop in 2023
let's over it up that is nightmare the nightmare that's the product hello tis I
nightmare the night mayor yes I'm the mayor of the night how about that I'm a
mayor drunk and this is the funniest thing I've ever heard in my life I'm a
mayor I'm also a mayor and a night and a mayor of the night and a nightmare this
is the mayor of the night the mayor of the night do we have any old business
oh yeah all right the council will adjourn after we dedicate a tree oh tree
oh yeah the mayor of the night yeah better haze groups check out I'd like to
apologize to all of our listeners there the mayor of the night was really
cherry-picking what business he wanted to attend I'm sorry it was what was
offended by it was in fact a cherry tree I was planting a cherry tree so that I
could cherry pick the whole thing yeah yeah yeah so there's someone reporting
their tin scoop part two of me with the sealed deck it's got 217,000 views on
tiktok and that'll be great as soon as tiktok starts to monetize I would tell
you also the weird thing about it is because I've had some of those clips do
well but they've not gained me followers this one's gaining me a bunch of
followers which is a weird which is a weird moment as well and I can't chase
this right you can't go like after oh I should start busting everyone's balls
then you will just be a thin-skinned magician like we're gonna experiment with
this company with our podcast right we're gonna give them a little month run
and see what they do it and they asked me they're like is your brand on ice
cream social like like similar to your brand as a magician like do they
compliment each other and I said oh not at all no no I'm a relatively clean
magician and I am absolutely filthy on this show so no it does not not exactly
brand synergy now I started off as a magician I was filthy when I started
there so originally it did it did compliment each other right right but I
don't I was remembering that I used to ask for a borrowed iPhone by asking for
a hand jobs machine right yes for the hands jobs machine I asked for the hand
jobs machine I still haven't donated my Halloween candy I got to look for a
place to do that still I got 20 pounds of candy download just send it with a
Sarah to work she'll bring to work it'll be gone in 20 minutes European
acrobats will eat the shit out of that candy we already got we already got snow
up here oh no yeah yeah yeah we already got snow and it actually stuck to the
ground so I'm very concerned about what's coming this winter yeah yeah yeah
but I'm also pleased to say that my Christmas decorations went up at a very
timely time because half the neighborhood is up and cooking now a week
after I put my stuff up so it's it's all good you're a trendsetter buddy I was I
was speaking of our regional news Jacob are you excited that the shuck era has
begun down in New Orleans what's happening so is this a is this a ball
player of some kind yes let me say some my kids are suddenly into football
enough that they're curious about watching it when I watch it okay but part
of was we were sitting around two quarterbacks came up one was Michael
from Atlanta my kids literally were like does that say Phoenix and they were
hysterical that someone's playing football has a robot penis called my
called the Phoenix and we just made robot penis jokes if the Atlanta Falcons
were smarter they would follow your lead oh yeah and then then there was the
beginning of the Tyler shuck era in New Orleans and which my kids are really
loving being part of the shuck era they don't give a shuck they're part of the
mother shuckers they're ready to rock isn't his name pronounced show is that
true I don't think it I don't think you say the C at all in his name oh I have
only listened to anyone pronounce it Chuck is it pronounced is it
mispronounced I thought it was Tyler show I don't know okay I just as easily
be the person wrong here is it Patrick wah is that right yeah there's some new
ones too there's a new rise out there are there more was there are there's one
who plays for Vegas now yeah but yeah no that's that's great and to answer the
question you're really asking I can't get behind the New Orleans Saints this
year at all they're just so bad I get I mean we're on we're on our own text
message shades and everything so Matt sees that I get genuinely aggravated
when New Orleans wins the game what are you guys doing we want the draft pick
yeah stop it yeah are you guys sincere feelings now that the FBI has come out
and said that all of all of organized sports is a psyop is there I guess you
haven't really lost interest it hasn't changed my view on it in any way okay
because there's not a single part of what they're saying that I'm surprised
about right I don't know what you're talking about Paul oh that's a just you
know the the corruption of bedding throughout all the coincides with the
fact that like games are fixed and rigged and yeah fixed by the Mafia
leaning in on on individual players so it's scarier than it being rigged like
ha ha ha they wrote a book of football or something like oh it's scarier yeah
but it's yeah but it's funny so what's crazy to me is specifically the
pitchers indicted for throwing a first pitch ball on purpose right because that
I know it sounds strange but the competitive balance of that is really
funny to me because everyone's happy right so if you're betting the first
pitch is gonna be a strike that's a really hard task for the pitcher right
but but the batter also wants the first pitch to be a ball right and the and the
other team wants the first pitch to be a ball so the idea that like I'm gonna
throw a ball first the catcher is to just go like oh let me just stick my
glove over here no problem like it's like the ease of everyone making money
off of a first ball is hysterical to me it's like it was like great that's just
easy and fun and for basketball and for basketball it's hysterical where people
were betting unders mean that like I'm gonna go in and not rebound I'm not
gonna grab a ball I like that to me is like hysterical and as you uncover the
stories like these are people who are making a lot of money suddenly making
money on like dumb bets that don't pay in the in the arena of the money that
they're making right and so like one of the players it turns out like he just
had never paid his taxes on his crazy NBA salary and had just a crazy ass tax
lien that he was trying to get out of and so that's why he got into it people
being roped into illegal poker games the poker game thing with like Chauncey
Billups and all those yes that's that's bizarre and what this one Paul no so
it's literally like sports celebrities luring just other motherfuckers into
playing poker games with them and then not playing an honest poker game yeah so
so illegal poker yes I did hear about that illegal poker rooms and states that
the guys gambling of the ice poker running illegal poker game so they're
running these crazy rooms using celebrities basketball players to lure
in people with money yeah and then using literally like microchipped cards and
like technology I saw like right they had these glasses on and you could see
every card like every card was clearly visible from the back like I knew what
everybody had the whole time yeah it's wild and I was laughing at someone who's
one of the sports podcast listen to is a big card collector and stuff he goes to
card collecting conventions and he goes I mean I don't want to say nothing but I
was wondering why Chauncey Billups was at every one of these events why it's
this active NBA coach and Hall of Fame basketball player finding time to go to
every card event there he's getting paid like 50 G's each time yeah fucking job
because coaches make the fucking donuts coaches make millions right so like the
idea there's no way these card things are paying and like that's actually worth
this time but yes they are in a way they are in a way yeah right yeah it's just
free money that's crazy what's crazier is the argument so like what happens is
this is this is a thing where both sides think they're totally correct right we
should stop all this legalized gaming gambling on sports it's gonna mess with
people's lives right and then the fucking degenerates that are like no no
no by having the best out there and we and we're catching these these spikes of
weird bets we're exposing what could be happening behind the scenes or off off
books and smaller books other places like you want to keep it out in plain
sight you want to get some I feel like that's a really good point I think it's
a good point with all of them except for first pitch ball that's the only one
that I'm like you just can't everyone's favor to do it like it's just everyone
will take it it's the worst what do you think about the always go into game seven
thing or often going to game seven thing oh I don't we've tried to rig that I
don't I don't think those stuffs can be that on that level I don't think things
can be rigged on that level I just don't that's tough I mean especially with this
world series which was crazy great the amount of ones I went to extra innings I
mean you can't say let's have one game go to 18 innings when they have to play
the next day at 5 o'clock like yeah no one's no one's writing that right like
no one's rigging that but the fact that three of the games that went went to
extra innings I think in the World Series including including one literally
literally a bonus game they literally did 18 innings they accidentally played
yeah they doubled they played eight games so I think it's just I think it's
it's just a testament to the competitiveness of you know these
athletes are still athletes so they're still psychotic to be professional
athlete you have to be a psycho like we have to remember right so I don't I
think you'd only rig it so much football being the hardest one right like that's
the one where like you you can't oh football is is just impossible to rig
the full game without like truly cooperation well that yeah very level
cooperation and if you like these real dumb plays where you're like oh that was
an intentional fuck up but the thing is the thing is it's so precious right so
like if you drop a pass on purpose yeah to underperform to pay a bet you you
might get yanked out of a game for good like like like you're right it's so the
marketing that ego for those guys too yeah like a team maybe scores four or
five times you know an entire game you know they basically get like eight to
ten chances at driving it's just not there's just not enough leeway for
someone to purposely underperform and then not suffer dramatic professional
consequences for it yeah it's just not it's just not the this is the I could be
proven wrong I would be some of the stuff that's come out it's been baffling
I reserved the right to be corrected but so far I mean look look at me like the
Giants are trying the hardest and for three quarters they'll do well and then
for the fourth quarter guess you could you could probably that's your best
argument it's that the Giants are paid by the Mafia to stop trying in the
fourth quarter there's really not a lot of evidence to support against yeah I
again I have made good on my promise not to watch any NFL this season and I
haven't but I do see the memes keep coming up in my feed because I am in the
Pittsburgh area and you can't avoid it and it's just every week I see them I
see Steelers shame themselves like stuff like that like Steelers embarrass and in
prime time and I'm like of course you hired a schlocky freak to be your new QB
they are a confusing team they're using team you ain't kidding why I'm glad I'm
not watching this year because it's just every time they're like these guys are
dirt they come out and they score like a thousand points and they look like a
juggernaut and then right you go like oh I guess they're good and then they're
like oh we can't score at all no no no 10 scoop says the Giants are great it's
the damn game that's too long yeah you're right we've got that fourth
quarter out yeah three-period game why don't we just if they just copied hockey
to be under three quarters in my in my family in my family in my family text
read my oldest brother said he doesn't trust anyone who dies their beard anyway
and I said I feel attacked and then the goes right though and the coach got
fired tonight this week and I just thought up it's bad week for the beard
dye boys bad bad one my brother's in beard die that adds up quick man that
ain't cheap yeah no it's not like cologne you know I actually you should
see that I just bought a seven thousand dollar case for my beer tie for my just
for men right in yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes different beard
dyes for different events sure well some days you're going all gray some days
you're going yeah yeah and instead of having like a 1 through 10 for the for
the for the for the case lock it's just different jewels right it's just diamond
ruby emeralds you just go through it real jewels yeah yeah it's all hold your
eight dollar just for men okay that's right that's right that shit is such a
mess to do too I've only done it like twice yeah I was in 50 Shades I was
using the brush and stuff and that was easier so III do I do both yeah now
we're getting into yeah now we're getting into it I the the brush in one
can feel like a little a little cakey on the yes it definitely does and so I find
it like makeup yeah I find it hard to go to bed right like oh yeah you got to
wash that shit off your face right but then you're trying to scrub it and when
you do comb in beard dye when is it washed like when is it done I don't like
I don't have a base of all white do you know what I mean so like right I just
simply go from yeah it'd be easy for me greyer to know there's there's my all
white beard then I go to bed with like a big scratchy face and but it looks so
much better the the the comb and beard dye looks so much better than the just
for men diet it does look sharp right yeah someone pointing out just for men
not the most woke name and the modern selling points right yeah I mean that's
just that's just on them they're just they're just losing money by still
having it called just for men right yeah that's the whole that's the whole men
problem thing that it's all just you heard that whole crazy thing with the
the the art gallery and the ladies her art project was a women's only club and
yes yeah it was that was fast no oh wait let me it's something to do with the
bathroom yes yes yes I think about think about it let's do a let's do a sponsor
and then we'll and then we'll do this when we get back it's someone yeah so
someone someone in the chat if you can dig enough as a woman got in trouble for
putting a women's only art gallery together but she did in response to a
bathroom controversy someone could find that and post a link idiot basically
proved her point over and over again yes yeah it's a good story and I want to get
the details right so yes if someone wanted to post a link to that I'm gonna
go to our following sponsor today's show introducing the forest gump vibrator get
get off from coast to coast with one of two settings the intermittent stutter
vibe or the more regular never-ending shrimp menus setting ping-pong paddle
shaped to focus on that special spot thwap that twat new random setting
lasts your session wait let's your session be a box of chocolates leg
braces sold separately warning knock recommended for use on a park bench this
person did the whole ad they didn't Paul you don't think anything right they
wrote the whole thing I got it yeah it's a super trooper scoop in 2024 mom always
said life is like a box of dildos you never know what you're gonna get this
here one is called the forest plump it's all about girth you can inflate it to
three times its normal size once inserted use it at your discretion
lieutenant Dan has one that he puts in his butt lieutenant day and boy lieutenant
Dan is fun at parties he's easy to get at cuz he ain't got no legs better hey
scoops to check out I'll put a vibrator up his butt a museum in Australia oh I
didn't I did a bad job of 46 ish great a museum in Australia is being forced to
allow men into art into an art exhibit originally conceived for women only
after a tribunal ruled discriminatory following a complaint by a disgruntled
man who was design a denied entry right let's see so Tasmania's museum of old
and new art Mona has been ordered to stop refusing entry to persons who do
not identify as ladies to its ladies lounge exhibit within 28 days after
ruling was made blah blah blah does it say why she's doing it yeah it's hard
to find out why she did it yeah experimental artwork by artist and
museum curator Kersha kaech ele is billed by the museum as a tremendously
lavish space where women can indulge in decadent nibbles fancy tibbles and other
ladylike pleasures hosted and entertained by the fabulous butler some
fella from New South Wales had paid the $35 Australian entry fee it's about
$23 u.s. and was barred from entering the exhibit on April 1st last year so was
barred on April Fool's Day according to the documents he said that it made an
equal rights argument yeah there you go there's basis a priceless like Picasso
was like in the women's restroom was the her first argument for putting it as
women's only okay but I thought it was done in response to something but I
might be I might be just trying to find it here yeah Nick Newman you're in the
chat unmute yourself if you can are you walking around where are you I'm here
fellas what can I do for you I was realizing the other night why we came up
with the turn barn and you can tell me if I'm wrong on this all right I'm
learning this as you are yeah yeah because if you said horse house it gets
really confusing I'm only gonna call it the horse house from now on please bring
all that hay to the horse house please who built the horse house oh we should
call it something else people think sex workers in my backyard I love it hey
speaking that I just got my tickets to a great show for January 23rd jokers of
magic yeah oh awesome you're coming out oh this is Lexington you come you'll be
back in town I'm back in town and that's my birthday oh wow we got to go off to
your birthday yeah let's do that yeah cuz you are now you're at your other
horse job right now right you're at West Coast where it doesn't rain it does not
rain what's what's what's what's the horse news out there what's what's going
on out there on the West Coast you know it is a whole different ballgame out
here this ain't Kentucky kids now Kentucky I think Kentucky is like very
like lavish horse farms a lot of like crazy money going into these like
perfect conditions for horses and that kind of stuff it's right out there if
you're on the West Coast and you have that kind of money you will buy a two
bedroom house or groceries different different level of investment I want to
grab like is here in Solana Beach it's a it's an upscale place mm-hmm and I want
to grab people by the shoulders and go you know that very small house you live
in you can buy entire horse farm in Kentucky that's exactly what happened to
Las Vegas post-pandemic before the pandemic is to say it all the time I was
like wait till people from California realize they can sell one of their
houses and buy two out here and then just commute as needed as soon as the
work from home thing took off that's exactly what happened out here is
everyone oh we can't even get one house in Vegas but we could get one in
Pennsylvania right absolutely well it's close to Pennsylvania that West
Virginia is one of the few states that have a uptick in in population because
the one thing people left those these terrifying hell scapes and went to West
Virginia and bought all the land you can have right now the big the big race out
there's the Breeders Cup the Breeders Cup just wrapped up so that it just the
first week in November it wrapped up so that's the world was what was the big
news what was the big scuttlebutt from the Breeders Cup last-minute scratches
horses got all the way to the gate and they they were not allowed to participate
because of due restrictions because one person is federally oversight it now we
have federal oversight gate it got all the way to the gate and they were like
no not you there's like leading horses off the track yes and it's like okay and
then like owners just embarrassing it's really embarrassing when your horse has
to be led off the track by the pony without a saddle on what were the
reasons the differing reasons but but veterinarians seeing signs of soreness
or or not okay unsound horses but oh okay the track that they run it at the
particular track had a problem for a couple of seasons of an unusual amount
of horse deaths not that particular track the okay the track you're thinking
of is Santa Anita which is in Los Angeles oh yes you're right the track
here I have to say has one of the highest safety ratings in the world it's
it's it's San Diego got it okay okay I'm mixing it I'm mixing my West Coast
tracks this track was built this and I'm Paul if you want to warm up this track
was built on in 1939 on a loan taking against taking against the life
insurance policy of Bing Crosby that's true so somebody just bet against Bing
living and won 100% they shorted Bing Crosby's life insurance to build this
track it was a friend of his name Pat O'Brien fucking friend yeah boy gotta
let you know this cough isn't getting any better go ahead and take a shot
hey that sounds well all right nobody I've said it for years nobody does a
better Pat O'Brien impression the Nicholas name that's it go ahead and load
my body I like it let's have some more horses coming up and they're wearing
makeup like a beat-up person just like don't mind me I'd sure like to race
today I fell in the paddock I I should have cooked the dinner right I should
have cooked the oats right oh you you don't know Bob Baffert like I do he can
change I can change him everyone the other claim to fame of this of this track
is that this is the place where Chris Jenner and Robert Kardashian first met
oh so everybody brings it up like that's that's this boy is that what's going on
I didn't hear you go ahead is is it an old cursed Indian burial ground as well
as that what's going on with that fucking place God might as well be it was it was
Shawnee ghost popping up in the middle race during World War two this track was
used as a as a plane wing assembly factory where was the where was the fancy
wing assembly factory really interesting Beverly Hills here in Del Mar that's a
really interesting tidbit I wonder what they use Santa Anita for and then
everybody immediately was like don't ask so then I looked it up and it's like what
was it it was an internment camp yeah and I was like well that's not that's
good not gonna be on the tour that they at least get to race the horses you
chipped neck up on that one Paul so what were the big horses that won and should
we keep keep an eye on them for upcoming not for long episodes and then also what
was the attendance like oh absolutely so the attendance was was was a like a
thousand down from last from last year okay a thousand fewer guests which is
hardly noticeable in a place like that you're talking about 63,000 people over
two days okay okay okay okay okay and then the so your current world champions
are the Japanese are the current world champions of horse racing oh they the
the current world champion is a horse named forever young from from Japan okay
did Japanese horses usually do well in these races so I last year they sent
19 horses to this event and and they won none of the 14 races no that's a tough
that's and I said they could have sent 19 hermit crabs and got the same result
so this year guess who called Newman's bluff and sent 19 hermit crabs literally
they can't they sent nine horses this year and just absolutely crushed oh wow
okay okay all right well then that's exciting we'll have to look out for so
they're figuring it out and then I I got to briefly talk to Mike Rapoli listen to
not for long Mike Rapoli is a real character a real treasure so Mike on
Twitter has named himself the Commissioner of horse racing as he walked
by me we made knowing eye contact and I said a good luck Kamish three paths on
the back and a smile so that's there you go he got so Frankie to Tory had
himself a nice weekend Frankie to Tory this is the best thing if you again not
for long podcast the show tries to make it crazy that Frankie's still racing at
his age and then we find out that it's very common for racers to race at his
age they say down those lock and he's just trying to clutch it any opportunity
he gets and he ends up working with Bob Baffert one of the world's most famous
trainers and they give him a horse and the Breeders Cup so it's like really
that's the it's the last the last that's that hard Scrabble Road we're following
with him he's just fallen on hard times but possibly due to his suspension and
we will just say for legal purposes made up the fact that we also think he's a
cocaine and so we often make jokes about that as well total fabrication we're
just a comedy show we're just wacky guys we made Robin Lee to cut the maniac we
just do these things and so we can't be held responsible for things that we make
up Frankie Dettori's bread surrogate so Frankie he would never eat bread get
real that man hasn't seen a carb in 30 years so Frank he did not he was not
riding the Japanese horse I imagine he was not all right well I'm still looking
out for that tough luck kid I feel like he's still gonna find a place to shine
he's gonna land on his feet somewhere all four of them well thank you thank you
Newman for I want I wanted my Breeders Cup update oh wait also how's the how's
the horse you and my dad bought claims in how's that horse still training well
looking for that first start should be fine that's where your dad's gonna have
a lot of fun with that it should be fun what's the site you guys went to yeah my
race horse calm calm you can buy really small shares micro shares of race
horses so my dad owns like $120 $120 share of like a five hundred thousand
dollar is your father the world's oldest brony at this point my dad yeah world's
oldest like that's a bonus brony he's basically a My Little Pony fanboy yes
he's basically living out of My Little Pony fantasy this is amazing yes yeah
does he have does he have a small statuette replica of the horse that's
what I should get him for Christmas actually get him a custom pony get him a
little get him a My Little Pony with whatever share it is like one you know
three thousand some horse hair in an envelope my little ponies like they do
custom the the if only there was a way that you could figure that out oh my god
well before you pop is there any what's Briarfest okay so Briar horses are the
the collectible horse action figures what they're made by the Briar company
and they're not getting into that that fucking bullet I bet and they have a
full-blown like week-long festival for these plastic horses here in Lexington
every year oh my gosh and they are fanatical to the point where we think
about closing to tours during that time oh there's so many people come out for
the for the for the horses for the toy horses they will they'll buy two hotel
rooms at the clarion and they will get permission to remove the furniture from
one of them and right and they just turn it into a store a store for any other
people who will do your your plastic horses hair for you like a salon yes
dude and and and the nice website they've got like pictures of these of
these this horse yeah that they are I guess introducing the 2026 Briarfest
celebration horse Corgi Hill Flinka and it's a real yeah yeah yeah it's just a
picture of a real horse and then right below it they've got like the plastic
things that they've made of that horse and they and the kids I get a good job
the adults will fist fight over that horse right I can't picture someone
getting their horses dolls hair done to present it to another person like huh
oh you can't my world would do you show off the grooming of the hair of your
figures it's all about customization yeah so you get your base you get your
base bucks yo like this is your standard buck and then it's all about people who
can trick these things out there's a guy I follow on YouTube his channel is mr.
home arcade this cat has got money and he gets four of everything basically
yeah and he also pays all these other awesome creators to send him customs so
the stuff that he has is one-offs totally unique but really cool really
well done but a lot of it is you take the base figure and then just build on
it ah that yeah yeah true it's all about that base true or false Newman that one
of the biggest briar collectibles is just a Katherine the great with her legs
wide open yes the great playset would sell like hotcakes
talking about this place is the longest saddest fistfight so I'm gonna be two
punches me hit you and you hit the bed me hitting you and me your surface and
yes good Jesus with legs wide open but then you like custom satellite there's a
person make it tiny little saddles out of real leather see that's where that's
when it gets really yeah yeah yeah yeah see with with the Masters of the
Universe especially that's my forte it gets to like characters and people that
were featured in the cartoons that have never been made into figures which
that's getting that list is getting smaller and smaller and smaller of
course years of yeah yeah Masters universe figures for that but there are
still some and these people want these one-off figures it's been their dream
like oh I really want this figure from this episode and if it's never been made
people will make it but then the interesting thing is the fandom will
respond and if it's a nice enough custom and enough people go oh well I really
wish I had that figure too Mattel follows those boards and they build out
figures based on fan demand and that's how we get a lot of these really rare
weird one appearance I'm telling you right now the person making custom
leather saddles for those Briar outfits doesn't know that there's a whole
battle cat saddle universe out there oh yeah I don't know I thought they might be
they might know they might know looking at some of those Mondos but but that's
it that's the fact too is I would not be surprised if some of those what do you
call that Newman the whole on Psalm I guess it's a lot of livery right the
tack the livery the tack is that what it's called it can be liver yeah so that
would encompass the what the jockey rides what the jockey wears the colors
oh that's sure yes and then the saddling and all that kind of stuff would be tack
so I mean I'm gonna go out on a limb and say there's probably been an occasion
where a model tack maker has inspired a real-life replica oh sure oh yeah I'm
sure I was worried we were gonna look at this like as a strictly parasitic
relationship but no no no it's copacetic
yeah yeah yeah no these guys these guys absolutely inspire you know the big boys
to make the big toys that's how it goes all right does have three battle cat
saddles already you're right rich scoop I have more than three so past Breeders
Cup how long is your season out there Newman I'd get right ahead home just
okay just for it to be cold in Kentucky and then what's the next big race on the
radar for for possible Triple Crown people because the Breeders Cup starts
at all right starts at all the Breeders Cup juvenile starts at all and then the
next in March there there are some there are lots of there's the the Arkansas
Derby there's the rebel stakes there's a Florida Derby but what everybody's
really got their eye on because of the international horses that are making a
bigger impact is the Dubai World Cup the the United Arab Emirates Derby is
probably gonna be the next that's that's early early March okay flying horses
makes me scared mayor force one so cuz do Americans and other best horses to
Dubai or is it always this thing oh always you said a horse flights the most
boring flight in the world right I hate it so much it's not that boring it's
like a it's like fucking Russian roulette the way you described it yeah
standing on there with with a needle with a put down and a dope up in both
hands that reminds me of how I used to describe being a fireman oh yeah it was
just long periods of just complete boredom and then every once in a while it
goes freestyle crazy so that's about what it is okay back to chili chili chili
don't work it up I forgot about the put down juice Paul somebody you can murder
a horse at 30,000 feet that's amazing that's it numerous times someone has
spent tens of thousands of dollars to ship a horse to somewhere and have it
arrived dead that's what this was that is what has happened the numbers that
makes me sad about that is just like my recent experience with the injected die
I'll wager that if you put death juice in a horse you can't really go glue or
meet with that bad boy either that's pretty best you're pretty much just
throwing him on a fire pit or great question Paul Nick how edibles a horse
after you kill it so it's okay yeah all right the half life's pretty low there
is well it's kind of like it's kind of like how much rat feces they'll let into
a McDonald's hamburger how much how much how much phenol barbital they'll allow
into an average mix of puppy chow I don't know what's going on skippies just
kind of low key today breakfast I don't know a lot of horse meat man he had his
he had his purina he had his kennel ration I don't know thank you Newman
thank you Jack vs. nerd buddy thank you guys go get them pure Reno failure here
we go of irradiated horses oh they didn't make it
oh that's too bad I paid a lot of money for this flight do I get any of that
money back or anything oh no no no no I I guess she did I guess you did
transport the horse that is that is all I paid you to do that seems totally fair
by the way the ladies lounge is the name of the Tasmanian Museum Mona that's the
name of the art installation in Mona it was ruled illegal by the the first
judges who dealt with it it has gone through to the Tasmanian Supreme Court
who did uphold the legality of the exhibitions women-only policy there are
now ways that men can see it there are a couple of different ways that they've
made it so that male visitors can go in and see the display there are it features
what you were saying Matt it features expensive jewelry and art including
Picasso canvases as a comment on sexism and historical exclusion though some
pieces were later revealed to be fakes or replicas I guess you're making the
point yeah oh man that was that was it he inadvertently made the point of you
know how dare you exclude me oh yeah while women had been excluded from male
spaces forever and there are still so many of those things still on the books
today yeah so it's almost like that guy didn't didn't get it he really we got a
scooper he coming to us today from Canadian scoop crystal Canadian scoop
crystal sent a whole email along with this we will get to that email at a
different show I've got it set up in the queue this is a scooper T all about
Canada it's provinces Canadian singers Canadian actors slash actresses oh that
makes sense and animals I want to be first I'll try animals for 200 what
animal is found on our nickel and started the fur trade I mean your mom oh
it's your mom and it's her beaver because it's also a beaver it's your
beaver Matt you're up I will take actors for 200 what actor is known for humor
superhero movies and was the world's second highest paid actor in 2020 was
the second highest paid actor during kovat Ryan Reynolds that's probably my
guess oh it is Ryan Reynolds good job Paul I'll go singers of our 200 what
Canadian band wrote the theme for the song the theme song for the Big Bang
Theory and that would be bare naked ladies the bare naked ladies look at us
three for three on Canada we're so much better on Canada than we were on the
other country the other day and it's almost like it's closer to us let's see
I'll try provinces 200 what province has a significant cultural heritage shaped
by its long history of fishing whaling shipbuilding and funny accents
oh wait is this the is this the new fees is this gonna be Newfoundland New
foundland yes we done the new fees Matt all right we've cleared out the 200s
guys it's anyone's game yep I will do actors for 400
who started out as a model on home improvement and is now acting on
Broadway Broadway Broadway shoot there are so many there was three three
different models but is Pam Anderson on Broadway right now I think this is Pam
Anderson on Broadway yeah Pam Anderson Pam Anderson is
correct bing-bing-bing-bing-bing I don't know what she's doing on Broadway but I
didn't know she was on home improvement yeah was the whole thing with her and
Liam Neeson was that completely staged or was that partially real or does
anybody know did it ever come out as far as I know it's real are they still
together oh see as far as I know it was staged well I we actually I thought
about trying to even Kevin come on but I know one of the writers of the movie
okay I know who wrote airplane and he says it's legit okay well there you go
but it's also in his interest to say it's legit sure that's fair Paul you're
up I'll go with Canadian singers again for 400 this singer started her career
at 16 and has won 10 Junos a Canadian Music Award and nominated for eight
Grammys now Canadian scoop crystal I recognized you felt like you had to tell
us what a Juno was you had to tell us that it was a Canadian and you were
correct that is did need to tell us 100% Alanis Morissette Alanis Morissette is
in Avril Lavigne Avril Lavigne the other one the other one there's a bunch
I'll try animals for 400 what urban animal plagues most cities especially
here in Canada that we created a sidewalk memorial to one most cities
especially here in Canada okay is this gonna be like a rat or is it gonna be
like a moose I think because it's Canada I think it's a raccoon oh or a raccoon
yeah raccoons are big in Canada that a cartoon called the raccoons was mostly
it was made by Canadian animation house all right well I'll pass because I have
no idea okay Matt that passes to you
I don't know I mean I want to guess pigeon but oh that's a good guess - oh
yeah yeah the chat wants me to say raccoon I'll pass Paul I will go with
raccoon raccoon is correct Matt you're up provinces for 400 what province is home
to the to the large nickel a wonder of the world and is surrounded by most of
the world's fresh water
pass passes to Paul Nova Scotia I'll pass that passes to me I is it Ontario
that was gonna be my guess area oh right yeah I should have guessed it I should
have guessed it I should have I'm an idiot I'm a weak weak person well we
both passed on raccoon I wasn't passing on Ontario that's true I'll go Canadian
actor for 600 daily double here it is now the real money redemption to her what
actor is Canadian and known for being optimistic despite his diagnosis that he
has a foundation for in finding a cure that'd be mr. Michael J Fox Michael J
Fox is correct yeah I always forget that he's Canadian uh yeah he seems too
aggressive agreed agreed I'll try I don't know animal 600 other daily double
whoa man now the scales are flipping what Canadian animal was adopted by a
vet and ended up in a zoo in London England to inspire a writer to create a
beloved character what Canadian animal was adopted by a vet and ended up in a
zoo in London England to inspire a writer to create a beloved character okay
this is a real this is a real long way to get Canadians credit for this famous
English character it's a bowl winkle a moose it's just a moose the moose and squirrel
let's see there's bowl winkle there is what whether like beloved animals could
come out of their one is this a bear is this a bear is this a bear I don't think
it's oh man could be Paddington Paddington bears my I'll say a bear I'll
say it's a bear it's Paddington bear Oh Winnie the Pooh the Pooh you should just
stay with their buddy you should have I should have just said I don't know
Winnie the Pooh was British yeah Christopher Robin that very
American name yeah yeah Apple pie Christopher Robin okay I think I'm gonna
go with singers for 600 what country artist worked once worked at McDonald's
starting writing songs at age 10 and was forced to take a hiatus from music due
to vocal issues caused by Lyme disease we all know this famous Lyme disease
the McDonald's worker mm-hmm you worked at McDonald's at age 10 no so writing at
age 10 I'm trying to remember I don't know pass this this country artist was
forced to take a hiatus from music at age 10 due to Lyme disease Paul she was
a Christian singer and then not I think I think that's who I'm thinking of Amy
fuck Amy fuck no Amy fuck ah it's not what is her name Amy fuck fuck fuck fuck
Amy fuck Amy fuck the chat is trying to help you again Paul if you want to look
at the chat and cheat it's right there I'll pass well I mean yeah but I'm gonna
I'm not gonna cheat oh it passes to me I have no idea and I can't see the chat so
I pass oh that was wrong that was wrong when I was thinking of the Amy fuck of
country music well she thought Amy fuck wouldn't sell records as you change her
name she was wrong imagine my career that Shania Twain could have had as Amy
fuck my favorite joke one of my favorite jokes is you know Shania Twain's not a
real name it's Shenaniel Clemons Canadian singers what band is a
Canadian indie band known for Neighborhood Rebellion and Black Mirror
fuck I don't know pass oh shit it passes to me oh I think I do know well oh what
is it my only guess would be Our Lady Peace but I can't answer it in good
conscience because I don't like them but I don't think they're indie they're
pretty big I don't know yeah I don't even know what makes an indie band indie
anymore it seems like half the indie bands are signed to record labels and I
don't understand how that works I'm passing to Matt this is obviously
Brian Adams guys oh it's Arcade Fire oh they're indy for that matter it's all crazy to me it's me I'll try animals for 800 what animal
medium-sized wild cat characterized a character characterized by long dense
fur triangular ears with black tufts at the tips and broad snowshoe like paws is
that a Lynx that sounds good to me I'll go links oh my goodness Jacob Tari's
failed system let's do a score check Jacob score check Paul and I are tied in
the lead with 800 apiece but Matt is right on our heels with 600 there aren't
any more daily doubles left but there are three questions left provinces for 6
and 800 and Canadian actors and actresses for 800 it's gonna be tough
you're up hmm do I want to leave the two province questions for you two or not
of course let me just remind you that I got Ontario I'll take Canadian actors
please for 800 who had a career spanning 60 years he appeared in more than 100
films and 150 television programs portraying more than 220 actors and die
or characters and died in 2010 I have to remember a Canadian actor who died in
2010 that's that is precisely what the question is asking you to do yes I'm
just okay where was I in 2010 and let me try to picture when I was grieving the
loss of Canadian actors let's see I had been really upset about 9/11 for nine
years at this point I can't I pass like that I can't Paul John Candy died before
that right yeah yeah yeah I think so yeah who else is kind of like John Candy
lemurs screamer creamer says or name one of the 220 characters oh man it's red
green no I have to pass I don't know it passes to me I definitely know this but
I'm passing anyway out of sportsmanship Leslie Nielsen oh that was who I was
thinking of hilarious but I was like no you just have airplane on the brain
because the earlier questions oh it is Leslie Leslie Nielsen okay yeah that was
who I was thinking of that's so funny Wow there you go could have one to cost
me the game guys cost me the game well Paul and I could both miss our questions
Paul you're up gamesmanship I have to go for 800 800 going for the win what is
the most recently added territory to Canada it was added in 1999 oh my
goodness it's just it's just gotta go Edmonton
Alberta it's just some town in Vermont that everyone's really nice it's
Detroit you're going Edmonton Alberta yes I just said Paul all right none of it
none of none of it none of it none of it damn it and Jacob closing out the
category and the game provinces for 600 will Jacob win this game who knows
what province is home to the world's largest hockey stick it was originally
created for the expo 1986 huh oh pass it Jacob is Montreal a city or
province mmm great question I I think Montreal is wait is Quebec a province
shit in Montreal part of Quebec is that the province I think it is I'll say
Quebec British Columbia well played I really have to say this might be one of
my least impressive wins and I owe it to just the fact that Jacob could just just
passed it is my passivity is never you know weaseled to be out more than this
game yeah I had two right answers in my head and didn't even guess them Canadian
scoop crystal thank you Canadian scoop crystal I'm gonna get your email later
your email is in my queue here if you want to send us a price of scryte jock
versus nerd and obelisk jock versus nerd or a scooper a jock versus nerd just
like the one you just heard head over to hey scoops calm hey scoops calm right
there on the home page you can also send us an email to be read it as part of
scoop mail but yeah do all those things over there at hey scoops calm we need
some more games to play so head over there make us some jock versus nerd
games and send them on in we'd love to hear from you yeah I want to thank all
the people supports on patreon we'll be getting lists together soon I hope me too
but yeah was no over read the thank yous for everyone who supports us and we
really appreciate it so much and we've got a lot of new sound so we have a lot
of new people to thank which is also awesome yes welcome all of our new very
excited about that but you can join the ranks of our supporters by going over to
preaching fun.com
or if you like me found out today that Bing Crosby is entirely responsible for
the Kardashians head on over to farts in a bag dot biz that along with preaching
fun.com it takes you over to our patreon page where for as little as three
dollars a month you can help keep this show on the air the reason we were able
to do this show is because of our patreon supporters so if you would like
to join their ranks preaching fun.com farts in a bag dot biz those are the
places you can go if you think this show is worth more than zero dollars if you
can't go over to those places and do any any monies just tell people about us be
part of our obelisk scheme tell one person one person only if you tell more
than one person it's a pyramid scheme that is unethical we don't do that no
we do an obelisk scheme you tell one person one person only they tell one
person only find that person that you think is gonna really dig on this weird
thing that we've got going on over here let them know and help us out and always
subscribe and review leave us those five star reviews they really help us Mike
Lush thank you for becoming an ice cream truck driver thank you Mike yeah just
that email in the hopper yeah all right thanks for listening everybody stay safe
out there we love you and we'll see you soon
a fun see ya