Oh, hello there! I'm so glad you're here. It's time to thank the Ice Cream Truck Drivers.
Thank you so much, Ice Cream Truck Drivers. This is a bank show, so I don't have a list,
but thank you to each and every Ice Cream Truck Driver out there. We sure do love you,
and we're glad that you're bringing this fucking ice cream straight to people's fucking ear
holes. If you want to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, head over to PreachingFun.com. PreachingFun.com
is where you can go to sign up to be an Ice Cream Truck Driver, and who knows? The life you save
may be your own. Now here's the show. Hey Johnny, do you want to go to an Ice Cream Social? Yeah,
I'd love to. Great, let's go! It's a bank show. It's the day after the bucket show. Here we are,
Paul Mattingly is still in town. In the churn, churn, churn, churn. It's time for Matt Mattingly's
Ice Cream Social. Sitting over there is Paul Mattingly. Sitting over there is Matt Donnelly.
Sitting over here is Shakeup the Audio Guy. Can I get to the 8.8? We're preaching fun. Maybe. No,
this is a stopgap. Yeah, this is churn stopgap. Churn stopgap. Stopgap churn. You make me want to
stop my truck and fuck you. Stopgap churn. Ooh, I knew it was roomy. I don't know what to talk
about first, whether we had a good bucket show or not, or that Paul gave my children porn. I don't
know which one we should dive into first. Pump the brakes. I would say let's start with the bucket
show and let's billboard Paul giving your children porn. Fine. I'll take it. I'm no prude. I feel
like that was shots fired at my direction. Oh yeah. There were. There were definitely shots fired. Now
I'm going to talk about it. Now we're going to talk about it. Okay. Now it's out there. So,
why did you give Matt's kids, Paul? So I got to go to visit Ralph's, which is, you know, my favorite
comic book shop in the world and got to talk to my buddy. Um, he's doing good. Don't miss Ralph out
at Alton alternate reality comics. Um, it is the, the hotspot for the comic bookage out there in
Vegas. Um, and I got Keeler. Keeler is very into comic books right now. Yeah. I got him some books
last time. Got some, some fantastic force and he's got a couple of, uh, old guardians of the galaxy.
So we were looking for maybe get some more of those guardians of the galaxies, that kind of thing.
Ralph did not have those. No, they're a little hard to come by. But he did have a copy of
a infinity gauntlet trade. So I grabbed that. That's a, that's a key thing that, uh, Keeler
needs to check out because like, and I, I, you know, it's been a minute since I reread that story,
but Mephisto plays a role in that. And that's the new, no, this is not by the way, where the
story's going. Paul's just doing a recap of all the comics that it's not, it's not fisting porn
that he gave you. And then, and then I bought him, uh, well, he gave your son fisting porn.
What was the other one? You haven't gotten the latest issue of the angry goose.
I got him a pissed off goose. You're waiting for the trades to come out. I don't want to get it.
Those spoilers, please. Angry goose game is hot shit. Um, no, I got him the, the all star Superman,
uh, new mini trade. And that's the pornography. No. Oh, okay. Then I went to the, the, the 50 cent
bin because I love to raid me some old comics as you can find some gold. And I did find some gold.
I found a early 2000 Savage dragon, number one minty fresh bunch of stuff like that. I got him
some Rob Batman record this bank episode twice. One where Paul tells his version first and one
where I tell my version first. Right. Yeah. It's going to decide which one they want to listen to
first. And then I see there's a copy of powers. Okay. One of my all time favorite book powers,
Brian, Michael Bendis, Austin, Michael, a von Oming, who, whose artwork I love and follow
through a bunch of different books. Um, so do they have any particular styles to their artwork? Uh,
it's very angular. Okay. It's very angular. So I think, um, Batman, Batman, beyond right now,
I'm thinking of the movie heavy metal. That's what I'm picturing right now. More Batman beyond.
Okay. You know, Batman beyond you film familiar with that kind of have very, very angular, almost,
almost, uh, Bruce Tim. Oh, Bruce Tim. Sure. Sure. Sure. It's a, it's very, it's very Bruce Timian.
Great. Michael, Yvonne Owing stuff. Anyway, uh, I pick up that book and I'm like, oh great powers.
And this is a, it's a, it's an, oh, uh, a newer issue, newer and that it probably came out 10
years ago. You were like Matt's children need to be introduced to power. I was like powers is such
a good book because the guy who made it made, uh, invented the miles Morales Spider-Man. Yes. My
kids love. Yes. That's the, that's the spider verse, uh, Miles Brown. Okay. Brian, Michael Bendis
did ultimate Spider-Man back in the day. He invigorated the character in whole huge ways.
And he is a juggernaut of, I still haven't seen that second movie,
comic stuff. The first one was so good. I just never got around to see it. And he's deep with
that movie too. Like he was, he was big in, I think he had a, it's one of the only movies where
like the multiverse really just is the plot and works like you're like, oh, this is just a really
well-earned, uh, did you not see the, uh, the Dr. Strange? What was that? Which one was that?
It was the Dr. Strange. Yeah, I saw all of them. First of all, Dr. Strange, Dr. Dr. Dr. Dr. Yeah,
that was good. And then finally came back. Dr. Strange, like guys, seriously though,
you won't believe it. Dr. Lots of places. That was Dr. Strange. So I get it. And then I've got a
couple of other books and then we're, we're heading out and Paul's brothers, by the way,
Paul's brothers in the house, by the way. Yes. Honks here. Yeah. And so I bought these books
for Keeler and then I'm handing them over and then I'm like, Oh, wait a minute. Sometimes we
got in the car, comic books in hand. Everything's purchased. Matt has had enough. Paul turns to me
and goes, Oh, there might be like boobies in one of, uh, of those comics. I hope that's okay.
Okay. Are the kids with you? What am I going to do? Okay. What am I going to do? Turn around,
yank it out of his hands, go back into the comic book store. If I knew it was to the 50 cent bin,
maybe I, maybe it would have been more of an option. But, uh, uh, I was like, well, there's no,
there's no turning back now. We live here now. This is the multi-person that we currently live
in. I'm not upset that he did it. I'm upset at the sequence of events. Well, I, but I sequenced it
out of my head in the wrong way too. Cause I just didn't remember. I was like, Oh yeah, there's some,
but it's very like circle with another circle on it. It's very like happy face eyeball.
Paul, some of the great graphics of the boom. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. My son has to understand that
the main character in the very first page is at a strip club. So I have to let him take in that plot
point and just figure out how he's living his life. Look, my kids are being raised in Las Vegas.
They pass little darlings billboards all the time. I'm not, there was a moment at the bucket show
last night where, uh, I think Jonathan stopped the show just to make sure that everyone knew that
those two kids in the front row were your kids. It was like, everybody, I need you to know something.
There are two children up here. They're Matt's children. They're fine. Jonathan made some real
hay about them in the front row. It was like, uh, why would you bring these children to this R rated
Joe? What he went to duct tape, uh, Hillier's eyes. Oh, good. Well, it was funny as the last
bucket show, uh, and we'll get back to, there's no, there's, there's no way to go back to it.
Basically, I was just, it was like, you, you, you, the sequence of events is before you hand my child
the thing, think is there boobies in it? Uh, the second thing is then ask me before you purchase
so that I can get cool dad points. Right. You're right. Instead, Paul just put me in a position to
just be a, uh, an impotent fuddy duddy. Right. There's no way I was going to stop. And I won.
I won completely because then we pull up to another, we pulled up to another comic shop.
Paul, what did you win? I'll tell you what I want. We pull up, we pulled to another comic shop and
we're getting ready to hop out of the car. And I was like, I, you know, I was, I was like, I was
kind of, you know, half apologize. Like I am, I, I, I may have overstepped there. I didn't really
recall that there are boobs, possibly boobs, but I think it's fine. And Danny, he's got to learn,
he's got to learn some time. You know, it's, it's fine. That's what I want. I want, I want old uncle
Paul to be in charge of my child's sexual awakening. If he ain't awake now, if he ain't
awake yet, it ain't happening. Um, he's 12. I'm sure he has membership. He's awake. He's awake.
Yeah. Filthiest. Oh yeah. That's awful. Yeah. He's got his own only fans. Um, no, uh, he's got a
subscription to jugs magazine. Nudie magazine day. Do you mind if I get the mail? Uh, any, any
discrete packages? Just go get the mail. I'm looking for a rather discrete package. Hey,
but it's been a huge help having you at the mail. Oh, yeah. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. I love to do it.
I camp out there now just to make sure I don't miss the man. We're good friends. He and I,
can you imagine, he brings me comic books. Can you imagine like a wink, like here you go,
some good editorials in the back. Here's another issue of powers for you boy. These
circles really kind of look like tits. You won't believe it. He's, he's circles are so
fun. Every time he goes to get any basketball or soccer ball in the garage. Yeah. We just,
now we're just associated with just the very basic shape. It's a protractor. Oh, it's roundish.
Yeah. Uh, no, it's 12. So he still yells boy every time I raise it. We have to communicate our
household. When you're 12, it makes that sound. It is that strong. Um, uh, I miss it. I know,
right? Like those were the days. Uh, now it goes, I thought something was wrong with Matt's car.
Turns out there was a sexual awakening happening. I also was reading powers.
I'd already fished out a few of my copies of 57 when they were in another section,
but we're hopping into this new, uh, this, uh, to go browse around a little bit more.
And, uh, I was like, yeah, you know, I'm sorry. I may have overstepped, but you know,
it really was like, he's got learned sometime. It's fine. It's a, it's just a round little boob
and both your, your, your ping pong between two incorrect things. But then Matt's, Matt's like,
Matt's like, it's fine. He can have it. No problem. It, which is, which is great. What other choice
did I have? And then now then Keeler goes, I'm trading for Paul's my dad. And I said, and I said,
you are going to regret that decision so quickly. I said, but you are going to enjoy your meals more.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're going to love the food. The food plan. Top notch.
Bologna and cheese, hot dogs, mac and cheese. Forget about pizza every day. If we want it,
who cares? Um, but, uh, but that soccer game, forget about it. What time does it start? No, no,
no, no, no. How hot would it be? No, we're not doing that. Will I sit in the sun? You want me to
coach what? Eat shit. A plastic folding chair. Here, here's two game boys. Leave me alone forever.
And then we were in the second comic shop. And when, when I stayed away by the near shot,
he turned to the guy who works there. He goes, do you have anything more adult? And he slid a
$5 bill across. Do you have any of those Tijuana Bibles where Mickey's like really slipping it to
all kinds of kids? You got any books? You got some Tijuana Bibles back there? Cause that's what I
really, I'm hungry for that poor art. I didn't think we were going to get an episode title out
of this story. Yeah. I'm not familiar with the term. So a Tijuana Bible is a bootleg comic,
usually involving big brand name characters doing pornographic things. Yeah. And it's, uh,
they're, they're usually published out of Mexico Mickey mouse, fucking Cinderella. Yes, exactly.
And so we're going to call me up to the chalkboard to solve some, I'll just be back here with my
inconspicuously wrapped package. Nothing to see here. Mrs. Johnson. Oh, I got a divorce mini
Paul cemented his love for, uh, with my children. Yeah. I'm sorry if I'm cutting off Paul's
narrating of, of, I was telling you, I was telling a dumb joke. It's, it's, it's, it's, uh,
Donald goes, Mickey goes up to Donald, I got a divorce mini and, and goes, why Mickey? Just
because you said she's crazy. I didn't say she's crazy. I said she's fucking goofy.
I want to hear you Donald duck voice more. What were you saying? So his kids love me
more than him. Yeah. He also got a, a scratchy Funko pop for, for my other child. Yeah. Keeler's
not so much pain there reading tip right now. I feel your pain of your children loving Paul more
right. It's uncle Paul is fun, fun uncle. Yeah. Yeah. He's like, you know, he knows his job.
He's no limits. Yes. No limits. Well, cause I am still there. Right. What? No. Yeah. What?
Not at all. I don't know what they're talking about. Peter pan do, do, do fly me to neverland.
This is what Peter pan really looks like. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. I am Paul has a, sorry, Wendy
Paul has a green tights of giving gifts to people like of things that he likes and therefore things
you want. Well, like, uh, yes. Most people who don't have children don't understand like how
different they are from year to year. Sure. Yeah. But Paul got your, yeah. So I was explaining this
to you last night. So when Eve was two, uh, for Christmas, he always sent stuff for Christmas.
Yeah. Sure. Which is great. Yeah. It's awesome. Um, and he sent the entire DVD full collection of
loony tunes and he's like, now you can, you and Eve can like watch all the loony tunes. And I'm like,
great. She's two. Like there was no, she, there was no understanding sign language for more loony
tunes. Yeah. She's like, yeah, yeah. I want, I want more food. I need to be burped. Yeah. So
can we watch all of loony tunes? Yeah. Right. But now almost 10 years later,
what was that? That was manian devil. That was better than his Donald duck. Everything's better
than my Donald duck. Let the listeners decide. You think anybody's still listening? No, but then,
but like, but, but it comes around. So almost 10 years later, um, Shelley was, uh, out of town
and I had the girls and I was like, all right, we're going to have movie night and let's go
rummage through my old DVDs and see what we found. Cause I was like, we're going to watch the three
amigos. And so I was like, I'm going to introduce you to the, the great singing Bush. It's, you know,
all of it, just a plethora of wonders. Uh, and so we go through there and we find it, but on the way
to finding the three amigos DVD, we also found the box edition set of loony tunes and they know
loony tunes at this point. They've seen a few and they're like, and they flipped their shit.
And we watched loony tunes and I introduced them to like the coyote road runners for the first time.
And it was like one of the greatest nostalgic, like awesome moments with Mike, cause they're
first, and like, it's the best. So it comes around, but I, but I hear your, you know,
listeners are familiar with the amount of movies that Paul says I should watch with my kids that
are just just not appropriate. To be fair to me, I made a big list of movies I thought could be
appropriate for the last time. Honk brought the girls out and we've landed on back to the future.
Oh, it crushed. It did right. She's still loving it. Right. It crushed. Eve, Eve was like, Eve's in
that, uh, she's 11th, but so she's now starting in that, in that area of like being able to
understand the uncomfortable humor. Yes. And so when, you know, Marty's mom is like hitting on
Marty, she was, I mean, contorted in the chair, but it's a testament to how good that movie is.
Like it makes you feel how much incest still affects people. And I guess how healthy your
children's internet porn searches will be since the, since the, that, that seems in vogue on the
internet. It's everywhere. It's so bizarre, but that's good. Yeah. So she's still like, did you,
have you done the follow-ups yet? We haven't done any of the follow-ups yet. Yeah, but well,
that's great for sure. Nora was still a little too freaked out when the Libyans came and shot
up dark brown. She was out. She's like, Oh, that's too much for me. I'm not, she's gone. Yeah. She's
like, Nope. But Eve stuck through and really the Libyans. Um, but yes, I would definitely at this
point have shown, had I had children, they would have seen way more inappropriate material and
being supposed to way more inappropriate stuff. Now, now John, how much are you looking forward
to next year? Paul bring your, uh, then 12 year old, uh, pornography. Are you looking forward to
this or you have a little trepidation here? As long as the quality is a little higher than, uh,
eyeball boobs, maybe. Yeah. Yeah. All right. All right. Well, but I mean, he's sort of, you've,
you've given some stuff like a couple of years ago, like you, you gave her the entire
Elf quest series. Right. Now that's not super out there, but it's like a little more. It's
mature. Violent. Yeah. And you don't like the bull feral movie, 10 year old, but my, but my
girls, I guess the ball seems a little brutal, a voracious reader. That's why I got it for like,
she does not, she does not stop now and she really loved it. She will read anything. And so she
devoured it. She loved it. Yeah. It's a big volume to the point. Like she reads so much that like
she will, um, oftentimes come and like, she'll just be talking to us and then she'll say a word
weird. Like, you know what she's saying, but she like pronounces it weird because she's just,
she's only seen it. She's only read it. And then she's, you know, read it as it's phonetically
spelled or whatever, and then she'll come and she'll say it. And then we sort of laugh and then she
gets mad and we're like, no, no, it's crazy that you know, these words and it just, it's pronounced
like this. And she's like, Oh, okay. Well, it looks like this. I've had a hard time explaining
to my younger, it's like, basically like, I don't know how to like busting chops. Like when we laugh
at the thing that you're known for, we're not trying to hurt your feelings or ridicule you.
Maybe that's the thing because like early on here with it, it's, it continues through your whole
life. Yeah. But within funny people, it's, it's love language. Yeah. And that's the thing. Like
as soon as we're on that group chat with Jonathan and Brad and Brad starts busting my balls, I'm
like, I'm fine. Yeah. I'm like, we're good. Nope. We're going to have a great show. I got nothing to
worry about here. He feels comfortable giving me shit. That's all I need out of a comedy partner.
Right. That's it. And, but it, I guess it just takes a little while to know that, to learn that.
Yeah. But maybe you can explain it to him like that, that it is love language.
Yeah, I think we're trying to, you know, like in the moment, it's still like, it's like,
well, when it's the first time, right? The first time you've ever been called out on something silly
and you go, Oh yeah. I take it every time, but also, but also the bucket show in a minute,
thank fuck. He can feel a little bit of shame because that's what's wrong with the world.
Nobody feels shame anymore. That's funny. That's true. You know, I think it's also like a control
thing. Like you're not in control, but you're not in control of people's narrative of you.
And it can be a little jarring. I'm like, Oh shoot. This is how people say, talk about me. And I
can't do anything about it. It also depends on their age. I don't know if you've noticed that
because like when they're younger, they've, it's just, but like now my oldest is like reaching an
age where like it, her, her appearance is becoming more important to her and the way she, you know
what I mean? Yeah. And she started becoming aware of other people's, if you go further,
it's just becomes a nightmare for me. Go keep going. Yeah. But you got boys. Yes. Yeah.
Different. You got the easy, easier to buy porn for that. Yup. That's true.
Way easier. This, the sapphic comic book is a rare beast. I, it's weird. Like I think it's backwards.
I think boys are harder when they're younger. Well, traditionally they're harder when they're older.
And then, and then there, and I think it, and then it like reverses because like little girls
are, I didn't know that in their forties, they're really difficult. You know, who else got Matt's
children's of pornography? That's the following sponsor. Today's show, Mad Man's Ice Cream Social
is brought to you by Greasy Al's Parmesan scented deodorant. That's right. That's Greasy Al's
Parmesan scented deodorant in 2022 from Dungeon Scoop and Dragon Scoop.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da. Hey Paisan, why don't you get your face up in
this pit right here? You're going to smell a fricking pizzeria. What do you think? Oh, that's
nice. Yeah. That's my Parmesan deode. Made with only the fresh grated cheese. It goes right on.
Guaranteed to stick to your pit hair. Oh, I got that. I also got Gorgonzola flavor. And for the,
for the ladies out there, I have tampons made of prosciutto.
Enter Ace Group's checkout board.
Paul's pronunciation of prosciutto really got to Matt. Matt did not like that pronunciation.
Oh, Cap's version of boy, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Whatever the early days of accessing celebrity porn on the internet, not porn,
you know, whatever. Naked pictures. Yeah. Clips from movies that already exist. Right. Like
Mr. Skin. Yeah. Yeah. But Mr. Skin before Mr. Skin. Yeah. Mr. Skin before Mr. Skin or whatever.
What was that like? Cave drawings? That's right. What was it? Circles on Circles.
Penelope, what was it? Who's a Penelope Cruz? Is it Penelope Cruz? Penelope Pitstop? That's it.
Penelope Pitstop from Wacky Races. That's it. Latin actress who was briefly Tom Cruise's.
Penelope Cruz. Penelope Cruz. Okay. Yeah. She spelled it with a Z though.
That's right. It was Tom Cruise and Penelope Cruz. Did she put them on the glass at some point?
So, you know, when early, I'm showing my age here by describing the porn I'm looking at.
It was in a comic book. No, it was, you know, it was just screen grabs. Right. Of, and it was,
so it had subtitles on the screen grabs of her taking her top off or whatever. And she referred
to her nipples as slices of pepperoni. And I was like, oh, like, it's like. He took it right out.
Yeah. I was like, oh, come on. I'm out. Whatever the opposite of boy. Chang-a-lang-a-lang. Whatever.
That's it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're, we're, we're, we're waa-waa. Is that Pac-Man dying?
Yep. Pac-Man dying. Yeah. The last thing I want to do is be sucking on a nipple and get a little
garlicky aftertaste. That's going to throw it off. I don't want any aftertaste. I just want,
I want regular garlic taste. You want full flavor? I want full, full garlic. Garlic nipple sauce?
I'll take any nipple I can get at this point. I'll just, uh, John, let's go get it out, buddy.
Pickled nipples. John, nipple in this Papa John sauce. Garlic buttered nipples. That's my
favorite shot. So yeah. So, so we, we, last night we did the bucket show and, uh, it was, uh, super
fun. Matt Mattingly, Jonathan and Brad. Yeah. Jonathan, Magnum and Brad came out. I just had
someone mess with me now and do the thing I hate the most. He goes, I didn't realize it was Brad
and Jonathan. I was like, dude, there was never a difference. Come see the show or don't. Also,
like every post about it, every ad about it had all four of you on it. I wasn't, I wasn't keeping
Jonathan off anything. He was on the poster that, uh, Eric made and he was, uh, and he was in the,
we mentioned in the video. He didn't, he didn't get billing last time cause it was a last minute
thing. Yes. Right. Well, we talked about it. He didn't get as much, as much billing. We talked
about him after the show last night. Cause he was, yeah, he was the last minute addition to
the last bucket show. I actually, uh, paid to, uh, boost the post, the video of Brad and I talking
about the show. And it's not because I was concerned with turnout is that I hate the like,
Oh, I didn't know you guys were doing that. I was like, shut up. Like Facebook makes me pay to talk
to my friends. I'm paying the money to make sure that none of my friends failed to know that it
happened. Uh, and so to get like, I didn't know Jonathan was in it. I was like, no, just stop it.
Yeah, just stop it. But, uh, uh, super fun show. Great turnout. We were worried it was July. It's
July. It was July 5th of the night, the night of July 4th, not the biggest theater going hot night.
It's hot. It's hot Vegas. It was a Saturday night. We don't usually do stuff on a Saturday.
Other things to do in Vegas on a Saturday night turns out. Uh, but it was packed. We had to get
extra chairs. We got extra chairs out like four or five different times. Yeah. It was, it was so
because we got there, you know, we had rows all set up and everything. And then like, as soon as
we opened the doors, we're like, well, those chairs are full. Yeah. Yeah. Um, so fun. Great crowd. Uh,
we were, we were destination tourism, multiple scoops. Yes. People actually, I mean, John came
out for it. John came out for Lee popsicle. That's right. Sherman. Yep. Yep. It was wonderful. Um,
it was a really fun, I mean, uh, Sarah boy and bat scoop, but they live here. But, uh, it counts
though. They keep showing up, doing, doing thing. They're diehards. Yeah. I love it. I'm blanking on
his name, but he flew out from Northern milk lake scoop. Yes. Milk lake scoop. Oh yeah. From, uh,
Northern Cal. Yep. Oh, milk lake scoop. That's right. He's the guy. Yeah. Did you miss him?
He was out there. He beat you in the costume contest. Close. I'm glad you didn't see him. It
would have been so awkward. It would have been a fucking fight throwing down. It's on site with
milk lake on site. Uh, and, uh, uh, my children were there as well. And, um, it was such a super
fun show. It was a super fun. It was, we had, we had, Brad had some really great ideas in our,
the way we generated our information for our scenes with hot seat, having it, having it mostly come
from interviews on like three different games. That was the key way you see like a short form
improv show. It's like, can we have a location? Can we have a relationship doing that? And so
Brad's idea was like, let's really chat with people and then kind of take whatever we want
out of the interview and do the scenes off of that. And one, that was successful. And two,
our most ambitious swing on that ended up being great, which I was like, instead of doing a scenic
game, let's use a interview to set up jeopardy and we'll get our occupations from the interview.
We'll get our categories from the interview. Like you got those great categories was,
she said she wanted to, uh, do the four horsemen of the apocalypse cartoon. I go great. What are
those four again? And she named the force. Like that's our category. Well, her idea was really,
really good. It was about the four horsemen of the apocalypse, having to deal with the ramifications
of, of taking care of all the souls that came up during COVID. It was, they were, that's what she
said. She said they had, she said the four horsemen are forced to deal with all the idiots that died
during COVID because they didn't take proper precautions. So that's her whole idea. The pitch
is like dealing with the dumbest ghost you've ever dealt with in the afterlife. I thought that was
really a fun idea. That is a fun idea. That is, uh, I was, I was in and out of the room while she
was, uh, while you guys were interviewing her and, uh, yeah, so I only heard little bits and pieces.
I heard the four horsemen part and then I heard something about COVID and, but yeah, that makes
a lot more sense. That's a good idea. It's a good idea. I like the gem was the gem was her talking
about her sort of relationships. Oh my gosh. I stumbled into gold, gold and diamonds. I would
say these two people were sitting right in front of where I was standing. Uh, to the degree that
when Matt said, uh, at first, when he, when he, when he picked out this young lady, uh, he pointed
back there and I was like, is, can Matt not see me? Is he, is Matt pointing at me? Am I a shadowy
figure in the back of the room? What's happened? Like what? Okay. But, uh, but yeah, so she was
there. Her boyfriend was not there with her. That's what we discovered. Her, her friend, her, her,
her friend who is a long time friend was there with her. We all know what that is. Yeah. Yeah.
No, we, we definitely stumbled on to, because in the order I said, you know, do you, do you have a
roommate? No, I live at home with my mom. I said, oh, okay. Do you have a boyfriend or a girlfriend
order? She goes, I have a boyfriend. I go, how long has been out? And he goes, five years. And then I just went,
Oh, yeah. The audience did the math real quick. You ain't shacked up after five years. Yeah.
Something's up. And then I said, is your boyfriend here? She goes, no. Right. I go, who are you here
with? And she goes, a friend. And I, and I, and the whole, it's been like, Oh, I let it go in the
audience. I go relax. I think I'm going to actually authentically extinguish this. I go like, and you
have a girlfriend or a boyfriend. He goes, Nope. And then the whole, I just went, yeah.
But you thought you were genuinely knocking that out. I mean, I was going to be still playful with
it, but I thought I was going to, like, it was building fast. I thought you were egging it on.
No, I thought you were actually trying to make her more comfortable because the audience was like
flipping. I was like, okay, they were going really hard. And she was going hard. I was trying to just,
I was just trying to like spread it out a little bit. I understand. I definitely thought you were,
you were like playing the dumb a little bit to egg the audience on. Well, I was about when it,
when, uh, I wasn't going to ask him the question I asked him no matter what. Right. Uh, which was
if you were dating someone for five years, would you think you'd move in with them by now?
And so I knew I was going to that question next, no matter what. Uh, and, uh, and, but she was a
great sport. And he was great. I talked to him a little bit after the show and yeah, I was like,
you guys were, you guys were fantastic. Thank you so much for being good sports. And they just had a
great time. Yeah. And so for the occupation, what's great, what I loved about it was that in
jeopardy, it takes a while to set up, right? So you decide whether you're going to get categories
or not, but that's a, that's another round of suggestions. Then you get three occupations and
then it has those occupations and you have to come up with it. And then you have to worry about their
expectations with the occupations. You have to like, you have to be the funniest plumber, the
funniest, you know, whatever bus driver. So, uh, with horsemen of the apocalypse. So all we do is
interview her and I said, well, you're not going to believe this, but you've inspired this fever,
dream jeopardy. And then boom, we start playing the game and, uh, Brad plays a guy who works in
the back at Nordstrom because she, uh, she works at Nordstrom rack. Yeah. That was part of her
interview. Jonathan played, uh, the guy in the back, the guy in the back, the friend in the back.
That's right. The back rack. Yeah. And then, uh, Paul played the mother that she lives with. Yeah.
And then the jeopardy categories were, uh, conquest, war,
famine, uh, and the other one and the other one, uh, and so pestilence and pestilence and the
other one and the other one. Yeah. I kept all five. Yeah. I thought it was war. She lists death,
death is one famine and pestilence, but she named, she didn't name death as one.
She said conquest and war specific. Cause I made a joke. I go, good. You got to keep those separate.
Right. I'm like, what? No, it's, it's war, famine, pestilence, death. I did. I did think it was wrong,
but that's fine. But who knows? This is why her cartoon is not going to get me. That's right.
Can't even name the four horsemen you're making the cartoon about. No, the four horsemen are
Rick Flair, Arne Anderson.
No, no, no. The four horsemen are Mickey Mantle, uh, Tully Blanchard.
There's Greg Maddox. Schultz was in there. Uh, Steve Avery. It was Mike Singletary.
Are there four horsemen in every sport? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Well, the, uh, what was it? The,
the, the 90s Braves pitching staff, they, yeah, they were the four horsemen. It was what Greg
Maddox, John Schultz, Steve Avery. And there was one other guy in that, in that line. That's when
the Braves won the wonder division, like 20 years in a row. They said all the pitching, uh, uh,
conquest, war, famine, and death. Oh, she did nail it. Yeah. No, she got them. Well,
she didn't say death. She did. She said war and conquest. She said pestilence. Did she say,
she said pestilence? She said pestilence. She might've said pestilence instead of famine.
Okay. Well, but she didn't say death. She said death. Okay. Well, the white horse is interpreted
sometimes to be conquest or pestilence. So I guess, okay, I thought that was death road.
I'm going off of chat GPT, so she could be wrong. Don't ask tap GPT. If it made you feel better,
I think Paul was going off of the movie tombstone. There was a pale horse coming and you tell them
I'm coming. The pale horse is death. That's not the white horse. The pale horse is different.
Pale is different than white. Trust me in my Irish household, pale is different than white.
It's also known as the bucket horse. The black horse is famine. Right. The red horse is war.
I'm going to go ahead and ask them to make a Penn and Teller jokes out of this,
out of the four horsemen. That'll, that'll sing. Matt is typing into his phone.
It was a faster joke to make than to type. So that went really well. All the, all the scenes
went really well. We had a great time doing songs. Spadoni came through again. Oh yeah.
Dropped it like it's hot. Um, which was great. Uh, he's just, he's just on it. And I think that was
lovely. And I, you know, Spadoni is such a gift, man. That's what I'm saying. Like he,
he's no small part of why we shine a hundred percent. And I try to explain Spadoni to other,
to other performers in town and other, uh, committee performers in town, especially.
I really, and I mean, this is Spadoni will listen to this, I'm sure. And this is just
blowing smoke up his ass now, but, uh, he is so fucking good at Spadoni. Tasmanian Spadoni.
If you want to break it up, I can read a Penn and Teller joke about, uh, pen. This one comes
riding out to conquer the world, just like Teller here when he discovered tick-tock.
Oh boy, boy chat GPT. Well, you know what? Job security, writing jobs, officially safe.
Horseman spreads plague. Teller spreads 15 second card tricks that cost us actual gigs.
Teller is a burden you guys. Oh boy. And, uh,
chat GPT's fake on the Penn and Teller relationship is that Penn is dragging Teller along.
And, uh, uh, also this joke is really the future is I'm pretty sure Teller is still
yet to discover tick-tock. So we'll just, uh, but when he does, it's going to be a mess.
No, I mean, Spadoni did, uh, my, my shows for the French festival. And, you know, one of the
things we did was, uh, you know, we, we tried a big swing and then we made an adjustment together,
like on the fly over like one phone conversation. And then it was just flawless, uh, for the final
two shows. And, uh, I was like, it's just great to have him up there. Right. And my wife was like,
well, it's just like having him for the bucket show. Right. That's a special, unique thing,
like to just have like someone who's just the fingers of the glove. Right. Like I just went
through those shows effortlessly. He got his laughs for adding awesome musical references and
stuff and absolutely building my tricks to a crescendo. And I did this without any,
we did no major rehearsal, no major notes. She's just, he just does it.
Yeah. It's a, he, he catches things that you do and adds, adds things like the flashback stuff.
Yes. He is perfect at, at finding those moments and doing the, you know,
and even though he did it last night. And, uh, what was interesting about it is that, uh,
I think it was, it was Brad. It was Brad and Jonathan. No, no, no. I had to tag in.
You tagged in because they didn't know it. Correct. But you were right there and hit it.
And then as soon as you did, then it was perfect. He's like, of course. Then, and then, you know,
yeah, Brad and Jonathan, who don't work as a building, he played flashback during their scene
and they both froze. And I tagged out Jonathan and said to Brad, I go, Hey, it's me. You're dead.
You're younger. Yeah. You're younger than you were. Yeah. And, uh, we kept going, but it was,
it was a fun, that was a fun moment. But, uh, yeah, I mean, I was driving the car with Paul
last night and I just said, like, honestly, it's like the first time we, we, we did it,
we jammed together in 2008 at the, uh, you know, uh, what was that theater called? Onyx. Onyx.
Use your microphone, please. Onyx. Judgement night. Paul is holding his microphone in his mouth,
or in his lap and just having a conversation. The Onyx, uh. Through the sex shop into the back.
If we, if we, if we took a photo of a packed theater with Brad and Jonathan performing with
us and send it to us in 2008, we would be like, this is awesome. Right. This is, this is badass.
And it was so fun. Who are those old motherfuckers? Yeah. Like, am I dying my beard? What color is
that? Um, and, uh, and it was fun. I mean, all these guys, I mean, it's just, it's just so fun
to play with those guys. Brad's so smart. It was a gift. So quick. And Jonathan is just so playful
and so fast and just always is ready to push anything off the rails and make a bit out of
anything. And it's great. Even backstage, Brad was being, I think Brad was nervous. We're, yeah,
we're yeah. Yeah. But Brad was like, uh, uh, uh, expressing it through like, like little,
little fastidious activities, right? So we had like four liquid death cans and he's like, well,
how are we going to know which one's which or whatever? And so I wrote my name sloppily on mine.
So he decided he was going to write his very, uh, precisely on his can. He put little bees,
little bees all along the lip and it was like, make sure you don't put it too close
to where your mouth's going to be. Very strong marker taste of water. You don't want that.
Yeah. And he was totally bidding and it was very funny. And then Jonathan came in and did the same
thing. It was water can just picked up his own water cans. Oh sure. No problem. And just started
writing the same bees all over. Just like a half an inch, not even like a quarter of an inch lower.
Minor, a little bit lower, but pay attention. It was so funny. It just, it just bits for days
and just, oh, it just ready, ready, ready, ready, ready. It was good. It was good. And again,
and huge thanks to Troy for giving us the majestic space. Uh, let's think it's like last time was
just everyone doing art for art sake, right? Jonathan flies in his own dime just to do an
improv show. This guy does tours with Wayne Brady, right? Brad and Colin play thousand,
2000 seat theaters across the nation. Right. But they come out just to do improv because just to
do something else, just to do another improv show. And you know, Paul flew out and I, I guess I had
the easiest job. I'm here. I'm already doing it. Um, and then Troy, you know, gives us an amazing
deal, uh, to be there. And that's the thing is like, we're all doing art for art sake. That's
right. And that, that I felt like that, I feel like that doesn't happen when you're older as much.
Right. And, and, and, and Paul, um, and Troy is doing the lion's share of art for art sake. Yes.
He's not making a lot of money at that theater and that theater being open. Uh, but Troy just
wants, this is what happens. Troy's gives us such a good deal. I simply go, what dates open,
right? Like what, how can we not interrupt any flow of your actual money-making endeavors in
that theater? Uh, and, uh, and he just gives me a date and, and that's a really cool agreement to
have, uh, with him. And, uh, so when he said July 5th, I was like a Saturday night, what, what, what,
what? Uh, and he said, yeah, it's July 4th weekend. I go, oh, right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm dumb.
So I was really worried that we were not going to, people are not going to come out, but it was a
great, great house, jam packed. Uh, there were at, uh, so it was an eight o'clock show at about, uh,
seven, right about seven o'clock. I had to walk outside, uh, just to, just to go to the car for
something, maybe put something in the car or whatever it was. And, uh, there was just a guy
outside at seven PM. It was like, Hey, you guys open in the house? I said, no, no, no, the shows,
the show's not too late. It was, oh, no, I know. I just wanted to make sure to get here and have a
good seat. Oh, great. Yeah. The house will open about half an hour. Um, yeah, no problem. And then
he goes, great. Yeah. Thank you so much. I was just going to finish cooking these eggs on the
sidewalk. No problem. And so he walked off and the, but sure enough, like he was back
15, 20 minutes later and he was first in line at the door and he was, he's ready to come in.
I was like, man, as soon as I walked up there, getting ready to open the house,
there was a line down the sidewalk. All right, this is, this is going to be good.
It's going to be a good night. Paul was up and down off of the ground. Paul was rolling around.
Paul, Paul was so physically ambulatory once more in the show. It is revolutionary. Well, and I'm,
you know, I credit, I credit myself. No, I credit my fantastic doctor for fixing my hip, but I also
credit myself for continuing to press forward with a somewhat physically demanding day job.
Even though it's part time, I am up and down, stocking shelves on the ground, back and forth,
lifting heavy boxes, dah, dah, dah, dah. And it has really helped keep me cooking. I am, I, and,
and that's why I'm going to send my kids to work in a factory. It's a good idea. Good. Yeah. But
yeah, I'm, I'm soon as they turn 12 and a half, it's really just turning a corner for me now.
Like honestly, I'm just getting back into teaching, just getting back into just being able to drive
around and feel like, okay, I can get out here and walk. Like even just at the airport, I park in the
far off space to try and save a couple of bucks for the company. Cause it's not that much further.
But when I was walking with that fucking hip, it was like going through the desert. I was like,
and just walking the other day, heading back in, I was like, man. That's why I like Paul as a business
partner. When he has a bum hip, he's still parking at the back. I do saving that $6. I do it. I do
it for the company. Company man, company man, company man through through, but it was to be
clear. I'm not as good as a company man. That's all right. No, no, no. I only park in the very
front spot. A valet. Yeah. How much is it? I don't care. But of the, of the three of us,
I probably need the steps more anyway, so it's fine. S J does ask every now and she'll be like,
is the, is your company paying for this? Yes. Or yeah, why don't you, why don't you just spend this?
It's my company. It's not someone else's company paying for it. It's not a different, it's,
it's still our money. Yeah. We have 900 amazing bosses out there. They don't want us
getting the valet service at the airport. No, no, no. Whose money do you think I'm spending?
Exactly. And, uh, we went out, we, uh, the three of us went out to brunch yesterday and, uh, uh,
we came back and makers and fixtures, makers and finders, makers and finders. Yeah. Yeah. I thought
it was fixtures, but either way, the name makes no sense. Who cares? Yeah. But, uh, neither one
of those, neither one of those words mean empanadas. And that's what that's known for. When I first saw
makers, I'm like, that's a, like a poop analogy. That's what, that's what people say to their kids.
Now, does, does, does baby need to make? Oh, no. I don't like that. You've never done it though.
No, no, but it's gross, right? Yeah. That's when I heard makers and finders. I'm like, oh no,
I find you got to find, oh, if it's a sinker, I find makers and sinkers. Cause if you make it,
you can make, you can make a sinker. You don't want it to sink. Right. If you're, if you're
healthy, it's floating makers and floaters is what you want. That's what you want. That's it.
Our health expert, Paul Mattingly talks about the proper poops. This guy walks more than all of us
from a sparkly space at the airport. It's true. And shit's more than all of you combined.
I'm just up there dropping off the car at valet and here comes Mattingly. It's a sweaty mess.
I know about the parking lot. I'm not a sweaty mess. That's the other thing too is like,
I have some endurance again. I have some, some stamina. I wasn't winded during the show at all.
Good. Good. Like this is great. I can do this show. I made a point of, um, during the week,
the, the two or three weeks before the show, I made a point of doing a lot of singing in the car
because I hadn't been using vocalizing singing a lot to get my voice up. Keep that mic in front
of your face. I'm, I'm, I'm what they call a performer. Yes. Yes. That's right. Who called
you that? And she says, what sort of performative is this? And I say, thank you. I thought I was
eating pussy. Yeah. And she's like, well, why don't you tell your mouth sideways? Like a typewriter.
God damn it. Damn it. Always with the sideways, just running a bit into the ground. I'll tell you
who else was not impressed by Paul's Cuddlingus. And that is the following sponsor. Slappy tears.
That's right. Drive through funeral services. Say that final goodbye to your loved one from the
comfort of your car. One, uh, with one slow speed slap on their urn or casket before going on with
the rest of your day. That's from little Sally scoop in 2024, slappy tears, a drive through
funeral services. Here, but it's, uh, it's the Elvis, uh, it's Elvis from the, we know where
you're from. It was, it's okay. Yeah. Well, that's right. Yeah. That's where I live depending on
which there's only one of you, right? Well, no, there were two of me. Did you know I was a twin?
That's true. No, it's true. My babe, my baby brother died. My baby brother died before I was
more before you were born. He died. He died. Born. He bored died anyway. So I've been prepping for
this my whole life. Essentially. I was prepping for this before my life even started. Oftentimes
we have to say goodbye to our loved ones, but we don't know how. So Elvis here has made it easy.
I made it real easy for you. I got to do is get in your pink Cadillac and to drive,
drive right on by and give that older and a slap. Just come on by and give that earn a slap. Say
goodbye. Baby brother who died in the womb with me, who I hung out with dead in the womb. That was
something, boy, not much of a conversation. It's my baby brother. He's dead. Yeah. He was stillborn.
Yeah. She's not going to talk. Yeah. That was the funny thing of my mama. Mama said, mama said,
mama said, your brother was stillborn. I said, well, yeah, he came out, right? And she says,
yeah, but that means he's dead. I said, oh, I thought you meant he was dead, but then he
was stillborn. She's no, he was stillborn means dead. That's a real clever turn of phrase of us.
Good work. Good work talking to your mama. Thank you very much. I came over that one on a fly.
Me and mama, me and mama were having a little conversation about it. You know, it's always fun
to hang out with your mama and joke about your dead baby brother. That's what you do at home.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, speaking of gallows humor, come on down to my funeral home. Elvis is slappy,
slappy, goodbyes, slappy, goodbyes for your dead baby brother or whoever else might be dead.
And you can slap them and just go, you don't have to stay and listen to some bullshit about
the Lord or whatever. Just go home, go home, go home. Thank you very much. Interhase groups to
check out. Boy, I'm glad Paul was doing that vocalizing in his car to warm up for that.
Yeah. I'm, as they say, performative. Paul would have, I thought you're eating pussy.
Boy, are you eating? Oh, look at that. Look at that circle in that circle. God damn. That's,
that's the finest looking titty I ever saw. Hey, uh, hey Priscilla, you might get a little bit of
work done. So you booze look more like circles and circles. Okay. Okay. Great. You don't like
these pepperonis? Oh, well, yeah. You know what? I'm going to put a little fried manner sandwich on
him. Okay. On him. Nipples. Fried man or nipples. I just don't want to see the translation in the
screen grab. Uh, speaking of SJ. Yeah. We've not talked about this. Okay. Piff the magic dragon.
Oh yes, this. SJ and the ruckus. Winners. Winners of best comedian and best band. Yeah, that's right.
From the Las Vegas weekly. Uh, and, uh, you know, uh, a lot of that was that we, we, we,
we launched a campaign. We launched a campaign and our scoops, we talked about it on this very show
and, and, and they got scoops friends. Yes. Put them over the top. That's what scoops do. That's
right. They come through and change the subject for a moment. Congratulations to city cast of
Las Vegas for winning best podcast. Congratulations to be fair. We have had David Jan Fiegler on the
show. How is that fair? How does that help the argument of fairness? We know the winners. Yes,
but we are, we are, we've been on their show. Right. We helped them win. We are winner adjacent,
but I will also say in this, it doesn't feel like winner adjacent. Paul, they're in Las Vegas. It's
Las Vegas awards. Of course we're adjacent to them. We're also in Las Vegas. In this situation,
I feel okay because David Jan Fiegler that makes one of us is the one who helped Jimmy Sloanina out.
Yes. His pinch David figures as a, as a, as an attorney legit fucking hero. Yes. He is representing
all the people who've been wrongfully arrested during protests. Right. He's been helping people
get out of jail. Uh, he, he's a, he's a better person than us, but is he better podcaster than us?
We're not disagreeing that he's a better person than us. It's just, is he a better podcaster?
Right. Maybe the answer is also yes, but still does he need this award more than us?
Yes, but even still, I'm okay with it. Well, that's good. I'll get there. Okay. Paul's okay
with it. Yeah. And you know what? I'm not planning on stopping this. So now that we have one best
podcast, we did win back in 2016. Exactly. We peaked and I'm done. And that was, that was,
that wasn't just best podcast Las Vegas. That was just best podcast. Yeah. Period. Yeah. That's the
problem. The category is too narrow. That's what it is. That's the problem. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. You guys consider yourselves a Vegas podcast. I consider you universal. Yeah. That's why they
found a Paul is in Pittsburgh disqualified us. That's what happened. I mean, David's podcast is
about Las Vegas. It is a Las Vegas podcast award. Like his show is about Las Vegas. Our show is just
happens to be in Las Vegas. Uh, so it's just another way that he's better than us. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, David has a law degree, you know, like a real sub this show, we don't have to keep
listing ways that he's better than us. We just, I just don't have anything. He can hang his diplomas
and degrees on the wall. I can't, I need awards. Right. I need awards to hang on the wall because
I don't have any other things I've ever accomplished. Matt, Matt, don't say that.
We got some pictures from last night. Yeah, we have pictures. Put some pictures up from last
night to be like, look, I performed with some great players. Actually, one of the guys we got
up was a photographer. I will shout out his Instagram because he, he took a lot of great
photos, but let me find him. Uh, I leaned up because I had to put a microphone stand down,
but Paul thought I was trying to show him my phone. Ah, yes. Uh, third, third I viz, V I Z
third. I viz took, yeah, it took a lot of great photos of us. Yeah. Uh, we'll put them up on our
socials as well. And he does a lot of, uh, a lot of comedians in town. Yes. Yes. Pictures of comedy
shows. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was really fun hanging out with me, me hung out for a bit last
night. I got him a poker chip. I brought poker chips to hand out to people. Good. I know everyone
I tried to give a chip to already had one. So weird. I was watching Matt would go around and
be like, hi, can I give you a poker chip? They'd be like, Paul gave me one. Yeah. Sometimes that
does happen, but that didn't happen last night. Okay. All right. All right. But plenty of times
I've beaten you guys at a punch on a poker chip thing. Yeah. Because you haven't, we don't. That's
right. There is that you are chipped for. Well, I'm trying to promote this goddamn podcast. Get
some more ears on this shit. I want to be awarded to do that. We're out here spinning gold. I'm
going to say it's been an Elvis gold. Uh, you got some more chips. Yeah. You still like in general
or on me, you had a discovery of some, well here. Oh yeah. Yeah. They're chips. I need to grab some.
You were doing some construction in a wall. You found some old chips from like the fifties and
someone asked him a Monte auto chips. That's right. I thought I had, I thought I had buried
these forever and they are rediscovered. Do you think we've got some red ones now? Yeah. There's
some red ones out there. Sweet. I think we've got red and black. I love it. I think those are two
general colors that we have. Yep. Speaking of SJ and the ruckus. Oh shit. There comes SJ.
Winner of best of Las Vegas. Good morning. It's like back in the day when SJ would just pop in.
That's right. Roll out of bed. Go see what the boys are doing. Pretty much. When we had,
now she has my mic. I know. Yeah. As they just walked in, took Matt's microphone and then walked
away from that. It's okay. Well, you did hand it to me. Yeah, but I didn't know where you were
going. We can share. Yeah. There you go. There we go. John, give this to the mic. There you go.
Yeah. We can share. There you go. What's going on y'all? Winner. We're looking at a winner right
now. We were just talking about you. Are you winning the best of Las Vegas? No. And how we
didn't. Yeah. How one of us is a winner. I got to tell you guys. SJ's pity tone just made Paul spit.
I got to tell you, it really changed our relationship in the house. Our relationship
in this house has not been the same. SJ just patted this podcast on the shoulder and said,
we're really good friends. Exactly. You guys are so sweet. You're like a brother to me podcast.
You're like a brother to me. Oh shit. Well, Jacob told me, he was like, hey,
he told me, he's like, hey, Pip was here and he wants to win this thing. But on the same page is
best band and best podcast. So we were like, oh, this would be cool. Let's just do all of it.
Let's get a sweep. Yeah. Yeah. And we almost did. Two out of three aim bad. That's right.
We won the Derby and the Preakness, but failed at the Belmont. There we go.
We also didn't win a best patio. Yeah. That's okay. You might have though, because I don't think
I got like, they found me through Facebook. You might have one, but Jacob's whiskey pit doesn't
have a Facebook page or a phone number. It's fake as hell. Yeah. We didn't follow through on the bit.
That's what we're saying. We should have made a Facebook page. We should have made an actual
Jacob's whiskey. You might've won. You just didn't know. We don't know. We don't know. You'll never
know. So what's it like? What's it like being a winner, SJ? What's it feel like to win in life?
We want to know. You already know you've won stuff before. I think we've won. I think we have won the
weekly. I think we've won the award we're talking about before too. Was that 2017? Yeah. The year
after we won the first one. Cause that was, Corey helped us out with that one. That's right. Getting
us. Yeah. Cause like we went to the event for that. SJ went to the event this year. Yeah. I was up at
the Mandalay Bay at the time. Oh yeah. It was at Founders. What's that place called? Yeah. Founders
room. Founders room. The post party. That's it. Yeah. The post party was cool. Founders room is the
room at Brian Brushwood's place where all the founders hang out. That's where I went. That's
where I went. Is that near the break studio? It is. Okay. You guys got it. You know what it's like.
It was at the resorts world this year. So yeah, it was really cool. Honestly though, seriously,
it was like super, I, I forgot about it. Jacob told me about it and I totally forgot.
And then I got this call from this guy and he's like, from the weekly. Yeah. Yeah. From the weekly.
And he's so excited. He's so excited to tell me. And I'm like, what are you talking about?
Give me a lawyer. I know. Right. It was really great. Um, but yeah, we went to the,
the band was like, what? We won? Yeah. They like, I was like, yeah guys, like this happened and
everyone's just like freaking out. Right. So a couple of them went to the party with me,
but it was just like, I don't know when the band it's, it's great because it all ties in so nicely
because the band knows the scoops because the band plays in front of the scoops at scoop fest. Yeah.
So like they were excited not only to win the award, but they were excited that the scoops had,
had banded together to support them and everything. So they're the guys, especially, I think we're just
genuinely touched by the whole thing. Yeah. So we're pretty pumped. Yeah. So thanks guys.
The awkwardness of feeling is that you're not leaning in and I think you guys should walk around
like we are the best. We are the best. Yeah. So we've been posting like obnoxiously about it and
like you, you got, I don't know, you guys probably don't have it, but like in the Vegas, like
entertainer world, like everyone's already throwing shade at us. Like they're like someone posted,
Oh, isn't it cute when like Vegas people just give each other awards, like right after we were like
going off about this and people were like, yeah, I know it's so stupid. I'm like, you're not getting
hired again. You're not getting hired. These are people who like sub for us. These are musicians.
Yes. What are you doing? That's really dumb. That's just really stupid. I know. I know you guys
probably didn't run into that, but we only have, we only have nice. Sarah, Sarah Ross and Brenna
Folger were like, fuck those guys. We, uh, we really, you know, the scoop community is the
outlier community of the internet, which is wonderful. We are, we are insulated from all that,
that crazy shit, but also personally, and I think you as well, I think all of us ascribe to this.
I am okay with applauding, being happy for people and giving them their flowers when they are rising.
Right. Even if I'm not doing so great, I mean, because it's, maybe it's just not my time right
now. It comes around, but if you don't about not my time or whatever, don't be an asshole. Right.
But, but if you can't celebrate other people's victories, what do you expect is going to happen
when you win? Exactly. You know what I mean? Like you gotta be, well, they're not going to win because
they just talked to themselves. Well, that's, but high tide raises all boats, man. Right. That's an
improv thing too though. I mean, like we, we literally have each other's backs because if you,
cause that's all you got out there on the stage. And if you're not just ready to be like that
motherfucker just nailed it. No, I have some, I also have some hack bits I can go to any moment.
Oh yeah. No, you do. I keep some stuff in the back pocket. Yeah. Yeah. You know, well rehearsed,
clever bits. Oh, you have clever ones too. I didn't bust them out. So saving for a rainy day.
But you got all those away. You gotta be happy for other people's successes. Yeah. It's also
business. Unless it's a business, unless it's like, unless it's like a billionaire won something,
then you're like, well, fuck you. Even then it's just people giving each other awards. Right. But
it's always going to be like people in the same industry giving each other awards. That's what
awards are. Whereas the Oscars are very much more globally merit based. They're very external.
Right. Well, even if you're not super happy for them, don't come out and talk shit. It's like,
just let it be. That's so dumb. Like whatever. Like obviously, you know, just moving on,
but I just thought it was funny. Like throw in shade like that, but wow, come on guys.
Yeah. Well, basically like the, the, the, the whatever's darkest, uh, not darkest, the most like,
um, detached or whatever. What's the emotion for like not wanting to give a shit about nonchalant.
The most nonchalant you should be is go, Oh, well they're going to get more work. Like that
should be the most like, Oh, good for you. Good for them. More work. I used to be the, like the
most, the limit of whatever, like how dare they reward locals stuff for doing a working local band
won an award. Fuck off. Yeah. I scroll through those awards and I go like, Oh great. These people
won. And that's the end that I, that's, that's the last that I think about. Exactly. And by the way,
like in terms of like for you guys, like it actually does, like if you, if you put a best of Vegas
sign up, uh, uh, out before, on the, on the casino, before they go into the lounge and say going in,
they're going to be a little more curious about like, who are these guys and maybe give you a
little more credit. It's so interesting. Like we're yeah, exactly for that reason. So anyways, um,
I know it was like funny for you guys, but thanks. Well, we're glad with no, it's, it's, you know,
it gives us a good band at scoop fest guy. Damn it. That's best band in town. Hey, I know. So
that's the other thing too is, um, we actually got, um, asked to go to lawful net weekend for like,
it's a big concert weekend out there. And I was talking to the boys and I was like,
guys, we got to play scoop fest now, figure out a way to handle it. She left it up to the guys. She,
okay. The guys, the guys decide to do scoop fest. They were like, we got to do scoop.
Also, it's a much more fun gig than, uh, than anything else. We actually didn't want you to
lose out, uh, uh, uh, on scoop fest. So we, we went on the Loughlin message board and so I guess
I'll let anyone play Loughlin now. Uh, see if we can just get them to pull the offer.
Oh look, Loughlin people giving each other awards.
Loughlin all the way to the bank. Did you guys see speaking of Loughlin, uh, did you guys see
the plane emergency landing out there? So Loughlin, Nevada is right on the border, uh,
with, uh, Arizona. It's right, it's right there on the Colorado river. It's beautiful,
beautiful town out there, uh, right there by the Arizona border, uh, right on the other side of the
river. Jacob, all of our listeners watched Viva Loughlin with Hugh Jackman when it was on TV.
That's right. They know. And so they don't need to explain Loughlin. And so they know all about bullhead city over
there on the other side of the river. So bullhead city is like Loughlin, just a small Arizona city
right there on the, on their side. It's the Nevada border, an American airlines flight. The other, uh,
the other day earlier this week, it was all the crazy storms, crazy wind, an American airlines
flight, you know, like a seven 37 size plane, whatever type of plane it was, had to land at
the bullhead city airport in Arizona, which is just a landing strip. There is no airport. There
is no airport staff. There's nothing. So a plane full of passengers had to land in bullhead city,
Arizona, uh, to divert there. There was, there are no other planes for them to get onto the crew on
their plane timed out. So they weren't able legally to fly anymore. Yeah. And so a plane full of
people, uh, come from away style. Basically it was, it was the come from away in Arizona.
What's interesting is that Loughlin is actually, and this is a true, uh, thing. They're, they're,
they're lobbying to get, uh, support from the state because basically we're going to be building a new
terminal because our airport traffic is getting crazy and they want to be an overflow terminal.
Okay. And so they want the resources to quickly shuttle people from there. Oh, it'd be great.
Oh, that'd be amazing. I mean, if you do that, you can build out Loughlin. You can make it a
suburb. Yeah. It just, all you gotta do is put a billion dollars into a, uh, uh, high-speed rail.
Well, I guess, uh, maybe in 20 to 50, maybe, maybe, maybe. Um, but, uh, best in Loughlin now.
But so, but I bet like, but basically like that helps them make their case. Right. See, see,
we're right here. We're right here. We're the closest airport. Yeah. It is like an hour drive.
I mean, it's not, it's not very far out of Vegas. No, but that's, but, but if it had high-speed
train, you can get there in 20 minutes. Paul, no one has not, no one said high-speed rail. You're
the only one who said high-speed rail. You're right. It is much more pleasurable to just drive
to Loughlin. That's the only option on the table, Paul. Yeah. It's gorgeous drive though.
You're the only one who said there's going to be a high-speed rail between the two.
No other, I didn't say it. I'm demanding it. I'm demanding it. And then you just shat on it.
Drive that fucking thing. Drive. Eat shit. Cars. I don't want to do that. No, it's a beautiful drive
where you see nothing. Fuck off with that. Yeah, it's garbage. And then once you get there,
you're in Loughlin. So that's the upside. Oh yeah. This is where we're launching
the SJ and the Ruckus party bus shuttle from Loughlin to Vegas. 45 minute concerts. See,
once you get a few things, yeah, once you get a few things out there, then you can do it. Yeah.
Lawless Loughlin. It is the Loughlin's for scofflaws. You can have them for free, Loughlin.
Loughlin's for scofflaws. Give them time to get out of bed. Just like Virginia's for lovers.
Loughlin's for scofflaws. And are there whores out there? Is that the thing?
No. Is that the other direction? I'm pretty sure whores are in every direction.
You know what I mean? You want me to bite your whore in Loughlin? Legal whores. You're thinking
about Perot. I know. No, I'm not thinking about it. I'm thinking about Loughlin. Paul's always
thinking about Perot. I'm trying to get Loughlin on the Perot bandwagon here. I don't know if
Loughlin has legal prostitution or not. See, and there should be because just like everything,
technology-based, porn goes first. Where porn goes, technology goes. You are fucking so out of
pocket on everything you're talking about. I don't know what he's doing anymore. I'm just so glad
that he warmed up his singing voice. We want a train. The only way you can get a good train
is if you run high-speed rail on some whores. You know when they show the public access meetings
and the one guy gets up and talks and everyone's like, "What is he talking about?" Paul's like the
second guy at the Loughlin public access meeting. I'm just 10 years ahead. I'm just 10 years ahead.
You're light years ahead, buddy. Okay. Honestly, that's where technology is always guided by
pornography. That is the truth. From the printing press to the Tijuana Bible to the speed train
between Loughlin and Vegas is an overflow airport. Porn leads the way. Absolutely. Absolutely.
As always. In conclusion. In conclusion, split some rails on these whores and get this train built,
Governor. Town meeting adjourned. Meeting adjourned. Meeting adjourned. Hey, Sharks,
did you know the sex industry is a ... If you build a whore train, people will come.
Get on the ho train. You can ride ho train. The ho train to Loughlin would be sold out every day.
I can't believe. The ho train to Loughlin. And I'll fuck you at the station.
I can't believe you're putting SJ's new band name on blast. Ho train to Loughlin. The ho train
to Loughlin. Listen, I think that sounds fun. Right? Just a fucking party train full of loose,
loose men and ladies. I'm actually not here to ... I'm just watching season two of Severance,
but I just like the atmosphere. You're the one nerdy guy on his laptop the whole time while there's
just balls swinging. If you built a bullet train to Loughlin, that's what it would be anyway. Just a
bunch of loose people. Of course. The ho train to Loughlin would be. And the people who like
the Colorado River. Colorado River enthusiasts. But the other thing is-
Man, that count. It would make a bunch of these people feel so like,
because it would end up being, if it's a good high-speed rail, 25 minutes tops.
Oh yeah. Plenty of time to clean up. Done. Don't have to be overly performative with your lover.
It's the rushing of cleaning. That's really what's been holding back the industry here in Vegas.
Don't rush me. But you've only got 25 minutes,
so you better just get to the biz. Do your business and clean up.
Grab your copy of Powers. Get on that train and go. Well, I hope everyone who has governance over
Loughlin is listening. I hope the Arizona and Nevada governor have taken notice.
They know what. Isn't the founder of Loughlin, his name is like Ted Loughlin, right? Don Loughlin.
Have you even been on the cruise that tells you all this stuff? I've been on it twice.
Today. It does seem like a fun town. I've never split any horse there, but it's been fun. Loughlin
is for scofflaws. I mean, I'm going to tell you right now, if next year we had scoop fest in
Loughlin, it would be awesome. I'm on board. On board the whole train to Loughlin. I'll
fuck you at the station. We already have another location in mind. We do. We do think,
it's maybe premature, but I think we're pretty confident. I do, yeah. This is our last year at
the Orleans, I think. I think so. Don't tell them that yet. Don't let the Orleans know yet.
They don't listen. Oh, you think? Actually, they're probably really grateful. We are happy
with the Orleans. We love the Orleans. Whoever's listening for the Orleans is working somewhere
else in two months anyway. Ah, it's through. That's true. There is turnover there. Except
the one tech guy. The one tech guy. We've had the same tech guy. Yeah, he's got it easy over there.
Yeah, he's great. That's hard to replace. Yeah, probably not him. That's like being like,
you know where the rats chew the wires. Oh, yeah. Right. Yeah, yeah. When the lights turn off,
he's like, the rat got to the wire again. Hold on. Exactly. Well, we're coming to the end here,
and I just want to just say that let's go around the room and let's all just say things that we
could teach. We could teach the people of Loughlin. Loughlin lessons is what we'll end on. Loughlin
lessons. All right. Take a fucking bath, you stinky cheese assholes. Learn to wash your ass,
you Turkey track underwear motherfuckers looking like you fucking fast and furious in your drawers.
Fix it up. Don't just be fucking Paul Walker and write down your ass crack all day long with your
burnout. Peel, peel poo poos. Fucking wash that crack. You dirty Loughlin bitches. If you want a
high speed fuck rail, wash your ass and balls. Paul took mine, so Jacob. Sorry, I didn't listen
for all of it. Did he say the thing about wash your ass and balls? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, okay.
Then in that case, I'm good too. I'm good too. Yeah. Got it. Okay. Well, thanks for listening,
everybody. I want to thank Ben's left great in this podcast. Thanks, Ben. If you want to support
this podcast, why wouldn't you? People have often episodes like this one. There's a few clean people
in Loughlin. We could use support now. We're trying to save it for a new studio. Moving to a new studio.
We can use your help right now. So go over to preaching fun.com and support us today.
We know why they have to be waterproof. You don't have to spell it out, Paul. We know. I'm spelling
it out. Between the Loughlin dirty asses and all the spilled jizz, wash them trains.
That's fartsitabag.biz. If you want to support the hay scoops railroad that's going out to Loughlin,
head on over to fartsitabag.biz and preaching fun.com. Therefore, as little as $2,
you can be part of the railway to Loughlin experience. We're going to raise the bonus
episode amounts to 2 billion. And if we hit it. So many bonus episodes and a train to Loughlin.
And just mouthfuls of boxcar wheelies. You're just going to be choking on hobo rail riding wiener.
I don't wash my ass or balls. I've been fucking on the railroad.
All these Loughlin whores with dirty seats and sweaty meats. We're heading out to Loughlin.
All right. Can you smell that Loughlin train? It's coming down the track. You can smell that
dirty underwear. There ain't no coming back. All right. Thanks for this everybody. We love you.
We'll see you soon. You filthy Loughlin bitches.
[Music]
It's a business proposal. It's a business proposal.
Ain't no sensitivity when it's business and it's business.
I'm fucking whores in Loughlin. That's all I ever do.
It's fun down there. Y'all don't even know. I bet Loughlin's great. I don't know if we're
still on air. I don't want to pull my mic forward. We're still on the air. I was trying to see if I
could do magic shows out there. I love it out there. I think it's so cool. Is your underwear
stinky enough to get in? That's what they asked right away. They hand them over. And the answer
so far is no. You'll get there. I guess the Febreze method works. Covering it is oftentimes just
worse. See ya. That's the joke I made. That's what I and I followed up.