Oh
Hello there I am so glad you are here
I want to thank you the ice cream truck drivers who are the ice cream truck drivers or those are the folks that deliver that
Frickin ice cream straight to your frickin ear holes. We're not getting demonetized yet, right?
You want to be an ice cream truck driver, and I hope you do preaching fun.com is where you can go
Over there sign up to be an ice cream truck driver, and you will get thanked at this part of a future episode
I don't have a new list yet
It's a new month
But we will thank each and every ice cream truck driver by name at this part of the episode coming up this month
So if you want to be an ice cream truck driver preaching fun.com head over there sign up and who knows
the life you saved
May be your own
Boom
Hey, Johnny. Do you want to go to an ice cream social? Yeah, I'd love to great. Let's go
Oh, man, we start the show today. I want to say that my wife is a beautiful as intelligent
Okay
A round of applause for my wife. Yes. We must have really messed up
Social sitting in Texas. That's Matt Donnelly sitting at Pittsburgh. It's Paul Manning Lee sitting in Las Vegas
It's me shake up the audio guy. We're preaching fun. That's right. I'm in San Antonio
Which of course is French for the Red Stick. Yes. I'm excited to be here
I'm in the west side of Pittsburgh, which is French for Aaron Rodgers can suck my balls
This comes out we'll know I'm telling you
The oh, yeah, yeah, so they'll be out the truth will be out are you expecting a Rogers Renaissance Matt Donnelly
Here's the thing one. He's old and the only person to be able to play old is Tom Brady and no one else has been
Able to play old, right?
but
You know Saquon Barkley came back from an Achilles injury last year for the Giants struggled
Then got traded the Eagles and became an MVP candidate offensive player the year in Super Bowl champion
Most people are better their second year back from an Achilles injury
So if Rogers is going to be healthy last year's not a sign of way he was going to play. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, do you think he's got proof?
No, I just think out of sheer karma like that
We live in the most annoying timeline and the most annoying timeline thing to happen with
Aaron Rodgers Renaissance would absolutely be oh my god, Jacob. I forgot to talk to my mic for the whole first
Okay. Now. I have my mic up to my thing
Fantastic I will I will patch something together between the recording the zoom -
There goes sweeten it up Donnelly there goes all the trends we were gonna hit on social media
No, the most annoying thing that I agree with you completely Aaron Rodgers having it being the comeback player of the year this year
Just just goes along in line perfectly. Yeah. Yeah, I wish him no ill will but I hope he snaps like a twig on the first play
I mean
His other Achilles does have the opportunity to do something really funny right now. It's true. Come on Achilles
Do it
Though I I wouldn't got I went to get into the truck last night to go to work
SJ had left for the for the week. He's out of town until Sunday night and
So I wouldn't got in the truck last night to go to work
Got in hit the little it has a push button start hit the push button start and nothing happened
Nothing happened at all. Yeah, like uh, the uh, like the lights didn't come on. No clicking nothing
Just just dead ded dead. No, this is your gas
Vehicle. This is the gas truck. Yeah, is it all gas?
It is all gas. No, it's metal. I
Mean some break some metal some oil
Gas no breaks. No
So I got in and it was dead
So I had to uber to work and then uber home from work last night and then had to get up early today
Because that's J's out of town. She has the other she has the car. Yeah, so I can't I can't jump the truck
I don't have another car to jump the truck off of
And so I I call roadside service. I call Dodge roadside service
They very sweetly came out this morning. However, very early
After getting out of a show at midnight boy, does that early morning come early? That is tough. Yes. Yeah
and so
He gets here. He puts the jump back on there. I say I don't know what happened. The trucks pretty new
It shouldn't be having any battery issues, but uh, who knows let's see so he puts the jump back on
Instantly everything comes on everything everything turns right on truck powers right up. Yeah, the battery was dead
But I can't tell if it's charging or not
Looks like it is though. And but he had another call to run to
So and you said can you before you go put those on my nipples and give one more one more go
Yeah, one more one more just hit the button clear
Don't look at me. Okay, look at me
Clean up my pants. I'm a triple-a member. I said clean up my pants. I need roadside assistance
Come on I'm quadruple a I have
Fourth a stands for the you know what the final a is in the backseat brother. Yes, sir
Go ahead and find that. Oh, you had to come out and say it. I was trying to be all
No, not me anal a states for anal. What are the other a stand for? I thought it was all supposed to be anal
Yeah, yeah, it's anal anal anal anal anal if you have four a's
That was five a's what company are you working with? Oh, dude, I've exposed the fifth a they're gonna kick me out
only the secret fifth a
Jacob you have to edit this out and they'll kick me out. I just quick not don't talk into your microphone again
It's actually they wrote the theme song to the second level of Super Mario Brothers for goes anal anal anal
Anal anal anal. Oh my gosh
That's only the triple-a. Yeah secret lyrics. Well, Jacob
I I don't want to step on your story here. Those pipes goes right to the trip the 5a meeting
I don't want to step on your story here, but I have a sneaking feeling that
Since the technician had to go away quickly and wasn't sure that the battery was charging
I have a sneaking feeling all did not go to plan now. I know after that
Everything is fine. Everything is currently peachy keen really battery charged up
I took it down to Autozone and
And they they put the the tester on it and checked it checked it over real good
And they said it was all all good get in the thing though Autozone anal
When Autozone used to be called Auto Shack and Radio Shack sued them. Yeah
No, who made them change the name to Autozone who's laughing now? Who's laughing now radio?
They were called Auto Shack, huh? Yeah when you were a kid, it was Auto Shack when we were kids. It was Auto Shack. I
Guess I have any other shacks in Kentucky getting a shack Auto Shack Auto Shack. Don't tell your parents
The weird thing though was when he put the the the jump pack on the truck
Everything turned on I like I watched nobody in the zoom laughed, but Paul on that one
Which is fine by me, but I thought I got Paul is good
Why just taking a drink too, yeah, it was dangerous
No, the weird thing was everything though was turned off
So like the radio was turned all the way down and turned off
The all of the climate control systems all the air conditioners and everything was all turned off and the doors were unlocked
But everything was like folded up and like the mirrors were folded up and everything like like it does when it when it locks
So what we figured out was the new Dodge and I bet other new cars have this too
Has like a power save mode. So if it is getting down to almost dead
It'll start turning off auxiliary systems to try to save the battery
So it turns off there. It turns down the radio turns off the radio turns off the climate systems
Unlocks the doors just just so you don't get locked in or locked out or whatever
It's like a Starfleet Starship that diverse like a Starfleet Starship. Oh shoot Paul beat me to it
It's like it's all power. I knew you were gonna say it though. It diverts all remaining power to life support
That's it. Yeah, just bare life support
and so what we figured out was right before she left town SJ had unloaded a whole bunch of stuff from the truck, uh-oh and
She had when she went to turn off the truck
We think she might have double-clicked the button or something and just turned all the auxiliary stuff back on after turning the motor off
And just left it running. Wait, is it a keyless car? Yes. Got it makes sense
And so I think she turned the auxiliary stuff on left everything running. It looks like it ran for about nine hours
Yeah, wow, but the battery held out for a really long time. It's pretty good
Can that be good for your battery to run dry like that? If you just woke up early Jacob, you'd be fine
You know if you just woke up a little earlier
Well motherfucker I did today
Usually I'm up for like 45 minutes before we start recording I've been up for three and a half hours today
Buddy, I feel you in San Antonio every day and I just walk like a different direction
See if I can discover they're basically just is basically I'm going to discover a place for coffee in a place for breakfast tacos
I just have to go whichever direction. I pleased to find a new place
right, and I saw the sign for coffee and I went inside there's actually this lush lobby of a hotel on this beautiful coffee station that
was there and
Then on the menu is clearly like put together by like a true coffee
enthusiast all kinds of different drinks and syrups and that I don't normally see dirty sodas
Basically a lot for dirty sodas and the really nice espresso
Cappuccino machine, you know those real real deal machines. Yeah a lot of Starbucks push-button one and
Ask the lady if I could have you know an Americano and a point of one of the syrups and she goes I
Yeah, yeah, you want like a big cup. I was like, yep. That size is good. And then I was like pastries here
What are these what are these things in the middle?
see, I I
Think they're danishes
Okay, was this like her first hour on shift? I go I
What I didn't want to say but I go I also think they're danishes. I just don't know what
You and I both recognize the circular shape but I was curious to the contain with the contain I
Concurred doctor. Those are danishes. She's a cheese. I think cream cheese danish. I think that's stepped on cheese danish. That's super
That's a that's a classic
Let's give one of those a whirl then, you know, and
So see that up. She's making my drink. She's pouring espresso over ice into my little thing
and then I see her like almost look over her shoulder at me and then she just pulls out like a bottle of water and
Pours a bottle water into my thing for the water for the espresso. I'm fine with using bottled water for my water for my
But curious that this is very fine station doesn't have working plumbing
And she goes it's it's it's bottled water she's like it's it's good water I said no, no, it's good go help yourself go for it
I'm happy. Everything's fine. And then I
Said brown sugar cinnamon brown sugar was the name of one syrup. I was like, yes, let's do a couple pumps of that
two pumps, please and
She's looking around she's like turning around every bottle and she's like I found a sugar-free one. It's like don't
Don't worry about it. Just I bet you I bet you have vanilla. Yeah, give me two pumps of vanilla
I bet you know right where that one is, right? She goes. Are you sure because I have the sugar-free brown sugar cinnamon here
No, no, no
Did you find out if this was like somebody's kid or something was it was it take your kid to work day, what's that?
Actually was using the kidnapped hand gesture and I missed it
She kept asking you if you wanted an angel shot, it's quite possible
There was a robber underneath the counter with a gun pointed to her the whole time
You just weren't being nice
You want sugar free? I?
Think I have some more
Pumping syrup with the brown sugar under the counter. I could just look under the counter
If you take these out without paying for them they sometimes trigger a silent alarm
I
Have to come out now. I'm sorry. I'm sorry everybody. I have a gun
The only thing I said I told this young lady was please don't tell this guy that I'm under here
And that's the one thing you did I say I didn't
Strongly implied I couldn't I just couldn't take it. Mr. Robber. Mr. Robber. I believe the second chances
I have to go record a podcast. Anyway, I'm gonna leave and then you guys just start from one, you know
Start from scratch when I go ahead. I don't even want to rob this place anymore
I'm this is really just taking all this theme out of my sails
The reformed robber
Selective partners like the Helena Rubenstein foundation
It's such a good feeling to know you're alive because I left you living though
I was robbing you inside and I said, you know, not today. I will not shoot you then run away
It's a good feeling a very good feeling a feeling
You know that I'll be back to chase my fucking money bitch
And if you don't have it this trigger is gonna itch and it's gonna go off and blow your head away
I promise you ladies and gentlemen, welcome to mr. Robber's neighborhood. We're happy to see him
He's just changed out of his sneaky clothes
Wherever he goes near or far. I still don't know what danishes are
What did you know so she goes to get the yeah the the French vanilla syrup right? Oh, yeah, here's the thing
Baristas your syrup things you got to wipe or what if you have like the removable spouts you wash the spouts, right?
Right if it's the pumps you still have to at least take it like a warm cloth at the end of the shift
Or the beginning to shift to make sure you wipe those puppies down, right? Yeah wipe them puppies
Mm-hmm. No, no, sir. Oh god. You saw the glomp just jizzes right in her own face. Just
Like a joke at a naked gun, she just assaults her own face with
Trying to make you a coffee man, she just wants you to have some coffee in a day
Can I have some flavoring?
Just and like literally was like I hate it's like literally with like syrup across her face goes like I hate these things
Mondays am I right?
And I was like been there girlfriend
How do you think I started interning for Penn and Teller I
Made them coffee. Can I tell you how I got these claw clackers? Let me tell you I
Used to pick up pastries with my bare hands when I was first working here
That was just a little too
Grotesque of a thing to do so I I went ahead and got myself some tongs and I used those
To pick up the bear claws and the pastries and the Danish and I was a fiend for the day
Even though I didn't know what was in the Danish that was part of the fun picking up the Danish that I couldn't tell what was inside
But I went ahead and ate it anyway
And then I rigged all your fucking things to explode you
I
Was wondering where the story was going but now it was worth the monologue
It was worth the fail they say he's a super criminal and I know I was the whole time
I was like this doesn't sound terribly criminal at all to me, but then the ending though it took a turn
It's all about the way like hide the syrup sheepishly showed me this container of cinnamon
She's like this is like cinnamon and I go it is cinnamon
It's like cinnamon. Yeah, she said it's like cinnamon and I was like like cinnamon
I was like, that'll be great. You go ahead and you go ahead and clean your face. I'll throw some cinnamon in here myself. I
Got it
I don't believe that I can a good conscience ask you to do anything else for me
I'm gonna see myself out. Please. Have a better day
I don't want to leave this establishment with you having 10 drink additives
Sorry splattered all over you because of my take that on my god
No, this is just outrageous that she leapt onto the wall and stuck to it. Just
You know who else thinks the walls when they jump at them
The following sponsor today's show man Mally's ice cream social. First of all, shout out to Froyo who wrote why is so syrupy?
Today shows brought to you by a vacation packages for nerds that's from Big Ben in 2021. That's vacation
packages for nerds
Hello there
I know you're all dying to go on some kind of a trip or a journey or a jaunt of some sort
Maybe go on to a balloon or a flying device
What I'm offering is a trip that you can take with your loved one or your sibling or what-have-you
And you could go to a place where they will love you and take you and embrace you. This is nerd
Vacations brought to you by nerds who know the way to do it. Of course nerd vacations are all at home
That's exactly what we're doing. We're gonna be at home and we're gonna play
Magically gathering that's it magic the gathering. Of course
everyone knows is a vacation unto itself taking you to the many varied lands all across in a stride and
Phyrexia and all places in between
You can only imagine the kinds of locales you will find yourself in when you are
mid battle with your cardboard warriors go ahead and place them onto the the forefront and
See how much mana you can deal damage to your opponent with and while you're there
Just imagine yourself in the fields of Ravnica floating away on an island on your all your own
Yes
That's that's my idea of a really great vacation or hey, how about this for a nerd vacation?
Why don't we plug in the old game system, huh? And let's go to a place. We all know it love
Vice City. Yes, let's all go to Vice City for a vacation where the toots are plentiful
And they can be beaten for the money
After you do it so much it sounds like a trap
This is definitely a trap
I'm not saying that that
Grand Theft Auto the video game is any kind of secret government sigh up
But I'm certainly not implying that the new Grand Theft Auto 6 is going to actually literally entrap people into
Virtual game world where they will be unable to escape
Where they will be actually shackled to the game for many many hours of their day playing it to earn real-world money
only to just spend that on
Food and water delivered to their home because they can't leave because they have to keep playing the game because they're gonna be the game
You say it's not gonna be that though no way no way
We're gonna be utilizing actual in live players
replacing
NPCs that would be uncatchable
No way as long as you're not gonna do that. I'm fine with it signed off. Don't check out you tricked us
You super nerd you tricked us good
Ha ha ha ha take a vacation bitch
So I was doing fair enough
Ended up, you know, I put myself on all these different
Websites trying to increase my corporate work for magic. Oh, did we ever get resolution on your?
Bachelorette gig did that they they canceled I was gonna do it and they canceled day. Well, there's the resolution they called off the wedding
They put up a picture like this is who I'm going to bring in front of us at 10 o'clock at night in this private
Suite and they say do you have do you have a cancellation fee? Yeah
Nice, so you made a little money
was it like I'm joining all of these sites to figure out my best practices and why I went through with this battery party was
to make sure I could create a performance agreement Chad GBT and
like basically ask my shame best practices and
And just yeah, I'm sorry. I'm not gonna hire an entertainment lawyer for my $300 gig
I get you on that one, but still
The AI zombies are coming for us all. Oh, they are. That's true. I'm terrified. That is true. Yeah, I don't disagree but
So same on a different website. I ended up
Just
Agreeing to do a birthday party in Redlands, California about three hours away from us
Same thing I was going back and forth the person signed up agreeing to do it. All right, and so I I
drive out last Saturday to a party in
the Redlands, California and a beautiful backyard for someone's birthday and
I'm doing a
Rope trick right and I say that my I have a magic wand and it's a giant bowie knife. It's an eight ten inch bowie knife
Make jokes about a game through TSA blah blah blah blah blah, and I always had it someone
right, you know and say
Do you believe in the power of this magic wand right and then I have them?
Turn two pieces of rope back into one pieces of rope mirror. Huh, right? Yeah, and I get up this
Person who's honestly I believe presenting mail. So I watch my pronouns
Okay, and they're also seem to be with someone who also seems
gender fluid in the back, okay, and
So I hand this person the knife and say do you believe in the power of a magic wand and she quietly?
Dead-eyes me and says I believe in the power of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh
Ridiculousness and I'll raise you
Say, you know, you know, it's funny about knowing how magic tricks work
It's I know yeah exactly I know how con artists work
I want to be like you are surrounding yourself with self-hatred. Do you understand this? There's a place
Where you are free to be whoever you want and that answers anywhere, but a church community
Let's just go let's just go have a nice life
Part get the car part of the whole religious thing like
The self-hating thing is a is a real deal. Yeah, it's it's it's legit
I mean, I can't you and your partner you guys help me load out and we will go I'll take you to the gayest area
We'll go get you we'll get you fixed up. Yeah. Yeah. This is gonna be the best night of all of our life
I promise you will see Jesus in the back of the Piranha Club. Yeah
He dances in there. Yeah. Yeah
His name is Jesus and he will blow your mind. It's and other things. Mm-hmm. I
Basically said fair. Do you feel like helping with this little magic trick?
Sure, I'd love to not have that conversation right now
Were they the celebrities my routine I have seven more to go who were they
Friends of just just just friends
Had to be friends of either the children of the person who's celebrating someone's 70th birthday. So they were an outside irritant. Yes. Yeah
yeah, gotcha and
then I go further in the show and I
I'm doing my arm chop routine and they write person up and I go and who are you?
The man I gonna and that and you know, everybody here she goes. I'm you know, I'm his I'm his daughter
Like sit like there's like a weird awkward. It's like I'm his daughter
Okay, and she's a nurse that gave plenty of good humor to the arm chop routine and then
Later on I get the couple right the the wife hired me for the 70th birthday party
And so I'm gonna do the wedding a wedding ring routine with them celebrate the birthday guy and his wife
Uh-huh, and I go how long have you guys been together and they're like, mmm ten years
I was like, oh
Now I know the awkwardness of the daughter thing. Yeah, got it. This is
Daddy picked up a new a new piece of ass here. Yeah
Daughter might not be incredibly thrilled about this is hotter wife. Number two is here
Yeah, or could it be the other way around? Could it be dad is new dad?
Or did she look just like her dad?
She was not old enough to be the mom of the she didn't say I'm Amanda's mom or anything like that. Oh
Yeah, what did she have a beard that gave away like she had the same facial hair as the dad
That's it
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, that's a key indicator. I mean, I guess Paul is just really holding me to the coals here
I don't know. I
Don't know is wait a minute. Wait a minute
The last time I saw a birthday magician all he did was asking appropriate questions about family lineage. That's right
This is like and his name was piff the magic dragon
That is if you put on a dragon suit you can get away with more
I want to end up following through with it
You know, I did I said have you ever hired entertainers before and she said I have we hired a comedian
It was not a good experience. Oh
Go like oh gosh
You know and that's it and making me and snare myself into saying like well I can make up for that guy
You know kind of was this this is before you started your show you as you were meeting them as the booking. Yeah the booking
Okay, so this is well, that's good, but you didn't just show up at their doorstep go
Hey, you ever hire anybody to do stuff like this before?
And was it okay and were they wearing pants cuz I'm not
Is a blowin nice and free
Uh
Comedian was
Chaotic runs writes in jet to be fair if a boy from Jersey thrust a boy knife at me
I think I'd believe in Jesus - fair enough fair fair enough
No, I did not ask who the comedian was cuz okay, there's no good either
I don't know them or I do and that's are you do I don't and then I have to what am I gonna call that person up?
You like absolutely Jason you suck, buddy
No, no upside I don't think to knowing who it was and it's out in California, so I imagine if some guy from LA is actually
okay, yeah
But yeah, so
Because of because of the reputation of a party magician. I was absolutely trying not to ask any questions
To not clarify anything just like great moving on
So, uh, do you have any kids you do and here all right, could you bring them out?
Did you did you leave me alone with them for a while? I I have some magic. I'd like to show them
Mary for 10. Well, then who's her mom?
Is she doesn't track
Get everybody up here. Everyone who's been married to my friend get up here everybody all the wives get them up any miscarriages in the audience
hands up
Anybody have a child die young anybody take it from this magician pregnancy is tricky
Whoa boy
I do it
Look in my head appropriate party magician. It's pretty good bit though. You're looking my hat
I've got my own form of IVF
I've vanished flowers
You can actually use that one Matt
Hold on let me get out a pen a pen with an invisible ink
Just send me just send me on our edit I'll add to my notes
IVF
Vanished flower gold gold
Under the gold column of my notes
So funny, let's see, uh, oh
Ultrasound that's the noise that I associate with applause
That's my ultrasound
applause
How about you guys give me some ultrasound right now?
Oh
wait, this is this party this party has been catered and
that means
Just like IVF
They're gonna feed us
It's a catered party, so they're gonna feed us
This is a this is a long way to go here, but let's see, okay, so I'm going to
Start my own
television mystery series and I'm gonna employ a famous TV author
who's gonna help he's written tons of screenplays and
He's gonna help me with
Getting this new project
Born, huh? Oh, his name is Stephen Jay birth canal
Yeah
All right. So what else happened?
I just thought you're gonna make a way worse joke and I'm just glad you didn't that's all
What TV producer were you thinking of Roger still, okay, so
Out to people, okay
Oh
Claire abortion I'll tell you one of the cool things that happen out here is for the second time
Tim jennison has left his
Ranch to come out and have have a meal with me. Oh, that's so nice. Great. Get out of here
Where where do you guys miss this podcast?
Where'd you go? So he picked me up and he says have you ever been to Rudy's?
And I said no this Rudy's is a very famous barbecue place. I'm gonna take you the original location. Ooh, and so we go
about 25 minutes out of town and
It it lives up to the hype. It is attached to a gas station
Yes, it is just built into the building. It is all bare bones
Like there's no air conditioning. There's just fans going on
Uh-huh. Yeah, you walk in and kind of like a cafeteria kind of lineup you order your sides first then your meats
Seconds and their plates are pieces of wax paper. They have you yes
Have just the brown paper. Yep
The guy with the science is handing out small samples of the cream corn to let you know how today's batch
Tastes. Oh, wow
And so we're eating cream corn and we get some some briskets ribs
There's chop brisket and barbecue
And turkey it was crazy and you all just sit at these like big picnic tables
you get a big bucket of soda and
I tell you just superior to a microwave hot dog. Just so good
That's a fancy new location
Jacob the original one is literally just attached to a gas station like you see gas pumps on the side
I can send a picture to oh, yeah. Sure. Yeah, let me see if I find the original. I love me some good burn ends. Oh
Yeah, yeah
And I mean getting you know that it you know when you go into those places
You just see like the the plywood walls people putting food on to a
Under a basket with some paper on it, but you know, what's gonna be the best thing after we did style switch
The last time I was in Austin with my brother and I got their burn ends and it's just
Really? Well done pork belly. It was just I yeah, I've regretted ordering
The brisket. I was like I should have just doubled up on the burn ends because it was so fucking good like perfection
they
Yeah, and then
In line he's about how rough to get ourselves a sausage these, you know, Texas barbecue place are always known for sausage
We'll get half a link. Yeah
And they go. Oh, that's good. I can't wait to have a barbecue when I go my my podcast partner
He grosses me out. He likes a like some microwave hot dog
And Tim Jenison says
Heats it up. Just fine
Yes, I am in good company with super genius Tim Jenison and then I said
He also does it with with bratwurst and Tim goes. Oh, no. No, no, that's terrible. You got a grill of bratwurst
I
Not an Aldi brat
It barely counts as a bratwurst agree you're right you're right
I believe Aldi brat is disqualified from the conversation. You and I both agree there. No problem. Yeah. Yeah, it is bratwurst asterisks
You know what? I'll take I'll take half support for my preposterous dining habits
That makes me happy
You know who else is happy to take half support and have support only
and that is the following sponsor today's show is brought to you by a
sweet relief
24-hour hotel and spa where you can always come in us. Oh god Jacques Scoop toe
From 2024 that's juxtaposed with 24 for sweet relief 24-hour hotel and spa
Hello
My name is
Mr. Bill Stevens and
Aaron this hotel
Called sweet relief
It was built by my father
Jerry Stevens
Here
In our house
You can come to my house
Built by Jerry Stevens and you can have a sweet relief
That's right the secret of our spa
Hotel is that every piece of art is
fuckable
That's right. I have made yes art
Okay
We have waist level paintings throughout the hotel
She don't even take it off the wall
No, no
They're there. They're all of all of our paintings are equipped with glory holes
They are all glory hole
paintings and
They're all themed
Now here is the trick. I'm sorry. I'm sorry before we go here. We go here. We go. We continue this negotiation
Always with the questions, huh? Are you are you French?
What do you mean?
I'm just curious about your accent. My father's name was Jerry Stevens. I am Bill Stevens
Does that sound French to you? It does not sir. It does not. Okay, then I would not think that
That needs any more
Explanation
You know, I I hear you saying that
But I I'm very curious about this accent, sir
Listen, here's the thing about
about the
This is the thing about in my place, okay
All of the artwork is a god. It's on a waist level. Okay, and
it's all got holes in it where there's mouths or butts and
That's what you can insert your stuff in now. I have not a lot let out of the ladies
Either I have another forgot about the the ladies what I have another forgot about the the ladies. No, I mean, I'm curious
Huh? I heard you. I'm curious. Well, how you plan to help the ladies? Oh
the lamps
And her hey scoops a check
Those are choking hazards, oh you don't put them in your mouth I
Mean you can you can all right? You can do anything you want that sweet relief. I don't care
My whole house because it's my house and it's filled with the calm of a thousand strangers. I
Don't I can't get I can't access the back of the paintings
They're built into the walls
This
Legal
That my home reasons they'll take over my home reeks of bleach and sour apples. It's just a bad scene
it's I
The walls weep you understand me. I
Have to take a moist towel to most of the walls every morning to take away some of the seepage
And it doesn't stop and keep sipping there's a girl who works at a coffee shop who's looking to get extra work
Do you think you can help her out? Oh
I love a barista
Bring her over
You should use socks says chaotic in chat
Oh too late I've it's in the drywall I
Really should just replace the drywall
Look, my only good thing is
That it's at waist level. So at some point I could cut it all away and put like, you know
What they call that design what they call the waist level?
beams
When they go on, you know at this point in the big you're asking for architectural specifics. Yes
Okay
Asking for a chair rail
That's exactly chair rail and runner board. Is that what it's called?
Sure, okay, great
Well, funny is I want to bring up something that Tim and I talked about but now I can't tell me this is episode
Next episode next episode. Well, I want to bring up something real quick
It's too late
Bad pirate scoop
Sent me an amazing an amazing gift from Australia. He is friends
With a creator
Called salt
Andrew salt marsh, I guess is the
creators actual name and he does this art by salt and
He made these really cool stickers and sent them to me. They're all
Crazy Star Trek themes. So this is a bat left in a piece of pie. This is a good day to pie
Or a good day for pie
This is a
doctor
Which I believe just says hey in
Klingon like hey, what is the doctor for our audio listeners? Which a doctor is a
Klingon dagger
Okay, it's a Klingon dagger with the word. Hey on it. Yep
This is a zombie hand giving the Vulcan salute and says live long on it
Which is that is you were just flipping off the camera
Yeah, and then this is a red shirt
What remains of a red shirt with a damaged calm badge and blood all over it clearly the victim and then I got a couple others
That are beautiful stickers. They are and I've already put them on a couple of them on
some notebooks I have that I'm gonna be using for the
the upcoming improv classes that I'm about to start teaching this month, which I'm really excited about and
I just wanted to say thank you bad pirate
for that gift and I am holding on to the letter and
The envelope because it might be the last piece of international parcel that I received for some time
Well, there you go, there you go, congratulations, where do you where you want us to support this person? Yes, I would say
Yeah, check out art by salt
Salt Andrew salt marsh is that individual? They're an Australian and
yeah, you can go check them out and
Yeah, that's it
Does really great work so I was talking to Tim and
We were getting it, you know, he's he's he's a total like audio nerd, right? Right. And so
We were talking about like the recording of sound and basically like I alright cuz he has like the Beatles microphone and stuff like that
Yes, right. Yeah. Yeah, he's got some real real interesting shit. Yeah, and he
And basically we just get into it. I was like I basically was like I was like I've had many people who understand audio
Explained to me how we actually record physical sound into an object which I still don't get no matter how many times people explained to me
What happens and he says it's even crazier than that is that there's like a French scientist one of the first known people to kind
of figure it out and
He was recording sound into like, you know, like like like cylinders
it wasn't it wasn't quite that was like it was a really like loose like metal material like similar I guess would be like
Tin foil now, but it was kind of like a very very weak probably pewter pewter, right something like that
Maybe I don't have to look it up, but a soft metal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and that's the song was also soft metal
No, but um, yeah
But the person's first known recording audio is by this French scientist
We gotta get a soft metal Jacob Alvarez. He just whispers
Jacob soft metal
Quieter quiet softer
That's better and but it's still just full volume music
The music is still just blasted take my hand
So
This is not a heavy enough of a story to carry the bit but
But so so he said the crazy way
How to record stuff I haven't gotten to the punchline yet. We've done too many bits in between
He was definitely the punchline is he was doing it before the phonograph
So before we had an ability to listen to what we were recording this guy figured out that we could record
Yes, I have heard about I have I've been told
Several times about how we we figured out how to record
Sound before we learned how to play it back and Tim couldn't believe that I found this to be hysterical
I was like wait, it's like everyone's singing and playing and then some some nerds going like see the wrinkles
It's here
Can we hear it no, no you can't
We don't have that kind of technology you fools keep playing though. It's making the coolest wrinkles. How long?
how long between learning to record and learning to playback I
Don't even know I don't you even like they discovered that because they discovered this guy's recordings later
They didn't know at the time
He had done it
So it was like it was like seriously centuries later where they found the recordings and then found a way to play them and sure enough
you heard the voice and music of like basically a popular song at the time in France, which is
Baffles me that baffles me so much digital sound makes so much more sense to me
then
being recorded into a
Piece of I don't know I can I can wrap my head around analog sound a little bit better because it is you know
It's just it's a needle
vibrating it's the actual vibration of of
Stuff and then
Well, I mean it's the vibration of the needle against the groove of the record then amplified through
The air which is what's the only when you get right down to it if we didn't have air
We wouldn't have any of this shit. Yeah, that is true
Take that you people take care for granted because it's all got to go through the air and the compression of air, right?
Yes, I mean, I think that's what that's yeah, he's getting all kinds of crazy shit. That's a that above my brain
Capabilities like he's vibrating air is above your brain
For it to be like centuries later for me to take a needle to it and go
Oh, there it is and then hear it like what sure I don't know there was about a 20-year gap between
Scott Scott Scott de Martinville
patented the oh
Boy, I don't even know how to say what that word is. It looks kind of like phonograph, but it is definitely not phone
It's pronounced autograph, maybe
graph
And it could transcribe sound waves as a visual line onto a piece of paper
but had no mechanism for playback Scott intended the recordings or
Phono autograms for visual study rather than listening to it
So he was trying to invent something that could record the the sound so that he could visually study
Oh, and then Edison invented the phonograph about 20 years later
Say was it called phono phono autograms?
Yes
Phone autograms is it phone autograms or phono autograms phone autograms?
Phone autograph was the machine and phone autograms were the things that the machine made phone autogram is a wonderful
Mr. Burns kind of line. He would know he would he would drop that
Yes, Smith is I recorded this onto the phone autogram. Yeah, exactly
I recall I I had a recording of this on phonogram when I was a boy
When I was but an adolescent is
That means 20 years that's like enough gap for the people to come back they're still living right think back
Hey, right. We're really dicks to you back at that early recording party you had and
Sorry, we haven't spoken in two decades since we ridiculed you but turns out you did and I have a recording of you ridiculing me
We just figured out how to listen to it the world's first DJ the world's first DJ the world's first record producer
Cuz that's what because we were talking about like basically that you had to play like such with such ferocity for the early
Oh, it had to be so loud. It had to be out and then we figured it out later how to do it soft
Like that's where you know, you're from from Bing Crosby to Sinatra to like that era of crooner
Like we can't empathize with how much of a baby maker that was we cannot
We can't go back in time to forget that we used to have to have such loud
Things to hear it and all this everything had to sound like this because we were kind of shouting half shouting half singing me
Am I baby? Yeah, and the very first time someone's like, you know, like the solitude
You're like, oh my god
That's fuck right now. Oh hard
Knocked my son into next Wednesday for sassing off so hot being so yeah
He made a wrong move at the corner of smart mouth and bullshit attitude
so I had to correct that behavior a
Wonder Bing's gonna be in Hollywood Squares at scoop fest. We'll have to find out who can say I don't know
I'm really excited now now for those of you don't know we're I'm going in but lined on this
So it's gonna be really really fun
I can't wait to just not know what
Impressions I'm supposed to do by the way scoop fest.com go check it out. Yeah. Yeah
End of September end of the month this month
Come on out to Las Vegas. It's gonna be awesome. It is
Did you invite Tim to scoop fest? I didn't
See now I actually mail specifically. I don't know Paul
I know what you're gonna say, but I did in fairness to Matt already send Tim an email specifically tell him to stay the fuck away from
scoop fest
All right, I guess we don't want him is only really for one hot dog microwave er in this town. That's right
After Matt told that story I just sent the email fun fact all you have to do to send Tim jenison an email is just
Write Tim in the send bar and and it gets to it
Who did I have laws dead? Laszlo might actually make it out to a scoop fest?
Dead Laszlo come on. We love last-minute scoop fest tickets. Yep. Oh
Yeah, come on out in the meantime we go play a little jock vs. Dirty
Time
Explosion
Hey gang long time listener first time caller
I made a scooper before you using questions that I pulled directly from a grade 4
Brain quest that I picked up at a thrift store for those of you who aren't old
Brain quest is a long skinny bundle of paper bound together with 1500 questions and answers
Grouped into categories that was used to learn things in the pre-internet era. Hope you enjoy that's Johnny
So Johnny made us a brain quest scooperty. Did you guys have brain quest? You guys know what that is?
That's familiar. Well, it sounds like a
Primarily Canadian thing since it was called grade 4
No, no
Canadian scoop crystal says I remember it first thing up in the chat. I'm telling you I remember
Oh, I'm sure they made an American version. Nope. Jacob Paul gets full credit. You get none. Sorry buddy. All right
Tough but fair. Hey the categories are before we get into the categories
Let's say happy birthday to didgeridoo scoop one of my best friends. It's his birthday. Yeah
Man, they buddy. Happy birthday didgeridoo
Ah early days of this show having didgeridoo scoop make didgeridoo covers
Famous songs. God damn the funny one of the best thing is that was ever done gold
It's that is a truly gold bit. That is really funny shit. Yeah
Talk about you
So good so good
It is right up there
Science math geography and grab bad if you insist
Matt you're up first. I will take math for 400, please
Which is it the better buy three shirts for 978 or 335 per shirt. Oh
Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's see here. I
Have to divide 78 by 3 here three goes into seven. That's two times
Yeah, nine said three shirts for 978, please
All right, three shirts for 978 less than that. It would be 10. Oh five the other way around. There you go
Oh, that was an example of the
dramatic
Pricing that's gonna be going on as you shop now at Walmart
I'm just gonna randomly check up everything that you buy. I'll go with grab bag, please
For 400 and the song what color is the Rose of Texas? That would be yellow
Yellow reading the question. I almost reflexively said what color is the yellow Rose of Texas hilarious?
It's me I'll try science San Antonio stands for is yellow rose and of course the
Arapahoe legend that the flower got its color from horses peeing on it. That's right
That is what puts the yellow in the yellow Rose of Texas the yellow Rose of Texas is colored like that cuz it's pee
That's right. That's how the song goes which two planets have no moons
I
Don't think mercury earth is one of them earth earth doesn't have any more moon is a myth
Yeah, if you're flat, you can't have basically a spaceship. Don't sign twisted. Yeah, that's right
Yeah, which two plants I think mercury is one and
Let me see Venus or Venus has a moon my guess Jacob and I'm not sure I
I do recall pretty recently one of the planets got
Re-evaluated and basically called the moon. So maybe that could work
Or not even called a moon called like a large body. Yeah, Pluto's like a large celestial body or writing. Yeah, so
what do you think I think it is mercury and
He gets shit
this is an old book, I
think it's mercury and
Neptune I don't know. Wait. No, it's an old. Oh, I see what you mean. Yes, of course. It's Pluto
It's gonna be mercury and Pluto. I'm thinking
Well, you know, I was wrong. So Pluto has moons. I don't know or
Yeah, or already not a planet by them though, maybe
Matt you're up. I will take
math for 800, please
The sum of 16 plus 5 plus 8 is the same as the product of 4 times 7 true or false
Let's see here 16 plus 5
that's 21 plus 8 is 29 and
4 times 7 is 28. So it's false
false is
Correct 29 is not the same as 28. I'm literally showing my math. Are you smarter than a fourth grader? I
Will try grab bag if you insist
Here we go
Long fellow wrote the song of Hiawatha. Is it a short story or a long poem? It is a long poem
It is a long poem
That's me I'll try math for 1200 Fanny. Well Hiawatha
And how well is mighty warriors of 24?
Let's see 24 divided by 8
Thanks
We're divided by oh wait, how do you do that?
Multiply 3 times 8
Right, oh that's right. Yeah, so that would be yeah, so
3/8 of
24 wait, I
Am just so confused right now. I don't know why you did
Make any sense at all
No divide 24 by 8. Yes, that's what I was doing
But then subtract 2
Or it would be 12. So it'd be 9
Yes
Well done boy, it is hard to do math and pull telling me things already confused
I will take math for tooth
2000, holy crap using pencil and paper divide $50 and 40 cents by 14
Matt do you have a pencil and paper handy?
You have a calculator because that would work too am I allowed to use the calculator probably not
Okay
Let's do this. Okay, so I'll try by multiplying 14. So times 2 is 28
which means times 4 is
56 so it's somewhere between 3 and 4
So if I say 3 point something something does that count for this this yeah to get us on with the game. Yeah
3.6. Okay. There you go. Yeah
Paul
grab bag, please
For 1200 name the main villain in the series of unfortunate events books uncle Olaf
No count Olaf
Count Olaf is correct. Save my butt. Oh
Is he their uncle I don't know I think he claims to be their uncle and they that's the whole thing but yeah
Oh, okay
I'll try grab bag 2000
What is a pistachio
Ooh, oh like is it a nut or a legume or a berry is it a berry? I bet it's a bear our I bet it's a berry
Because it grows on trees, right? So I think that I think that means it's a berry so I'm gonna say berry
That's a nut
Boo
Matt ah, boo. All right, come on
Guys, come on
science science for 800
Now for 3200 oh yikes I was doing so well
You were which creates the fastest wind on earth a hurricane a cyclone or a tornado
Oh, this is tough. Okay. Their tornadoes are tiny
But they're tinier, but I don't know if that means their winds are less
Force frame more. Well, I think technically a hurricane and a tornado are the same thing
It's just one forms over water. Nope. No, I quote cyclone and hurricane are the same thing
Tornado and a water spout are the same thing right because a water spout is a tornado over the water hurricane and cyclone are the are the different
coasts
For us, I believe so, right? It's and it's the rotation the way they're spinning, right?
Hurricanes in the Atlantic and cyclones are in the Pacific. I think so. That's vaguely what I know
So if her kids are suckers the same thing it has to be one thing so I'm gonna go with tornado
All right
It is a tornado juice look at you with the big brain
I may or may not be currently helping a fourth grader with homework all the time. So maybe gives me an advantage
But I'll try science for 1200 name the only planet that orbits the Sun on its side. Oh
What but
What does that mean I
It means that other planets are not on its side and one of them is oh
Wait what
There's some planets because you have like you have the magnetic poles
So I think that's what it's referring to is it referring to the axe the tilting of the planet
Or is it referring to what side of the Sun it rotates around?
No, because it rotates around the Sun it doesn't just rotate on one side I have to pass I have no idea
Passes to me. I'm pretty sure it's Uranus
It is Wow
It's just like it's it's tilted way over on its axis interesting
Okay, I think it's I think I think it's part of why Uranus has such an odd orbit
Also, the planet goes around the Sun in a weird pattern. Okay
Because of that because of its rotation, right and tilt on its axis interesting. Okay science for 2000
All tropical fish live in salt water true or false. Oh, this is this is a tricky. Oh
false
It is false something's live in freshwater. There you go. There you go
Matt you got geography that we have all avoided for four eight twelve and two thousand
Give the word for the farthest edge of a settled territory
Over yonder
That's the ball border Oh
Frontier ass
Nope frontier
Paul
Can I try the 2000 just to try and win? Yeah, I don't even know if I can win you can't
Shows the location of a city that is not a capital
Go ahead Paul what map symbol Paul actually go ahead and just name a map symbol dots
Letters
I mean it's been an arrow that says city been a minute since I used a
Map
And it's not a capital. Oh
You remember the old bit that was in like every third movie where you'd have a couple of people lost in a car somewhere
And one of them would just pull out the biggest map in the world
I would just keep unraveling the whole front seat wasn't that a good in Dumb and Dumber where they had to keep flapping open the
Or not dumb. Yeah Dumb and Dumber. I think it was I don't know
I'll have to pass because I really am at a loss. That's to me. I just I certainly don't know I'm at
the location of a city that is not a capital it's just a dot
microphone
It's just a black dot. I believe I said dots
You want to try black dot? Yeah
All right a black dot and fuck me
That was the first thing I said shit ass
That's me I'll try geography for 800
Put an order from east to west Texas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Alabama
Alabama is the farthest east then Mississippi then Louisiana then Texas
Alabama Mississippi, Louisiana, Texas well done
Matt I'll take geography for 1,200 Jacob
Which is the world's largest body of fresh water Lake Superior or Lake, Victoria
Well, I have to guess here cuz I've won the game. Yes
Yeah, you win no matter what I guess although if I pass who does it who's the pass to?
Passes to Paul. Oh good. Then Paul can try to beat you for second place if I pass can I that's true
Mm-hmm. I think yes, you can I'm 800 points ahead of you Paul. All right for game a $1,200 question for gamesmanship. I pass
Paul I'll go Lake Victoria
It's Lake Superior in Africa is second-largest Paul is wrong and that is the game
Matt wins with 8400. I am in second with 2800 over Paul's best efforts
He only got 800 points not my best efforts and that is from Johnny. Thank You Johnny
If you want to Johnny Cooper tea, I've said as a price of striped Jack
It's an obelisk jock versus nerds and it's all the things over at hey scoops comm go right there
You can send some scoop mail over there as well right there on the home page. There are links for all those things
There's also a link right there to buy some tickets for scoop fest. It's gonna be awesome
And it's gonna should be there change there are less than three weeks away. It's happening
fest
Let's do it
Let the panic attacks ensue Oh in four weeks, I'm gonna be so relaxed. Yes
In a month, I'm just gonna be so relaxed. Exactly. Exactly. I want to thank all the people support us over on our patreon page
Did you send lists or we don't have lists yet? We don't have lists yet. Ah
Well, normally we'd be going to our list here to thank the people individually who support us at a particular level
So if that's right haven't checked it out go over to preaching fun and select a level that fits your budget today
Or if you like me are a little shocked that we didn't talk at all about the new Nebraska
Re-release album that Springsteen is doing head on over to fartsinabag.biz
That's fartsinabag.biz that along with preaching fun calm it takes you over to our patreon page
We're for as little as three dollars a month
You can help keep this show on the air if you like what you hear if you think it's worth more than zero dollars
Head on over to preaching fun comm head on over to fartsinabag.biz
Go to either one of them or go to both of them and make two accounts
That'd be fine with me too. You can do all those things go over there. Keep this show running. It gives us
Money to just keep the show going. I don't know how else to put that
Let's do the show
Yeah, pay for websites
About to pay the Orleans a lot of money we are
Matt the Nebraska the the new gift pack of it
It comes with a blu-ray concert that he did at the count Basie theater in Red Bank. Oh
Well, that's great
Yeah, I'm in
You're gonna go for the deluxe edition
Jersey, right? Yeah, I'll go for the deluxe edition
Yeah, I've got the they've got a CD and a vinyl edition. Both of them have the the blu-ray there
All right. Well, thanks for everybody. Stay safe out there. We love you and we'll see you soon
Oh
Baby metal baby metal I've seen in concert several times. They're really really good. Thank you. Yeah
I think we should cement by the way
See you soon and then see you at the cone to the music on the pickup is good. I
Like we do live podcast people to sing along and I think that's the way to do it
All right
Well, we'll see ya