All right, before we get started, I'm going to thank the people who have recently joined me on my tour co-tier.
These people are very integral to this podcast as well as my touring life.
Big thanks to Steve Neruda, Bob Baker, Galactic President Scooper star McScoopsalot,
Sebastian Robbins, BB Hermit, Colton Satmary, Jobeth R. Bowers, Adam Mancini, Michael, Brandon Allen,
Mike Mayhem, Jesse Miller, Jason Yager, Robert Sherman, Matt Klawacki, Russell Martin,
Nate Walk, Jeff Loomis, Smitty Scoop, Lee Popsicle, Greg Chapman's History of Magic,
Gray Whitaker, Ben Sherman, Wendy Bumgardner, and Jonathan. Thank you so much. Enjoy the podcast.
Hey, I'm Matt. I'm R.J. That's Ready Rich. Hello. And this is Fool Us! Behind the Scenes Season 11
Episode 13. Brought to you by Gershman's Magic Shop and Deli. I just figured out Zoom.
I'm in San Antonio. R.J.'s in Las Vegas. I ended up hitting a bizarre traffic thing as someone who's
out of town. It took me 12 minutes to leave downtown San Antonio and 42 minutes to get back.
So, R.J. stepped up and was hosting the Zoom. R.J.? They were doing you a favor.
Keep me out of town. Keep me out of downtown. Give you some time to think about it. Reconsider.
Don't ever leave here ever again. All right. So, we're going to get off right here. And I wrote a
special intro for Brooke that was meant to be Barbara Walters' nightmare. A lot of waskily wabbit
words in that. And she crushed it. She nailed it. Moving on. All right. Our first magician is
Michael Farrow from Canada. Candice on Michael Farrow. I love his shuffle.
Ready Rich, take us through Michael's routine. Michael the refrigerator Farrow.
It's called the stack time prediction. Penn and Teller each select several items out of a fridge.
Teller picks a color from the rainbow and Penn spells a word on the fridge with magnets.
Michael has the crew roll video to reveal his prediction in it. He pulls the same items out
of his home refrigerator, puts them on a tablecloth with Teller's color and reveals Penn's word on his
fridge. Yeah. Now, there is a trope that says that all Canadians are just super sweet and nice and
you know, and he proves it. He's just such, it's him and the other Canadian guy.
They're just, they're so nice that you kind of have to like them, you know. When this trick was
pulled off and Penn and Teller went back to their seats, the first thing Penn said to us,
well, there's only one way to do that. Yep. There's only one way to do that. And sadly,
the thing that gave it away was not Penn's bust was when he sat down. Had he not sat down at the
table, no one would have been the wiser. You think so? When he sat down at the table, he was in a
trailer. Yes. And you're like that you're not at your home, right? Unless you live in a trailer
and not many people live in trailers in Canada because they have free healthcare.
The trailer, I think I can talk about this. I mean, I don't know. It feels silly to talk
about this, not talking about the method openly, but. Well, I can say it and you can read that.
All right. Yeah. You don't know the method. So you can, you can tell. He's got a twin brother.
Without confirming or denying RJ's speculation. Yes. It was a prediction sealed inside of Winnebago.
Yes. But just what the title of the trick should have been. Yeah. That Winnebago was on, was near
Fool Us. And so we had to worry about where Ben and Teller were coming to work and leaving work
and if they were leaving for lunch and all this other stuff because they weren't able to notice
what weird as Winnebago next to the production truck. If the real all suites hotel only had RV
parking. If only. If only. We should have, we move it to Circus Circus next season. We'll be,
we'll be good to go. There we go. It's a fun trick. It's a really fun thing to pull off.
It kind of is, it's interesting because like from the time we, what's fascinating is from the time
we taped this to the time it aired, how far AI has come. Oh yeah. You know, and like, you know,
there were some pretty cool AI apps sold to magicians out there where you could live predict
stuff on a pre-recorded piece of video and that kind of things like that. They were getting pretty
sophisticated and now AI has gotten much more sophisticated than those apps and those tricks.
And so what was curious about this airing was simply that like, I believe a lay person could
just be watch this and just think AI and be bored. Yeah. But it was not the case. But it just goes to
show you like, I think like a little bit of the impossibility. We've reached, we've reached a weird,
a weird, maybe uncounted values, the wrong term here. We've reached a weird spot in lay person's
brains for watching predictions that like at some point really know. Like I was just talking to
another magician who's doing a variation on West Isley's coin flip. And so he found that with the
coin flip, this magician's opinion was simply that like having someone picked out of the audience
and things like that, and having so many details at the end of West Isley's coin flip, if anyone's
familiar, you flip a coin heads and tails, the audience chooses it and the audience slowly
self-selects down to one person. And one person is one, the coin toss competition and lo and behold,
there's a prediction with what that person is wearing or even a drawing of them or something
on those lines where they're selected. And I have a friend who decided to hand out a deck of cards
to everybody in the room. And then the coin flip went down to a particular card. There's one person
left. That person took their card out of their pocket and it was the card was accurate. Yeah.
I was saying that like, I love it, even though it makes it slightly less impossible than having a
person completely dead to rights. It is actually much cooler to me that the trick happens just
simply in the room. Yeah. And I was like saying how much I really liked that adjustment because
I really liked the idea that it just happened to be a, you're forcing a coincidence and not
something totally impossible, which is knowing exactly who the exact person was. Right. I would
have liked to have seen a miss in this. There's a lot of things that I, the two E's I should have
been swapped. Oh yeah. Yeah. Or just simply have all capital E's or something like that. Yeah.
Yeah. But he couldn't do all capital E's because there's only uppercase and lowercase. Yeah. But
then also there were too many items that just went on and on and on. Yes. You know, if it's three
items, because the items were just like logically pursued, they didn't build an impossibility,
right? They just, they just kind of like, and what else is in the fridge, you know?
Right. Yeah. Yeah. On the AI thing, there was that video with the infinite stairs,
like not even 10 years ago, right? There was a viral video with the stairs at the university.
You remember what I'm talking about? I don't. With the people going up the stairs and they
were on the same floor. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I remember that. Yeah. It's the same method as
this trick. Right. Right. Right. But it really fooled people, even a lot of magicians. That's
true. It wasn't set up as a magic trick. It was set up as like a magic spot. Yeah. Right. Time warp.
I do know what you're talking about. Yeah. Yeah. And that would just not register as anything
with anybody. Right. Yeah. I mean, that's, that's, that's the, that's the difficult thing.
Proprietary knowledge is certainly a magician's friend, right? And in this case, you know,
very proprietary. And, you know, there's only so many ways you can take advantage of it where the
audience just isn't going to catch up eventually. Right. And this is, you know, I think when you
try to come up with magic tricks, you're like, what's impossible, right? So you're always trying
to come up with the most impossible thing. And then the only guiding principles you have are like,
don't run when you're not being chased. And the two perfect principle. Right. And the other one,
packs flat plays big, which is completely broken.
Does pack though. It does pack. Hard to ship that Winnebago.
That's not a portable refrigerator. I guess technically it was a portable refrigerator.
I've said before, my mother in law was, her mother was in a vaudeville trio. She has a 66 key piano
on iron castor wheels in her living room. And that was considered a portable piano in vaudeville days.
So yes, that is a portable refrigerator.
Havin B3 was commonly chopped to be portable, but still at 418 pounds.
They just took the legs and the pedals off.
All right. We've had our people on Patreon join us today.
Does anybody have any thoughts on Michael Farah?
I felt that there was too much clue.
Too much clue in the trick itself and the performance itself?
No, too much clue from Penn. Oh, yeah, yeah.
He did two digs at the clue and only needed the first one.
Interesting. Okay. That's fair. I think that is fair
because even as someone here in the chat, Ron says he understood.
He had a different theory and then Penn's bust made him go like, ah, so there you go.
And if Ron got it, then everyone gets it because Ron's dumb.
Is that what I just sounded like? Thanks, man.
That was not what I was going for, but I thought that's what I sounded like.
So I had to call myself out.
All right. Moving on, we have Julio Moreno.
Julio, a former fooler and on Wikipedia, described as a fooler in this episode, but not a fooler.
But take us to Julio's trick. He was a fooler in the past.
That's probably the mistake there. Yeah.
This is Spongeball Synchronicity. Teller picks a card.
Julio puts it in the deck.
On fanning the deck, a Spongeball rises and pushes out Teller's card.
Julio repeats this several times before ditching the deck and moving to phase two,
where the Spongeball multiplies and invisibly transposes between his hands,
following the action of Teller's now-torn card.
In the final phase, the four Spongeballs heal into one large ball as the card is reassembled.
Then the healed Spongeball restores the torn card.
I am impressed by Julio's ability to do what he does with those little tiny sausage fingers that he has.
They got one overhead shot of the table in his hands, and I'm like,
he's got snossages for fingers. How is he hiding anything?
And they did them dirty, real dirty, at one of the angles.
They did, yeah.
Yeah, the first transposition.
Yeah, the first transposition of the Spongeball when the torn card was in four pieces on the table.
Really shot to some bizarre angle that I've never seen, just to expose the transfer
and then go back to the scene. I was like, did he piss off Dennis in rehearsal?
That's got to be, that's got to be, I didn't even think of that,
that if you piss off Dennis in rehearsal, he could do anything he wants to your edit.
Yeah, no, exactly.
Oh shit.
No, no, and Dennis really takes a lot of shit, so you can, you could conceivably convince yourself
that you could say whatever you want to Dennis and it won't affect him, but who knows?
No.
The ease of which he does Spongeball routines, I know everybody else that rolls up the sleeves
and does everything else, but the light touch as he packs four balls into Penn's hands and lets go.
Right.
Like he, like he barely touches the hand. It is so effortless.
But also his, his retention and swapping of the balls is imperceptible on video watching it.
Yes.
I mean, he's just, it's, and when he's, when he's doing the false transfer, not false transfer,
I guess it is the reverse false transfer where he, where he's, he's keep pulling a ball back,
but popping one out of the other hand to make it look like that's the ball he just set down.
Yeah.
Is so perfect, just perfect.
And this routine name, the, the writing of this routine is so strong.
It is like, it is everything you want in it. It is built in a proper order.
You know, there's a couple of just really nice writing moments where,
where you just, you know, burn, burn an idea before moving on.
Right.
Like I really, if you're, if you're, if you're going to sit down and be like,
I do sponge balls, but the guy wants me to card tricks, you have like, watch this.
This guy wrote a perfect routine of transferring.
Right. Exactly.
Card tricks. It's really playful, really fun.
He's so charming.
Yeah. Yeah. And it just was, it was a really fun routine.
I was thinking you were probably going to tell the story on the classic force on Teller.
Oh, I, I, I didn't note it. So he did, he did a classic force on Teller.
Yeah. And his response to it is like, what the fuck are you doing, man?
Can you believe the balls on this motherfucker? That's the face that he makes.
The spud balls on this motherfucker.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's pretty great.
I thought it probably would have been better to have a
volunteer from the audience just for that moment.
Right. Yeah.
Or even Brooke.
To have somebody to go to. I don't know that I even do it on
Brooke at this point, because this is second or third season, right?
Yeah. Yeah. The first time he fooled, I remember the first time he was just doing
sponge ball stuff. And it's funny what he wrote in his routine being like, you know,
sponge balls are children, you know, starter magic or whatever.
I remember watching him go like, I guess that's pretty cool or whatever.
And close turning to me and being like, he's going to fool them.
Then I was like, what? With sponge ball?
So he is, I enjoyed his comfort and improvement and confidence and performance in his second.
Yeah.
I think he came back a much more stronger, charming, polished performer.
Absolutely.
I really liked the line in the package. I want to be the best Julio of Julio's.
Anyone in the gallery here? I have any thoughts on Julio?
You don't have to flip me the bird, Fred King. You can just say no comment.
You don't have to give me the middle finger to your camera.
He didn't, he didn't. I'm just
Fred King, Fred King.
I'm driving down from Reno on that lovely stretch of 395 between Bishop and Mojave.
And I was so afraid I was going to keep dropping out. Can you hear me okay?
We can. 10-4, good buddy.
I'm to drop a few names. I'm going to spend the night at your friend,
Sean McMaster's house.
I love Sean's.
We all do. And he's having George Tovar and Jonathan Lovett and Tony Clark over.
And we're going to talk magic all night. So I'm very excited about that.
Listen, wear a wire and we'll put the conversation up on the abracadabra feed. All right?
And watch your water on Tony Clark.
Very funny. I'll see what I can do.
I heard you want to be careful for bears in the air. Come on.
Hey, good buddy.
I've never seen more CHP cars on this stretch south from Reno than I have today.
So I'm being very careful.
You're on the meth super highway.
Yeah. They're just going to be checking your colon for combos filled with drugs.
So you're fine.
Or are you, Fred?
Look at me. Do I look like a drug runner?
They all say when they get pulled over.
No, Fred. No, you don't.
Just to finish out the bit.
All right. Safe driving, pal. And thanks for checking in.
Good buddy.
All right. Next up, we have Topaz.
Ready, Rich. Take us through Topaz's routine.
Called this the backstage prediction. I don't remember why.
Penn names a musician. Topaz pulls a lanyard cord from his pocket.
He keeps pulling several feet until it stops.
He reaches into his opposite pant cuff to free the other end
and pulls from there until the first end is gone and catches elsewhere.
He reaches into his sleeve to free that end from there.
Quickly releases it, whereupon it snaps to the opposite sleeve.
After pulling it all the way from this location,
the other end finally clears, revealing the backstage pass sleeve.
The pass bears the name that Penn said.
I will say that it was great to see Professor Cheers.
I still have my rig that I built for it.
Because one of the biggest issues with that is that if you do it with rope,
like it's supposed to be done, your rope gets tangled
and you end up with a wad of knots stuck usually in your crotch.
And it's awful.
That was awful.
It was nice to see it done.
That's you.
It was nice to see it done differently and with the lanyard ribbon was great.
I just, I want Topaz to be genuine and real just once on stage.
Oh, no.
I'm just sick and tired of happy, goofy, go lucky magician guy.
It's just like, come on, just be real out there.
Nobody's that happy.
Not even the fucking Canadians.
Well, yeah, I mean, I totally, I mean, I respectfully disagree on a big time.
I, you know, I think this is Topaz's third appearance on the show.
The other two times were via, you know, basically remote video, right?
First time was our first COVID season.
Does a drink prediction.
That was when we're like language barriers and first time doing, you know, remote feedback.
Topaz pushed back and then Penn laid out the exact product that Topaz used and edited that out.
Second time he did like a really cool illusion with like a treadmill and weights.
The one in the gym, yeah.
And between that time and this appearance, I did the Foolers Tour.
And on the Foolers Tour, Alex Ramon loves Topaz.
And on the Foolers Tour, we did what you think we did,
which is stay up to three o'clock in the morning playing YouTube clips of magicians we liked.
In the bus.
Nerds.
Exactly.
I'm sorry.
The crew smoked weed and played video games and the magician stayed sober
and stayed up to three o'clock in the morning playing magic clips for each other.
Hilarious.
And we did a deep dive on Topaz and I just loved so much of his stuff.
I just loved it.
And then I looked back and I was like, oh,
I think we've been unfair to him on this podcast a little bit.
Now, you've I've instigated the unfairness.
I just and I'll stand by what I say.
So that's fine.
It's totally fine.
I don't think we have to be in agreement.
It's like Yellow Suit Magician Guy.
Remember Yellow Suit Magician Guy?
The maniac?
You guess.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It's just he's in the same.
Nobody's that happy.
I love his like, you know, making blank your own.
Like, this is a very much a great example of making a rope magic routine.
And adding something to it.
And not to mention the prediction at the end was pretty, pretty goddamn stunning.
This is where, again, I know the work on this.
And I'm not going to say it, obviously.
I'm telling you, I could tell you all right now and none of you will do it.
Well, you get that from from Penn's bus when he said
when they told us how it was done, we were like, you motherfucker.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, you know, this season, one subplot of this season
is that he works with Yana Felicitas and Nicolás Trebel.
They call him a mentor.
When you talk to him, he says he is not a mentor, that they are a three person team.
He's very humble about it.
There's an interview on this feed of me interviewing Topaz shortly after this appearance
where we hint at the fooling, but don't don't say it, but get into stuff.
And then, you know, for him to have done very
like kind of more classically impossible tricks,
but maybe something that wouldn't necessarily fool Penn and Teller
to come in and do something really for Topaz to really play the game.
Yeah, and that's what it was.
And he was so psyched to finally be there in person.
They really he went over the brainstorming process for the trick
and it was really fun and fascinating.
And when he finished, I stayed with him.
And, you know, the subplot of this is always that I piss off the crew
when I stay with the magician because they know if I'm hanging out there,
it's because I know that Penn or Teller want to meet him, right?
Right.
So I'm going like there's no way Teller is going to not
want to come right out and talk to Topaz.
Yeah, because they're the same height.
And Teller loves people the same size as him.
That in costumes, that in costumes.
Give him something funny to wear and give him a midget next to him, he's perfect.
So they are getting wise to me,
ushered Topaz into the basement again, into the waiting area again,
to not slow down recording.
That's funny.
And so I go like, well, I'm coming with you.
And I'm basically like, I'm like, let me give you your schedule.
There's no way Teller is not going to want to meet you.
So we got to figure out how to make this happen.
I'm going to try to do it.
And in it, Topaz was so emotional.
He was really, really overwhelmed with emotion
from the whole experience of being on the stage and fooling the guys.
And he just had this beautiful speech to just me
about how important Penn and Teller are.
And he just was like, you don't understand.
Those guys are artists.
They're not just magicians.
He's like, people care what they think.
Even when you're not talking about magic,
people want to know what Penn and Teller think about things.
They want the right things about the world.
It's like, those are true artists up there,
not just magicians and to have that moment with them.
And he just was so emotional and it was so beautiful.
And I was like, oh, my God, I got to get you to Teller or whatever.
Right.
But I couldn't believe I shared that moment with him.
And so that was a really cool moment for me.
And then I did help facilitate Topaz and Teller getting together later on.
And then totally used that chip to interview him on the podcast,
which I did.
So please enjoy the interview I did with Topaz on our feed.
It's fun to go back and let's do it again.
Just knowing I was interviewing him like a week after he fooled the boys.
That's great.
But I, on that nerdy deep dive on the bus, I just love his originality, man.
He is definitely original.
He just really comes up with different original stuff, you know.
And I know he did recently like a one that was all like on headphones thing.
So that was the thing about Live is that we had a guy had everything on headphones
and then Topaz had a show and everyone had headphones.
And there's a third person who had a headphone,
everything on the headphones, you know, show.
I heard mixed reviews of all of them.
So I couldn't hear anything.
But but but just another sign of like his ambition.
Yeah.
All right.
Jim, is that your hand raised?
Yes.
Go for it.
OK, just want to say, you know, give credit to Topaz.
The prediction was pretty brilliant.
Having it folded up, having it in the protector, you know,
that just adds so many levels that make it seem impossible.
So brilliant payoff.
But I felt the setup just he dragged it out for way, way too long.
And it ended up killing the impact.
I mean, I'm assuming that had something to do with the method he needed that time.
And I get how a fool, but for me, if he was doing that in like a live stage show,
I definitely think he'd want to find some method to speed it up a bit
so the audience doesn't lose interest.
Well, in a stage show, I mean, like I said,
I think he's doing this to play the game.
I think he's doing this to play the foolish game properly and to go for foolish trophy.
Because there are so many ways where you don't need that kind of timing,
that kind of dancing, that kind of misdirection to get it right to a thing.
Right.
I think in this case specifically, it's just about fooling the guys
and the guys know methods A through E, right?
But methods A through E will work in a stage show in a way that would fool most people.
Yeah.
And I do give him credit for coming up with such a clever method.
Just I don't see it having much applicability outside of the show.
I don't think he does either.
Look, look, Topaz is not short on material.
He's just short in real life.
Well, you don't want to insult him, you might make him a sauerkraut.
I had him on this feed.
We can't.
What's up, RJ?
You're 6'5".
Everyone's short to you.
I know.
You should see me in heels and hair.
Oh, please.
Let's do that.
Thank you, Jim.
Sauerkraut joke and all.
Thank you.
Thank you for having me on.
Anybody else have thoughts on Topaz?
Anyone besides me want to defend him from this mockery?
Okay, let me just try to explain my mockery.
I find that his use of clowning, which he uses a lot in his stage show, is off-putting.
Okay.
It's a little juvenile.
Like anything with style, it's a style with good points.
It's a choice.
Right.
So I'm not going to argue that his style shouldn't turn you off, right?
Thank God.
And when you talk to him, he's actually quite humble about who he is in his career
and everything like that.
And so I think he is the artist he's going to be, and that's part of who it is.
All right.
Look, I love the looks on Pentel's faces when it started.
I like the looks on the faces in the middle, and I like the looks on the faces at the end.
Yeah.
There are certain foolish tricks that it's fun when Pentanteller kind of let their guard down,
to be like, "What is this?"
And then all of a sudden, the end makes them go like, "Damn it."
I also, I thought, "Ready, would you point this out?"
I think there's a red herring on the handling of the prediction at the very end.
The flip?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it was too.
He does a full hand up to the faces at one point.
At one point, the whole prediction is hidden behind his hand,
and it's held flat like a card trick.
And that's a red herring.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, that's not the method.
So I was like, "Oh, I thought it hurt it a little bit."
But in the vein of playing the game, he played it well.
That's it.
I think this whole trick was simply playing the game.
I don't think Tobias is trying to take this as a building block for something down the road.
Right.
Although it might.
I'll just say, it's only a method that maybe I would do.
No other magician would do it.
Okay, I'm interested now.
All right, let's see.
Next up, we have Toby Rudolph.
I feel like we have to score the fourth acts in their own category.
You mean filler?
Yeah, I find Toby Rudolph to be a higher ranking among the fourth acts on this show.
Okay, I'll give you that.
But still...
Yes, when watching it, I thought, "We'll see him fourth in an episode."
He breaks one of my cardinal rules, which is telling the audience,
"And what I'm going to do next is, and what I'm going to do next is,
and then I'm going to do this."
And just fucking do it.
We don't need that explanation.
Oh, I forgot with Michael Farrow.
He broke my rule, which we talked about in the previous episode,
where he is struck by the writing on the pizza box.
Like, "Oh, the video."
Like, "You're the one who brought all the props, Michael."
Yeah, you put it in the freezer, fuckface.
Reddy, tell us about this trick.
This is the classic Bill to Tomato.
A volunteer brings up a bill.
Toby tears off a quarter, gives it to her as a receipt.
Penn writes down the serial number.
Toby has a volunteer select a fruit from several.
He burns the bill to ash, then slices the selected fruit to reveal
the bill rolled up inside.
The serial number and receipt match.
All right.
Classic Bill to Lemon.
His handling was adequate, a little fumble at the beginning.
I found him to have American-like charm for a foreign performer.
So no charm whatsoever.
And I was curious how everybody think
you felt about the snip instead of the tear.
For me, it provides a cleaner transition when he restores it,
because you can add a sharpie line to it and make it look like
it's an actual, you know, it actually healed itself.
That's the only thing that was there for it.
Yeah.
And who knows, maybe he is, where is he from?
I don't remember.
I mean, he didn't sound like he could tear a paper.
So maybe he couldn't tear the bill.
Right.
I think, yes, I think it's common.
Other currencies are harder to tear.
Correct.
Some of them are impossible to tear.
Yeah.
So this might come from that.
I was just like, oh, we do the tear because it makes the matchup look impossible.
But the cleanness, the cleanness is also pretty hard to.
And I think at the end, when you've got that sharpie line.
Yeah.
There that shows a healing point.
It's kind of a convincer for me.
It's kind of like, oh, that's that that actually works.
Yeah, I was like, I was surprised when I saw the snip.
I was like, oh, not a tear.
And I was like, oh, the snip is actually kind of beautiful.
It's like it's right from a distance, right?
Let's just see a clean snip than a sloppy tear.
Right.
I hope I remember to call this episode Clean Snip Versus Sloppy Tear.
Which is how I describe sex.
And Matt's out of frame.
Anything else on Toby?
Was there an edit between I don't want to touch it and immediately touching it?
Probably, yeah.
Or was that in the script that way?
No, it wasn't in the script that way.
But yeah, tomatoes are gross.
Yeah, they're the devil's fruit.
Yeah.
No, there was I don't want to touch it for a convincer.
Oh, yes.
You're handling this, I'm not.
And then he immediately handles it.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
I think there was an edit.
Yes, I think there's an edit there.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I'll agree.
I'll agree with Penn and Teller.
She was one of the best audience participants they've had in a long time.
Yeah, she was great.
I bet you they kind of wanted her for if this was shot in chronological order.
Right.
And that was she would have been the perfect person for that final trick.
Yeah, I like the one that Matt had and the one that they had for red darning needle.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's really just a fruit choice that got him on air, right?
It's the fact that he gave her a round of things that could be loaded into.
I think it was a suit.
Next up, we have Penn and Teller performing an eye chart routine.
Ready, Rich?
Take us-- Volunteer takes an eye test to prove she has good eyesight.
They bring out a EULA for her to pick a word from.
It's too small to read, so she uses Teller's eye loop.
The word she picked is rolled out behind her on all over a giant poster.
They go back to the eye chart.
It's doped up with nothing but her word.
Yeah.
I call this views la force, Christy.
RJ, have your hand raised?
I do have a question.
Yes.
Was Vinnie Grasso involved in any part of this?
[LAUGHTER]
Yes.
OK.
[LAUGHTER]
Duh.
Some listeners at Penn Sunday School might listen to Penn Revel the fact that they
ripped Vinnie apart on his last fullest appearance and then used his method in a trick.
Yep.
I saw it coming, literally.
And then I was like, but I-- who's their prop builder again?
Nate.
Boy, Nate.
Yes.
You should sell that one.
It's beautiful.
That's a good one.
I mean, I've used that method in the wedding band one.
Yeah.
Where you pop off your ring and then use that.
Yeah, exactly.
The LED light's inside, so it's brighter.
So you read it.
That is such a clean gimmick that if Nate was able to--
Yeah.
That's a good prop.
Not that Vinnie's isn't.
That is a good prop.
Yeah.
Well, both serve great purposes.
I think the catch on the Penn and Teller one, which is funny because at rehearsals,
is that Penn and Teller both have terrible eyesight.
Yes.
So we kept getting approved.
They kept getting the terms and conditions approved and then we'd run a rehearsal
and everyone who came up on stage could read without the eyepiece.
Oh, God.
That's not how it should be.
So there are several rehearsals where we're like, even smaller, Nate.
Even smaller, Nate.
He can.
It also said authenticate all over that eye chart, like up and down.
Yeah.
And I saw the Trower runs and Penn pointed out a lot.
He pointed out less in this one, but there's a couple other fun spots on the eye chart
that were pretty cool that it was all over there.
The authentically sneaking in a giant billboard behind someone is pretty great.
Yeah, that was a fun one.
That's the kind of thing that feels like it'd be good for a late night
host to do like Jimmy Fallon or something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, totally.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And the fact that Jimmy Fallon's not too bright, he wouldn't get it.
It'd be perfect.
Authentic something or other, I don't know.
Yeah.
But yeah, this is not in their show now.
This was definitely a Fool Us trick and it's a giant billboard.
I remember in rehearsals, so there's a really big dust up heading into Fool Us
with the Piko the second gorilla trick.
Yeah.
And I don't think we've done Piko yet on Fool Us, right?
No, it's an old, old.
Yeah, so I won't burn all of the background on that trick right now,
but I'll just say at one point it got pretty heated.
And at one point we were all just sitting around with Hondro and I staring at each other
wondering who's supposed to talk because Penn Teller and Andrew all looked content
and not speaking at all after the awkward exchange.
And in the middle of that, Nate comes in and we're dead quiet,
so there's no problem interrupting rehearsal, saying, "I have the giant Authenticate board
up on stage and they're about to load out everything to bring in the set for Fool Us.
Do you guys want to come out and approve?"
And Hondro and I were just so happy to be like, "Leave the room?
Yeah, let's set that up.
Absolutely.
Let's go look at that."
And then Penn stayed behind, kind of still in a little bit of a sour mood.
And he goes like, "Well, I don't see any good reason I need to go out there."
And I said, "I mean, I think you're one of the people that has to approve of it, no?"
And this is why I love our competitor, Teller.
He literally was still in a bad mood.
He was like, "You're right."
And he got up and just walked out and said, "Yup, looks great," and approved it.
And then went back to being in a sour mood for the rest of the meeting.
But I'll reveal much more to that story when they do "Pycho, the Psychic Gorilla."
Yeah, so it airs.
We're in episode 13, and I guess it has aired because we're up through 16 right now on the CW
right now.
So it has aired.
Thank you, John, for noting that.
So I'll get into all of that on that episode.
Awesome.
All right.
Any closing questions, remarks from the babblers?
Today, I learned that other people don't read their ULAs.
Their ULAs?
The terms and conditions.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You read yours?
End-user licensing agreement.
I don't read mine ever.
I had a quick question.
Yeah, go for it.
Going back to the original refrigerator trick,
Penn says something like, "This is the greatest trick ever," or something.
He says it twice, something like that.
And I don't understand if that's maybe the name of the actual trick,
or why he says that, unless I'm missing something.
I think he was being genuine.
Okay.
Matt doesn't?
No, I do.
I think he was genuinely like, because of the method he loves,
when people use a crazy-ass method for something.
Yeah.
So when people go out of their way to do something really hard to pull off,
just for the sake of a magic trick, I think it really tickles him.
And so I think he is really struck by that.
And also, like I told you, we're riding the wave of him sitting down,
turning to Teller, and be like, "Well, there's only one way to do that,"
and just kind of riding the wave of both his joy and satisfaction
with what he saw as happening the whole time, I think.
Am I misremembering the language?
Because my recollection is he said, "Almost nobody else could do this."
He says that too, yes.
He says, "Almost nobody else could do this with ready-found satisfactory."
And later in the bus, Penn says, "I hope you and your whole family enjoy this."
You and your family, yeah.
The first one was fine.
Second one was okay.
A little on the edge, yeah.
Yeah.
For the listeners, I want to mention that Steve-O is in the Burt Reynolds Playgirl pose.
Steve-O's always in the Burt Reynolds Playgirl pose.
He is the most relaxed person in every one of these.
I mean, I've taken mushrooms today, and I'm not as relaxed as Steve-O is right now.
Oh, I made you tackle Zoom strategies with mushrooms?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, then there we go.
Thank you, Ready Rich.
Thank you, RJ, for stepping up.
You're welcome.
Learning the Zoom protocols, and we'll be back with more Fool Us.
I think we should do another maybe one of these for Africa Babble as well.
All right.
Not today.
Not today, I don't think.
I had a video.
It's getting a lot of play.
I've aired basically me.
I have a clip of me saying, "Hey, this guy literally is trying to interrupt my show.
I'm doing it, Mystique Dining."
I say, "Hey, no one cares."
I'd say, "You know what?
I only have 45 minutes to do the show, and we're behind."
That's the sting, right?
So, of course, I put up on YouTube.
Everyone on YouTube says, "I'm an asshole.
That guy's right.
I'm wrong.
I should never free in show business."
All that other stuff, because that's all that happens on YouTube.
No one on YouTube is ever on my side of the perspective of the clip.
They think, "Oh, a magician posting his own clip.
He must be an arrogant prick, and we need to take him down to Peg."
Is all of YouTube as far as I understand it.
My clips do better on Facebook and Instagram.
But this guy Marco goes, "That spectator is not wrong.
I find lots of clients saying, 'Glad you are not doing only card tricks.'
And I find the problem is when every magician I know are doing card magic,
even on stage when it's hardly visible for the audience.
Let's work a bit harder and offer variety."
None of that's happening in the clip.
None of that.
I am doing a card trick in a parlor environment where everything can be seen.
And also, that is the only card trick in my show.
And the spectator is not saying, "Hey, you're doing too many card tricks."
The spectator is literally interrupting me so they can tell me
that he saw another magician do a card trick,
and he stayed up at night and figured out how to do it.
And the reason why I know all the beats of that is because before I went out to Mystique,
he told the server that same story.
He told the table that same story.
He told Steve that same story.
So I was the fourth round of that story for everyone in the room
when he was interrupting my card trick in my parlor set at Mystique Dining.
So Marco is piping in to both tell me that I do too many card tricks
and the spectator is championing variety.
And ending with this grandiose,
"Let's all work a bit harder and offer variety,"
as if he's doing us a service when he's completely interpreting the clip for himself.
When you click on his profile picture, it's him holding a fucking card.
Yeah, of course it is.
"Hey Marco, let's all work on minding our own fucking business and shutting the fuck up."
How's that, Marco?
I take down the stuff that's directly insulting.
But I don't take down the dumb shit like this because my social media people encourage me
that there's engagement happening on it to let it happen.
And other people are taking on Marco, so I'm letting it happen.
But I'm not chiming in because I don't want to debate anyone.
I don't want to debate a stranger on the internet.
Because that can only lead to victory.
Yeah, surely at the end of this road is a sense of satisfaction.
I have done it, Eureka!
A remorseful person concedes.
Oh, you know what, Matt? You were right.
That's remorse, sorry. You can't even do remorse.
I'm going to guess that Marco didn't read Matt's EULA before watching his viral video.
All right. Well, thanks for this, everybody.
That was Foolish By the Scenes African Babble.
Bye, kids.
Bye, dude.
[Music]